N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Damn, Ed, Jordan, I am sweating
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for Knowledgefight
Knowledgefight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Saying we are the bad guys
Knowledgefight
Dan and Jordan
Riddleware, riddleware, riddleware
I need, I need money
Andy and Kansas
Stop it
It's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding us
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan
I love your room
Knowledgefight
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledgefight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're a couple dudes, like to sit around, drink novelty beverages
and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are Dan
Jordan
Dan!
Jordan!
Quick question for you
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, Jordan, is something, it actually happened a little bit back
but it's something I've been reflecting on and it's appropriate for the 500th episode
that we're doing here
Oh, nice way to smooth in that little 500 reference
Yeah, for sure, I'm very, you know, so it's all about smoothness
I like it, I like it
Um, so I recently was asked or invited by listener Sarah Beth to give a little bit of a Q&A session
discussion with a college course that she presides over
and it was just such a rewarding, interesting experience to be, you know, asked to talk to these college students
about, you know, issues like researching topics
and it was, it was amazing
and I can't thank Sarah Beth enough for inviting me and these kids were great
Although scary, I'm scared
Sure, sure
I'm scared of college kids
Sure, naturally
For one, because they look so young and they are adults, technically
Yeah
That scares the shit out of me
Yeah, that is a problem
And then also, like, I remember back when I was in college, I would just be disapproving by nature
sort of like the default look on your face is
Sure, sure, sure, sure
Yeah, you're in class
Yeah, yeah
You know, I'm used to being a stand-up and I want to elicit a response
Sure, sure
A positive response from the
Yeah, yeah, yeah
And so it's always tough to imagine, like, just even myself back in college
Oh, yeah
Like, to try and look at my face
Trying to convey a message
You know, we've had plenty of friends who've gone back and forth from doing stand-up and teaching
You know, like they were teachers while they were stand-ups
and it never occurred to me that you would have to stand up in front of all the same types of people
but they don't make a response at all
Yeah, it's
That's infuriating
It's terrifying because they're a crowd, but they're not a crowd
Yeah, they're not a crowd
Yeah
I can't do crowd work
I'm not going to do a little five minutes up top every time
No, that's not going to work
Yeah, so thank you so much to Sarah Beth and those students
It was just a great experience
That's really cool
First time
I get to call myself a guest lecturer now
I think
I believe you do
I can put that in my title
I believe you do, that's in there
Yeah, so how about you?
Oh, my bright spot, Dan, normally would be that Assassin's Creed Valhalla is coming out
Sure, but not yet
Not yet, it's not here
Although we set a bad precedent with me being able to do a preemptive one with Pikmin
That's true, that's true
But I won't be choosing that because, Dan, my audiobook is finished and it is up on the website
for everybody to download at their leisure
Congratulations
Yeah, it was cool, it was really fun to do
Thank you very much for helping me produce it
Sure, made a tiny cameo
Yeah, absolutely
Yeah, if you read it, there are some easter eggs and some weird things that are there on purpose
I promise you to confuse you and kind of disorient things for a little bit
Awesome
Yeah, yeah
And people can find that at thequietpartloud.com
Indeed, yep, that's where they can find it
I'm very proud of you, I'm excited that it's out and people can enjoy the fruits of your labor
by which I mean screaming in my apartment
If you want to go straight from listening to four hours of us talk
and then instead get rid of the best part of this podcast, I think it's a great idea to listen to my audiobook
Get rid of me and replace it with you doing voices
More me, yeah
Very exciting
Yeah, it's not great
Um, that's great, despite what you say
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's awesome, I'm very happy about it
So, Jordan, today we got an interesting thing to do
We're going to be talking about a little bit of Election Time Infowars
Oh, yay, I've been hearing about things
But things might be a little bit different than what people could have expected
Last week, Jordan, we talked about how it would be too difficult to do an episode about the election
to be released on that Wednesday
And that remained true when it came time to record Friday's episode
At that point, there was just too much uncertainty
It felt very difficult to discuss the whole thing without having any feelings of closure about the election itself
Now, as it stands on Sunday, as we record Monday's show, there's a bit more of a sense of finality
All the networks have called the race for Biden, and it looks like the basis for any kind of legal challenge Trump's campaign could make
It'll be weak, and it'll probably go nowhere
Everybody celebrating the Biden win owes a huge raise of the glass to the on-the-ground organizers and voter registration activists
in those battleground states that could easily have gone the other way
Oh, easily
It's still mind-blowing that it was anywhere near that close, but right now our country probably owes a deep debt of gratitude to a ton of people
whose names you'll likely never know
So, now, there's a bit more of a sense of what's going on
I feel like I'm standing on more solid ground, so it's time to get to Alex's election coverage
Let's see what happened
Or maybe not
As I reflected over the weekend, I had a bit of...
I do like that twist
That was a very good... I was like, yeah, that was the time when you're like, or maybe not, fuck you, Dan
I had a bit of a realization, Jordan
A large part of the motivation for me doing this podcast was my revulsion at seeing Alex and his crew laughing
at the diverse crowds of Hillary supporters crying on election night 2016
mocking what was, for many of them, a very real and justified existential fear
So now, the tables are turned a little bit, and we have an opportunity to laugh at his behavior on election night when things didn't go his way
Do we mock his tears, comfortable in the knowledge that they're probably fake?
And even if they are real, the things he's afraid of aren't real?
Is it just as bad for me to do a show where I relish in his election night lows?
Obviously, the answer to that is no, it wouldn't be just as bad for me to do that
Oh, of course not
It would be totally cool, and maybe fun
It'd be fine, it'd be great, I'd love it
But also, I'm not going to do that, but for slightly different reasons
What Alex Jones did on election night literally doesn't matter
We can mock his freaking out and yelling the same bullshit he yells every day
We can discuss his very dubious claim that he decided not to go on Rogan's livestream of his own accord
We can talk about his obvious intentions to incite violence, but here's the thing
The most disrespectful thing I think you can do in terms of Alex's election night coverage
is to treat it how it deserves to be treated, and that's to say, who gives a shit?
You asshole
Eh, get the fuck out of here
The lashing out, the tears, the yelling about demons, it's all meaningless
Some pills might have gotten sold, but if I'm going for schadenfreude, I'm not going halfway
And saying, we'll talk about your election coverage sometime, but it's totally not important now
That's way harsher than playing clips of Alex yelling nonsense and then saying, haha, your guy lost
Yeah, that's true
So we're going to talk about the election coverage another time
Maybe a year from now, who knows, I don't know
But it's not out of respect for Alex and his crew in this difficult time, but out of a deeper disrespect
I'd like it
So fuck all of you at Infowars
Yeah, this is a straight up needful things twist that you have right here
The reality is that Alex is now entering uncharted territory
His audience has been led to believe that any non-Trump win would be the result of large-scale election fraud
thereby making any Biden presidency illegitimate
Further, he's extensively characterized his opponents, from high-level politicians to street-level activists
as pedophiles and vampires in the employ of the literal Christian devil
Over and over again, he said that Trump getting elected was the equivalent of the biblical story of God giving a reprieve to Nineveh
In that story, Jonah is enlisted by God to warn the people of Nineveh to repent of their evil ways
But he decides to go somewhere else
He ends up getting swallowed by a whale and then realizes, I got a job to do
So he goes to Nineveh after he gets out of the whale
And then he convinces everyone there to repent
thereby saving the city from God's judgment and destruction
According to the way Alex characterizes Trump's role as being reminiscent of this story
combined with the people of the United States not deciding to repent by getting on board with Trump
this naturally leads to a different conclusion than Jonah's story
We're all gonna get eaten by a bigger whale
This is kind of more like Sodom and Gomorrah in the way that Alex is characterizing it
If you take Alex seriously, Alex has taught his audience that his enemies are literal demons
dead set on the killing of the entire planet to appease Lucifer and turn into robots or whatever
and that Trump was the US's only chance to repent and be saved
Now that that has been passed, it seems like it's time to become a full-on wrath of God doomsday preacher
That's one possible avenue Alex could be going down
I honestly have no idea what Alex's pivot will be
but I'm interested to see how much of the stuff he retains and how much he just pretends
I never said that shit
His audience is captured so he could just start walking another direction
and as long as he talks fast enough and jingles those keys around
he'll retain some percentage of the audience
Some new lieutenant colonel will tell Alex about some new piece of intel that'll make everything make sense
how there's still good guys fighting off the devil inside the government or something
We'll see what he ends up doing
but I've learned not just to assume that the boat is gonna sink
because it looks like, boy, that boat has gotta sink
Alex still has a few cards left to play
The boat should have enough holes in it and his box should have no air holes in it
and that should be enough to take him down, but it doesn't seem to be
For sure
So I'm going to leave desperate and intensely boring electoral Alex to his games
He can try to whip up excitement about his attempt at branding Trump's lame duck session as the 79 days of hell
but I don't think that's gonna catch on
and I wouldn't be surprised if Alex even loses interest in it before January comes around
Oh yeah
But where does that leave us?
What are we gonna cover here for today's episode?
Episode 500
Well, I've found that this show works best when I follow my heart and my instincts
and there's only one thing that I want to talk about today
and that's how Infowars has been reeling at the beginning of this 79 days of hell
We could talk about Alex going to Maricopa County on Thursday
and using an adult-sized bullhorn to yell about how they needed to stop counting ballots
but honestly that just seems like a waste of time
The race in Arizona has been called for Biden
and honestly that wasn't much more than a sad and entirely predictable publicity stunt on Alex's part
No, that would be a waste of time
What I want to discuss is something far more important
which is what happens to a propaganda outlet that's run by a tyrannical central authority
when their anointed God King is losing an election
and their tyrannical central authority runs off to Arizona to do a publicity stunt
How does the leaderless and almost certainly confused underling who works there
how do they keep the operation going?
How do they respond?
Wait, how long has he been gone?
Well, he's back now but in the period he left on Thursday after his show
and then I think he got back on like Saturday
Okay, so for two days he just wasn't there
He might have been back on Friday, I'm not entirely sure
We're going to be covering Thursday evening into Friday morning
and just sort of what goes on when the daddy's gone
Right, so we're going to watch a bunch of incompetent people scramble around
A little bit
and it's going to be fantastic
We're also going to hear Alex's show on Thursday
A bit of that as well
I present to you, Jordan, episode 500
or why Infowars doesn't work without Alex
Okay
But before we get down to business on that
got to give a shout out to folks who have made these past 500 episodes possible
Oh, nicely done
So first, KevKev, please, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, KevKev
Thank you, next, DJ Booth, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, DJ Booth
Thank you so much, next, SickFucker, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, SickFucker
Also, that's just all vowels taken out
I didn't know how else to… I couldn't just say so...
Anyway, Dr. Milton Wigglesworth, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, Dr. Milton
Thank you, next Antifa Bogeyman, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Ah, thank you very much, Antifa Bogeyman
Thank you, next, Amber A, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Amber
Thank you, next, Kristopher R, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Christopher
And then I'd like to give a shout-out to someone who donated on Elevated Level, we appreciate
that very much.
And this person has a bone to pick with someone named Peter from Denmark, one of our listeners,
who is the ordained ruler of the wonks in Denmark.
I did not know that.
There apparently is tension in Denmark, and there may actually be a bit of a feud.
Are you saying there's literally trouble in Denmark?
There may be trouble in Denmark.
All right, okay.
We have a contender for the title of blank of Denmark.
Okay.
So we have Peter from Denmark, who's now been the from Denmark.
He's the only from Denmark.
But now we have Dines M from Denmark.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate.
That's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right, we got to go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why are you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much, Dines.
Yes, thank you very much, Dines from Denmark.
I'm going to stay out of this conflict and see who comes out on top, and then say that
I was always on this side to pick it up.
What are you, Ireland?
Come on now.
Finally, a special wonk shout out I'd like to make is to Bex, who sent us a wonderful
care package a while back.
I thought that we'd done the whole technocrat shout out, but I believe we might have forgotten,
or maybe...
I'm not entirely sure what happened.
I believe we've already done it in the past.
Maybe.
There are a handful of us, if we did mess up or miss it, so I want to attempt to right
this wrong by declaring that Bex, you're not a technocrat.
No, no, no, no.
You're a raptor princess, and in honor of that, I've made a special drop.
There was a request that we use the old technocrat drop because it included the Daddy Shark clip,
but I decided that it would be better if I just made a new one, which also included the
Daddy Shark one.
It's 45 seconds of just the Daddy Shark one on repeat, isn't it?
That'd be great.
So thank you so much, Bex.
Also, thank you for...
We got a special episode 500 package that we're going to be opening on a bonus episode
that'll be out on Friday from Bex, and I don't know what's in it, but it looks cool.
It's very exciting.
It's very thoughtful and awesome.
I'm very excited.
Yes.
We appreciate you very much, and my apologies that I'm absolutely terrible at social media
correspondences.
This one's going out to you, Bex.
Thank you so much.
You are now a raptor princess.
I'm a policy wonk.
You know, they got Baby Shark, deet deet deet deet deet deet, Hillary Clinton.
It's fun to laugh at Alex Jones.
It's fun.
No, my religion is facts.
Get that through your peep ring.
They got Mama Shark, beep beep, beep beep beep.
I'm dead inside.
I have no guilt.
I'm a really good guy.
There's three ways to learn, or maybe four.
I am that Messiah.
What can I do?
Daddy Shark.
I hate myself.
And I feel like a complete failure.
Thank you so much, Bex.
Thank you very much, Bex.
Oh.
That's a wonderful new drop.
It will never be played again.
Never be played again.
One time only use.
Absolutely.
All right.
So, Jordan, now let's jump into this episode.
Let's do it.
Because we are deep into this.
All right.
So, we're going to start here on November 5th.
We are past the election.
Alex is reeling.
You know, the count is still going on, but all indications are that, you know, things
are not looking that great for Trump to win.
There's a number of paths, but they all involve winning Pennsylvania, and then some other
things also.
Hope is getting, you know, at that point, it's getting to the area where some conservatives
are talking rebrand.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Alex is a little bit like Wile E. Coyote in that Trump is the roadrunner who painted the
way forward on the wall, and Alex is the one who crashes headfirst into reality.
Exactly.
He hits the barbed wire.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not good.
So, here's where he's at.
Now, let me give you the big announcement here.
If Joe Biden gets in, they're never getting rid of the lockdown.
Think about that.
It's a lot bigger than just kicking Trump out and flooding everything with fake ballots
using the lockdown as the cover for it.
They want to bankrupt us and then have us have an app to be able to leave our front
door and step one foot outside of our house.
That is the admitted globalist chai con plan.
So I guess that's now the angle is if Biden gets in, then the lockdown is never going
to end.
COVID's here forever or something.
I kind of think that one might even be hard for his followers to buy.
Yeah.
Really, you're going to say that Joe Biden is just going to say everyone stay inside.
Also, what do you want us to do now?
The election's over.
Yeah.
What are you trying to...
Also, furthermore, the lockdown already happened and nobody listened to it anyways.
What are we going to, what's Biden going to change about that?
He's going to have even less evil fucking DHS coming into people's homes.
He seems probably less willing to use a lot of the force that Trump has been.
I mean, except for against left-wing protesters.
Well, but look, man, there was an election and it was fraught with fraud.
There's a lot of it.
I remember that.
Well, maybe you didn't hear about this.
Oh, okay.
And there's videos of what appear to be Chinese individuals in Michigan arriving with those
ballots at 4 a.m. illegally and going into the buildings with ballot boxes that then
were all for Biden.
The arrogance level is so atrocious.
I don't even know.
So, is he implying that China sent people from China to Michigan with marked ballots
for Biden?
These marked ballots ostensibly also coming from China.
Well, and the box itself is the only thing that you probably see in the videos.
It has to say ballots for Biden on the box.
Exactly, with the Chinese flag.
That's the only thing that makes sense.
There were a bunch of these videos that were going around.
There were drastic misrepresentations of things.
There was one that was a television crew that was unloading gear that people thought were
ballots going in.
Then there was a video that went around that was actually from years ago in Russia that
people were just saying was from one of these states.
Yeah, there's just a hundred of these things.
And Alex has really latched on to the idea that there was a suspicious, possibly Chinese
person.
Yeah, that's real.
That's just real sad on a conspiracy level of just like, man, they could have mailed
them to San Francisco and had a white person drive them there.
Why would you fly directly from China to... What did they land on top of the ballot counting
building in a helicopter?
Look, there's a lot of problems with this from just sort of a real world perspective,
but you listen to it and you can kind of hear what his, like where he's coming from.
You can see why this is the story that he's telling.
So Alex is, I would say, pretty close to a line.
And that line is what I like to call the saying, hey, let's do some offensive violence line.
He's pretty close to that line.
They are involved in a revolution fully conquering the United States and killing our republic
and they're hammering the last nails into the damn coffin to bury us alive as slaves
of their system.
So I'm not a macho guy.
I don't say things just to say them, but I'll tell you this.
Yeah, you do.
I'm not going to launch any offensive violence at this point because I've not had time to
really think about the right course in history.
But I know this.
If we let them steal this election and we let them put a Chinese communist agent who's
fully compromised with all the proof in there to have control of the nuclear codes, all
of us are aiding and abetting the destruction of our country and the handover to the most
authoritarian nation the world's ever seen, communist China.
And I will not be an accomplice and I will not aid and abet this type of takeover.
So if I understand correctly what he's saying, first of all, I have to take issue with the
idea that he said, I haven't had time to think about.
Yeah.
You've done nothing but talk about this.
I would suggest that you've been thinking about this almost nonstop for-
Since 1995.
Yeah.
You've been talking about it on air since-
That's pretty much the only thing you've been talking about.
I haven't given any thought to when you start being violent.
Wow.
The course of history, blah, blah, blah.
Yeah.
What is the course of history?
Well, if you understand what he's saying, he's saying that Joe Biden is controlled by
China.
Yes.
So if we, by we, I mean, Alex and the Patriots, if we allow Joe Biden to take office with
the nuclear codes and what have you, you are complicit in aiding and abetting the Chinese
communist takeover.
So I mean, that would be the Joe Biden getting into office would be the condition then for
offensive violence, right?
Yeah.
That's the only thing that makes sense.
That's the only way we can understand the sentence.
Yeah.
Him saying all of this is simply, I am not counseling actual violence until they're swearing
him in, I guess.
But once they swear him in, well, yeah, we got to blow it up because they're the most
authoritarian.
Or if you could do something that you could conceivably argue is going to stop him from
being sworn in.
Sure.
Right on that line.
Put a limousine in front of the gates to the White House.
If he can't get in, buddy, guess what?
Yeah.
Never becomes president.
Alex is doing well.
Yeah.
I think so.
So Alex is just, it's bland.
I would describe this show as flat.
There's very little going on that even peaks my interest at all.
It's just the hits.
It's just kind of like him saying the same things and kind of hitting his bases.
Sure.
These are criminals that have brokered the shell out of America and they want to position
the global government and they want to atomize the family and domesticate us so we can never
rise again and never resist the nightmare future they've got for all of us.
The chains are going on right now.
You're being disenfranchised.
All of us are.
So we better work peacefully now so that war does not become inevitable.
But we are now entering this season of war.
Our country is at war for its very life.
You are under attack.
You are being conquered.
You are being taken over.
We are in the midst of a chai combat attempted takeover of the country and we're losing right
now.
I just can't feel anything here anymore.
Yeah.
Honestly personally, like I was thinking about it whenever we heard the first clip of him
talking and then I realized that right now the only thing I'm interested in really is,
is he going to take the plunge?
You know, what is he going to do?
What is he going to do?
Yeah.
He's going to take the leap or you're going to back off and if you back off, fuck you
forever.
And if you take the leap, all right, now let's see what's happening.
And also fuck you.
Or do you pivot?
Do you change your whole brand to God?
Sure.
Like do you do that?
Do you become televangelist Alex or whatever?
That seems to be the way to make way better money than what he's doing.
And it seems like a place where he could play a lot more games about like state oppression.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like he could get Infowars into an actual church, you know?
If he pivoted to becoming Scientology and then like just made it his entire life's mission
to be a nonprofit or for the government not to tax him, I can see that working.
Yeah, that might be the next best thing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I agree with you.
It's like, I'm not really interested in yelling about the Chinese.
I really, you know, maybe it's just a momentary thing, but I'm a little bit bored by the like
waffling around offensive violence.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's just like, we know what you're doing.
It's not really, I'm not interested in his going to Phoenix to yell into a bullhorn that
much.
I'm not that interested in it.
I'm a little bit interested in it.
I think the bullhorn was too big for me to be that interested in it.
I agree.
Yeah.
I think somebody might've told him that the tiny bullhorn was a source of humor.
I mean, you know, it's just a, yeah, the thing that is the most interesting is like, what
are you going to do?
Yeah.
You have a problem and I want to see how you fix it or at least I want to see how you deal
with it.
Cause I don't think you're going to fix it.
That's a probably a good note.
Yeah.
Good correction.
What we're seeing right now is what we see him do a lot at times when I think people
could probably predict that there's going to be a possibility for some violence.
I think any right thinking person, I'm not making any specific prediction or anything,
but I do think that as we get closer to the inauguration, we do see probably an increased
danger of some kind of right wing violence.
I don't know that it's going to happen and it very well may not, but I think the odds
of some kind of a thing happening maybe possible.
I think Alex recognizes that.
And so he goes out of his way to very consistently talk about how false flags are coming.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
Well, I promise you this.
I'm not giving up ever because I know the more I bend over, the worst stuff gets, and
I will not sit here and be part of this.
Now, that doesn't mean they blow something up and say, I did it.
I'd never do that.
Okay, cool.
We see this all the time, and it's the times that I think that Alex is most keenly aware
the people in his communities might blow something up, and I think that this is a good strategy
for him to preemptively characterize anything as them false flagging in order to make us
look bad, but it's incessant.
He goes on this tip quite a bit.
And the enemy's next phase will be to frame us as terrorists or evil, and they will stage
terror attacks and blame it on us to then discredit any resistance.
But we need to be ahead of that and understand that, and there are other forms of civil disobedience
and things in the threat continuum of projection before we get to that point.
But it is our right, it is our duty to resist this by every means necessary.
And we are now at war for our very existence.
America is on the edge of death.
So if you understand that, kind of what he's saying is that the enemy is going to false
flag themselves in order to make Alex and his friends look bad, and they've got to be
careful about that.
But also, I should tell you that there's something called the threat continuum projection, and
then also we have the right to commit terror attacks if we want to.
Yeah, I'm confused as to how it is you can play a game like this where it's like, hey,
we would never do those terror attacks, it's a false flag.
But whenever, if it does happen, then the people are going to be like, yeah, good job,
we do terror attacks, we love terror attacks.
Is everybody a false flagger on the far right?
Is the entire far right, is all of the boogaloos a fucking false flag?
I think Alex thinks that.
That might be true.
Yeah, he said that they were like a cutout group or something.
Oh man.
Was that last-
I think he says that they're Antifa.
Was Larry Nichols' last act to false flag us with the Proud Boys and the others?
Oh no.
Do you think so?
Yeah, he did some witchcraft.
I think he might have.
Oh, speaking of which, I was going through, I was making that new drop, and so I was going
through these old folders of episodes, and whenever I do that, I end up finding something
that I had completely forgotten about.
Did you remember that a year ago, Alex was saying that the Queen had joined the Patriots'
side?
Do you remember that?
I do remember that!
What the shit?
That's right!
Yeah.
Oh, that's-
I completely forgot, and there was like a two-day stretch where Alex thought that the
Queen had succumbed to Donald Trump's side.
Yeah, I think that's going to be something fun.
If we ever do look back on these four years, like whenever it'll be funny again in 50,
we'll look back and we'll be like, at one point in time, Alex said literally everyone
he's hated before was a patriot, and also that he hates them later.
It's everyone.
The Queen has flipped her dictator switch.
The Pope is evil, but the Pope likes it, and says, well, the Pope is good today.
But someone who Alex would never speak ill of-
Stephen Miller?
Now, or 500 years from now, is his brother-in-law.
I don't know who this dude is.
But apparently his brother-in-law caught some election fraud.
So we have-
That's a good catch-fire.
We have Alex's wife's tennis partner informing us about Antifa attacks, and Alex's brother-in-law
coming in with some big scoops.
So helpful.
And then my own brother-in-law, who I've never seen get mad in the many years I've known
him, calls up shaking yesterday, and I go, what's wrong?
I just had 50 ballots.
He's down here at Congress, post office.
He had 50 of them.
He was filling them out as a name.
They were taking them.
They didn't do anything.
I said, why don't you videotape it?
Well, I'm in the post office.
It's a federal thing if you do that.
He just knows the law.
But let me see.
He followed the law.
They don't.
And he was shaking with anger.
I said, come on the air.
And he goes, well, I don't really want to do that.
I don't want to be on TV.
But I said, cut an audio piece.
Send me a voice memo.
He did.
We'll play it next time.
Don't you dare fucking give me a goddamn break.
It's against the law.
Yeah, I found globalists committing.
I saw Mass Motor Front and I was like, I follow the law.
I will not videotape his crime.
I would never, as a far right person, I would never videotape a crime.
Here's this thing that my brother-in-law yells about all the time.
I have proof that can make him look not crazy.
Oh, no.
I can't pull out my phone.
Don't you think there's a, if that really happened, there's a moment in his head where
he's like, nooo.
Well, here is his testimony because he did record an audio and it's meaningless.
I went to the post office today to drop off some packages with some products and there's
this guy there, real sketchy looking, and he had a grocery bag filled up with about
50 million ballots.
And he was taking pictures of them, taking pictures of himself and filling them out right
there on the counter.
And I could only see the ballot that he had in front of him on the counter and the one
on the top of the bag.
But they had the same signatures, same information on him.
And he was just taking pictures, doing one last check, marking some things and then putting
them straight in the ballot box right in front of everyone, right on the counter.
And no one did anything.
And I was thinking about doing something, but all I could think about was, you know,
me getting some kind of federal charge for interfering with the election with this guy,
putting in, you know, 50 ballots.
That is what you would be doing late, because I don't think they're supposed to accept them
now.
But I mean, if you have a lot of these people doing that, it's going to add up.
And the only reason you would do it is to try to overturn what the state has already
decided and Texas is red.
So one can only assume that these votes, all 50 of them are going to Joe Biden.
Ah, ah, ah, this, this guy shows, wow, I mean, he's the brother-in-law, so he's not related
by blood.
No, but there's something about being close to the Jones family that just makes you good
at figuring things out.
Good at investigating.
There's like something in their, in their family and their extended family that makes
them not jump to conclusions about stuff and really just get to the bottom of it.
I admire that.
If you need somebody to help you fill out your ballot, does that person also need to
sign the ballot?
They do.
Yeah.
I mean, this person could have been like a proxy or something.
Could have just gone to a nursing home.
Yeah.
That is a possibility.
Or I mean, if he's saying that this is like after election day, they might not have been
balanced.
They could just be anything.
I don't trust this guy's instincts.
Absolutely not.
I have no idea what he did or didn't see.
I don't even know if he's Alex's brother-in-law.
Quick question.
Did he mail in his ballot?
I doubt it.
Does he know what a mail in ballot would look like?
No idea.
I don't trust any of this.
And I love the part at the end there is like, the only reason you do this is to try and
change things.
And Texas went red.
So therefore all of these votes, all these votes that I have just decided are 50.
I didn't count them.
I have no fucking idea.
They must all be for, what if they're all for Trump?
Dumb, dumb.
You can't prove anything.
Furthermore, uh, Texas has already got, I suppose they hadn't called the other states
by this time.
Okay.
That's fair.
Alex tries to make sense of this, that they're being sent from Texas to other states.
You guys got to work on this.
If that's the case, I mean, it's 50 votes.
I don't know what kind of, I don't know.
I think this is stupid.
Trump won Texas by a million.
Anyway, Alex thinks that there's only one solution.
I think we just call for a new election.
Fair enough.
Uh, so he wants a new election.
I can't think of anything everyone in the United States agrees is the worst idea that
anyone could ever do.
Run it again.
More than let's do it again.
The most stressful time.
It doesn't matter what team you're on.
Don't do it again.
Well, just anything but that.
Okay, fine, fine.
Let's not do another election.
But how about we nullify this one?
Okay.
But then we'll have to do it.
I'm playing all the clips when we come back, but I'm going to say this right now.
Whatever happens with Trump, he's done the right thing fighting this, but he didn't fight
the censorship like he should have.
But we're in the bed we're in now.
We're going to have to sleep in it.
But if we get the point out that it's a chai con globalist takeover and it's the end of
the country as we know it, and that it's illegal, not just that they're stealing the election,
but when you have Chinese and foreign backing, it nullifies what's happened.
And if we stand on that and say, oh, does it try to nullify Trump saying he was a Russian
with no proof?
We're going to nullify Biden a hundred percent.
We're going to demand Mitch McConnell and all of them do it and not have a fake investigation
because we've got him red handed being a chai con agent.
And that's what's so dangerous.
That's super constitutional.
Oh man, we're going to nullify his election and I'm going to have Mitch McConnell do it
without a trial because he's a red handed.
You know, if you're caught red handed, you still go to trial.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's like in the old west, if you get caught killing somebody, they just hang you right
then and there.
It's that simple.
If you get caught in the act, you're still called an alleged killer.
Nope, Nope.
Unless you're a far right murderer.
In which case, well, of course you didn't even actually do it.
Here's a false flag.
Um, so yeah, I guess Alex wants to know this.
This isn't going to work.
I don't think so.
Now, one thing that I thought was really strange was this is like all, like I said, flat, feels
like nothing.
Um, and then Alex has a guest on and this guest, I don't know what the fuck he was doing.
So this person is named Amanda Milius and she is the daughter of John Milius.
He's the director of Conan the Barbarian, Apocalypse Now, and of course Red Dawn, Alex's
favorite documentary, Red Dawn.
He was the director of Apocalypse Now?
Or maybe producer.
I'm not sure.
He was involved in Apocalypse Now.
Okay.
I was going to say, because there's a pretty famous guy who directed Apocalypse Now that
wasn't that guy.
If you researched into it and it turns out that it wasn't him at all, then we've got
a whole story.
He might not have directed any of those.
He might have produced them or wrote them or something, screenplay.
He's involved.
He's in the mix.
Whatever.
So Amanda, she's become a Trump propagandist and she just released a film called The Plot
Against the President.
And so she is in, and she has some interesting things to talk about.
I love the smell of...
You were a huge part of why I left Hollywood.
I was listening to Info Wars all the time and I left and I volunteered in 2016 in Nevada,
which by the way, Nevada is a huge battleground for us right now.
Nevada is where everything's happening.
And I ended up leaving Hollywood completely and joining the Trump administration, working
at the State Department.
How proud is your family of you?
They're pretty happy.
You were already being successful in Hollywood.
I admire the fact that you cut bait with those guys.
Not to be a dick, but Amanda Milius is not somebody who you would say walked away from
a vibrant career in Hollywood.
If you check out her IMDb page, she has two primary credits as a director, one being this
new Trump film and the other one a 2015 short called The Lotus Gun.
Her only credits as a performer are as herself in a documentary about her dad and appearances
on Tucker Carlson and Sebastian Gorka's shows, most likely promoting Trump and her new propaganda
film.
That would make sense.
It's all good to do this interview and be like, hey, look at this famous, you know,
movie person's daughter who likes Trump, but it's entirely another thing to pretend that
she was like an A or B or even C list person and then walked away from it to get on board
with Trump.
That's insulting to her and to us as listeners.
Look at this important movie person.
Of course, his daughter, independent of his success, has also become a massive success
in the film industry.
What was that?
No.
Oh shit.
Yeah.
And you heard her.
She said she worked in the State Department.
Yeah.
She apparently was involved in Trump's State Department.
She had some kind of a role in that.
And so there is a feeling of her being here almost in an official capacity and the fact
that she made this Trump propaganda film that you just released while she had been working
at the State Department is just a, just a bizarre, um, it seems inappropriate.
I don't think someone with less than my resume should work at the State Department.
And I don't think I should work at the State Department, Dan.
I don't, I don't know what was going on, but everything felt wrong about this.
Yeah.
And then it got even worse because we introduced another weirdo into the mix.
All right.
So you can introduce you better than I can.
I love Ali Alexander.
He's been on fire a long time, but you were talking about how you just suddenly brought
all this together and reached out as a catalyst.
He months ago was saying, stop the still getting it ready.
But he is an example to others.
He just reached out, got a bunch of key people together and now this is a super viral movement.
So Ali Alexander is this, uh, you know, the zealot weirdo who's been coming on Alex's
show a bit lately.
And now he's involved in something called stop the steal, which is, you know, they're
doing the, you know, I don't know, it's maybe the catchphrase of a lot of these totally
not astroturfed, uh, 100% grassroots.
I don't care.
Whatever.
Yeah.
I'm more interested in the fact that I only remember this because we just talked about
it.
Stop the steal was the name of the thing that Roger Stone was involved in in 2016.
Yeah, exactly.
Jesus Christ, that was Roger Stone's whole thing that he got sued about.
Oh man, 2016 is the year all their evil tricks worked in 2020 is the year they almost worked.
Like that's, but everybody found them far more disappointing and sad this time.
But it's also super weird.
Like it's the same name.
It's the same name.
Why?
What are you going to copyright it for your, for your protest movement?
It seems very strange to me.
It makes me wonder if Roger is somehow involved, but I have no idea.
He is nowhere to be found.
Does Roger still have the email address?
Stop the steal at Gmail?
At Yahoo?
Yeah, probably.
Um, so Ali wants sort of the same thing Alex wants, which is a new election, but only in
the States that Trump lost.
What?
Well, because there can't be a recount, you know?
Unfortunately even winning, uh, Nevada wouldn't put us over the top.
That puts us at two 65 or two 66.
We have to win Pennsylvania and look, I know it's not popular.
The Republican party doesn't want me to say this, but we need a revote in Wisconsin and
we need a revote in Michigan.
The fraud is so wrought there and we are going to get a recount in, in Wisconsin, but here's
what I'm afraid of.
Alex.
I think the Democrats have baited us into a rigged recount on recount trap guys, classic
recount guys.
You just lost it.
We didn't bait you into a recount trap.
No one wants a recount.
It's a classic recap.
That's not even a thing.
That's a recount trap.
It's a set up.
When was the last recount trap that happened?
Every election since Hoover.
This is what he thinks the Democrats big prestige is at the end of the film.
They're like, ha ha.
And we wanted you to do the recount the whole time.
We won the state and we want you to force a recap so we can also win again more so we
can win more this time.
Cool, Ali.
Can't imagine why the Republican party doesn't want you talking for him.
Strange.
Yeah, he believes Ali believes that Trump's just got to seize power.
Well, we certainly need to use the full weight of the federal government.
And and what we got to do is we the people have to say you have a mandate to do that.
President Trump got more votes than any candidate in American history.
The idea just just visualize this.
Go to your child and ask him, do you think that Joe Biden would be the top vote getter
in American history?
No, nobody believes that.
And so we know that it's rigged.
They just had a plus one system rigged in every Republican ballot that came in.
They found a dead person.
They found a covid ballot.
Somebody did a mail in ballot and then voted in on Election Day, too.
They rigged the election.
There's no body who's going to believe that Joe Biden is the most popular politician in
American history.
I agree with you.
One from you, two for me.
So, so did.
So excuse me.
We just did we win by what, 66 percent of the popular vote must have.
Yeah, this is dumb.
I would say don't ask your child this question and then assume anything, because, you know
what, a lot of trivia is surprising.
Yeah, yeah.
And sometimes you'll be surprised by facts.
Ask like a six year old with no prior actual experience and really no understanding of
the American system at all, whether or not Biden would be the most popular candidate
in history.
I guarantee that no one would think that in a bubble, Biden would get the most votes of
anybody ever.
But I think given the circumstances, yes, if you look at the context, it makes a little
more sense.
And if you consider like how a lot of that is voting against Trump, it makes sense.
Yeah.
But so Ali is like, yeah, Trump had to have won because you can't imagine even a child
couldn't imagine that someone likes Biden more.
Yeah.
That's not good thinking.
Oh, no, that's that's real bad.
This guy sucks.
And he leaves.
And Amanda and Alex start talking about, like, what happened with Drudge, man?
Drudge is Drudge is gone.
Oh, guys.
He doesn't like us anymore.
Guys.
What happened to Drudge?
You tell me, you know, everybody thinks he was kidnapped and there's somebody else in
place because this is very bizarre.
His behavior this year.
It's very weird.
It's not helpful is what it is.
But whatever his game is, I'm not super into it.
But but anyway.
But yeah.
I'm not into it either.
I mean, was he blackmailed?
Was he kidnapped?
I mean, they're willing to do anything.
No, I think.
He was at the White House.
Somebody didn't listen to him.
He saw some betrayals.
He got really pissed.
They weren't standing up against censorship.
And Steve Bannon through the grapevine told me that CNN leased it and that CNN.
That's what it seems like.
CNN leased it.
But then I was like, OK, I was like, I don't believe Steve Bannon because what Roger Stone
said.
I think Steve overall is a good guy.
I don't want to be mad at him.
I don't want to have fights with people.
I'm not trying to be a Washington guy.
I don't care.
I don't get in the middle of it.
But then I look at CNN and then I look at Drudge and it's it's their flavor.
It's their signature.
It is.
It matches very, very well.
Yeah.
Drudge Report's now CNN.
They're leasing it.
Man.
When we go back to the stakes where it's like he's saying nonsense like Drudge Report is
leasing, Drudge is leasing the Drudge Report to CNN.
Yeah.
But what's the contract like?
What's the seriously clandestine contract to because you can't release an option to
extend?
No point.
Yeah.
Is it hard?
Look, does everybody get to share or is it like the Super Bowl thing where you can only
buy ads at a certain time?
Let's pretend this means anything.
OK.
If this does mean something, then imagine that the hero of your media sphere, the guy
who has directed the course of conservative talk radio for the last like 20 years since
the Clinton days, the guy who can make or break people.
One hundred percent.
The guy who brought us Andrew Breitbart and therefore brought us Breitbart, brought us
James O'Keefe.
You got it.
The guy who's like responsible for so many shitheads.
Yeah.
He's also someone whose site you can lease.
See, but that's something that I think they would buy.
Well, that would be like I'm a grifter.
He's a grifter.
But that would kind of implies that he's had a lease prior.
Yeah.
Who is he leased out to prior?
Who is he working for?
Murdoch can't afford his prices anymore.
Now it's just CNN.
Is that the implication?
I think that might be the implication.
Wrestle with that, Alex, because I think Alex actually kind of touched on what probably
could be a reasonable explanation, and that is that Drudge got led in a little bit, saw
the disorder, saw the quote unquote betrayals, recognized that Trump wasn't taking the issues
of like online censorship seriously, which is something that he would be super interested
in given his brand and his entire market space.
You would think.
And so he followed his principle, which is I can't support this anymore or whatever.
I mean, the guy wants to get rid of 230.
I aggregate conservative media, so I am fucked if they do that.
Yeah.
I'm a single issue voter.
And your guy is going to kill my business.
Exactly.
Yeah.
And so I think that Alex kind of recognized, he kind of gave up the game that he understands
actually what's going on.
Yeah.
But you've got to play some fun thing with like he's getting leased out by CNN or he's
kidnapped or blackmailed or whatever.
Have a fun time with that.
No, whatever, dudes.
So there's another question, not only what's up with Matt Drudge, what's up with Trump?
Where's he been?
Let me ask you this question, because you are an insider for the Patriot movement.
I was flipping out the day after the election saying, OK, he gave a three a.m. speech.
It was amazing.
I want to see him Oval Office addressing every fraud, fireside chat, graphs showing it, you
know, Gateway pun.
And I think some of the best job overall analysis and force on video the best.
But I don't care.
I just want to win.
He should be up there showing it.
But then he's been dead silent for a day and a half.
And then talking to the crew, they all separately.
I went to different offices.
I respect people's actual view, I say, because I was missing.
I'm like, where is he?
He needs to be up front attacking.
Yeah, they go.
He's waiting for the people to mobilize and he's going to see what we do.
It's now up to us.
And I think that clicked.
Is that an accurate statement?
That is a great leader.
As our fearless leader, he has decided to allow us to choose what he will do based upon
our disorganized actions.
I've concocted a way to look at this.
So if shit goes bad, it's kind of our fault.
Trump put the ball in our court and we just didn't storm the buildings or something.
Trump is a genius.
He's just saying, hey, people, you do whatever you to do.
What a leader.
It is.
You know what?
I'm almost I'm almost like, God damn it, America can't even get a good dictate, a good dictator.
Like we're just shitty people.
We're just shitty people who got a shitty dictator.
Other places know how to get a fucking dictator, you know, like Russia's had 30 dictators.
They know what they're doing.
It's it's it's a little strange.
The the the sort of the position that Alex has put in is like he's he's he's presented
this guy is like strong, competent and a good leader.
And now in a position where like the everything is pretty uncertain, things are tense.
There's election counting going on.
Trump's nowhere to be found.
No, he's not assuming a leadership position.
Oh, that's right.
The thing he's supposed to do.
Yeah.
And you can do that without asserting power or claiming you won the election.
You can still be visible and say, you know, this is going along.
The process is moving.
We support the vote counters.
Totally.
You know, there is a way to do that and still give the appearance that someone's here, someone's
in charge.
And instead, no, Alex even recognizes, I don't fucking know.
I don't know if I've seen Trump since election night.
Yeah.
And no one knows what to do.
And if you look at all of the people on the like, this is maybe another thing that we
got lucky with because Trump's such an actually shitty leader.
Everybody went apeshit in their own little pockets, like throughout all of election night.
And as the votes have come in and they they declared it for Biden, you see more of those
little pockets of everybody frantically discussing with all their friends.
But there's no unified, yeah, we're going to do this.
It's everybody separate.
Like, I don't know what to do.
Q hasn't said anything.
I don't know what to do.
You don't say anything.
I don't know.
We have no leaders.
Yeah.
And actually, that leads us to our next clip, because there's a phenomenon that Amanda discusses
that I think is really interesting.
Power vacuum.
Cernovich got to Arizona in like, what, like a couple hours?
Like he was like, I'm there, I'm going.
And he gathered all those people and did it.
I mean, that's what's happening right now is everybody's putting aside any kind of,
you know, critiques of the administration or whatever's happening.
And they're just they're just jumping in, because this moment is everything.
She repeats that a number of times about, like, people like Mike Cernovich and Jack
Posobach and all these people, these influencers, not Alex.
Well, they're all on.
Alex is presumably on the same page because you haven't like Ali Alexander on another
one of these figures who they all put aside their differences and they're like, we got
to do something right.
It's like, yeah, no shit.
They are.
Their game is over.
Yeah.
They have to.
They all recognize that the door is closing on the scams they've been running.
Right.
Much like Drudge is like, hey, fuck Trump.
He's going to destroy my business.
Cernovich is like, I think we should probably start a war because they're fucking up my
business.
Yeah.
And we're just like, we're going to very quickly not have much relevance.
We're going to be in the opposition.
Right.
Uh, there's already, I guess I could just be an MRA guy again or I could be, do my pickup
artist thing again, maybe.
Just get your real estate license.
Shit.
Cernovich.
He's a lawyer.
Just sell houses.
He's technically a lawyer.
Yeah.
He should sell houses.
Sure.
Why not?
Um, yeah.
And I think that phenomenon is kind of interesting.
I don't experience it because I don't know what any of these ding dongs are up to privately,
but it is, it is interesting to hear her say like, oh, everyone's putting their, their
heads together.
They can't, they have to figure out how to survive.
What's our new scam.
Yeah.
The, the swamp is congealed.
How do we, how do we escape this?
Yeah.
Uh, let's claim Laura Loomer actually won.
That is, that is, that's so stupid.
They because, Oh man, here's the great thing about later on.
And here's my, here's my guess.
We're going to see a very close parallel between what happens at info wars whenever Alex has
gone and what happens in the far right whenever Trump has gone.
I think there'll be some, some fractioning, you know, some of them are competent.
I think there'll be some splintering off, but you'll see, you'll see kind of, I think
what's going to happen to everybody is basically what's happened to people who've been kicked
off Twitter.
Yeah.
It's just like they will sort of spiral a little bit and be like, even if you had a
platform, this is worse.
Yeah.
Um, and, and I think that, you know, you'll really see the difference between people who
have something and are safe and are not.
People like Jack Posobick and Mike Cernovich are not secure.
I don't think they're stable in their media position.
People like Ben Shapiro or Alex, they are, they're, they're like, Alex has some issues
to iron out and figure out what he's going to do, but he also has millions and a gigantic
media operation.
Like he's going to be able to figure out something to do.
It might be embarrassing as hell.
He might lose a bunch of his audience, but he'll figure out something.
Ben Shapiro's probably going to be embarrassed for a little bit, but he'll be fine.
Yeah.
He'll be fine.
He'll figure out something to do.
He'll become a different type of mass asshole.
Yeah.
Jack Posobick is going to keep working at like what, these, these fringe OAN type outlets.
Probably.
There's just nowhere.
There's no path forward there.
Speaking of people who are going to be fine, I think because they just have a big enough
brand.
James O'Keefe comes on.
You think James O'Keefe is going to be fine, huh?
Yes.
I think he's going to be fine.
I think he has enough of a brand and name recognition inside of like the larger conservative
sphere.
Sure.
That he could sort of abandon a lot of these like things that are tailored to the Trump
base and he could be fine.
He'll, I think he, he's, if you're associated with Andrew Breitbart personally, I don't
think you're ever going to be like, yeah, yeah, there'll be, there'll be a way for you
to keep failing upwards.
Yeah.
He comes on with a terrible phone connection and he's just talking about voter fraud.
It's really hard to listen to because the voter, sorry, the phone line is awful.
Yeah.
And then it's also very sad.
It honestly comes off less about like he's trying to prove some kind of claim.
It seems more like he has this narrative that he wants to sell to people and he's trying
to recruit other people to play the role of whistleblowers for him, like to use them as
props.
He's multi-level marketing.
Yeah.
Would you like to be a prop in my next?
Absolutely.
And you can recruit three more people to be props in yours.
Yeah.
But what we need today is more people at the polls, people who are poll watchers, people
who handle ballots to blow the whistle in an army of whistleblowers.
I can't emphasize this enough.
Now is the time today, tonight for you to do this.
Absolutely.
Don't wait.
Our destiny, our future, our, our very birthright's being stolen.
So yeah, he's just trying to enlist people to come like be, be a guest star in my next
video.
It seems like a, the way he gets all of his quote, whistleblowers.
Yeah.
I found it very uninteresting.
So Alex has now decided at this point in the show, I got to go somewhere.
Cernovich went to Arizona and people seem to enjoy that.
Yeah.
There's people yelling in States.
This is still wet concrete.
Yeah.
We could still do something.
Sure.
There's still some attention and Arizona seems like it's getting closer.
So that might be one where we actually might eke out a win and Maricopa County's the home
of Joe Arpaio, who I also love so much.
I hope he dies.
Um, and so Alex decides he's got to go somewhere, but he doesn't know where
I feel like I'm in Las Eisley spaceport, go to Los Eisley, what airplane to get on where
I'm going to go because there's no way I can sit back while this is going on.
Should I go to Arizona or should I go to Georgia or should I go to Michigan?
God almighty.
You ever try to fly direct from Los Eisley to Arizona?
It's hellish.
It's a long flight.
Yeah.
You're going to have to take a couple of stops.
And you wind up in a wretched hive of scum and villainy.
Yeah.
So Alex, you know, we all know that he eventually ends up going to Arizona, but he has a really
difficult time figuring out where to go.
Sure.
And now as the show goes on too, like earlier, he was kind of just like puzzling over why
Trump is not appearing right anywhere.
And he's kind of like, Hey, he's just letting the people act.
That was earlier.
Yeah.
As the show goes on, he starts to get a little bit mad about the fact that Trump is hiding.
Wow.
It begins Democrat lawmakers call on Twitter to remove us president from the platform because
he's not giving speeches, but you're a hundred times more viral.
Where is the president?
We haven't seen him unless I'm wrong crew.
Your watch as much as I do or more, a lot more eyeballs than I do.
I got two eyeballs, two eyeball at four, six, eight, like 12, 14 eyeballs in there.
Has Trump been seen since three 30 in the morning on a Wednesday?
Just asking, you know, we're talking 36 hours ago.
Has anybody seen the president?
Did the cookie monster eat him?
Oh, cookie, I mean, I mean, where, where is the president?
Where is the president?
I've tried to like defend the president and I love the president and I think he overalls
in a great job.
And I, but I mean, we're in the middle of the Alamo war here and we ain't seen Colonel
Travis in a day and a half, huh?
Just like the real Colonel Travis, he's off drunk somewhere.
I mean like, I don't know.
I don't take fault with that thought like devoid of anything else he's saying.
It's like, yeah, you should be, you should be frustrated that Trump isn't really guiding
the folks.
Is that, is that why, what if all of those predictions of like Trumpism is never going
to leave us or are all countered by the fact that we didn't expect them to eventually be
like, Hey, Trump sucks at this.
Hmm.
I think so.
When he finally betrays them at the end, they're finally like, Oh shit, we got conned.
Well, no.
I think a lot of the underlying things are what you have to be more worried about and
someone who isn't as much of a very clear con man carrying out some of those political
things and the flaws that in our system that Trump has exploited, the recognizing that
there is no reason to not act like a dick hole and there are no reason to follow norms
apparently because well, decent people do unwritten rules are just things that people
whine about.
Yeah.
So people have generally been beholden to a lot of those things and I think Trump has
really exposed that there's no reason to follow them.
There's no consequence for breaking any of them.
Totally.
I mean, even in baseball, if you do a bat flip to agree, just you get hit in the back
with a bit of a fastball.
Well, yeah.
I will.
Okay.
We get to hit Trump in the back with a fastball.
I think that's fine with a 97 mile an hour.
Someone who's less of a very overt con man and someone who's a lot more capable and has
the same sort of policies that appeal to people who recognize the ways in which they can break
unwritten rules and stuff.
And that's kind of what you more have to be really worried about.
And I think that those people will again fall for that.
Yeah.
It's not hard.
No.
So Alex, he's like, fuck, I need to go somewhere.
I haven't seen Trump on TV in a long time.
I'm going to fucking take a nap.
Maybe I'm going to get a jet airplane to fly me up to DC.
That's where I need to be.
See, I'm ready to take action that I'm trying to like, I can't overanalyze this.
I have to, I have to go to my sleepy place.
That's the joke of a meme of that.
But I mean, I have to like, I literally, I'll go take a 30 minute nap sometimes and go,
what is the answer to something?
And I go to bed and then I'll have a dream of what to do.
So I got to get dialed into my subconscious, allow show secret sauce there.
And I think I got to sleep here.
I got to have the engine turn off with in my mind.
What do I do?
And I'll wake up with the answer.
Is it DC?
Is it Georgia?
Is it Arizona?
Is it Detroit?
I don't know.
Go to hell.
But I mean, I just can't sit here with this amount of history going down and do nothing.
I've got to take action.
Oh my God.
I just love the idea that he's sitting here.
I got to do something.
I just, there's so much history going on.
I'm going to take a nap.
I think I'll dream my solution.
The reason that this show is, I do recognize that even, you know, with Trump not being
in power, I'm still entirely fascinated by Alex.
And the reason is that this show is like, it's a compelling psychodrama.
It is.
We're in the next season where he's just confused for the next year.
Well, I think he'll be confused for a bit, but I think he'll land quicker than that.
Maybe he should just go to Tibet.
I hear that's where people find themselves.
Let Owen take over.
Yeah.
Yeah, totally.
Just become a fucking Buddhist out there.
Just do it.
Calm down.
Relax.
Live your life a little bit.
That certainly would be interesting.
Yeah.
But there's a 30% chance that he won't need to do that.
Okay.
I'd give Trump a 30% chance we pull this out, prove the fraud.
But no, it's, we're a judge nation.
Nobody came for those babies getting chopped up, 62 million of them.
Nobody came for all the kids getting kidnapped by the left, putting torture rings.
And so we just had it good too long and God's sick of us not caring and not being involved.
God says, I'm going to burn you now.
Whoa.
You got to get a better God, man.
So I guess we've been judged and we're going to burn.
God is really, really turning on a hairpin these days.
30% chance that's not going to happen though if Trump somehow proves that the election
fraud.
He will stay God's hair.
Proves it.
Good God.
Yeah.
What are we doing?
So apparently Patriots are being culled from the internet and Alex has a familiar thing
happened to him as he's trying to discuss this.
They're going through everybody that's been identified as a Patriot for this coup and
they're blocking and freezing or banning your account.
This is a takeover.
When the lights go out, the communications go out, that's when the troops start coming
down to the parachutes, metaphysically.
Well, this is it.
This is the bigger soul.
At least you're full grown adults.
You're not a baby in the womb, got chopped up, didn't have a chance.
So we deserve what's about to happen.
Get close to Jesus and wake up or get your head between your legs and kiss your ass goodbye.
Go ahead and play that report.
The one that Rob do gave us where it's like five minutes long, but we're gonna play the
one where I predict all of the stuff is now happening.
That was the one I talked about.
We have that.
Also need for that either.
No need for that either.
All right, we're going to push Matt Bracken back because we're going to have a moment
of clarity here.
Rob came in about two hours ago and he said, we've got this video and I said, that's wonderful.
Just tell them about it.
We'll have it.
No problem.
Take care of it.
And, uh, we had a little meetings about it and now we don't have it and I'm not mad.
I love it.
It's okay.
So it's all of us phones and computers have obituated us not to get face to face and have
a meeting.
So my crew works their ass off.
They're amazing, but they produce so much information that if they don't face to face
and have that decision, it never happens.
So that's okay.
Cause it's not bad to have a mistake on a live show.
We're going to air that on air.
It's going to happen.
If I have to host the next five hours, it's going to happen.
So that's what all this is about.
That's what all this is about.
You understand?
Did he just tell me that his employees don't read emails?
Um, maybe they got to do this face to face face to face.
They ignore me if I'm not yelling at them.
I can't get tone and email.
I try all caps.
It doesn't work.
It doesn't do anything for me.
Yeah.
I mean, I just thought I'd put that in there cause I mean, that is what this is all about.
People thought, I know that I've heard this feedback from the audience a lot.
Sure, sure, sure.
If Biden wins, Alex's tech problems will go away because he'll recognize that he's got
to get his shit together and they'll really clean up a shop and take care of business.
No.
Another storyline to follow in, uh, Alex and Tibet.
I'm going to call it that this season.
That's what we're going to do.
Um, sure.
I'm down with that.
So in this next clip, this is the last one from Alex's show on November 5th and that
is him handing it off to Matt Bracken.
Uh, noted weirdo, uh, Matt Bracken, fourth hour host and nothing else, Matt Bracken.
Um, Alex needs to go somewhere and he needs to get some guidance about where to go.
So you ask Matt Bracken, where am I going?
I'm planning to get on an airplane and either go to, uh, either go to, uh, Arizona or go
to Georgia.
Let me ask Matt Bracken this question.
I'm gonna play this clip.
Matt, where do you think people need to be the most on the ground?
Is it, is it Detroit?
Is it, uh, is it Arizona?
Is it Georgia?
They're trying to steal them all right now.
They already got Detroit.
It's a multi-front war.
I would probably say Philadelphia because if, if, uh, if it's, if it doesn't happen
in Pennsylvania, it doesn't matter.
The other ones are peripheral, you know, the path, all of the pathways for Trump require
our Pennsylvania.
Good point, Matt.
I'm going to Arizona, Arizona.
Why do you even ask people stuff?
All right, Matt, that's a, that's a very good point.
That is a good point.
I have friends in Arizona and Philly will beat the shit out of me.
I will get my ass kicked.
I'm going to go to Arizona.
I'm not going to be in Philly.
Not going to be in Philly.
Did you see that?
There were people dancing and they want to hurt me.
Yeah.
Uh, Gritty is going to kick my ass.
Gritty will kick your ass.
Uh, so Alex goes to take a nap, I guess, and then the spirits come to him and tell him
to go to Arizona.
Okay.
I don't fucking know.
Something like that.
Uh, but while he's taking a nap, Owen Troyer comes in to host the war room and, uh, Owen
has a big guest, uh, on the show.
Oh no.
I get the sense that by this point, Alex has left.
I think he's already on route to Arizona.
Yeah.
Okay.
Uh, because there is a sense of like, we should get Alex in on this and he's unavailable.
Uh oh.
Uh, so he's either taking that nap or he's on his way to Arizona, but big guest.
But Dr. Steve Pacinek, uh, as we're in the middle of this, the election's over.
We're now in the stealing process of the election.
Uh, what are you seeing?
What's going through your mind as you're witnessing this gigantic hoax?
Number one, it's not a hoax.
What's happening now and the reason I couldn't come on the Alex Jones show last night was
I was not given the permission that I needed to in order to say what I'm about to say now.
I do not work for the federal government.
I'm not paid by them.
Make it clear I don't work for the government.
We know.
We know, Steve.
So yeah, it's at first it sounded like he was talking from inside a bottle.
Sure.
But, uh, I guess it turned the game up on us.
Turn that up just a little bit so we can hear the doctor.
Yeah.
He didn't have permission to say something.
I didn't get the go ahead from Melania and now we will be taking over everything.
I am consort to Melania, queen of the earth.
Can I be honest with you?
What's that?
I think that he knew that this shit wouldn't fly with Alex.
Yeah, I absolutely think that.
I think that that's what permission means.
That's exactly what I thought.
Yeah, because here's what he's got here because I couldn't say this on Alex's show.
He wouldn't let me.
Here's what Steve recently got permission to say.
Gotcha.
This is really a sting operation, contrary to what everybody else said, Trump knew this
was happening.
Eric knew this was happening and warn the public.
I knew this was happening, however, I could not say anything about it.
Of course not.
What happened was we marked watermark every ballot with what's called the Q F S block
chain encryption code.
In other words, we know pretty well where every ballot is, where it went and who has
it.
So this is not a stolen election.
On the contrary, we reversed the entire game of war along the lines of the sons of the
art of war.
And Trump was brilliant and still is brilliant at it.
So what we've got here is Steve claiming that the election was actually a sting operation
to catch voter fraud, wherein the department of Homeland security has watermarked all of
these ballots with block chain.
He does not explain what he means by that.
Oh, don't worry about it.
And they can be traced.
They know literally where every single ballot is at any point.
And because of this watermark, they can tell which ones are fake.
So there's a bunch of ballots.
They know, Oh, no watermark, these are fake.
This is a load of horse shit.
Yeah, this is not good.
This is real bad.
One of the reasons why this is really particularly bad is this is a narrative that is so provable.
This is one that like, if you have this information, if Trump really does have this, first of all,
he needs to bring it out.
That's the only thing he needs to do.
I still don't want him to be president, but he has a moral obligation to tell the nation.
This is exactly what you would do like the day after they called everybody would be like,
okay, now we're going to reveal that this was all a sting operation.
Yeah.
Now it turns out this backfires because no one cares and they all think I already lost
the election.
It's...
Oh, that's not good.
But you'd have this hard evidence.
That's true.
This is hard evidence.
I'm sure it is.
You have to keep these conspiracies non-falsifiable.
They have to be like vague and about coups and counter coups and moves and shadowy things.
This is too concrete.
It's absolute.
I have a, I have another problem with this.
Oh, just one?
Just one.
All right.
So he is saying we, I assume he can't mean he, he's not including himself.
He always talks like that.
He says that I have, I have 17,000 troops in Germany.
I was going to say, he always does that.
He speaks in the first person about everything.
It's just like we have watermarked these ballots, but then he started with, I don't work for
the federal government.
He's a ramp...
What the fuck do you work for that's watermarking all these ballots?
He's a rampant narcissist.
Totally.
Yeah.
This is a QAnon thing too.
This was going around in QAnon.
Yeah, no, I've heard this one.
Yeah.
And also I was thinking about it as like, why is Steve into this?
One, I think it's cause he's into QAnon.
Sure.
Two, I was researching like watermarked ballots and one of the places that it comes up the
most as like a very like con, like a normally used thing is in condo association elections
in Florida.
Now Steve lives in Florida.
So it's gated communities.
That's where all watermarked ballots...
It's an issue that's discussed on a number of websites about condo association elections
and like ways to keep them secure.
And so like, I think that maybe he has some experience with the idea from that.
That's very funny.
And maybe he's projecting that onto the world.
Anyway, this is silly.
Yeah.
It's not good.
And it gets worse.
All of this was expected.
All of this is part of the sting operation we're running.
And let me tell you that 48 hours ago, not only did we put markers on those ballots,
but I can say now with the permission of people in the intelligence community and elsewhere
that we have sent out thousands and thousands of national guards to 12 different States,
Washington, Delaware, Texas, Arizona, Alabama, and everywhere.
So now you have to consider and rethink what this is really about.
This is about the constitution, clearly.
Wait.
So the governors of those States, I assume, approved the national guard.
Invited in the national guard.
Because that's how it has to work.
And all these States who run their own elections have agreed to his watermarking of the ballot.
Of course.
Yeah.
Okay.
Whatever.
This is deeply unconstitutional.
Get the fuck out of here.
Yeah.
Anyway, so that's kind of like how you would respond if you were Owen, hearing this.
Sure, sure, sure.
Fuck off, Owen.
Get the fuck out of here.
Fuck off.
What are you doing?
Come on.
This is terrible.
He's wearing a Hawaiian shirt, too.
Yeah.
He was not.
Yes.
You can't be running the revolution in a goddamn Hawaiian shirt.
He's sitting there.
He's like, ah, I might as well have like a drink and a coconut in my hand.
Yeah, why not?
Yeah, yeah.
Here's how Owen responds.
Okay.
Steve, you've just broken certainly perhaps the biggest news since the election here on
the show.
I have to play this out logically in my head.
Okay.
That's why I go on your show to basically, I keep saying-
Well, I love you, Steve.
I'd kiss you on the lips right now if it wasn't digitally.
Aha.
So he's thrilled.
Of course he is.
Now, Steve wants to make this even better.
Yeah, of course.
Because there's even better news.
Come on.
People will be arrested as of tonight, tomorrow, and it will go on for quite a while.
And this was a total sting operation that I can say.
Okay.
Well, this did not happen.
The Red Wedding will play itself out every night for years to come.
There will be blood in the streets.
Until only Melania is left.
Melania will stand to take the Game of Thrones.
Yeah.
All right.
Okay.
This is getting a little more Q than Steve usually is.
Like he's usually either cranky, racist, anti-Semitic, homophobic.
He usually has something going on, or wants to insult Alex a bunch.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Those are the best.
He does seem to have themed appearances.
Yeah.
This is quite Q.
And it's strange, but I also think that he knows on some level, whether it's rationally
and consciously or just sort of, ah, best not to try, he knows that Alex wouldn't put
up with this, probably.
No, no, no, no.
We're trying to say that this election was stolen.
Yeah.
That's the business.
That's where the money is.
You saying this is something that's going to be completely disproven, or it'll be like
never proven, like why wasn't it?
Exactly.
This is going to be a big problem for us.
We can't make money off this.
You're trying to build a pay-per-view match that no one wants to see.
This is a day-long story.
At best.
This is a day-long story at best, and that's only on the War Room.
This is a distraction for the junior varsity.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
Give this to Owen while I'm out.
So Steve talks a little bit more about this.
I still don't really understand what he's describing.
I would love for him to actually say what all this technology is, but he doesn't do
that.
All right.
So how is this watermark on the ballots, what is the significance of that as to, is it going
to stop from fake balance being counted, or how is that going to be used?
Well, we use it in any way that we need to use it in terms of counting, knowing which
ones were fake, which ones were not.
It's a very sophisticated code.
So if you just throw them away, these are cyber communication implementations that we
have the code for, and we know exactly what was thrown away.
We know exactly what was placed.
We know exactly who has it, and we know exactly where it went.
I can't go any further than that.
Wow.
This is a huge news that Steve Pechenik is breaking on our show right now.
Some would call it news.
Some would not.
I mean, yeah, I'm going to go with, I don't think I'm going to buy that one, Dan.
If I were Owen, I'd be like, wow, Steve's having fun today.
He's on one.
Yeah.
Steve's dressed for the occasion.
He showed up in his uniform for what this is, which is bullshit.
Hold the fucking phone.
Yeah.
If you know where every ballot is right now.
Like God's Eye from the Fast and Furious movie.
Like why are we bothering with all this nonsense?
And if they're fake, why didn't you tell people at the ballot counting places that they were
fake?
Everywhere had people watching them.
But you're not a showman.
You don't understand the need for the reveal.
You're right.
This was all my fault.
Yes.
I didn't realize that we have to have the prestige.
I apologize.
Why do the trick if there isn't the reveal?
I get you.
You've got to do this.
No, no.
You're right.
That part makes total sense.
If in Ocean's Eleven they just stole money and then left, that's a very bad movie.
I get it.
Yeah.
He needs to explain a little bit more about what this tech he's describing is, why it's
so powerful.
Sure.
And then also, it's a big problem when nothing comes of this.
Yeah.
That's a real problem.
Because if you take Alex's instincts, even if he's desperate to come up with a way to
spin the election, he would know better than to take this on as something that he's going
to have to then deal with tomorrow and the day after and the day after.
It's much easier to say that there was someone who might have been Chinese who showed up
at four in the morning with a box of ballots.
Done.
Try and disprove me.
You don't even care enough to disprove me.
But if you start saying some shit like, I know where every ballot is, now we're in trouble,
man.
Yeah, yeah.
Now I got to deal with shit.
Absolutely.
Like somebody saying stuff like, why didn't you just use a barcode?
So Owen gets a little bit high on this.
Of course.
On Steve's inside exclusive.
He's young.
Yeah.
And he perhaps just broke the biggest news story of the day.
He did it in a floral button up shirt with a smile on his face from his kitchen.
So Fox News and mainstream news and all you with your billions of dollars and your big
pharmaceutical contracts, I'll keep it PG rated, you can go fudge yourselves, okay?
Go fudge yourselves and enjoy it as well.
Now I want to hone in on what Dr. Pacinik broke.
Again, folks, Steve can reiterate this in his own words.
The whole election theft was a setup.
Try and say it.
That's my favorite thing.
That is just the best.
That is my, like what I like to laugh at is Owen taunting the mainstream fake news.
Defiant.
Defiant in the face of all reality, listening to Dr. Steve Pacinik while he's masturbating
looking to photos of Melania.
Oh my God.
Now Steve, he's a weirdo.
Yeah.
I agree.
Even when he comes in with this kind of thing, he's still going to say some things during
the interview that are big problems for InfoWars.
And one of them comes in this next clip because Alex has been very, very clear that the Democrats
are run by the Chinese.
And the devil.
Well, through China.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
China is like the intermediary between the devil and the Democrats, basically.
That's a tough job.
Steve says, nah.
Who is running this Democrat party right now?
I mean, who is running?
Who is the brain trust?
It's obviously not Biden.
I don't think it's Obama.
Is it the Chinese?
Are the Chinese setting them up?
No, the Chinese are not part of it with all due respect to Chinese communism and all that.
I know Chinese communism quite well.
I know Xi.
I've known about Mao Zedong.
The real issue is the inherent corruption of a democratic party and its machinery.
Wait, wait, wait.
So the Chinese aren't involved at all?
So the Chinese aren't involved at all.
Wait, wait, Steve.
I'm very familiar with Chinese communism.
Xi and I hang out.
We play golf on the weekends.
He's part of my condo association.
Before I leave, I'd like to contradict Alex's entire world here.
Perfect.
Wow.
And while I'm here, there's no such thing as God.
The Chinese communists are not important.
They're not a big deal.
The election was a sting operation.
I gotta go.
You know who you gotta worry about?
Uruguay.
They're big in the stealing elections game.
This dude is throwing haymakers.
Wow.
Yeah.
Love it.
So they get talking a little bit about Obama.
This is kind of funny.
When I heard Obama two days ago again say, in this democracy, we have the right to vote.
You moron Obama.
I mean, this is a CIA operative that I kept saying should have gone to prison.
Everything in battle.
Does Trump know that?
Does Trump know who Obama is?
He knew already.
He knew.
But does he have the intelligence files too?
I can't say that.
Okay.
Oh man.
So funny.
Yeah.
He knows it.
Does he have a file?
I don't know.
All of this seems so much more fun and less serious when I don't have like four years
of murder to look forward to.
You know?
Yeah.
I mean, there's four years of, you know, still trouble.
Oh, gonna be a lot of trouble, but not like every...
It's more a situation of, I think we're still in a little bit of like exhaling.
There is a big exhale going on.
And I think that you might be overselling like the...
I'm trying.
The feelings of relief and stuff.
I'm trying to do more things in America.
I'm trying, man.
And I think it's a really tough thing because, you know, like on the one hand, yes, don't
discount the fact that getting Trump out of office and him losing is very crucially important.
While, at the same time, don't lose sight of the fact that even though Biden gets in,
it doesn't mean anything is fixed by itself.
There's still exactly the same amount of work that needs to be done.
The same issues exist.
I tweeted out just like, oh, fuck, Biden is president.
And then, oh, fuck, Biden is president.
And people were like, don't ruin this for me.
I'm like, no, no, no, you can hold these two thoughts simultaneously.
These are not dissonant thoughts.
These are nuanced thoughts.
Yeah, yeah.
It could be, it could be, I mean, there's challenges.
Yeah.
And we just have to figure out.
Shit's still got to get done.
Yeah.
So Steve, we know from his time with Alex over the years, his normal methodology with
Alex is to flatter him.
Yes.
And we see this exact same behavior being applied to Owen here.
Please.
You know, self-deprecation is not impressive to me, Owen.
You're there.
You have to talk a lot and it takes a lot of cajonas and it takes a lot of sense of
self-worth and a sense of humor, which you and Alex have.
And you got a great staff with Daria and Scott and all of them.
But the point was you were selected.
I did not only selected you guys, but I personally selected you and those who I work with or
deal with, friendly with, they understood that it would come for your show.
That to me sounds like Alex wouldn't buy this shit.
I was like, who could I go on?
Uh, Owen.
Owen will buy it.
I think we're getting real delusional here.
This has gone past like fun conspiracy theories to him being like, I control the universe.
Well, and like I have this big breaking news and you know, you're so wonderful Owen that
I chose you to break the story.
That isn't like, I mean, it's nonsensical, but it's really him saying, I had nowhere
else to go.
No, it is.
Absolutely.
You were as good as I could do.
So I'm going to butter you up really hard.
So Owen's like, yeah, Alex, we need to get Alex in on this because this is big, like
for them.
Oh, and you are so, so young.
Steve, if you could hold over Alex Jones, as soon as he heard Steve Pechenik break the
huge news about the Trump sting, Alex Jones hopped in his race car.
He's probably going about 160 miles per hour right now.
He's probably on the phone with engineers trying to rig up like a car helicopter so
we can get here faster and avoid traffic.
Alex does not show up.
And Owen ends up interviewing Jesse Lee Peterson after Steve.
So I don't know.
I don't, I think I feel like Alex would be like, shut it down.
Yeah.
Shut it down.
Yeah, totally.
But Owen, Owen has that feel of like a literal apprentice situation where it's like the,
the master is out of the room and I found something that I think is really exciting
and it's like, this one and this one's mine.
I discovered this one, this one, I'm going to take it to the master and he's going to
be so proud of me.
And then they, he's like, no, this is fucking stupid.
Isn't that that Disney movie?
The Sorcerer's Apprentice?
Yeah.
Isn't that basically the plot of Fantasia?
Might be the plot of Fantasia.
Yeah.
You might be correct.
Owen's accidentally made the mops dance around and they're all making a mess.
Yeah, that's about it.
Yeah.
That is exactly right.
But it's still like, this is what I want plugged into my fucking veins.
Of course.
Ladies and gentlemen, we're back in the Infowars war room devastating the fake news media today
with Dr. Steve Pacinek giving us the inside scoop of president Trump's sting operation
that is ongoing right now.
The traps have been sprung.
Traps are sprung.
Defending the fake news.
There's a, there's a, there are two different completely feelings.
Two different feelings, right?
There's the feeling of being proud of yourself and then having that pride punctured by someone
else and realizing I have failed.
And then there's the feeling of hoping someone else will be proud of you.
And when that gets punctured, that's devastating.
I'm looking forward to hearing that from Owen.
I want to hear that devastation.
He thinks somebody's going to be so proud of him.
Yeah.
Or he'll, I don't, God, it's just, there, it's a complex feeling that is like, I've
done it.
Yep.
I have figured out how to save the world or something or totally, or even just like reduce
it down.
And on a cynical level, we're going to make a lot of money off this or something, you
know, like there's just, I've saved Infowars and you can see it in the moment.
Like no, exactly right.
But because I hate them, it's hilarious.
I love it.
Yeah.
This is, screw it.
I would never laugh at conservative tears.
Conservative hubris is the funniest thing in the world.
Exactly.
And that's really what I was feeling when it was like, what's the reverse that I can
feel good about of election night 2016, Alex laughing at people crying.
It's this.
It is this.
Owen being like, we're taking down the fake news.
Pure, pure, pure joy I get from this.
Owen either being unable or incapable of seeing through Steve Pechenik's bullshit.
So transparently stupid bullshit.
And being like, we got him, we got him.
Fuck you, CNN.
Oh, sorry.
Fudge you, CNN.
We're past the emperor has no clothes.
The emperor is walking down the street without skin and everybody's pointing and Owen is
like, that's the emperor, baby!
Love that guy!
So we have one last clip here of Steve, uh, talking to Owen and again, it's just the buttering
up.
Yeah.
I was given the privilege of announcing this, but I don't know who else knows it.
I don't know what else will happen.
The truth of the matter is that your show was chosen and you have the good or the benefit
and I hope this will result in a lot of arrests and the end of a problem.
Okay.
Yeah.
I wish you Godspeed.
So I hope this winds up with a lot of arrests.
Like I said, uh, uh, Owen goes on to interview Jesse Lee Peterson.
Yes.
Then everyone went to sleep.
Right.
And the next day we wake up and David Knight's show, uh, from November 6th, he realizes Owen
got these brooms and mops dancing all over the place.
I got to clean up.
No, I know there's a theory that's come out saying we have watermarked ballots and this
is all just a big sting and we should trust the plan and I'm telling you right now, I'll
give you details on why I think that is absolute total gaslighting from a CIA official still
working for them.
And uh, we'll, we'll talk about that coming up.
That is absolute nonsense in my opinion.
So it's pajama kicked off the show forever.
So David Knight comes in and he's like, fuck you.
When I first heard that this had gone down, the David Knight was pushing back on this
stuff.
I'm like, he is fired.
Yeah.
He is fucking fired.
Then when I sat and thought about it a little bit more and recognize like, what are the
dynamics here?
I think David Knight's fine.
Yeah.
And I think they'll just pretend.
Oh, and didn't do that.
Yeah.
They made a bad move, but it's like, that's an info wars mistake.
It's an, it's the apprentice mistake.
Yes.
You know, of course you forgive the apprentice.
That's how you learn.
It's an info wars mistake too.
It's in the world of info wars.
You were chasing down a conspiracy, you know, like nine times out of 10, maybe it doesn't
work.
That 10th time, maybe we make a million dollars.
Exactly.
So fine.
We'll let you do that.
It's embarrassing.
Pretend you didn't do it.
Move along.
Put Steve in timeout.
Right.
He's going to be gone for a little bit.
He's not coming back before the inauguration.
When I listened to this David Knight thing, first of all, I was like, wow, he is as boring
as I remember.
But then I was like, Oh yeah, no, no.
He's doing what daddy needs him to do.
He's doing the work of cleaning up this because the narrative needs to be that the fucking
election was stolen.
You can't have it be that Trump did a sting operation.
That's going to fall apart.
Real quick.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
David Knight had good instincts.
That's weird.
Uh, but it looked like it was like, you're fucking gone.
Steve, Steve has got to be on the outs.
He's got to have like at least had a talking to or something.
This one's too nuts.
Yeah.
That must've been a phone call of like, dude, dude, you can't be swinging that hard.
So David Knight, uh, before he gets down to business on, on Steve's nonsense, he, uh,
I just wanted to play a couple of clips of his show just to be like, the tones of these
things are so fucking different.
Twitter permanently banned Steve Bannon because he called for, that's the way the daily mark
of the beast puts it.
Uh, he called for the beheading of dr Fauci and FBI director Christopher Ray.
Well, here's what he actually had to say.
I'd actually like to go back to the old times of tutor England.
I'd put that their heads on pikes, right?
I put them on two corners of the white house as a warning to federal bureaucrats.
Now, this is what's known as a metaphor, I believe.
I always get that confused assemblies, but I believe it's a metaphor because he didn't
use the word like, I think that is the, wow.
What is this show?
Exactly.
I'm like, this is for grandparents or something sarcastic old man show.
Yeah.
Like this is, this is for people who need a little bit of a milder presentation to their
extreme and their rationalizations of, of people saying fucked up things.
Oh, these people, they're not going to cut off heads.
It's a metaphor.
Also, I will say that David Knight likes to make jokes.
All right, Nancy Pelosi has announced a big expansion of COVID testing for lawmakers.
Well, I saw this and saw testing, testing.
Well, I knew it wasn't going to be polygraph testing.
Now that would be funny.
Wow.
That was actually almost charming.
I was almost a little charmed by that.
Yeah, because you know what that was?
That was...
Grandpa laughed at his own joke.
And it had joke structure.
Yeah, it did.
It had structure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It wasn't funny.
No good God though.
But it had structure.
Unlike so many of the things that Alex thinks are jokes that are just like maybe something
that's off color or offensive.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
It's, it's grandpa at Thanksgiving and you're like, that was great.
You didn't say anything about black lives matter.
We're having a great time.
We didn't bring up how much you love Song of the South this time, David.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
So yeah, I thought that was so bizarre.
Like I was looking at that, I'm like, this is InfoWars.
He just made a joke and laughed at it.
And that laugh did not seem fake.
And did not use any old timey slurs in the process.
Very bizarre.
So it took a while and a lot of boring shit to get through, but we get to David talking
about Steve Puchenik's story.
But you'll notice that the way he's talking about it, he's very careful to talk about
it as a story that's being posted on Reason.com as opposed to an interview his coworker had
done the day before.
Find me a little thread.
Trump's likeliest path appears to be narrower.
He needs to hang on to both Pennsylvania and Georgia and he also needs to overtake Biden
in either Nevada or Arizona.
So that's where we are at the moment.
But of course we know that this is all rigged.
We know that it was all baked in, which is why I just about fell out of my chair when
I saw this headline from Reason Magazine.
Not when you were watching The War Room the day before.
He doesn't watch The War Room.
I wouldn't.
So one thing I think is really interesting is that David Knight, his approach on it is
very much like, this makes no sense.
That's unfair.
I appreciate it.
To me, if this was a sting, it doesn't even make any sense.
It's another one of these deals like the laptop with Hunter Biden.
They waited to the very last minute to put that thing out thinking it was going to be
a surprise.
And then everybody just said, well, it's not credible, but media is going to put out the
narrative that's not credible.
It doesn't matter if you've got documents, doesn't matter if you've got photographic
evidence.
You can have all the documentation that you want in the world and they're not going to
believe it because the mainstream media and social media are going to censor you and they're
going to put out their narrative.
So I don't see that's going to do anything other than to create a forest fire.
But the point he's trying to make, I would take issue with one little tweak.
I'd make one little tweak, but it doesn't make sense because no one would believe this
anyway.
No, there is that.
That makes sense.
But his version of it is no one would believe it because the media would put out their own
version.
I don't agree with that.
No, totally.
I would say that everyone would be like, oh, fuck yourself.
That is true.
Probably if that story came out, people would just not believe it.
Wait, so he's saying that it is true, but that the media wouldn't believe it anyways?
He's saying that they wouldn't do it because no one would believe it even if they did it.
Oh, okay.
I got you now.
Basically, I think is what his point is.
He's not saying that it happened.
He's saying that they would have seen that happening ahead of time and not done the plan.
The plan would have been fucked by no one believing it, so they wouldn't have gone down
that road to begin with.
Sure.
That makes sense.
I guess.
I mean, however you get there is how you get there.
I don't know.
It doesn't make sense.
No, no, no, no.
Absolutely not.
If that's your reason why it doesn't make sense, you work at Infowars.
Whatever.
Fine.
Now, in this last clip, he doesn't talk about it that much, but Steve does say something
that I think is great.
Do you mean David Knight?
Yes.
About Steve.
Gotcha.
David Knight says this thing that I think it's great, but also it's a classic Infowars
thing where you're right, but you're wrong.
You're right.
Yes.
But you are so wrong.
Ah, the paradox.
Look, I didn't jump into Pizzagate.
I don't allow Pechenik to come on this show because last time he came on this show was
right after the shooting in Vegas.
He came on this show to sell the lie that nobody died in Vegas because he's trying to
trap me.
This guy is a CIA shill and he comes on to trap us.
That's one of the ways that they discredit you.
I'm not having anything to do with that.
We'll be right back.
Stay with us.
So, David's right that Steve is a fucking liar and he fucks with Infowars because he's
in a unique position where he seems to be able to get away with it and he causes a lot
of chaos.
He has a great time.
And I do believe that that is correct.
I remember that episode where Steve was on with David Knight and he was talking about
the Las Vegas shooting being fake and David Knight's reaction to that was, I agree with
you that Sandy Hook was fake, but not this one.
Yeah, I remember.
That was even one where you pulled that clip from David Knight.
I have that clip somewhere.
That's how important that was to you.
I have it in a folder somewhere.
But I do agree with him.
Don't have Steve on.
It's a great thing you have that rule.
Now, he's not a CIA shill.
No.
He's a bored man.
Uh huh.
In a condo in Florida.
You got it.
Who wants to fuck with you?
I don't understand how one out of three Infowars hosts is just like, this guy's a CIA shill
who's trying to destroy our entire business and the other two are like, eh, come on, have
a, come on in.
Not only is he not a CIA shill, he is the best.
Right.
Exactly.
Yeah.
If he's a CIA shill, he's tricked me.
Oh.
Oh shit.
But here's, here's where this becomes a little bit less like of a severe problem because
that does seem like a problem for like David Knight to be on air being like, Steve Pechenik
is a CIA shill who's trying to trap me with these bullshit stories and that's how they
get you.
Going all the way back to Las Vegas.
Right.
Yeah.
A long time.
He's been on Alex's show since then saying a bunch of nonsense.
And so by that token, David would have to think that he's trying to trap Alex.
It would only make sense.
And somehow that's fine to still work at the same place where that is going on.
Or, or he's only trying to trap David Knight.
David Knight is the white whale.
He's the one that Steve is trying to get rid of.
He's the big prize.
Yeah.
Uh, I don't think that's the case.
I don't think anybody's particularly focused on David Knight.
That's probably true.
Um, but here's the thing, Alex has done this too.
Yeah.
Like after the Las Vegas shooting, Alex did turn on Steve for a little while and he did
say to a caller, I think Steve is still working for the CIA and he's fucking with us.
Yep.
And then they made their peace after a couple months of Steve being on timeout.
So that's probably what'll happen again.
Most likely.
Although it's pretty funny.
It's very funny.
It's, it's really funny.
And I think that the image of Owen being like, fuck you mainstream media, we're destroying
you.
That's the image of Info Wars 2020 election that I want to hold onto.
And I want to remember, I want that to be sort of the spiritual energy that we're coming
with as opposed to, you know, laughing at, oh, you lost.
Yeah.
I don't, I don't want to laugh at you for losing.
I want to be glad that your candidate lost cause I hate the policies.
But I want to laugh at you for taunting the mainstream media because you got tricked by
Steve.
So good.
You, and you will get tricked again.
You think you're so smart and you think that Steve gave you a scoop.
Yeah.
If you got it, it's not a scoop.
Steve's compliment to you.
That guy worked for the CIA.
He killed everybody.
If you have Steve in 20 goddamn telling you that he chose your show, if he even smiled
at me, I'm throwing a fastball at him.
Yes.
Something is up.
Yeah.
If he, if he wants to talk to you, he wants to use you.
Right.
Oh man.
He's not a CIA shell.
Oh, and oh, and really stop and think.
If, if Steve was coming with big stuff this close to the election, this important a time
period for, I guess, overthrowing the government, Alex isn't giving it to you.
Oh, and I mean, it's not relative audience size is huge.
It's a very big difference, a little bit of a difference.
And yeah.
Okay.
I'm Steve.
I got this big information that the election was actually secretly a sting operation.
I can't get permission to talk about it an hour early.
I'm sorry.
They had it on a clock.
It was 4 PM.
Eastern time.
Shit.
I could have done it at three.
I mean, if you're Owen, you always got to be looking for reasons to think that you're
like relevant and doing good work.
Sure.
Every now and again, you got to go yell at Congress and get walked out or something like
that.
You got to get, you got to get a high.
And I guess if, you know, it's believing Steve is what does it for you.
Sometimes it's got to do.
Hey, everybody needs a little juice from here from here from time to pick yourself back
up and get back on track.
Don't don't quit, quit.
This is so embarrassing.
You should quit.
You said fudge you mainstream media because Steve Pachek told you that the entire election
was a sting operation.
It was an elaborate ruse.
Oh boy.
Uh, yeah.
So this is episode 500, Jordan.
Dan?
Yep.
500 episodes, huh?
Quite a few.
That's weird.
Uh huh.
This is how we celebrate.
Yeah.
That's about right.
This, this is how we celebrate.
Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen, we're back in the Infowars war room devastating the fake news media today
with Dr. Steve Pachek.
I want to talk more about that clip.
Uh huh.
I love it for so many reasons.
Yeah.
First of all, you've got that sort of new metal base going behind it, which is great.
It's setting the tone nicely.
Oh, that's a six string bass.
You can tell.
We're devastating the fake news media.
Fake news media is what's being devastated with Steve Pachek while we talk bullshit.
Does Owen work for the CIA?
My eyes just got really wide.
Right?
I've broken some serious news to you, Dan.
You know where the CIA is based?
Where?
St. Louis.
All right.
I don't think it is, but that's where Owen's from.
Anyway, we'll be back for episode five Oh one indeed.
But until then, Jordan, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yeah.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledge, under quite an act.
Go to bet.
Jordan was on Facebook review.
And if you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area of the fights.
Not over.
Yep.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I am Daryl Rundis.
I'm devastating the fake news media with Steve Fagampagenic.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.