N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying we are the bad guys, knowledge
fight.
Dan and Jordan, knowledge fight.
Riddle her, riddle her, riddle her, riddle her, riddle her, riddle her, riddle her.
Andy and Kansas, Andy and, Andy and, stop it, Andy and, Andy and, Andy and, it's time
to pray.
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding us.
Hello Alex, I'm a fifth-time caller, I'm a huge fan, I love your work.
Knowledgefight.com, knowledgefight.com, I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledgefight, I'm Dan, I'm Jordan, we're a couple of dudes
that like to sit around and drink novelty beverages and talk a little bit about Alex
Jones.
Oh indeed we are Dan.
Jordan.
Dan.
I have a quick question for you.
Sure.
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, now spoiler alert to everybody out there listening, we just recorded
our bright spots and realized that it was not recorded.
Had not started the recording yet.
The thing had not recorded.
It's crucially recorded.
I hit the button.
It didn't start recording.
I'm not saying that I didn't.
And it didn't start recording.
I'm not saying that I disbelieve you.
So we're gonna share our bright spots with each other for a second time, so if any of
this sounds insincere.
It's a little bit weird to do it twice in a row.
Yeah.
There were some great rips.
Totally.
You guys missed out on gold.
And now I feel like I can't bring any, oh god.
No, it's tough to bring the same energy now.
I know.
Anyway, my bright spot is world music.
Actually, on the second time that is funnier.
Yeah.
It's not that funny.
I'm just worried, like I told you earlier on the first time, that I'm worried that I'm
becoming my parents, because they used to have a lot of interest in a lot of music from
around the world, particularly this band, Yuthu Yindi, which is a lot of synth and also
tribal sounds from Oceania.
And yeah, it was a running joke throughout our family, but I was on Spotify getting some
work done for the episode.
Just like to put on music in the background while I'm like researching and reading up
on stuff.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I always like to let them see what you got.
They know what I've listened to.
Let's see if you can hit a home run.
I don't trust nobody.
And there was some music from Malawi that ended up coming up, and I really, really enjoyed
it.
And I'm worried this is going to set me off on a path of just like getting into all sorts
of stuff from around the world, which isn't the worst thing ever.
Nothing.
No, no, no.
Orchestra Baobab is great.
You should try them out.
They're fantastic.
Writing this down.
Yeah, there's all kinds of great African music.
I think it's a little bit cliche to reference them because they're probably...
Or maybe not.
Maybe no one has any idea about them except for in the weird circles that I live in.
That might be.
Oh, it's so cliche to reference Orchestra Baobab.
You know the thing everyone knows about.
Well, I mean, on one of our bonus episodes, we did talk about your love of really obscure
music.
So you can't tell who knows what.
I have no idea.
Yeah.
Yeah, so this might be a new little bit of an auditory adventure for me.
I'm excited to embark on it and find out what the rest of the world has to offer in terms
of sounds.
A lot of great music out there.
Awesome.
What about you?
What's your bright spot?
My bright spot, Dan, is Assassin's Creed Valhalla.
It's a fantastic game.
I enjoyed it.
I want to say that I already knew that the first time around.
You already knew that before I had even said it the first time.
Right.
Now it's the second time I'm totally not surprised.
Twice as boring.
Not bored.
Not interested.
Just not surprised.
You even already know the story that my bright spot is, so it's not even an interesting story.
But I also knew that because you texted me about it before the first time we recorded
it.
Exactly.
All of this is terrible for you.
You're bored by it.
Please.
My bright spot is a video game.
Is that what you wanted to hear, Dan?
No, I'm thrilled for you, because it's been a long time coming.
You're very excited about this game, as you should be.
Yeah, it's my favorite series.
And I had originally ordered it.
I found out on the 9th that my copy wouldn't have rised.
I ordered a physical copy, like a boron, and it wouldn't have rised.
Well, you're a man of a certain age.
It wouldn't have rised.
Yes, I have reached that time.
Your console age, your cartridge age, game cartridge age.
I still blow on the DVDs, just in case.
Smart.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's very smart.
Yeah, no, and it wasn't going to show up until the 17th, so on the 9th I was like, fuck this.
It was 7 o'clock.
It was going to be available at 11.
So I scrambled and got the download copy as soon as I possibly could, and all troubles
were averted.
It's perfect.
Yeah, you got to.
I mean, it's going to be another week for that thing to show up.
No, can't do it.
Can't do it.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
People are going to say stuff like, it was good.
Spoilers.
Yeah, and I'm like, no.
I must experience it fresh.
I must be part of the zeitgeist.
So I've been busy, because the show and what have you, and sort of other related projects,
and so I haven't had a lot of time to play it, but I did pre-order a digital copy myself,
and I did play a little bit.
Like a genius.
I played a little bit the other night.
I've not gotten very far into it, and I'm concerned.
Now here's why.
I don't know a lot about Norse and Viking stuff, whereas other iterations of the game
were like sort of mythologies and cultural histories that I know a little bit more about.
Greece is your wheelhouse.
Like right up your alley.
Even the one before it was Egypt, and I know a bit about Egyptian history.
I know very little, and I realized why.
It's those letters.
It's the letters.
The ruins.
No, I just can't handle the weird combination of letters and the names and stuff.
It intimidates me, and I don't know what to do with those Vs and Js and Ys and Gs everywhere.
It scares me.
I don't know what to do.
Ah, come on.
It's fine.
It's hard.
It's Elvish.
You're fine.
It's very difficult for me, and I realize that subconscious bias has kept me away, whereas
I'm excited to embark on a little bit of this, find out some stuff that I can then maybe
read up on the real versions of.
And then I also-
I think what's really funny about that is having played just a little bit further into
the game than you, after the title card, which is four hours, five hours into that-
I've not even come close to that, I'm sure.
You go to England.
What?
Spoilers.
All of your worries-
It's funny to me that you're like, oh, I'm worried about the ruins, and I'm like, dude,
three hours from now you won't even see a ruin.
You're fine.
Wow.
I'm a little disappointed.
No, it's going to be great.
It's awesome.
But the other thing, that actually kind of puts to bed my other worry about the game,
having again played very little of it, I'm worried it's too white, but not in white people
way.
Sure, sure, sure.
I mean snow.
It's very snow.
There's so much goddamn snow around, it's visually monochromatic to a level that if
it were the entire game, I would have a problem with that.
I think it would be a difficulty.
Because of the open world exploration aspect, if you're just running around and everywhere
is snow covered, it becomes a bummer.
No, even with Witcher 3, it wasn't gloomy all the time, it was gloomy most of the time.
And there were sort of variations to the gloom.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's light gloom, dark gloom, you got them.
Well, I'm glad to know that some of these concerns that I have, whether it be letter
or snow-based.
Or weather, yeah.
Letter or weather, it's still a good game.
I trust the developers of those games enough to not make a game that's all snow.
I figured it would be such an elementary kind of thing.
Rogue was, did you ever play Assassin's Creed Rogue?
I did not.
Yeah, that one's mainly snow, so you skipped that one for good.
Skip it.
Yeah, skip it.
That one's out of here.
I don't mind a little snow.
Anyway.
You live in Illinois, you don't mind a little snow.
A little bit.
I live through snowpocalypse.
Yeah, we've been here, wow, come on.
So Jordan, today we're getting back into the present, we're going to be talking about November
7th and 8th, 2020.
I'm Dan, this is 2020.
Oh, god damn it.
We're entering that interesting period where we find out what Alex does during the 79 days
of hell.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
On our last episode, we experienced what happened when Alex left and Steve Pachanik tried to
throw a wrench in the gears.
Today we jump in and I guess we're just pretending none of this shit happened.
I was born in 1783, my father was a Highlander and so am I.
I had to kill him, there can be only one!
I don't know exactly how we're doing it, but I guess we're just pretending that never happened.
And we're here on Saturday, Alex is doing a broadcast on Saturday the 7th and then his
show on Sunday the 8th.
And yeah, we'll see, we'll see what's going on.
Alright.
He's a weird dude.
I like it.
Yeah.
But before we get down to business on that, let's take a moment to say thank you to some
folks who have signed up on our sporting show.
So first, Gn0x Revenge, thank you so much, you're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks Gn0x Revenge.
Thank you.
Next, Burt G, thank you so much, you're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks Burt.
Thank you Burt.
Next, Jared M, thank you so much, you're now policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much Jared.
Thank you!
Next Stu and Ger, Engerur, Engerrr standing.
Stu and Ger, thank you so much You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you so much.
Stu.
Next, Philbin.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Philbin.
Thank you, Philbin.
And then finally, I'd like to give a shout out to a couple of folks who donated on an
elevated level.
We appreciate that very much.
So first of all, HB.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
Fernando F. Thank you so much.
And don't go into the forest.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate.
That's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
Thank you.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right.
We got to go full tilt boogie on this, Watson.
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why are you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thanks so much, HB.
Thanks so much, Fernando.
Thank you so much.
Don't go into the forest.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
All of you.
I would like to, first of all, encourage anybody to have a donor name that is an ominous warning.
Oh, yeah.
I enjoy that.
Which forest?
Exactly.
That's an issue.
If you're out there listening and thinking, hey, I enjoy this show, I'd like to support
these gents.
You can do that by going to our website, knowledgefight.com, clicking the button that says support the
show.
We would appreciate it.
We would love it, but do not go to Schwarzwandt.
That's the Black Forest.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What else could people do?
Well, you know what, Dan?
Some people could absolutely be filled with that generous spirit and want to give or donate
to someone, but then realize that they would have to wait a week to deal with that.
Oh, yeah.
You just can't wait a week because the generous spirit is so strong within you.
Find a way to get that money out now, Dan.
To a local charity.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, yeah.
Nailed it.
Thanks, Dan.
I was worried it was going to end in Yggdrasil or some nonsense.
Not that that's nonsense, but whatever.
You know what I'm saying.
Sure, I get you.
So, Jordan, before we begin, here's an out of context drop from today's show.
I mean, it's like when you watch Dancing with the Stars in the final episode or whatever,
because I'm not a big TV guy, but I do like watching good looking women dance.
And when it's cool to watch the guys and all of it, it's really cool.
It's cool to see celebrities dance.
I mean, it's fun.
Okay.
You can't.
You don't need to justify why you watch a TV show.
This is a problem with being on the far right.
You can't just enjoy what you enjoy.
You have to fight for it.
Yeah.
I got tricked because Sean Spicer was on, and I watched it, and hey, some of the chicks
were hot.
Whatever.
Actually, I don't even like the dancing at all.
The way that they get pirouette, and the throws, and the...
It seems unmanly for me to enjoy watching people dance.
Exactly.
Isn't that what he just said?
More or less.
That's exactly what he just said.
Yeah, it's so sad.
I'm insecure about watching dance.
Enjoy what you enjoy.
Right?
Anyway, here we go.
We're jumping in on the seventh Saturday.
Alex's day off.
Sure.
Yeah.
Back from his trip to Phoenix, where he yelled into an adult-sized bullhorn, and, hey, man,
if Biden's really president, which it looks like he is, Alex has bad news.
Uh-oh.
It is Saturday, November 7th, the year is 2020, and if we accept the false claims of
Joe Biden and his communist Chinese deep state handlers that he is the president with the
fraud we've just witnessed, then you could really see this as a good day to put on the
Republic's tombstone, born July 4th, 1776, died November 7th, 2020.
That's what this is.
Alex has called it Death of America, November 7th, 2020.
As a millionaire, I can tell you that the tragedy of the Biden administration will be
that they raised the marginal income tax on individuals making over $500,000 a year to
above 35%, Dan, and that is the end of the Republic.
What's that I hear?
I think that's the church bells ringing for the funeral of America.
That's it.
It's going to go back up to 44%.
Yeah.
Can you imagine how angry 2 Chainz is going to be then?
So mad.
He's so mad.
In this next clip, we learn, look, this is the problem that I have.
He starts off the show talking about put this date on America's tombstone.
Sure.
Then he says things like this.
And we can talk all day about the failures of Trump and why this was able to happen.
We can talk about what Trump should have done better, and we're going to do that so we don't
make the mistakes next time.
What next time?
What the fuck next time?
According to Alex, there is no next time.
This isn't just a political party that you disagree with that now has control of the
executive branch of the government.
This is the fucking devil taking over.
Without Trump there to stop them, the story is supposed to be that there's nothing to
protect the Patriots from getting rounded up and the entire world being killed off with
a super bio weapon, a false flag ice age, or maybe nukes, depending on what Alex is
feeling that day.
Chicago's gone for sure.
It's downright insulting for Alex to have the nerve to act like a political commentator
right now when his candidate has been projected to lose.
He has this tantrum about the death of the Republic being on November 7th and immediately
gets into the mode you'd expect to see on regular outlets.
They're doing a post mortem on the campaign.
Where were the flaws in the strategy?
Where is there room for improvements?
We can do better next time.
Let's talk midterms.
Normal people get to do that because they don't live in an artificial reality they use
to abuse their audiences, where if their guy loses the election, pedophile demons will
run the street and God's fire filled judgment will be upon us.
Alex doesn't get to wargame about the midterms.
He lost that right when he made the terms of this election supernatural.
Yeah I believe it was if Biden wins, they're going to switch to plan B and kill all of
us immediately.
They're not even going to give us the three years?
That wasn't even conditional on the election.
That was just something Alex said they'd decided to do because Alex is too effective.
He was in a bad mood.
I gotcha.
The Infowar is too strong so they're gonna just kill us off instead of the fun ordered
killing us off that they like to do because the devil loves plans.
I don't even think that's, you know what, there's nothing to be ashamed about in losing
to the devil.
You're supposed to lose to the devil.
The only person who wins against the devil is Jesus, man.
Well, and Johnny.
Oh well, Johnny does too.
He rosined up that bow and played his fiddle hard.
I gotcha.
So we got two.
Yeah.
Alright.
And Johnny was really a Christ metaphor.
And honestly, it was more of a single issue thing.
That wasn't a real, like, he wasn't trying to change the whole world.
Right.
It was really just about fiddle playing.
It was mainly fiddling, yes.
The devil acts with honor in fiddle contests.
Well, if you count, like, the other ripoff songs of The Devil Went Down to Georgia, then
I think some other people might have been the devil too, because there's other versions.
There was at least one juggler who went down to Georgia.
Our friend Marty DeRosa informed me of the song, like, The Devil Went Down to Detroit,
I think.
I believe that's the name of it.
It's like a rap version.
Sure.
And these guys have, like, a DJ contest with the devil.
I think they win.
Okay.
I don't know.
Look, a lot of people may have fictitiously beat the devil.
But look.
I'm sort of saying it.
There's no shame in that.
You're not supposed to beat the devil.
Right.
Why are you beating yourself up over this?
I don't know if he's beating himself up by it.
Oh, that's fair.
I want to stress one of the compelling reasons not to respect Alex Jones.
He is an intellectual coward.
He can't stand to be wrong to such a ridiculous extent that he set up this election as a battle
between good and evil, which evil could not possibly win.
And even if they did, good secretly actually won because evil cheated in a way that's never
going to be proven.
Now that the supposedly evil side has won, Alex won't even stick to his own parameters
and act like the literal devil just beat his hero.
Alex doesn't even have the integrity to present for a minute that any of the stuff he was
screaming about and fake crying about on air means anything.
Because it's time to move on and learn the lessons of the last election and apply them
to whatever white supremacist he supports next time because they insist they're just
a nationalist.
He's a child.
This more than many other moments is a very clear and unmistakable instance of retreat.
Get the fuck out of here with that learning lessons for next time shit.
You don't get to do that.
Nope.
Other people get to do that.
I resent that.
Honestly, there are very few situations where I don't think now that many of these people
are private citizens, we should spit on them every single time they go outside.
Like there's no way Alex should not be spit on regularly.
There's no way that like fucking, if Trump walks down fucking a street in Manhattan,
he should be spit on by thousands of people on a constant daily basis.
Yeah.
I think that you could make an argument that spitting is a form of assault and maybe I'm
not into that.
Fair.
Yelling is better.
I'll go with you as far as yelling.
You'll go with me as far as yelling.
Tiny bullhorning.
All right.
Okay.
Tiny bullhorning.
Anytime Alex leaves his house, people, a crew of-
He should be surrounded with tiny bullhorners.
I think they're, I think you're right.
Yes.
The spitting on people I think is a little bit gross.
Well, now it's definitely attempted murder.
Certainly in an age of COVID.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's fair.
You know, you don't want to sort of express support for that kind of behavior.
Right.
Right, right, right.
Aim away from him.
Yeah.
Yelling with a tiny bullhorn through your mask.
I like it.
That's perfectly-
That's safe.
Yeah.
I think that's-
I think that's good.
That's the middle ground.
What I'm saying is these people should be hounded to the ends of the earth.
Yeah.
Bark at people through bullhorns.
I like it.
So Alex has a concern that a lot of his, you know, everyone's getting censored.
Everyone's getting kicked off.
All the patriots are being taken off all social media platforms.
Sure.
And you see the mass censorship now, as we predicted, almost total censorship.
No media that I saw carrying Giuliani's press conference.
Thank God there's right side broadcasting.
Thank God there's info wars picking it back up.
Thank God you're out there amplifying it.
But this is a serious war.
So yeah, man, everyone's getting taken down, except for people like info wars and right
side broadcasting that'll stand up and cover Rudy Giuliani's wonderful press conference.
Somebody's gotta-
I would suspect that most media outlets, if they didn't, they didn't cover Rudy Giuliani's
press conference out of respect for him, since that shit was super embarrassing.
Also, it wasn't censored.
People were making fun of it all over the place.
Yeah.
This was, of course, the Four Seasons press conference.
As best as anyone can tell, someone in the campaign may have thought that they booked
the Four Seasons hotel conference room for the presser, but it actually set up an event
in front of a small landscaping company called Four Seasons Total Landscaping.
I have no idea what actually happened here, if they intended it to be there or if someone
screwed up, but it was pretty hilarious.
Giuliani gave a rambling nonsense speech right at the moment when the networks called the
race for Biden.
Ooh.
It was a total mess.
Oh, brutal.
At the event, one of Giuliani's guests was an alleged poll watcher named Darryl Brooks,
who turned out to also have been, quote, incarcerated in the 1990s on charges of sexual assault,
lewdness, and endangering the welfare of a minor by exposing himself to two girls ages
seven and 11.
Ah, it's a false flag Democrat, if I ever heard one.
Well, according to an article in The Cut, quote, Brooks denied the charges and said
his arrest was a police setup.
Oh.
So-
There we go.
Claims of false flag-
So it's a double false flag.
Perhaps.
That's what led into becoming the false flag.
That's what happened.
I don't know.
Ah, must be.
Anyway, because this guy is somebody who's identifiable, it makes things a little bit
more confusing for the claims that were being made at this press conference.
Apparently, it was being alleged that Brooks was a poll watcher in Philadelphia and not
being allowed in to check the rolls and everything.
But he lives in New Jersey, and it's not like he's a low profile New Jersey resident.
An article in Politico quoted Reed Giscoria, the mayor of Trenton, New Jersey, as describing
Brooks as, quote, New Jersey's perennial candidate, because Brooks had run from many different
offices in New Jersey, including the Senate and House.
Wow.
The state of Pennsylvania requires poll watchers to be registered voters in the counties they
wish to poll watch, so he couldn't have actually been in a position to actually make the claims
that he was making.
Right, right, right, right.
This whole thing was a disaster for Giuliani, from the strange location to the almost comically
bad timing to the poll watcher alleged who he had as a witness who couldn't possibly
be a poll watcher but is actually a convicted child abuser.
If anything, I would expect Alex to want less coverage of this.
Everything is bad.
Every element of that press conference was bad.
Yeah, I mean, but that's a perfect example of how we are held hostage by their unreality.
That should be a criminal offense.
All the stuff that happened at that presser, I know they're not illegal, but if you do
that, you should be like, you can't be near other people.
Tiny bullhorns.
You're going to get someone hurt.
We need crews of people with tiny bullhorns on the ready.
That's what Arkham Asylum is for.
People who accidentally scheduled press conferences in front of the Four Seasons fucking...
Flamescaping.
Yeah, exactly.
That's Arkham.
It's not a crime.
It's something that people need to be kept there.
Imagine.
You got the Joker.
You got Killer Croc.
You got Rudy Giuliani.
Why are you here?
I set up a weird press conference.
They would all be like, yeah, no, you're the only one we're not letting escape.
You're too gone for us.
Whenever the Riddler comes and lets everyone out, he leaves Rudy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
At least we get the place we're going to heist right, okay?
Batman doesn't beat us there because we got to the wrong place, okay?
They're like, oh, no, no, no, Rudy, you got to stay here to give a message to the Bat
for us.
Give a press conference.
Outside of Arkham Asylum.
Yeah.
Ugh.
God.
What an asshole.
Yep.
Jesus.
So Alex gets to talking about the China.
He has this interesting idea that isn't based in really anything, but I got really lost
in thought after listening to this clip because I think it's really a really good example
of why it's really frustrating to take things that Alex says at all seriously.
So instead of making China a capitalist country at the end of World War II, criminal elements
of the Rockefeller Combine, Dave Rockefeller wrote a book about this and wrote two articles
in the New York Times, and I always go back to this because this is key, this is the real
world, and sent George Herbert Walker Bush in there with James Baker and the rest of
them to make a deal with the communist Chinese after they'd spent 25 years enslaving and
killing 80 million other people and getting them to behave and after they'd follow every
directive of one child policies and horrible things that the Rockefellers told them to
do.
They said, yeah, kill about 80 million of your people and one child policy and we'll
make you the global superpower of economics, but you're not allowed to have a big military.
But of course, wink, wink, they're globalists.
They were building a big military the whole time.
That's why you saw the pivot under Obama was because China wasn't following its agreement
to not be expansionist.
They were given all the rare earth minerals and all the economic power and they were allowed
to economically expand, but America would economically close, but then would have military
dominance still.
That's how you divide power.
That's the rollerball allegory.
That's really how globalism works.
The original movie with James con 1972 or whatever it is is dead on.
Yeah, of course.
It's always, it's always a fucking movie and that's why like it's so frustrating to listen
to him.
Like it starts with, you know, that clip there, it starts with him saying something really
absurd like that a decision was made by people like the Rockefellers to have China not be
capitalist at the end of world war II and that kind of thing gets me kind of interested.
Well, at least it would have earlier on doing this show.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, that's, that's a laughable and nonsensical claim.
You know that even without doing any research, like what does it even mean?
Yeah, yeah.
I would ask Alex to explain what mechanisms were used by the Rockefellers to keep China
from being a capitalist country.
If I were to do this because of doing this show, I know that Alex would just point to
John Birch society talking points about how the U S didn't do enough to help Shanghai
Shek in the Chinese civil war, which is the claim that's then exaggerated into the Rockefellers
installed Mao.
Sure.
Still, I like this absurd claim.
It's stupid, but probably sounds smart to his audience and I can kind of appreciate
that.
That's kind of the kind of the sort of thing that I dig my, uh, my, my teeth into.
Sure, sure, sure.
He claims that David Rockefeller wrote a book and two articles in the times about this whole
China stuff.
And that's just not true.
The op-eds Rockefeller wrote don't look great with the hindsight of history on our side,
but they're nothing like Alex is claiming them to be.
He also wrote a book called memoirs, which is an autobiography, but if that admission
is in there, it'd be really simple for Alex to produce it, which weirdly he never does.
Then everything falls apart with the rambling about the imaginary deal where China gets
to have the economy and U S gets to have the military, which incidentally is something
similar to like, uh, something Alex might be cribbing from a piece of dystopian sci-fi
from the time when he was a child.
Yep.
Seems to be a pattern.
Yeah.
It does seem like that is often the case.
The original movie roller.
What's your favorite X file, Dan?
Logan.
Yep.
The original movie roller ball was based on a short story called roller ball murder by
William Neil Harrison published in Esquire in September, 1973.
It's a little bit different than what the movie ended up being.
Uh, as it's far more a statement about the rising brutality and public's taste in entertainment.
There are also similarities to the movie version though.
Like it's a kind of clunky and not, not super great short story itself.
There's a lot of mention of various women's shapeliness, but I mean, James con was great
in the movie.
Sure.
Yeah.
I read it.
I read something that James Cod was talking about.
Like, uh, he's like, man, love doing those roller ball scenes, but then I had to go at
act.
All right.
Ah, that was about as a process for thief too.
I think loved those roller ball scenes.
In the short story.
It's not so much like different countries do different things.
It's that within the United States, different corporations run six different concerns of
life, energy, transport, food, housing, services, and luxury.
Each is a super powerful corporation and the main character, Jonathan E plays for the roller
ball team run by energy company based in Houston.
The actual story is about a guy who's the best roller ball player in the world, struggling
with his sense of self, finding himself unsatisfied while living a life filled with money, power,
sex, and celebrity.
The brutality of the sport has been increasing with new rules being added to satisfy the
public's lust for violence.
Gradually things get more violent with rules added to penalize players who aren't trying
hard enough by having their helmets confiscated.
This all culminates in the all-star game at the end of the season, where there's a new
rule that's added where there's no time limit for the game, essentially making a gladiatorial
contest where pretty much everyone is guaranteed to die.
Jonathan wants something more out of his life, but he doesn't know what, but as the all-star
game gets closer, his only request is that he'd be able to see his estranged wife again.
She comes to him and they fuck for a few days and then they remember their shared love that
they had.
Jonathan had convinced himself that in the past she'd been taken from him by the evil
corporation, but he realizes that wasn't the case.
Quote, it would be nice, I think, once to imagine that she was taken away from me by
some malevolent force in this awful age, but I know the truth of that.
She went away simply because I wasn't enough back then, because those were the days when
I yearnedbefore I yearned for anything, when I was beginning to live to play the game.
But no matter.
For a few days she sits on my bed and I touch her skin like a blind man.
It's implied that they both realize they can't go back to their younger lives even if there
is love between them, and Jonathan knows that he has to play the all-star game even if it
means almost certain death.
The story concludes, quote, before the game begins I stand with my team as a corporation
him plays.
I'm brute speed today, I tell myself, trying to rev myself up, yet a dream in my thoughts
I'm a bit unconvinced.
A chorus of voices joins the band now as the music swells.
The game, the game, all glory to it, the music rings, and I can feel my lips move with the
words singing.
William Harrison fleshed out the story into a screenplay that no longer really resembles
the point of this original work, there's some parts of it that are still carried over, and
it actually directly contradicts it at certain points.
The director of the movie has explained why they made the movie, telling the Guardian,
quote, I thought that violence for the entertainment of the masses was an obscene idea.
This is what I saw coming, and that's why I made the film.
The original and the movie are both commentaries on the idea of brutality as entertainment,
but in order to make the movie out of a ten page story, they needed to add a whole plot
about the corporations fearing that Jonathan was becoming too much of an individual in
the corporate world built on conformity.
Sure, Logan's run just came out recently.
The game and the people's reaction to it, as well as the violence depicted in the movie
itself and the people's reaction to that, were the point of the movie rollerball.
If it has any artistic merit, it's that attempt for a statement.
The dystopian sci-fi future backdrop, they're absolutely unnotable, and they only really
exist as a way of justifying why the game exists.
Yeah, yeah.
Alex doesn't know how to wrestle with or analyze works of art.
He refuses to understand subtext or deeper meaning, so it honestly makes perfect sense
that he'd think that all this dystopian fiction from his youth is secretly about the communist
conspiracy that no one will admit is right in front of their face.
Here's an example.
There is a phenomenon you could point to, which is that a lot of movies, particularly
dystopian action movies, seem to exist in a world ruled by rigid authoritarians who
have molded society into a state of uniformity.
You could point this out and provide a number of examples, and that's fair.
Alex might see this phenomenon and argue that this is because the globalists are using predictive
programming to tell the world about what they're going to do to them.
There's a cosmic contract law clause that states that these evildoers can't carry out
their evil deeds unless we all consent to them, so they put this stuff in movies to
get us to accept it.
That is the theory for why there's such a consistent feature like this in this genre.
I would argue that it's because the setting of a rigid, uniform world is one where it's
incredibly easy to differentiate a hero character from the rest of the world.
Even an anti-hero or a flawed person can easily be cheered for when they're the only person
who has any modicum of individuality in a sea full of facelessness.
Putting your character and their story into that setting is kind of a genre-based shortcut
for plots where the tension is about individualism versus conformity.
Engaging with text and art with even just a baseline of critical ability allows you
to see authorial intent and understand the more complicated things that are being said
by artistic works, and it brings a richness to your life.
It's a critically important exercise now more than ever, and honestly, it's one of the
things that I find most fascinating about Alex.
I do believe that most of the stuff he says is embellishment or lies or things he doesn't
actually believe or kind of believes, that his inability to grasp the point of literature
in movies is something so consistent in his career that I find it difficult to accept
that it's not a genuine feature of his brain.
So yeah, it's annoying to do this show because I end up thinking about Rollerball.
Yeah, that'll happen.
And thinking about like, huh, there was an attempted statement that they were making
there and the corporations and shit in the movie and all that is really just to make
it so you're watching this movie and you're like, oh yeah, that's why that exists.
That's why that brutal game exists that would never exist in our world.
The commentary is about people's taste for sport and entertainment becoming more and
more violent and the logical extension of that is a game where everyone's killing each
other.
Everyone's like, ah, that itself could not exist in our reality.
So the commentary couldn't be made by plugging it into the present day because there'd be
too many things like, hey, why isn't everyone getting sued for this?
This would never fly.
So you plug it into this dystopian authoritarian world in the future and then you're like,
oh yeah, that makes sense.
And it makes it so much easier to cheer on your hero, Jonathan M. Even if he's not a
great person.
I wonder what it would have been like if Alex, instead of being into hard sci-fi and watching
Rollerball at that age, he would instead watch like, they shoot horses, don't they?
Watching everybody in that fucking exploitative, destructive dance contest, realizing that
the real dystopia is where we live now.
I just, I, I, I just, I don't know.
I do wish that he was better at reading.
Yeah, that would be nice.
I wish a lot of people were better.
I wish almost everyone was better at reading.
It's a, it's a difficult skill.
It is, it seems like it should be easy considering we talk to each other, but then you think
about it and you realize most people don't even talk to each other, honestly.
It's really hard to understand what people are saying because their brains don't speak
the words that their brains think.
Yeah.
It's very strange.
One of the more interesting things that...
I feel like an alien right now.
These human beings, they act so strange.
So weird.
Yeah.
One of the more interesting things I found while I was looking at, I was reading about
Rollerball was that the writer, William Harrison, he was like, I want more violence in this
movie.
Of course.
He was like, he wants the movie to be super violent.
He wants to make the point that the violence is supposed to be repulsive.
So brutal that when you watch it, you go, no.
You're disgusted by it.
And then when people watched Rollerball, they were like, man, Rollerball is cool.
Yeah.
And then the director of it was talking about how like most of the, most of the European
audiences that we've talked to understand that it's supposed to be that this is disgusting.
And most American audiences are like, we should start a Rollerball league.
Frankly, what's CTE?
What's the difference between CTE and Rollerball?
We might as well get Rollerball while we're at it.
Anyways, Vince McMahon, get the XFL the fuck out of here.
Get the RFL right in here, man.
That's what I'm talking about.
So anyway, that sort of off sidetrack about the Rollerball off to the way, we get more
complaints about China.
That we live under this and it's all been one-sided.
It's not about Kumbaya and one world living together and all this great stuff.
Communist China was allowed to buy up our debt, buy up Hollywood, buy up our whole infrastructure.
So I've been thinking about this for a while, and I think that this is one of the newer
formulations of like the Jews run all the banks, you know, that kind of bigoted conspiracy
theory.
I think that the Chinese own all our debt is a sort of a new one of those.
It's one that a lot of people, if they don't do any research, kind of passively accept
because it sounds like something they've heard someone say before.
Sure, sure, sure.
And it's like, oh yeah, why wouldn't they?
They bought up all our debt is such an intimidating thing where you're like, why would you buy
debt?
I'll believe you.
Yeah.
But it's just complete bullshit.
According to Market Watch, the US government itself owns 27% of the US debt, with US investors
owning a further 32.5%.
The Federal Reserve owns 11.2%, which is just a slightly more complicated form of the government
owning it.
So all that added up is 70.9% of the US national debt that's owned essentially by US interests.
Sure.
Compared to that, the amount owned by China is not that much.
As of 2018, they held about 5.6% of our national debt in the form of like treasury bonds.
But Japan also had 4.9%.
And I don't hear Alex yelling about the dreaded Japanese threat.
Oh, well, they make our Sony stuff.
These countries have bought these bonds because generally speaking, they're considered good
investments, since most world currency is tied to the dollar.
Also in 2020, Japan overtook China as the largest foreign investor in our debt.
So the dynamic that Alex is describing is even more wrong.
Ah, but what you're getting wrong there is China owns 99% of Japan's debt.
So they secretly own all of the other 4.4%.
Yeah.
So people, they want to spread this fear, and what it's based on is the idea that China
owns our debt.
And what they can do is they can call in that debt, like you repay your debt whenever they
want.
Like a landlord who's giving you a slide.
Exactly.
And this is just another anti-communist conspiracy talking point that's based on more or less
nothing.
Alex wants to create that image because it means that China rules us.
They can say the word and destroy our economy at any second.
They don't own enough of our debt to really matter that much in that term, and also investing
in our debt doesn't work like that.
Our national debt is a super complicated thing, and it isn't the same as your personal debt
that you might have if you're like laid on a gas bill.
There are too many real world factors to make it sensible to discuss as like a one factor
thing, like bigger number debt equals worse, or whatever.
But that's basically what Alex is doing, and then adding on a layer of conspiracy China-baiting
for fun.
China didn't buy up all our debt, they don't own Hollywood, and they didn't buy all our
infrastructure.
Yeah.
These are all just talking points Alex repeats over and over again until his audience accepts
them as being fact, when it's all just kind of warmed over birch or nonsense.
Yeah, it's very interesting to me that like one of the ways that the conservative propagandists
get normal people to believe they're bullshit is because they try and make it that micro
level of like, you have debt.
If someone calls in that debt, that'll fuck up your day.
The same thing is true for the United States, but what they don't realize is that when you
get to the United States, money's imaginary.
If they called in our debt, what happens?
We print more, and then inflation goes up, and their money's worth less.
You know, like it's stupid.
There is a serious incentive for them not to do this based on their own economy.
Yeah, it's all imaginary.
You can print more money, and that's fine.
You're just, inflation goes up, and all other kinds of bullshit happens.
There's a hundred different after effects of that that, you know, there's, yeah.
It's all magic.
But even that being understood, what Alex is saying is just dumb.
Totally.
But it sounds compelling in the same way that, you know.
You have debt, and if somebody calls it in, it'll fuck your day up.
It's very simple to like get across.
So I want to ask you a question here, Jordan.
I think that you've done, you know, we've been at this for a while.
You understand Alex pretty well.
In this next clip, Alex discusses what his greatest sadness is.
Do you think that you could guess what his greatest sadness is?
The just unending swath of dead dogs in his wake.
I would assume that that guilt would weigh heavily upon him.
I don't know if he feels that bad about it.
Just an astonishing number.
Most of the time when he talks about it, it seems like those dogs had it coming.
It's almost wistful, yeah.
According to him.
Yeah.
No, you're incorrect.
OK.
Here's my greatest sadness.
The average person that's a leftist buys into the system, they go and they get one degree
and they can't get a job.
They get two degrees.
They can't get a job.
They get three degrees.
Or they get some little government or bureaucracy job and they tell them, once we overthrow
America and create a socialist utopia, you're all going to be in charge and have mansions.
And they believe this.
They're never going to be brought into the power structure.
They're absolute jokes and they're vicious and they're hateful.
So Alex's greatest sadness is over-educated liberals and leftists who can't find jobs.
Yeah.
So the socialist utopia is a capitalist utopia where we switch who lives in mansions.
Is that what he thinks is going on?
Yeah, probably.
He would assume so, right?
He doesn't understand socialism at all.
In this next clip, Alex has recognized that there are, you know, some people showing up,
maybe it's state capitals and being like, false flaggers.
Yeah.
No, I mean, they're, they're, they're, they're, they're, they're the real deal.
Patriots.
Oh, I wouldn't admit that right now.
They're good Patriots.
Just going down there to say, Hey, what's going on?
I wouldn't admit that preemptively votes, you know, and stuff.
Sure.
And because of this, there's also a lot of people who are showing up at the white house
and Alex thinks that, you know, there's a few people now, but soon there'll be millions.
It's so obvious by the weekend, they'll announce by the winter, they're going to pick a Saturday.
So people aren't at work.
And so they can all use social media to say, let's put a million people around the white
house.
It won't be a million today.
It'll be a hundred thousand today today.
Won't be a million today, it'll be a hundred thousand.
But by the time Trump isn't leaving in a week or two, there'll be a million, 2 million,
and they will tear those barricades up and storm the white house.
That's been the plan.
The Democrats said that's their plan and Hey, the globalists have never gotten in trouble
for anything they've done.
So why wouldn't they do that?
Because they're never held accountable.
I mean, if Trump like directly is like, I don't respect the results of an election,
you know, and it's like, I'm not leaving.
I wouldn't be surprised if tons of people show up.
I don't know.
I don't know how to quantify numbers, but I w I mean, a million people showing up outside
the white house doesn't seem impossible to me.
I think that's a pretty, you know, that, that might happen if a leader refuses to step down.
I could see it.
At a certain point, I think we can, we could go real high.
We could go real high then.
Not good.
Definitely not good.
There were tense standoffs outside the white house a couple months ago over the George
Floyd protests and what have you.
I don't, I don't know if people would storm the white house, but people would be shaking
fences.
You think we're going to get a moat around the white house soon?
I don't know.
You want to go with a moat?
I don't, I don't know.
I don't know.
You don't know.
I think, I think a moat's coming and I think it's, I'm fine with that.
Let them have the house.
Let them live there.
Lock them in there.
Give them a moat.
Put alligators on there.
I was just thinking about if they do a moat, I have the solution.
Tons of jello.
A bunch of jello powder in there.
Oh man.
Make a jello moat.
That's true.
That is true.
The moat system may be outdated in terms of defensive effectiveness.
Yeah, back in medieval times, they didn't have jello.
You didn't have jello.
So anyway, there's a situation here where Alex is, I just really can't stand this waffly
back and forth nonsense of the fucking devil's coming.
Oh, hey, let's learn lessons for next time.
Hey, come on.
Or this, apparently, you know, hey, maybe, maybe, maybe everything will be all right.
I'm going to air some clips and then I'm gonna get refocused and come back, go through the
election fraud, go through other key points of who's behind the machines, how there is
a very narrow way out of this.
A very narrow way out of this.
And then I'm going to explain that there is another path.
And that path actually is more destructive and very horrible, but will actually hasten
the destruction of the global order and the destruction of the new world order.
And they have stepped into it.
Now, I have no desire to go down this path, but I will go down it if they take us there.
And don't worry, you're going to go down that path, too, because there's no getting out
of this now.
Everyone is going to see world government manifest, you're going to see everything I've
told you come true, everything, everything.
So that's violence.
That's street violence.
That's murder of your neighbors and war and stuff.
That's the other path.
But there's a narrow path, which is Trump seizing power, basically.
You can kind of get the sense that, like, okay, now the conversation has become, Trump
has got to become king or else, like, we're all fucking shooting.
And that's not encouraging, I would say.
For sort of a baseline, so you're like, yeah, this is just where we're at, I don't know
if I enjoyed that.
No, I mean, right now I enjoyed the election results coming in and Biden winning outright.
That's good stuff.
But the amount of overconfidence and gloating that's going on before Trump has entirely
left the White House is a little nerve wracking for me.
I don't like it when people who I've seen gloat before and have all of our lives destroyed
because of it gloat again.
I don't like it.
I don't like seeing it.
Yeah, and I think because it's kind of untested territory, we really don't know how much of
the stuff that goes on between an election and an inauguration is norms.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's going to, we're going to turn out to find, it's going to be a lot, it's going to
be a lot of norms.
It very well may be.
It's going to be a lot of norms that are no longer on the, on Cheers.
So in this next clip, Alex has very few friends left in the media, or I mean, not friends,
just people who even just doesn't hate now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
One of them, Lou Dobbs.
Sure.
He likes Lou Dobbs.
All right.
First I want to play a very important clip.
Sidney Powell with Lou Dobbs discusses hammer and scope card.
And this is very, very important.
It's a good place to start.
So we're going to play this clip and we'll be right back.
So the long and short of this is that there's a conspiracy going around that there's a super
secret overpowered computer called hammer that can run a program called scorecard, which
was used to manipulate and change the results of this election.
This desperate and absurd conspiracy is being sold by people like guests on Steve Bannon's
show, Mike Flynn's attorney, Sidney Powell, and Lou Dobbs.
These are high profile people in right-wing spheres.
This just isn't like some fringe, completely online nonsense.
So I was wondering, where did this come from?
Luckily, I did not have to look too far.
Will Sommer over at the Daily Beast had already put together a great piece about how all the
claims about this supercomputer and the program come from a single source.
It's someone who I have a special bond with.
This all comes from Dennis Montgomery.
God damn it.
Yup.
God fucking damn it.
I was amazed.
How has Dennis Montgomery found a way to claw back into reality?
I was amazed to see his name come up again.
Motherfucker.
It would take far too long to get into this right now, but back in March 2017, on the
25th episode of our podcast, we dedicated two and a half hours to Dennis Montgomery
and his various frauds.
So if anyone's interested in why you don't need to take anything that traces back to
him seriously, go ahead and check that episode out.
My god.
Also, Will's article on it is a really good breakdown too.
I believe it.
This is how these dicks work.
Supposedly respectable outlets on the right are so desperate for a big overarching explanation
for how they were screwed in the election that they're willing to amplify and give credibility
to claims being made by a career con man whose lawyer is Larry fucking Clayman.
You can't do it.
How is it that even in this world, people don't just like, Oh, it's Larry Clayman.
Get the fuck out of here.
Like Larry Clayman, Larry Clayman's coming for you eventually.
Like it doesn't matter what if you're on the hard right.
It doesn't matter.
Sooner or later, Larry Clayman, Larry Clayman is going to sue you.
Hey, sued Alex.
He sued everyone.
Roger Stone.
Don't listen to him now.
No, you don't even need to worry about the lawsuits.
Just look at him and look at the things he's done.
Look at the, the, the, the track record and be like, yeah, pass.
Yeah.
Don't care.
You could have the biggest scoop in the world and I'm going to take the hit if you're right
this time.
Totally.
I'm going to just bite the bullet and say, I don't trust anything you say.
And if that bites me in the ass, I still did the right thing.
The idea that you might like see a James O'Keefe video pop up and just be like, well, maybe
he got it right this time.
No, no, no.
That's bad.
That's bad thinking.
Yep.
So this next clip, Alex, like I said, he's, he's, he's kind of interested in these ideas
about millions of people showing up at the white house, but also he doesn't like that
the media is downplaying the number of people that are coming to Owen Schroyer's rally in
Austin.
He's very preoccupied and spends a lot of time talking about crowd sizes in Austin.
Oh, and get out of studio for a while.
Notice that there are thousands of people at rallies at all 50 capitals around the United
States.
I was down there just a few hours ago at the Texas Capitol DPS estimated there were about
2000 people.
Thousands more are showing up right in front of the South side of the Texas Capitol.
And again, I sent some photos to you guys.
It's actually on Savannah Hernandez's Twitter from a building above that actually shows
the big giant crowd.
I'll just pull it up on my phone, but the local news you will notice is not showing
it because the local news does not want you to know what is unfolding and what is happening.
And that's, that's how they operate.
Yeah.
In fact, let's not even show it.
I want to show the above shots because I don't want to just look at my big fat ugly head
up there and, you know, talk about how there's thousands of people.
I'm going to, I want to show the overhead shot.
I'm gonna go to rebroadcast.
I'll find it.
It's not the crew.
I just have to have this.
I just have to have it.
Or I can't do the show.
Okay.
And then I'm going to read to you the breakdown from the president, a new statement that has
come out and then I'm going to go through everything else that is here.
But right now let's go ahead and play Ali Alexander at the Capitol.
And then I want to show the project Veritas.
There it is.
Look at that.
And I'm not throwing a fit.
I just want people to see that I need you to see this picture.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I'm not throwing a fit.
Yeah.
He doesn't actually go to rebroadcast though.
I mean, whoever he is, whatever intern he's hired was able to pull that up before the
pot bubbled over.
Before it got too bad.
Yeah.
All right.
But he does spend a lot more time than this even on just like the crowd size pictures
and it's like, boy, this is exactly the same as after the 2016 election.
Sure is.
This is just like a sort of fun house mirror version of, oh, we did the election.
We talked about fraud.
We talked about complaining about different claims about crowd sizes.
It's just that this guy lost this time.
It's almost exactly the same.
Yep.
Just beat for beat, just with a different angle.
I just, I just can't believe that they're going to accept this.
Like it's not going to, every other year during an election season, Alex is going to scream
about how it's the devil.
And then every other year he's going to be like, well, I know we lost, but we got a path
through this and it's never going to stop.
They will always be convinced that it's the devil and they will always be convinced that
it's fine that the devil won this time.
Well, if it's so inferior.
Yeah.
If things can keep going, it does seem like that would be just how things will go.
That's just how it operates.
Yeah.
And then just come up with fun, interesting stuff to say about whatever headlines he didn't
read the articles of and keep going.
How disappointing would, how disappointed do you think God is that they're like, we
only fight against the devil in an election year.
Come on, man.
And we fight against the devil's assistant during the midterms.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
The devil takes the midterms off.
You got to delegate responsibility sooner or later.
Otherwise you burn yourself out.
And if you're the devil, you're at high risk of burning.
So Alex is preoccupied with these crowd pictures and I could not find myself giving a shit.
And I ended up turning off this episode, this Saturday episode, because it was so boring.
It is so much just like over and over again, rambling, repetitious, the election was stolen,
but it also was really uninspired.
Like here's a little clip that just sort of sums up kind of how I feel it went.
They just stole this bigger than Dallas right out in the open.
You know, you think about stealing something.
You're kind of like a cat burglar going in to get the jewels.
There was no cat burglar in going on here, ladies and gentlemen.
This was done out in the open.
There's a feeling of resignation almost to the fact that like, ah, they stole it.
We've proven it.
What are you going to do?
And I don't understand that.
No, no, no.
I mean, I understand it if you don't actually believe any of it, then it makes perfect sense.
I understand that, but that's a weird space to perform in.
Especially if you've made your last entire year and a half, a referendum on whether or
not the tree of Liberty does need to be watered with the blood of tyrants from time to time.
And apparently, I guess not this year.
It's been abundantly clear what his position on that is.
You would think that you don't go back from that.
Yeah.
So we have this situation where we're, you know, in this period after the election where
it's the 79 days of hell and Biden is the president elect and Alex, you know, Trump
hasn't conceded and Alex doesn't know what he's, you know, I, I find it to be like one
of the most important points for us to be like really tracking what are the moves, what
are the things he does.
And I found this Saturday to be just almost unlistenable.
It's just banging the gong over and over again.
Election was stolen.
Treading water.
But yeah, but treading water, boring.
Yeah.
Um, and so I needed to jump into Sunday and like get a sense of something and I really
feel like Alex didn't do it for me at the beginning of the show.
I can tell you as bad as it is, we're going to come through this stronger on the other
side no matter what happens to Trump.
We're not.
The devil is killing us all.
I'd wish that we could bypass what's coming.
I wish we could have gone around this, which you could have had an easy landing and kept
Trump and there's still 20% chance of doing that.
There's about a hundred percent chance of doing that if Trump takes dramatic action.
So there's a 20% chance of him winning, I guess, I guess the election and then a hundred
percent chance of everything going cool if Trump sees his power, right?
That would be a hundred percent chance.
I don't know.
2020, I'd give it a 50 50 shot.
Well, no, no, no.
Cause with the hundred percent chances of Alex getting what he wants and he was still
wouldn't, but he would get the, what he wants in the form of Trump staying in power and
Trump, not Biden, not being in office where Trump to unilaterally declare himself a dictator.
That'd be great.
Yeah.
I'd be stoked about that.
So there's only 79 more days of hell.
So when I do these shows, it requires a lot of thinking, a lot of preparation, a lot of,
you know, sitting around and thinking like, what is he trying to say here?
You know, there's a lot of that.
And so I'm accustomed to stretches of, of intense mental exertion.
Sure.
Alex, he is too.
I brainstormed so hard this morning from about 6 AM to about 12 noon when I got to the office
that I got completely exhausted about an hour and a half ago and had to go take a nap.
Okay.
All right.
Thinking is hard.
That's fair.
I love shit.
I told everybody to kill everybody, but now I think that's a bad idea.
So what's my next move?
Power nap, power nap, seize power nap.
All right.
I know what to talk about today.
You know, I think this is a new thread that I hope will go on throughout the podcast as
Alex reverting to dream space for his, to find the answers.
Alex becoming sort of like the shaman of the right wing extremist world.
He's going to hire a Daniel who's going to interpret his dreams for him and then we've
got this all covered.
That's Rob Dew.
That's why he's still around.
Yeah, absolutely.
Owen's not going to do shit, but yeah.
So Alex gives a little, tells a little story about his family's breakfast time this morning
that I found kind of disturbing.
All right.
Well, this morning I talked to my oldest daughter and my wife at breakfast while my three year
old daughter played in toy cars and blocks on the floor and I prepared them both for
what was happening.
And both my wife and my oldest daughter finished my sentences before I could even complete
them and they looked at me and they said, we know you're right.
We're ready and we understand.
And it was a very good feeling, a feeling of strength because they weren't repeating
things that have been drilled into their head.
I'd never really put these things on them, but they'd been listening and they'd been
checking the truth.
My oldest daughter, Charlotte looked to me and she said, dad, you're almost always right.
A little tear came out her eye.
And that was meant so much to me when I gave him this speech at the breakfast table at
8 AM this morning and I laid out the future.
I told him we tried to stop what was coming.
I told him what was coming next and they understood.
You just imagine like sitting around with like some granola, Alex stands up and he's
like, at this breakfast I must tell you the future.
This is a dinner conversation for sure.
Totally.
This is a family meeting.
These kids are too young for coffee.
You can't handle Alex Jones predicting the future without a little caffeine in you.
Right?
Yeah.
That's not fair.
You can let him get through the morning.
I'm not going to deal with the apocalypse in the morning.
Absolutely not.
I don't know why, but that mental image to me is like in the real world, disturbing.
Oh, terrifying.
In a movie, hilarious.
It's so funny.
So funny.
Man.
And the worst part is, here's the worst part for me.
The kids don't know something that's fundamentally true that would change everything about their
outlook on life.
Their dad is Alex Jones?
No, they're going to be fine.
They're going to continue to be rich.
They're going to continue to be taken care of.
They're going to continue doing everything with no changes at all.
Well.
None.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess I would say they're going to be fine in many material ways.
Well.
They're not going to be fine emotionally.
Without your dad.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, no, no.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah.
If he just sat him down and been like, listen, I am always lying.
We're going to be fine.
Don't worry.
Why are you crying?
There's no need to cry.
We're rich as shit.
We don't actually care.
The tear in her eye and saying you're almost always right doesn't sound like something
that someone else says.
That sounds like Alex writing dialogue for imaginary characters.
It does seem like that.
Anyway, I would be more upset with him telling this story about preparing his children and
his wife for the coming tribulation or whatever the fuck if he didn't have really good reason
to suspect that there is corruption in the election.
And one of the pieces of evidence he brings to the table is, uh, I mean, fuck, I'm, I'm
convinced.
You know, Google has a big article that's up on info wars.com, Google analytics.
And they had a record search in the days before the election and the days after the election
that no one ever searches.
What is the penalty was one of the searches and what is the consequences and what is the
prison time and what is the jail time?
These are searches no one's ever done that they ever, but now it was by the thousands
per state in Pennsylvania, in Georgia, in Minnesota, in Wisconsin, in Michigan.
The search was for what is the consequences?
What is the penalty?
What is the prison time for election fraud?
Wow.
Cause that's election officials in fraud, not voter fraud.
Who do you think might be searching?
There it is.
Scroll up.
Google trends, searches for election fraud, punishment surge in the key battleground states.
It's not just those mores come out.
That is people checking to see what's going to happen to them.
What a conclusion he's jumped to.
That is a big jump.
So you're saying that people are Googling the crime they're about to commit or have
committed.
What kind of trouble am I in?
What?
Why?
Oh my God.
Yeah.
You don't think it might have something to do with maybe right wing people constantly
hoping retribution will come to their enemies and wishing that there's some sort of punishment
that they can discover that will be worse than death?
Silly friend.
This is a forensic fingerprint that proves that election officials are trying to figure
out what they got to look forward to because they committed election fraud.
Wow.
What a good thinker.
That is really good thinking.
Yeah.
I'm impressed by him constantly.
If that's the result of his brainstorming, he does not need to work for six hours.
You should take a nap though.
You should take a longer nap.
Yeah.
Because you'd probably have the exact same analytical abilities.
Pretty better.
So Alex says something in this next clip that I found really interesting and it's a good
example of like how there's sort of a dark mirror version of real world things that are
oftentimes behind his rhetoric.
When I come back from break, I'm going to explain what they're saying to the president
inside the white house right now and how they're trying to get him to concede.
But let me just say this right now.
If Trump concedes, they're going to blame him for the COVID-19 deaths.
They're going to set up a truth and reconciliation commission and demonize all of his supporters
and they're going to make the lockdown and the shutdown of our economy 10 times worse.
And now Biden's announced that.
So I find this kind of interesting.
I don't know if I disagree too much with Alex's assessment of things that could happen if
Trump concedes and Biden becomes president.
I just think that he's portraying these things in an intentionally false light.
First he says that they'll blame Trump for the COVID-19 deaths.
And to the extent that anyone should be blamed, it probably should be the executive officer
of the country who was in a position to make decisions that he failed to make.
Obviously no one would say that it's all Trump's fault, but the conversation about policy failures
and new information about what was known when and what was ignored would almost certainly
paint Trump in a terrible light.
Especially if he's staked his entire reputation on being a perfect chief executive officer.
Yeah, you could easily see someone like Alex experiencing a harsh, sober look at Trump's
virus response as the globalists blaming him for all the deaths.
So that might actually be a fair assessment just through a twisted mirror.
I mean, you don't get to take credit for the things that the, and then not take blame for
things.
Well, apparently you do.
Oh, okay.
Nevermind.
I forgot about that.
And there will be truth and reconciliation committees to demonize Trump supporters.
This is obviously Alex's way of spinning the inevitable necessity of trying to bring humans
in this country back to a place where we can even communicate with each other.
The fracturing of a shared reality is something that needs to be addressed, and any attempt
to do that is a threat to someone like Alex whose entire business relies on the perpetuation
of that false reality.
Attempts by people who aren't in his fantasy world to humbly reach out and reintegrate
people who got sucked into the Trump cult or Q-shit is obviously going to be painted
as communist indoctrination by Alex and truth and reconciliation committees.
His business cannot afford for him to present it any other way, but the attempts at reaching
out and having like, okay, look, that shit was really bad, but we need to figure out
a way to move forward.
That will be what this is if Trump concedes.
The third thing he says is that there will be even harsher lockdowns.
Now I'm not sure if that's actually the case or how Alex would define any of those terms,
but I do think that if Biden were to get into office, a more adult, reasonable approach
to a public health crisis would be enacted.
It would be easy for Alex to paint that as this harsh crackdown.
All of the things that he's describing, if Trump concedes, are things that are based
on kernels of things that could be real.
It's just preemptively painting them as these evil nefarious plans that the globalists have.
That's how he gives himself the credibility of having like all these good predictions
of the hell that will come upon us.
Sure, but it's not that hard in this case because we already have been told ad nauseum
what a reasonable response would be and we've already not seen it, so then taking a reasonable
response is already baked into their propaganda.
The fact that we didn't take a reasonable response makes us super smart for killing
200,000 people, and if they do take a reasonable response, then it's because they're trying
to hurt our economy.
It's just, yeah, they've already won that messaging.
On this Sunday, I felt a little bit still untethered, like there wasn't much going on.
He's just kind of saying the election was stolen.
Sure.
Hooray.
But then we heard this clip, and man, Owen Schroyer, he had Steve Pacanich on and they
sort of dropped the ball.
He's about to make up for it in a big way.
Let's go ahead and lay it out right now.
Owen Schroyer started tomorrow, he's going to launch a caravan that's going to leave
at 5 p.m. from a location we're going to announce, and it's going to drive you to Houston and
then along the Gulf of Mexico border through Louisiana, Mississippi, into Florida, where
it will turn north into Georgia, and we'll go up through the Carolinas into Virginia,
where I will meet it in DC on Friday.
I want to make a bet on this.
And we're going to call for others to launch caravans around the nation.
I want to bet on this.
I would like to bet on this a million dollars.
In the Midwest, in the South, and in the East Coast, to DC, truckers are already announcing
big strikes they're going to have, take over to DC this next weekend.
So don't worry, President Trump, the cavalry's coming.
Now I'm fucking excited.
Wow.
Yes.
Now we are in business.
Countdown to quit.
The new segment on Knowledge Fight, countdown to the caravan quitting.
Well, I mean, caravan is also an unfortunate term for them to use because the right wing
was all obsessed with the caravans coming from south of the border.
Sure, sure, sure.
Those are bad caravans.
Seems like a weird term.
They should have chosen a different word.
Yeah.
But-
Convoy is right there.
You guys are southern dum-dums?
C.W.
McCall would let you use the song.
Convoy is right there.
Yeah.
Hey there, rubber duck.
We got Owen Troyer.
What are we doing?
We got Owen Troyer with some Smokies on his tail.
Caravan.
Get the fuck out of here.
Turn it into a convoy.
Have a little excitement.
We're the epic convoy coming up top Trump.
And caravans are just plodding along from destination to destination.
Convoys?
They're escaping some shit.
Or they're running moonshine.
Or they're running.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're right.
It should be-
It should be a convoy.
Yeah.
And they could-
This is why the hard right sucks at everything.
They couldn't even get convoy right.
It starts with the same letter.
And if Alex really wanted to put some money into this, he could hire Kellyanne Conway
to run the Kellyanne Conway convoy.
Kellyanne Conway, yeah.
It could work.
I like it.
Alliteration should guide all choices.
Yes.
So I got very, very, very, very, very, very excited about this.
Yes, I am very excited.
I am so pumped to see-
What a great punishment for Owen, too.
Wow.
What a brilliant way to punish Owen.
Well, actually, I think it's two-pronged.
I don't know if it's necessarily a punishment, but it's like no one else could probably do
this.
True.
And Owen really came into Infowars by yelling at people on the street.
And the only real value to the organization isn't as somebody who can tell whether Steve's
full of shit or not.
Not good.
He can't conduct interviews-
Nope.
Credulously at all.
Really bad at it.
So why not just send him on a fucking tour convoy and have people yell at him-
That's what I'm saying.
And yell at other people.
It's play people to their strengths.
Exactly.
You did the pajonic shit.
You fucked up.
Totally.
Now we're going to get back to basics.
Yeah.
We're going to focus on what you do well, and then maybe you'll get your shot again.
He got knocked down a peg.
Yeah.
You wanted to play out of position.
Yep.
You blew it.
Now get back.
Apprentice, go back to where you began.
Exactly.
Absolutely.
So I'm excited.
I'm so excited for that.
The potential for hilarity is so high for this.
Is this documented?
Somebody has to have a camera crew there, right?
No, no, no.
Of course.
Owen Schroyer has his own show.
The One Room.
I want the raw footage of this road trip.
There's a channel on band.video right now for the caravan.
Is it live streaming?
No, no.
Oh, shit.
God damn it.
I want the raw on this.
We can edit something beautiful.
I can't tell you, I've not been this excited for some dumb idea because he can't stop this.
It's something that's supposed to happen over the course of this week.
Owen Schroyer is already somewhere, undisclosed location at this point.
This is happening.
I want to bet money on whether or not this makes it all...
I will bet you money right now.
Alex does not make it to DC.
I'll take that bet.
You'll take that bet?
Alex is flying.
He's already bought the tickets?
I'm sure.
I think he's going to cancel it.
I don't think he's going to make it.
What do you want to bet?
Let's bet 50 bucks.
Okay.
Charity.
Let's bet 10 bucks.
50 bucks to a charity.
50 bucks to charity.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll take that bet.
Sounds good.
I'm going to win this bet.
Alex is going to DC.
Okay.
All right.
I'm going to go dumb.
I feel like the better bet is whether or not Owen makes it.
Ooh, that's a good question.
Because he's actually got a challenge in front of him of stopping at all of these cities.
That's true.
Alex is just going to fly.
That's what I'm saying.
See, but what I'm saying is if Owen doesn't make it, there's no way Alex can save face
on that, right?
It would be tough, but it would also be...
It's debatable whether or not the presentation would be better if Owen doesn't make it.
That's true.
That is true.
I know.
Oh, man.
They have to make up some story about him being stopped?
Oh, that's what I want.
That's what I want.
You listen to me good and you listen to me well.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Now.
Okay.
If there were any way for this to have been possible, I would almost do anything to be
on that bus.
Like to be a Hunter S. Thompson type.
Totally.
Like, hey, look, I don't like you guys, but I want to do some Gonzo journalism where I
come on this bus with Owen.
I'll stay out of your way.
I'm not going to fuck with anything.
Just to be able to record this for history.
No, that's what I'm saying.
If there's raw footage, this should be filmed all the time.
This should be a road trip documentary and we should have the final cut.
This should be the new Cannonball Run.
Totally.
Holy shit.
There it is.
Writing it down.
Some...
Now.
Jordan.
Cold open.
I have to...
Fade in.
I have to punch this up.
Okay.
I have to punch this up in there.
Alright.
And he's got to get to DC through all these stops.
Sure.
Also, Antifa is there.
Right.
And they have to get to DC.
So we're getting to wacky racist territory.
Yes.
I want John Cleese involved.
Of course.
Absolutely.
Rowan Atkinson can get involved.
We have rat race going on.
It's a rat race all over again.
Yeah.
Yes.
We need to have an Antifa news organization.
And then there's, there's gotta be somebody who's dastardly and a dog that laughs.
These are the things I know about the wacky races.
And, and one car that's like, they're drunk, but we're not going to show them drinking.
We're just going to let that go.
Because they're driving.
Yeah.
They're characters who are drunks.
You know what's going on.
Yeah.
We're not showing this for legal reasons.
So anyway, you can tell I'm very excited about this.
I'm stoked about this.
Yeah.
This is an exciting new development.
This is the first time I've been really excited about something Infowars done in a while.
Yeah.
Although I do think that there is the potential for this to go really bad because I think
a lot of the people who might be drawn to that would be violent type.
Sure.
And certainly we, I hope that that's not the case and that's not what I'm excited for.
I'm excited for Owen tripping over his own foot all the way up the Eastern seaboard.
Totally.
That's what I'm interested in.
Yeah.
Imagine if Paul Revere had like a two legged horse.
That's what we're dealing with here, man.
Yep.
So Alex gets to talking to Ali Alexander.
He comes on and they're just trying to get Trump not to concede.
Sure.
And it's so critical Ali to not get the president to concede because the cavalry is coming and
the evidence of fraud is mounting massively Ali Alexander.
We know that the president is watching these broadcasts and so I want to say Mr. President,
the Calvary is coming.
So you got Calvary and cavalry coming.
Oh man.
It's exciting.
Calvary.
You're the guys who like the Bible.
Figure it out.
Maybe that's the problem though.
They like it.
They like it too much.
Yeah.
So you've seen Ali Alexander really coming into his own as a real like hardline zealot.
Real, real religious Christian zealot.
So maybe he is actually saying Calvary.
That could be.
The Calvary is coming for you.
We're going to put you up there.
So if the election is to be believed by the, you know, all the sources that are reality,
right.
Then Biden won.
Yes.
And even if that's the case, Trump should still be president.
I think that's great.
Even if he'd won the election in which he hasn't, we have a right to not let him beat
the president because they claimed Trump was this Russian agent with no proof.
With Joe Biden, my God, Ali Alexander, we've got incredible evidence.
We've got damning evidence.
We've got him dead to rights.
So I mean like why even do the election then based on what you're saying?
Pretty much.
Yeah.
You're, you're saying that the person is disqualified.
So like why wasn't your argument, I mean, why, why wasn't there like a position of fuck
this election, we shouldn't even do it.
Sure.
Instead of let's do the election, the Democrats are going to try and steal it and Trump will
win by a landslide.
Yeah.
I don't understand.
I mean, they tried to sell that with the only way that it's a fair election is if Trump
wins.
So why do the election?
Because if he doesn't win, it's an unfair election.
But at the same time, the argument with that wasn't let's just not do the election.
Yeah.
Now, now it's like we shouldn't have done the election.
We shouldn't even have done it.
It doesn't matter if Biden wins.
It turns out we could lose.
I didn't expect that.
Yeah.
I think that's another thing that they're, they're not able to comprehend how stupid
it makes them look.
Right.
Okay.
So you're saying that Trump had no, like it's all fake evidence and none of it's real.
They had no evidence for the Russia thing.
Right.
But we saw a lot of it.
Yeah.
And from varied sources all over the place.
Right.
So if that's manufactured, that's well manufactured.
Quite.
Currently Trump is proving that Biden stole the election.
We have very little evidence.
Well, we have Rudy Giuliani at a landscaping place.
Right.
See, so they're even admitting that they're bad, they're worse at faking evidence than
the, than...
Shut the fuck up.
Dennis Montgomery.
All right.
And hold your horses.
I'm sorry.
Hold your horses.
Google, Google data.
Alex showed the Google data.
That's true.
Come on.
Get it together.
I would, I would think that they could at least get one person like a, like a Michael
Flynn or a Michael Cohen to like flip for him just for a little...
Michael Flynn's lawyers pumping out the Dennis Montgomery stuff.
Yeah.
But from the other side, you know, they gotta get a, they gotta entrap someone and have
them like turn rogue or whatever.
So I think what they really want though, and I think that's something that we've been kind
of aware of.
Sure.
Is for Trump to seize power and is to be a Christian theocracy.
Yes.
And Ali is a little bit too open about that.
They're perverts and they're seeking to, you and I have talked about this, invert, invert
all of these holy orders that we have, that Christianity stabilized this, this feral version
of, of what Rome had, you know, after it burned and all this, Christianity injected into Western
civilization, a stabilizing formula.
And then Western civilization didn't work until we had it.
Exactly.
So the basis of what we call Western civilization now is Christianity because prior Western
civilization didn't work.
Oh, so whenever you talk about like Western civilization being what you're all about,
you're actually just talking about like a, I don't know, a Christian religious state,
a theocracy.
Oh, okay.
Cool.
Just, I'm glad, I'm glad that we can have that in the clear now.
It is, it is kind of, see, it is kind of obvious now.
I mean, in the clear again.
Yeah.
I mean, that's really their only option if they, if they can't even really lie about
the election results, cause nobody's buying it, except for everybody that they like, then
your only option is then just to out and out be like, well, in order to save the Republic,
we have to become a Christian theocracy.
Yeah.
I think that that's sort of the, the underlying trend that you see from people like Ali, obviously,
and a little bit on Info Wars, but actually the sense that I got from this Sunday episode
was very much not that interested in the election fraud stuff anymore.
Like he kind of, it's just like, ah, we proved it.
And he has stuff like this that happened, but his focus seems to be elsewhere.
Here's Biden two months ago saying, we've got the most people ever for election fraud.
And then Pelosi, a week and a half ago saying, I don't care what happens with this thing
coming up, he'll be inaugurated after, and they told us they do it with the ballots and
they did it because if there's one thing criminals do, they love to brag.
Only time they tell the truth is when they're telling you how they're effing you over here
it is.
Secondly, we're in a situation where we have put together and you guys did, did it for
our administration, the president Obama's administration before this, we have put together,
I think the most extensive and inclusive voter fraud organization in the history of American
politics.
But we are ready.
I feel very confident that Joe Biden will be elected president on Tuesday, whatever
the end count is, but on the election that occurs on Tuesday, he will be elected on January
20th.
He will be inaugurated president of the United States.
She's the one that goes to the salon, that's going bankrupt, doesn't wear a mask.
It's caught not wearing, Oh, but for the TV, she wears it up there on the stage.
I find that that like, uh, uh, sort of that second clip, uh, was useless.
I don't think that that was, I didn't, I didn't hear anything in there that was even like
suspicious.
No, I think, I think he's just trying to pass off just confidence as my knowledge for knowledge.
But I think that perhaps, but I think even he recognized that was so weak that he had
to complain about the salon instead of anything that's in the club that is weak to you.
Now the one of Biden sounds a little worse.
And if you think that he was just speaking and then accidentally said that they put together
a voter fraud organization, then you might reach the conclusion that Alex is presenting.
However, that's not Biden misspeaking.
It's a clip taken from an interview on pod save America from back in October.
In reality, if the person who found that clip had allowed it to play in full, it would be
painfully obvious that Biden was talking about organizing to stop and avoid instances of
voter fraud.
But honestly, that's not the best word that he could have used.
What he was referring to is more of the broad spectrum of voter disenfranchisement.
Immediately after the clip stops, Biden goes on to discuss the call-in line that had been
set up to connect people with lawyers who can help if they have trouble voting or face
intimidation at the polls.
These are the sorts of specifics Alex has because it's about appearances, not reality.
That clip sounds really bad, like Biden was accidentally admitting to setting up a voter
fraud organization, but it only does if you only listen to that little snippet.
So you know, you're creating this facade, this veneer, like, oh, we proved it.
He admitted it in public, but he's doing that to sort of not talk about it that much.
Because I don't think he wants to talk about it that much.
He wants to talk about this goddamn caravan, because that's exciting.
And then he also has an emergency message.
All right, I'm going to issue an emergency message to President Trump coming up at the
bottom of the hour.
So we've got that message coming up, and I think that that's really where he wants this,
he wants to put his focus.
Sure, sure, sure.
And we'll get to that in a minute, because his focus is never far from one person.
One person in this world haunts Alex like a- Keith Olbermann?
Like a weatch.
Bill Maher.
He's an indeed disgusting pus bucket that they're preparing to remove, and then Kamala
Harris will probably bring Hillary Clinton in.
What a time to be alive.
Indeed, what a time to be alive.
Still trying to fantasy book Hillary into this election.
I just don't, I mean, if you want millions of people outside the White House, try and
trick everyone into getting Hillary Clinton to become president now.
Wouldn't you just be vice president then, and then Kamala Harris would then have to
step down too?
No, she would step down, they would trade jobs, you know, constitutional stuff.
Sure.
Yeah.
So this is where I got, you know, I've already, I think, I think based on our behavior so
far, you can already tell I'm super excited about this convoy.
Yeah.
Now here's where I got real excited.
And then Owen Schroyer is coming in here live, he's live, and he's strong.
And he's preparing to deploy on a four day trip to DC and lead a massive caravan where
you can join it.
And if you decide to join it, it will send a message to the globalist that they are in
deep trouble.
Everybody always wanted to march on DC.
It's here.
When the chips are down, what are you going to do now?
Stay with us.
So I felt challenged by that, when the chips are down, what are you going to do?
Yeah.
And I realized.
We're going to join that caravan.
No.
We have to do an episode on Friday.
Of course we do.
We, this is, if there ever was an emergency episode necessary, we got to follow up on
the caravan.
Yeah.
The caravan is the only thing I care about now.
Yes.
It's the only thing I, because you know what?
I think that's going to be fun.
Yeah.
I think that's going to be fun for us.
I even think it's going to be fun for Owen and all the people in the caravan.
You'd forgotten.
It's going to be a good time.
You'd temporarily forgotten about Assassin's Creed because this caravan is exciting.
It's great.
This is a fun thing.
Yeah.
I want to, now I kind of want to do a caravan.
You almost, like you can just envision in your head like sad moments of Owen with funny
music behind it.
Totally.
Yeah.
God.
It's just, it's great.
So it's not going to be a normal regular thing.
No.
But caravan necessitates.
We got to do an episode on Friday about the caravan.
God damn it.
We won't know if Alex has shown up in DC by the time that episode comes out.
That's true.
It'll have to be decided on Friday, but there'll be plenty of caravan nonsense to get into.
I can't wait.
Me too.
God.
It's just going to be a series of banana peels.
I can't imagine it being anything else.
So Alex teased that he has this emergency message coming up, and here he throws to it.
Okay.
The video is at VAN.video.
It's at Infowars.com.
Alex Jones' emergency message to President Trump, do not concede.
There's over a million people conservatively on our streams, over a million listening on
radio stations.
That's 2 million people conservatively.
I love you.
I appreciate.
You're amazing.
I appreciate those that brought you here.
If you decide to spread this video, the president will wake up and say, no, if you don't, we're
doomed.
Here is the report.
I bet if you spread it, it still isn't going to, nah, it'll be fine.
I don't know if Trump's going to see like, Ooh, a lot of shares on that Infowars video.
I better wake up, better snap out of it.
Oh man, that Infowars video has almost as many likes as that dumb tweet I just posted
five seconds ago.
I better change all of my things.
Yeah, this is where I gotta go.
Yeah.
Now I felt cheated by this because the emergency message that he was teasing, I didn't realize
it was a prerecorded video.
He just did this so he can leave half an hour early.
He just, oh, that sucks.
He just leaves.
That sucks.
He just leaves?
No, but you know, he has an emergency message to Trump, so we better find out what it is.
Of course.
President Trump, you were about to be approached by Joe Biden and his new COVID-19 commission.
They're going to tell you that, sir, you're going to be blamed for the hundreds of thousands
of deaths unless you sign onto a new lockdown, contact tracing, and even people being taken
from their homes and forced inoculations.
When you sign onto that, you will be confirming that COVID-19 was your fault and legitimizing
the martial law take down of this country and the complete shutdown of our economy.
This will be the end of the Republic and you, sir, will be known as Benedict Arnold who
allowed it all to happen.
Trump you are going to be approached by Biden's team.
Trump, they are behind you right now.
Trump, at midnight you will be visited by 13 ghosts.
The fourth will give you an envelope, it has the location.
Come on, man.
What are we doing?
All right.
So this is kind of what I think Alex wants to turn this into as opposed to worrying too
much about like, ah, voter fraud or whatever, which feels just dead.
It feels deflated even on Alex's show.
What he wants to talk about is during the 79 days of hell, right, Biden and his transition
team are going to have some ideas about better ways to address the COVID-19 situation.
So what the real conspiracy is, is they're going to make like a fucking demand of Trump
that he get on board with their plan, their globalist plan.
And if he doesn't, then they're going to blame the deaths on him.
But if he does, then they're going to blame the damage to the economy that their evil
plans do.
They're going to blame that on Trump.
He has no win situation except to come out and say, go fuck yourselves globalists.
But then even if they do that, they're going to try and use the 25th amendment to take
him out of office.
Sure.
It's really much more exciting than Rudy Giuliani's press conference and the very, very boring
voter fraud claims that Dennis Montgomery is peddling.
I just, you'd think that that press conference should take an entire party down.
That's how sad that was.
I wanted to laugh at it because it's maybe objectively the funniest thing I've ever heard.
Yeah.
And it's confusingly funny.
Everything about it.
What I thought about it is everybody who is like, oh, comedy is going to be good under
the Trump administration.
And I'm like, every single thing I've seen of people trying to dunk on this is not as
funny and never will be as it's mere existence.
Like you're never going to win.
There's no point in trying comedy over Rudy Giuliani standing next to a porn shop with
a fucking pedophile right next to him.
It just doesn't get better than that.
There's no joke that is better than that.
And it's a landscaping place also called Four Seasons.
He himself is an implied pedophile after the 15 year old girl thing.
Like this whole thing is off the rails.
What joke do I have?
None.
Yeah.
So Alex's message to Trump is largely like, you got to talk more shit, man.
It's so essential for you now to not concede the election, but to come out with your bully
pulpit of the oval office and lay out the Newsweek articles and the new scientist articles
and all the documents that Fauci and Gates under Obama's command before you ever got
into office in 2013, 14 and 15 were running the very exact COVID-19 weaponized virus test.
Trump, you got to use our talking points.
You've got to get in the oval office and say info wars shit.
That'll really help me out.
Now what's really funny is if you watch the video of this, while Alex is talking, those
articles flash up on screen and one of them is that article from the scientist.
Oh no.
And right under the headline is an editor's note about how there are conspiracy theories
connecting this article to COVID-19 and the coronavirus and this is all unsubstantiated.
So even as Alex is trying to show this evidence, there's a, this doesn't work.
He's accidentally fact checking himself?
So they're going to try and remove Trump early is the thing.
That's what this emergency message is all about.
Sir, I want you and your advisors to know what they're planning to do to drive you from
office before January 20th and how they're planning to then blame you for COVID-19 that's
been their plan all along.
If they're able to trick you, then your legacy and all your supporters will be irrevocably
connected to the COVID-19 deaths and the American people will be persecuted and Americanism
itself will be demonized connected to the Wuhan virus, which is a Chinese communist
bio weapon.
Ooh.
I would say that history is not going to be super kind to Trump's fans period about their
response to probably not going to go well.
I don't think that's dependent on Trump leaving early or staying until January or being tricked
by imaginary globalists.
I think we're just going to look back and be like, huh, it's not weird how poor responding
poorly to a public health crisis seemed to be a policy plank.
Yeah.
Weird.
Doesn't seem like a good idea.
That's very strange.
Uh, my new policy is murder.
It's very weird.
The end.
So anyway, uh, they're going to try and use that 25th amendment to get Trump out.
They will demand that you who is still president elected under the constitution, implement
these plans.
If you do not immediately agree, they're going to say the 260 plus thousand most of the deaths,
as you know, from something else are on your watch and are on your head and that you are
guilty of this under the 25th amendment and are not fit to be the president of the United
States.
I want to further discredit you, not just with this fraudulent election, but to certify
that fraudulent election by having your own cabinet remove you under the 25th amendment
because you don't follow the recommendations and orders of Joe Biden's new globalist COVID-19
task force.
I mean, what's the point?
I don't, I don't understand why.
I think what's funny about this is that he's okay in, in his world, all right, we live
in a, they, this is what they would do.
So we do it, but they would do what our plans are that we're doing right now.
Right?
So I think Alex is actually saying that one, he knows all of this stuff is true.
This is all Trump's fault.
And that the only way, the best way for us to go about this is to use the 25th amendment
to remove him from office, to do all of this stuff early.
Like he's saying that the best plan is doing all that stuff, exactly.
He's telling us what he would do in our situation, right?
But that's not always still even the best thing to do.
It's not a good plan, but it is funny every time he does this because he's like, here
is what I would do.
And that's what they're trying to do already.
Yeah.
I hear it more like, yeah, it's going to look real bad if competent leadership comes in
and people are like, oh, this is what we've been missing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's going to look real bad.
It's gonna, it's gonna take a whole lot of the like, oh, the deep state, all these weird,
weird things that have been going on over the past couple of years, these weird excuses
are all just going to look kind of dumb.
And I think Alex recognizes that and, you know, you got to distract people.
The only way to do that is to create something fun in that 79 days of hell.
They're going to try and get rid of Trump before Trump has to leave anyway.
I mean, the thing that scares me is there's only two ways for Trump to go.
And that is to step down early and have Pence write the most broad pardon in the history
of the United States that somehow also supersedes any and all state crimes that Trump has committed.
Or not leave because anything other than those two and he's going to jail.
So I think he knows that.
First of all, innocent.
And he's not going to jail.
Innocent until proven guilty.
Sure.
First of all.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
Second, I don't, I don't know.
I don't know if that's the case, but I could easily see some kind of a brokered immunity.
I mean, I don't know.
There's no, there's just nothing to say.
If he leaves office, he's going to lose all of his money.
Like it's going to be a bloodbath for him personally because he's bad at everything.
And I think what's going to save us is he's too incompetent to do either of the only two
things that he can do.
Maybe.
I don't know.
That's my suspicion.
I think we'll see.
I'm not entirely sure.
That's my suspicion.
But Alex is presenting Trump with this position where like, if you're going to be approached
by a man in a trench coat, then he is going to tell you Biden's secret plan.
And should you say no to this plan, they will blame you for all deaths.
However, if you say yes to it, here is what you got to do.
Or here's what's going to happen.
If you follow the lockdown, they will put your name on the coming depression in the
United States and blame you for all the previous deaths, saying later, you actually admitted
that you were the one behind it all.
Again.
You did.
We have tapes.
Don't sign onto it.
You've got to come out and expose Fauci, Bill Gates, Joe Biden, and all of them in Oval
Office addresses.
And that is the only path to stop them.
So this is the 20% he was talking about earlier, I think.
Is Trump giving Oval Office addresses where he spouts Infowars conspiracies?
Yep.
Alright.
I guess I think 20% is a embarrassingly high chance to give that of success.
Sure.
I think as far as Alex goes, this is a great swing.
This is a great swing.
It's as good as he can do.
Because Trump has nothing left to lose.
And this would be great for Alex's business.
So why not see if Trump will do some shit for him now?
I think even Alex has to recognize that that's, I think, a fruitless strategy.
Probably.
But I do think that this is better for Alex than getting too hung up on the election stuff.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
And also getting too hung up on fucking, like, even addressing Steve's nonsense.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like, it's a better game to play that, like, oh, the COVID, it's really about.
Because then that kind of has a stage removed from the, like, strict electoral stuff and
the parties.
You can still, like, claim that there's something outside of politics, that this is about the
globalist's evil plan.
You know, and I think that that is good for him.
So I think that that's why he's focusing on this.
And this message to the president, supposedly, is not about fight in Michigan, fight in Pennsylvania.
You know, get there, count the ballots, make sure all of it, you know, like, get Steve
Pachanik on the phone.
He said it's a sting operation or whatever.
You know, like, he's not doing that, because, sure, that should live in the background,
but it's proven already.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's proven already.
We can move on.
We have to.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because there's more pressing information.
Exactly.
And that is that Biden's COVID response team is really a Trojan horse to get Trump out
with the 25th Amendment or, you know, that's that's pretty good on his part in terms of
spin and the way he's playing things.
Let Knight handle Steve Pachanik, get Owen out of the studio for a while.
Let me try and fucking thread whatever needle that I need to, to try and keep us in business
after next week.
Yeah.
And I think that's about as good as you can get.
And it's a better strategy than I would have expected.
Giant publicity stunt out of this caravan.
Totally.
Yeah.
No, this is a far better plan than I ever would have expected from them.
I don't even know if it's a plan.
I wonder if it's just kind of like, all right, what can we do?
All right.
This could work.
Yeah.
I don't know if it's some grand machination on their part or anything, but I think it
fulfills a number of the requirements that get around some of the problems they have.
It's still not a good play because it's still like, I mean, what happens when the 25th Amendment
isn't invoked?
What happens when these votes are certified and Biden is?
They do need to have the transition teams take over.
What happens in January?
These are only little band-aids you can put on this.
There's still a much larger problem that isn't being addressed by it.
But in terms of being like Alex Jones, where you got to keep moving, the shark of lies,
piranha of truth, shark of lies.
In terms of being that guy, it's as good as you can do right now.
And I agree.
Yeah.
I wouldn't be surprised if they half-assed their way into an accidental, competent move.
I don't know if it's, again, I don't know if it's competent.
Competent, we grate on a curve.
That's true.
We grate on a curve.
I have to keep reminding myself.
I would have expected him to be eating parts of his desk by now.
That's the curve I'm dealing with.
Yeah.
I make my desk out of survival foods.
Exactly.
Why not?
Yeah.
On this desk, it looks like it's made of glass.
It's actually sugar.
You need calories.
On my last episode, I fall into the desk from 20 feet above.
Giving Owen an elbow drop.
Yeah, exactly.
So on this next clip, Alex is talking, I mean, like, is it?
It's just background dressing that Trump won the election and it was stolen.
Sure.
President Trump, the mainstream media has choreographed all of this.
They have fraudulently blamed you for COVID-19.
The American people do not believe it.
They know the truth.
They elect you overwhelmingly and so this new fifth coup of election fraud is designed
to take you out.
If you comply, if you quote, take the olive branch of the neo cons and Mitt Romney and
George W. Bush and say, okay, I'll follow the recommendations of president elect Joe
Biden to lock things down, to wear the mask, to take inoculations and for contact tracers,
they will then turn around later and admit that you were repudiated and the deaths were
your fault and legitimize the persecution of your supporters.
So basically Alex is just being like, for our sake, please seize power.
Yeah.
But also the thing I find most interesting about that is that Alex calls Biden president
elect.
Yeah, I know.
I feel like he would be more petty than that.
They all know.
I feel like he would be, that's really weird.
That's really strange.
I feel like you can do a second take.
I know he's a one take guy.
There are cuts in here.
Oh, there are?
Oh yeah.
Oh my God.
You mispronounced a word fraudulent a couple of times.
Yeah.
It's not great.
But even in this message, uh, that is, you know, like I said, there's, there's some editing.
There's some effort that went into this and it's supposed to be like a message directly
to Trump.
There's an elephant in the room that Alex can't even ignore in this message.
And that is the Trump is not being a leader.
We are waiting for leadership.
We need the address from the oval office.
We need you to reconfirm in the face of Fox news and the other sellout traders that you
are never going to concede to fraud and sell out the election system in this country.
We know you're our champion and we stand behind you.
So even that is kind of like a call out a little bit, man.
I feel so like Joe Rogan and Alex, like so many of these people are sitting here being
like, where's Q, where's Trump?
Where's all this stuff?
And it's like, guys, they weren't your friends.
Yeah.
They've been using you.
I'm the fool here.
I know you can't admit it, but that's what you got to get.
You just brought up Joe Rogan, so I need to say two things real quick.
Someone sent me a message about Tim Dillon on Joe Rogan's show and they pointed out to
me that Tim Dillon is a sober person, like, or I don't know if like recovery or whatever,
or if he's just straight edge or whatever, so he doesn't drink or smoke.
We were saying that he was high and it was because he had kept saying he was high, but
I realized that what he was probably saying is he's high, like because he's around Alex
or something high on the excitement and I misspoke and I apologize about that.
I didn't mean to imply Tim was high when he wasn't.
I don't know anything about him.
No, neither do I, and that's why I made that mistake.
Easy to make.
Second.
I'm glad he's an asshole without PEDs.
I think I had this fantasy that Rogan, like, you know, he's like, I just rationalize having
Alex on my show.
Sure.
I was thinking about how fun it would be if he's like forced to have Alex's friends on
the show.
It's like, yeah, all right.
Okay.
You want Alex on there?
You got to bring a Pechenek on there.
Steve Pechenek is going to come fuck with you for a little while.
If you want to say that this guy's sources and shit are backed up and we've got a fact
checker right there, let's bring Dr. Pechenek right next to you and see how that goes.
Next episode, Stuart Rhodes of the Oath Keepers is here.
Let's fucking dance that dance, Joe.
You want to do this, do it.
Next time, Vox Day is coming in.
And now...
Nick Fuentes.
Florida Congresswoman-elect Laura Loomer is coming up on that.
I don't think it's outside the possibility that Loomer has been on Rogan.
That doesn't...
I don't think she has.
I don't think so either.
Yeah, I just had that fantasy.
That seemed pretty fun.
That would be very fun.
Forcing Rogan to have Alex's friends on.
Come on.
If you want to have Alex back again, sit down with these ding-dongs.
Wrestle with that bullshit.
John Rappaport coming on the Rogan Experience.
Is that Batman appearing from the bushes?
So anyway, Alex brings up a headline in his address to Trump.
This is one of his current talking points.
And now, President Trump, we have the head of the UK military, their Secretary of Defense,
their chairman of their Joint Chiefs, of their defense staff, General Sir Nick Carter, coming
out and saying this lockdown could trigger World War III and there's an extreme danger
of it and that another lockdown is not needed.
So this is a headline of an article that Alex didn't read about an interview with General
Sir Nick Carter on Sky News, where he discussed how the continuing COVID-19 situation and
some of the economic ramifications of it around the world has the potential to exacerbate
regional conflicts that already exist.
Many people don't feel like regional conflicts are too relevant to their lives, but Carter
was trying to point out that, quote, rhythms of history showed that localized tensions
can easily ratchet up and drag nations to war.
What he was saying is that regional conflict can often escalate when it's miscalculated
and ignored.
He said, quote, if you look back at the last century, before both world wars, I think it
was inarguable that there was escalation which led to the miscalculation, which ultimately
led to war at a scale we hopefully never see again.
His comments weren't meant to imply that dealing with COVID-19 could cause a third world war,
and he never said that measures that Alex would exaggerate into calling lockdowns are
unnecessary.
That's Alex's imagination about what an article he hasn't read says based on his impression
of the headline.
The interview is given to celebrate Remembrance Sunday, a UK day of commemoration for the
service persons of their country who participated in the two world wars.
Given this context, the General's comments and the interview made a lot more sense, but
it's exactly this context that Alex makes it his job to deprive his audience of.
It's bad enough when the intended audience is some listener who might buy dumb pills,
but it's another thing when he's imagining that he's conning the president with this
bullshit.
It makes total sense.
This is a Remembrance Sunday interview about these world wars and the concern that regional
conflicts can grow and engulf other people.
Yeah.
I mean, you know, World War One was a rich guy got killed and then a bunch of cousins
fought each other, you know?
So we have one last clip here, Jordan.
And this is such a metaphor.
This is a audio metaphor for Alex Jones's dumb, dumb message to Trump.
Mike down for this because I want you to experience this in its fullness.
We're still on air at mfullwars.com forward slash show and band.video and we're going
to be making major announcements later this evening about massive caravans from all corners
of the United States, descending on Washington, D.C. in the next few days, led by mfullwars.com
and more action we're about to take.
Mr. President, we don't just have your back.
Attention business owners, body slammed by overwhelming debt.
Just just amazing.
Just I can't even I can't say enough about that.
This is a commercial for Four Seasons Land, it would be amazing.
Oh, God, that would have been beautiful.
This is a video that Alex prerecorded so he could leave work early so he could give a
message of desperation to the president.
And it, first of all, ends with a plug for infowars.com forward slash show.
Of course.
He's plugging that in his message directly to the president.
Well, I mean, if Joe Arpaio is going to plug his book in a message to me.
What a dick.
But that does imply like, OK, the message to Trump part is kind of part of the performance.
Sure.
I think it's painfully obvious.
And then it's just hilarious that they mistimed it and he got cut off by the break.
You know how long it is.
You do.
To the second.
Yes.
It is recorded already.
There's numbers on there.
You can see it.
Three zero colon zero one.
Yep.
Don't run it till twenty eight fifty.
There's no reason that you need to be getting cut off by the break and your important message
to the president.
It's just not possible.
It's a recognition that this is performance art for the audience.
And then second, it's also an admission that, like, it's not as important as commercials.
None of this actually means anything.
We don't really care about getting the whole message in.
It's kind of just the fact that we did it.
We like.
And hey, Trump, get excited.
These Carol fans are coming.
Great thing to say.
We've got your back.
Are you having the overwhelming debt?
Just so good, because it's in the statement of we've got your back and then you literally
disappear.
It's just perfect.
Yeah, imagine if you're Trump listening to it, he's like, what else?
Not only do I have your back, what else?
It's an important message.
Pills.
I've got pills.
I got your back and I got pills.
So we come to the end of this and I ought to say, you know, rare need for a Friday episode,
but this caravan demands it.
I'm excited to follow the adventures of Owen Schroyer across these United States.
I'm excited to see what kind of goofs happen.
I wish I was there desperately.
This caravan has breathed new life into me.
This is very exciting.
And I just, whoever they hire, I know they've got somebody with cameras, you gotta give
us the raw footage.
It should be 24-7 filming.
This should be a fucking David Attenborough documentary.
Like that's what we're dealing with here.
There should be, the bus or whatever they're using to go down there should be like hardwired
video audio at all times.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Werner Herzog is there.
Werner Herzog has to be there.
Yeah.
The potential for this just to be an amazing story that might never get told, it's too
high.
It's too high.
I know.
Oh, dude.
Well, we'll do our best.
Yes, we got this.
And we'll see you then.
But until then, Jordan, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yep, or also on Twitter.
It's at knowledge
We are Facebook.
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work.
Yep.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Darryl Arundus.
I think it's totally fine if you watch Dancing with the Stars.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.