N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledgefight, knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys, knowledgefight.
Dan and Jordan, knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
Hey everybody, welcome back to knowledgefight, I'm Dan, I'm Jordan, we're a couple dudes,
I like to sit around and drink novelty beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Emmerich
Jones.
Oh indeed we are Dan.
Jordan.
Dan!
Quick question.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
What's your favorite part of Assassin's Creed Valhalla?
So I've had a little bit of time to sit with the game and I'm excited first of all to be
out of the snow now.
I've gotten to the point where I'm not just running around in the snowbank and that's
nice.
But also that they brought back the homesteading aspect of Assassin's Creed 3 that I love so
much.
I love the idea of just building up a little settlement and all that.
It was something I was really missing from the last two games.
I do enjoy that quite a bit.
It's fantastic.
I love it so much.
I've enjoyed, I still have obviously not played nearly as much as you, but I've enjoyed quite
a bit of the things that they fixed.
I think they fixed a lot of things that were kind of little hurdles in the past ones and
I appreciate that.
I think it's an improvement.
It's very very good.
I enjoyed it immensely.
I look forward to dabbling around and playing it for the next very long time probably.
It's going to be an insane amount of time.
Seems like a very large thing.
So the thing is, because I finished the audiobook and then it came out, I'm out of all other
work.
This is my reward, so I'm just putting hours upon hours into it.
It's good.
And I swear to you, I don't think I've gotten out of the, I still think the title card is
coming.
You still think you're in the intro.
Yeah, exactly.
It's big.
That's good, though, in terms of what the genre and the style of the game is.
That's what you came there for.
Yeah, totally.
So what's your Bright Spot?
My Bright Spot, Dan, is one...
Also...
No, no, no, no.
It is one Leslie Jones on the reboot of Supermarket Sweep, Dan.
It is fantastic.
This is the first I'm hearing about this.
Delightful.
I didn't know that existed.
No, it's so great.
The old guy was fantastic.
He was just that white guy who was five foot three and hosted a show.
And Leslie Jones hosts the show exactly how I would host the show and watches the Sweep
exactly how I watch it.
Like incredibly seriously?
Yeah, no, no, no, no.
Like this.
Get the goddamn turkeys!
Oh, okay.
That is exactly what I would do, and it's perfect.
That is great.
It's beautiful.
There's only two ways to go with it.
One is like that, and I think that's the better option.
Totally.
But the other one is treat it like incredibly serious, just straight-faced, like it's an
athletic competition.
Joe Bucket.
All right, he's coming down the corner and he's taking that.
He's got the cup of coffee.
That's $300.
All right, he's going to go back.
He's going to take the...
I think Andy Daley could do that really well, but it would be much more difficult to pull
off in an entertaining, funny way.
That's awesome.
I didn't know that existed.
I used to love watching Supermarket Sweep when I would stay home from school sick.
Every part of the show is better than what you remember, and Leslie is incredibly good.
Well, I'm thrilled to hear that congratulations, Leslie Jones, and congratulations to all
the people on the cast and crew.
So Jordan, today we are on our day off and we're coming in, because we have to.
There's a convoy deal.
Duty calls.
And if I hadn't had to pour over as much stuff as I have to get this episode ready, I was
going to surprise you by putting on a trucker cap.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was expecting something.
I was expecting to open with Eastbound and Down something, something, yeah, yeah.
No, no, no.
C.W. McCall.
Convoy.
All right, all right, all right.
That's the song for truckers.
Okay.
Eastbound and Down is for people who wish they were truckers.
C.W. McCall is for the real, the real Streak.
I didn't realize we had hipster truckers now too.
Yeah, definitely.
Okay, all right.
So we have quite a bit of nonsense to go over.
Over the span of November 9th to 11th, 2020, I'm Dan, this is 2020, and yeah, this is,
this is gonna, this has been fun for me.
I'll say that.
All right, that's good.
I'm excited.
Uh huh.
And I, I've decided that this series is going to have a name because Monday is the conclusion
of it.
Sure.
Because we don't know what happens, because Alex hasn't gotten down to DC.
He's not there yet.
And it would be legitimately impossible for me to cover everything by now.
So what I've done is I've broken it up into two chunks, and we're calling this Dan's Cara
Vanity Project.
I'm going to have to take words away from you, I'm just going to have to take them away
from you.
I'm going to have to keep them.
And if you want to use them, you can ask me.
Well, see, I was thinking about it and it was like a written request.
I was sitting there.
I was like, this is kind of a vanity project for me, Cara Vanity Project.
This is amazing.
Jordan's going to hate it.
Yes.
Yeah.
That was even worse because I know how long it took you.
It was good.
That was my second thought after coming up with it.
It's like, Jordan's going to be furious.
No, it's fantastic.
So we'll get down to my Cara Vanity Project in a moment, but before we do, we got to take
a moment to say thank you to some folks who signed up and are supporting the show.
So first, ominous warning.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
No thank you, ominous W. Someone heeded the calls for ominous warnings.
Next, Nate.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Nate.
Next, Jessie G. That's Jessie with an I.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Jessie.
Next, Phil T. Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Phil.
Next, Jeb P. Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Jeb.
Next, Jeb exclamation point.
Yeah, well, obviously.
Obviously obviously next Elizabeth B. Thank you so much. You're now policy wonk. I'm a policy wonk
Thank you, Elizabeth. Thank you next Joshua H. Thank you so much. You're now policy wonk. I'm a policy wonk. Thanks Joshua
Next the conspiracy grows larger. No last name given Chris. Thank you so much. You are now policy wonk. I'm a policy wonk
Thank you Chris. Welcome to the club
Then finally, I'd like to say thank you to somebody who donated on elevated level and we appreciate that very much
So Sailor Moon's spirit sister Stephanie B. Thank you so much. You are now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk crikey mate. That's fantastic. Have yourself a brew. How's your 401k doing, bro?
We got to go full tilt boogie on this Watson. All right, let's just get down to business
We ain't making that money off that heroin. Why you pimps so good. My neck is freakishly large. I declare
Infowar on you. Thank you so much Sailor Moon's spirit sister Stephanie. Yes. Thank you very much
If you're out there listening and you're thinking hey, I enjoy the show. I'd like to support these gents, too
You can do that by going to our website knowledgefate.com clicking the button that says support the show or what you can do is
Get yourself a big old cart run it up and down the metaphorical grocery aisle. Do not forget the turkeys
Those are a hundred dollar ball. Make sure that you get what's on the shopping list this week. That's an extra
$250. Dan if you get the bear you're gonna want to get the triple bonus
that's $300 Dan and take that all down to your local charity or bail fund and
Donate that not bad. Yeah, not bad. Thank you
Let me ask you this really quick about the new supermarket sweep
Is it all the same stuff has the same bonuses as the old one or did they flip up?
What items you need to get? Yeah, they flipped up items, but it's still it's still coffee and
Yeah, yeah. Yeah the spirit and now you also can toss in like
A thermoses and shit like it's great. It's fantastic. I'm gonna have to watch this myself. It's wonderful
I'm gonna have to get on this immediately do it
episode over
So Jordan on our Wednesday episode we learned of the new infowars plan to run a caravan from Austin
Texas down through the south then upward along the East Coast arriving on Friday in Washington DC the idea
I guess is that the cavalry is coming, you know
It's the troops that Trump needs to fight off the globalist menace, but the actual reality is a little less noble
That'll sound right on an optics level
the goal is very
Obviously meant to provide Trump with an appearance that he could use to make claims that the people are demanding that he fight back
Against the election results because he lost this caravan is an attempt on the people's part to turn themselves into human props
Which Trump can use to justify an authoritarian power grab on a deeper level. This is Alex attempting to pull off an outstanding
overly ambitious and
Protracted publicity stunt he's hoping that sending dumb dumb Owen Shroyer out to barn store in the eastern
Side of the country will force the media to pay attention to them in his mind
Owen's going to pick up a couple hundred patriots in Austin then by the time he reaches Houston
The number will be in the thousands and by the time they hit DC. It'll be a mass of people
It'll be impossible to ignore. Yeah, that sounds right. This is not what's gonna happen
So failing that he's hoping that people with big social media reaches will be unable to resist
Meming the fuck out of clips of Owen on the road and he'll be able to drive some traffic that way
The final thing that this stunt accomplishes is that it provides something with a drastic
immediacy that can distract the audience for realizing that if anything Alex says means anything
No number of people showing up in DC is gonna mean a damn thing
Because Alex has already said that the globalists are gonna kill everyone no matter what and that even if Trump is successful
There's a plan B that the Patriots can't stop
in this sense the caravan serves as the shitty
Shiny set of keys that Alex can jingle around to keep people from canceling auto-ship if at the end of the election
Biden has won. We need to kill everyone and overthrow the United States government
Biden just won. We're gonna go on a road trip. Hold on
I bought a URL
Literal devil has won. Let's get on the road. Hey caravan
Look, we're already just bullshitting about the apocalypse and the devil. Why not create our own tribulation? It's fantastic. Yeah
All that being said I love this
It's my favorite thing that infowars has done in a long time
Partially because it's so naked and transparent terrible if this ends up being anything notable
It'll be a collection of people whose various scams are in danger if Trump is out of office
It could easily end up being like the Rocky Mountain rendezvous
but you replace the Nazis and white power groups with pill salesmen and YouTube commentators who just now realize that they've
Overplayed their hands and they're in way too deep on another level
This also scratches a very particular itch for me and that's that I fucking love a road trip
I love road trips so much that I I've kind of fond memories of Tom Green's movie road trip
back when I was younger me and my friends would often just embark on random trips for the sake of driving a couple hours or
A day away to see what was there totally cool
Sometimes there was a destination but other times it was just the experience of being out on the road
Seeing things that weren't part of our normal routine, which was the actual reward itself
I loved that and it's one of the things that I feel is most missing for my adult life and probably a big part of
Why I dream of getting an RV and wandering the country
Yeah, so this caravan has been branded the stop the steel caravan and I cannot not pay all the attention in the world
Can they not have come up with a better name than stop the steel? That's terrible
Well, it is but they're trying to piggyback this stop the steel momentum that people like Ali Alexander have been pushing for a little while
I'm criticizing them for choosing that name as well
Then we gotta go all the way back. It's a terrible name. Well, we gotta go all the way back to 2016 the election
And the fake poll watching organization that Roger Stone started and got sued over all the way
yeah, there's a connection there, but I'm not sure what it is and I
It's it's frustrating to me
Something's up passing the torch an article from the Southern Poverty Law Center traced the current pushers of the term
Stop the steel strangely to be a number of new far-right folks who are connected to Roger Stone
Yeah, people like Jack Pessobek Mike Cernovich and Ali Alexander
their amplification of it reached other fringe figures like Michelle Malkin and faith faith Goldie and then even Trump's son Eric who pushed the
Term on to a larger audience. It's hard not to feel like all of this somehow still traces back to stone
But I can't prove it and it drives me nuts. He's everywhere
It's important to recognize before we get too far into any of this
There are two threads to keep distinct both of them which are branded stop the steel
The first is a series of depressing protests that are being organized around the country
Some of them may be organically started and organized and some may be astroturfed by tea party groups and right-wing money
They wants the result of the protests, but definitely doesn't want to be associated with them. That's really a smaller issue to me
What's organic and what's not it's something that I think a great investigator will probably publish a piece about in about a year
What's definitely true about these protests is that they're being amplified and pushed by this network of desperate Trump scammers
The second thread is Alex's caravan, which is spiritually connected to these protests
But is also trying to selfishly profit off them as well
Alex's publicity stunt is not about bringing more attention to these protests and it's an attempt to take whatever energy these protests might
Generate and steal it to increase the spotlight on his tank with a huge infowars logo on it
It's it's almost like this is a a conference of scammers and Alex is trying to scam them
Yeah, yeah, it is. It is lowly. It's totally like maybe maybe you have to scam them to get into the scam conference
You know, it's like an entry don't don't invite Alex to Conman Island. Yeah, exactly
Yeah, this has been Alex's mo as it relates to protests for most of his career
He just uses them to self aggrandize himself make the protest about him. This is no different, of course
That's why I'm treating Alex's caravan stunt as a separate thing from the protests
Even though they're technically both as part of the same desperation strategy that's being used by these doomed grifters
It's simultaneously more simple and more complicated than the sad protests themselves. Totally
I will say that as I'm preparing this episode
It does not look good
like and we're like the caravan has really set the world on fire if you judge by the number of views that the videos on
Band.video have the kickoff video in Austin has about a hundred thirty seven thousand views
But the drop-off from there is quite notice. Oh, is it? Yes
It doesn't feel like this is working out so far and that being said I
Still would give anything to have been able to go along for the ride 100%
I feel like I could have written my own fear and loathing long after the campaign trail
2020 if I would have been allowed to go
But sadly that will never be
For now the best I can do is this two-part series on our podcast about the tour Owen Schroyer is taking from Austin up to
DC based on the information available to me from afar
Since the timing is what it is
This is gonna be part one wherein we'll discuss what happened on the caravan tour between its launch on November 9th
And then to the end of Alex's show on Wednesday, November 11th after that we'll pick up on Monday's episode
So we'll wrap things up with the Wednesday evening, Thursday, and then the event in DC understood
This is very very stupid and I fucking love it. It's incredible. I love it. Yes so much
Yeah
I can't I can't believe the main reason that you do a caravan is because you believe
Wholeheartedly that you're going to pick up momentum along the way, right?
You know
It's gonna start out as a small thing and then it's gonna snowball and you know the premise before you even begin the moment
They said caravan. I knew it was going to fizzle out in the way that a firework
Should fizzle it like an inverse firework. Mm-hmm, you know, it's going to explode fizzily. Yeah, I don't know
I mean don't get ahead of yourself with predictions. Okay, but I mean, we'll see. We'll see what all this what goes down
All right, but before we do here is an out-of-context drop from today's show. I am the president. I am the president
I am the 46 president. Alex has declared himself the president. That'll do it. That's the indication of where he's at
I'm pretty sure CNN called it for him as well as a real aberration on the polling night
So I'm not positive if David Knight had any caravan business on November 9th
and I'll hopefully never know because I didn't listen to his show and I'm not going to yeah, so we start on November 9th on
Alex's show and
He's trying to keep spirits high. There's still a chance Trump can win this thing. Okay, there is still a
chance
For Trump
to win the election
Fairly and squarely, but I was sitting in one of the offices this morning
about 12 feet away from a trash can and
and I said watch this and I threw a little Gatorade container and banked it off the wall and a file cabinet and into the trash I
Am the president now. That's how Trump's got to get around this fraud. Yeah, man
Get around the road with a bank shot
Trying to bank around is the law. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The law is a huger issue
That's why you got to do a bank shot instead of a straight ahead
Imagine the law as a wall, right?
You cannot if we're gonna build a wall bunk bunk. Yeah, you can't do that. All right
Well, they can and they will if everyone bullhorns the White House. That'll do it call the White House
the Bullhorn the White House
The Bullhorn Marlago Trump's back and forth the point is is let
Him know what's happening and what's unfolding and I can tell you
That I can sit there and I can get on the phone with folks very close to the president or the president if I need
To I don't have a day or two to sit there by the telephone many times. They've called I've missed the calls
I missed some of the calls already the last few days. I cannot shit
by the telephone for a call from Trump, I
Cannot sit by the telephone to do this
It makes me sick. I take a nap or I'm on the air. Boom
I missed the phone call every time I'm at Trump calls
When I nap
No, what happens is every time I go to call him he's in the middle of calling me and then the line is busy
Dan yeah, man. I
Don't think this is a good angle because Alex has already said multiple times that he and Trump are literally psychically connected. Yeah
so I
Really don't think they understand that his advice and essentially bully your fearless leader into taking over as a dictator
Yeah, I mean that's really what it seems exactly. It seems like what they're there. They're their whole thing is yeah
Yeah, yeah be a bully to a guy that we think is
Unbullyable even though we obviously know if we just bitch at him. Apparently he'll do whatever we want
well, I mean that's kind of the premise of the
the the caravan as a whole is like that is directed at Trump
Yeah, exactly. It's not really for us. No
Absolutely not the caravan isn't really even to support Trump. It's to yell at Trump bully
It's to give him one last chance to be a fucking dictator already
That's kind of the idea it does feel like that yeah, that's a real depressing thought it is
In all ways. Yeah in conception and execution. It's very bad every part of it
I love that Alex is saying like I take this nap and then I miss Trump's call and
Recently, we've seen that Alex thinks that he gets prophetic visions and naps. Yeah, that's true
I mean you got to choose one or the other did he get the call in the nap?
He might have that's probably explain everything. Yeah
Yeah
So anyway, everyone else in the world is too dumb to see what Alex can see everything is so clear to him and you
Fucking idiots just won't get to get it together
And so America will probably burn that sounds right
I mean, I really feel like I'm on the planet of morons here and I'm not saying that in elitist way
I mean, we know their exact next moves. They're gonna call 25th amendment. They're gonna say all the deaths for Trump's fault
They're gonna say while he's president-elect
running his fake task force
Biden that Trump's got to do what he's saying or the deaths are in its hands to make himself look legitimate
Trump cannot assault
The statements Biden makes he has to assault the whole fraud of the scam and lay it all out in damn
White House addresses and it's over for these maggots, but everyone wants to argue every facet of the scam
instead of the entire
Enchilada of the fact that it's bad. It's like arguing
strategies with the former Soviet Union instead of looking at the Soviet Union being run by evil people and
And
Look if we don't get the funds to fund this place. I don't care
I'm ready to shut this down if America wants to lose and go down the tubes and burn in hell
That's fine. Sounds like a great patriot. It sounds like a guy who loves America so much
I'll stand with America no matter what or I'll throw a little tantrum and say you should all die and you can all burn
If I can't pay rent on my gigantic studio, I'm so patriotic and so much you cannot help me
You live in million-dollar homes. Yeah, I just will hope you all burn to death
yeah, I mean the pay the the the you know, this Republic is based on the blood of
Patriots, uh-huh, and I'll stand up for it as long as I'm a dollar. Absolutely, but that after that he can burn
I don't know if I'm broke you guys can all burn to hell
Yeah
So Alex has this strange thing going on about like how he can't get a hold of Trump and like I just can't sit by
The phone all the time. I've been airing a lot of tapes today
because
I'm officially choking on here at this point. Okay, and it's not because I can't handle the threat of the globalist
I love my crew
Is that we're all stressed out and we're all over the edge and we're and a lot of the crews being more professional
I am some of the crews being not as big as a jerk as I am. I know exactly their damn game plan
I know how to beat them and then I'm telling myself I could probably do more good. The audience is great on the phone
I need to go in my office and and and beg and then get a hold of Don jr
And then get the president on the phone and then hope he listens to me about this stuff and there's nothing more
Frustrating than missing phone calls from the president and and I'm just sick of it all. I'm sick of it Wow
hmm
Seems like what he is describing is that the normal way he gets a hold of
Anybody is to beg somebody to get a hold of Don jr. It does seem like that's the only way to get there
So that's that's not great on its face
It seems like all of Don jr's handlers are doing a lot to keep Alex Jones from getting it or maybe
Maybe they're all like Don jr. Will believe any old bullshit Alex. Please don't get him anywhere near there
It's gonna it's gonna blow back on us. He's an idiot. All right, there's a there's a feeling
Yeah of that and Alex is really mad. He is very mad. Of course he is. So he's got to get Owen into studio
Owens got to come in to discuss the launch of the care of I thought Owens already on the care
No, no, it leaves the evening of the night evening of the night. Okay, it's the first
Stop is Austin and five right on the ninth, right?
So he's still he's still there to be in studio
And what they do is is basically what we were already talking about about this this whole idea of going to Washington
It's a threat to Trump. Yeah, they're saying basically
We will stop supporting you and we're the only people exactly. Yeah. Yeah, you got nobody left, man
I'm more behind Trump now than ever. What about you Owen?
Yeah, and I'm gonna be more behind him for the next I guess
72 days and he better he better rise to the occasion in the next 72 days and save this
Republic or his name is gonna is gonna be you know
Not the gold emblem on the side of his buildings and his airplanes. It's sadly gonna be a new
SHI t word, but by the way, did we not call it the 72 days of 79 days of hell?
Ha ha good branding Wow
Yeah
So they're just saying they're like hey if you don't do we say we will abandon you and basically you see these scam dudes
Who are gonna show up in DC? Uh-huh, you know like me and it's Traca James Pacific, you know, like our Jack Pacific
You know thus we're the only people who give a shit anymore if they it's if we're we're the oceans 11 taken down
Fucking everybody who got in the way. That's what we're doing arguing with everybody who's accurately describing your action. Yeah, exactly
Yeah, why in God's name?
Would you think he's going to step up and be the leader now?
Did you really convince yourself that all you need to do to step up and be a leader is be a belligerent asshole on TV
That's it. I think yeah, I think that's all they needed. Yeah, I think that is what Alex
That's really what they think he fancies himself a leader and he's done very little else. That's fair
Yeah, so Alex has a little bit of an inflated sense of what could come from this caravan. I'll say
It might be a little might be a little bit
Are they gonna reveal that the whole thing was actually a sting operation through this care or not? Okay
The comm was gonna go pretty slow. It's gonna stop a few times a day
so you can you know meet up with it, but if tens of thousands of cars join this and the truckers shut down DC like
They're already saying and we use this as a focal point to get other caravans going to DC this Saturday and to hit this Friday
It's gonna change the world. So now's the time to take action. Ladies and gentlemen, it leaves at 530 today
I don't know if you're gonna get hundreds of thousands of cars now get truckers to shut down DC, but good luck
No, I doubt it. Yeah
And from what I've seen that might be a little high just a little bit
Unless a person can drive a couple thousand cars themselves
I really feel like what's gonna change the world is that massive scoop Owen has right about how this entire
Election has been a sting does have a scoop. He's got a huge scoop on this. Is he recanted this?
I feel like he needs to just really hammer this home because it's obviously the biggest story of the century
It would be he said it was the biggest news since the election. He did. Yeah, so Alex has got
You know, he's got to pay the bills. Of course. He's just straight-up reading ad copy
Like he's not even he's not committed to doing like pivots or anything
I'm just gonna read this to you because it's the truth
I'm gonna ask as an American patriot
There's somebody that's gonna stand in the gap for you and your family against what's coming down that you support us
I'm gonna read this to you right now because I'm pouring out all the money we got to run these operations
America in crisis emergency lockdown 2 is coming
Support info wars in the fight against total economic collapse and by martial law. This guy's is locked down to up to 60% off
Plus free shipping and purple Patriot points on everything. That's a big sale. Yeah, it's a real great great read
Yeah, that's a great read every sale though, man
That's uh, he talks about you know this a lot. He's like I need to get rid of everything
He's got to get rid of everything. Yeah, let me pay for the gas for this caravan. Yeah, I can't be cheap
It's not cheap. No, he's at least two vehicles out there. That tank looks like a gas gun. Yeah
God, I can't even imagine. Yeah, so he's running this sale where everything's 60% off free shipping triple patriot points
He's done pretty similarly extreme sales and talked about how he needs to sell everything pretty regularly
And so that's why this clip is kind of funny. So I had like, you know epoch times calling up
Is it true you're going bankrupt? No
Family. Hey, I hear going out of business
Crew members. I had a few people quit
Today while you're out of business, you know, I'm gonna go work for the blaze or whatever fine
I don't care as long as doing your job. I love you
So, I mean like Alex is the one who keeps acting like he's going out of business
Yeah saying we can't afford to stay in business pretty much non-stop
Yeah, so I don't know I can see where people would get that idea
I mean literally saying I've got about a year left of this and I'm going to retire maybe a year left of this
Yeah, really? That was two years ago. So who knows he does do this a lot
Yeah, and then in terms of employees like going and working somewhere else I would too
Yeah, of course constantly said on air that he's gonna have to fire people and he can't afford to pay salary
Exactly. If I heard that from my boss on air, I wouldn't risk it
I wouldn't I heard it one time even if I knew on air. He's a lying piece of shit
I'd be like just it's still in there. Why did it? Yeah, of course
I take the chance that he's not full of shit this time
Totally totally leaving you like without a job out of nowhere as opposed to like I'll go find someplace like
Fuck Glenn Beck, but I bet he has a better like working fireman. Totally. Yeah
I have to assume I get yelled at every time because I'm 14 and I don't know how to pull up a clip goddamn it
I'm 14
So Alex believes or at least is pretending to believe that he is actually responsible for Trump not conceding
That sounds right and he wants to see if the American people really are ready to fight for this country and have his back
Too I think there's an element of that because if he sees millions in DC
Well, you notice the White House told me as soon as they saw us now
I don't take the credit as soon as they saw everybody around the country mobilized and they said that's it
Trump told all of them screw you I'm doing it because they specifically mentioned Austin was the last straw
They were seeing that. Yeah, so they saw these people getting together in Austin and they're like, that's a life straw
We're not conceding. We're gonna fight this thing. I saw people get together in Austin. Uh-huh. Yep. Yep. The Texan is out
Yeah, all right. Okay. Trump has like advisor come up to him. He's like, mr. President the Texan is in play
So they talk a little bit about what people are afraid of and I kind of agree with them
He's to go right to the fraud right to jail with nobody how Joe's a chai comm agent how he's illegitimate
Now America won't accept it and call America out. That's what they're fearing is Trump calling us out to action
I don't agree with anything that he said except for yes, I think very much afraid terrified
Trump calling people like you and your crazy friends into action
It's because that would very much cause people to die immediately. Yeah, very immediate. Oh, yeah pretty much instantly
Yeah, it would be bad if he just said on TV. I'm calling on Patriots to take over this country action
Yeah, we're fucked. Yeah, we're gonna die. They would see that as like a green light
Totally straight-up non-stop mass murder. Yeah
Anyway, Alex said this next clip gives you a reason to think he's going out of business
Which I don't know why he was confused
Their responsibility stay on air plus we have products you already need but it takes money to do it
And we're not bringing in the capital we need right now to keep operating
So I'm watching what I did two months ago that brought in some capital when we last time
I we didn't have enough going Wow. Yeah, that's that's why that's almost like he's like, why would you leave?
I have been in this situation so many times. I'll figure out a way to pay you eventually. Come on
It strikes me as like I and I mean I'm guilty of this too like being like maybe this is the time that he's actually
Completely fucked on the money off totally and I'm I'm so
sort of
decent desensitized to it now that like the time that he is
Actually fucked. Yeah, I probably will just think a guy. Yeah doing it again. All right, whatever
So we get to a little bit of information here and this is about the vaccine
Candidate that Pfizer short has released information about I bet it's true boy. Alex doesn't know shit about this
That's not a surprise al rallies 1,100 points is up more that was this morning spoke the Dow Jones industrial average hits record as Pfizer
Says kovat 19 vaccine is more than 90% effective and cue up that clip though
I think it's on this list here governor Cuomo cannot said I don't care what he says
It's not safe because they want the lockdown to continue
I'm not endorsing the vaccine Trump got Pfizer and others to actually put out a real
Attenuated version of the virus not an mrna vaccine that changes your DNA. That's even worse
To again take control the fear get people not to be in fear to have a solution
This vaccine that was created by Pfizer was not done because Trump wanted to undercut Bill Gates and all that shit
That's silly and the Gates Foundation has given vaccine related grants to Pfizer in the course
Of course, they have a good working relationship
Actually also when the news about the vaccine broke Trump whined like a baby and claimed that the vaccine was withheld
So he wouldn't have a win during his term. They waited until after the election to bring out this news
It's kind of fucking stupid because he's still president until January. So it's still his term. Yeah nonsense
Yeah, Pfizer released a pretty scathing statement about how they don't care about politics and they're more concerned with the global emergency
What about it Trump thinks that the release of this vaccine is made to make him look bad
So I think that maybe he and Alex have different talking points on this one
Mm-hmm further Alex has no idea what he's talking about. The vaccine being announced by Pfizer is an MRNA vaccine
Of course this vaccine that Alex is claiming is the alternative to Gates as evil MRNA vaccine is the exact same type of fire
Vaccine he has literally no grasp of the subjects he's covering and he just makes this shit up as he goes along. It's embarrassing
I'm just more interested in what does he want? What do you mean? What do you want? You're oh, I
See Trump created this vaccine in order to control fear and they they don't want to give you the vaccine because they want the
Lockdowns to continue now. I don't want to give you the vaccine because I think vaccines are evil
But they are doing this to make Trump look. What do you positively want? What would you prefer happened?
No one vaccine ever and then what crush doctors, but then people would still blame Trump for them kill
Scientists. Okay. Well that actually does sound right devilry. It does sound right. It's witchcraft. It's witchcraft. All right
I forgot I should have started from the assumption that it's all witchcraft
Yeah, so Alex is mad cuz Cuomo doesn't want people taking this vaccine
I guess okay guys found it like a minute. I'm even asking
the clip of Cuomo
Saying oh don't take Trump's vaccine because they want the fear to keep going when you get their M RNA vaccine
That's like being shot by a BB gun
Versus being shot by a 12-gauge shotgun a double-lock buck. I'm not saying take the vaccine. I'm not saying take the regular Pfizer
attenuated where they microwave or radiate a coronavirus
And your body learns how to beat it. It could still cause an autoimmune problem. It could still be contaminated
It's still that liability protection. I still won't take over my dead body
See this is where it would help Alex to know what he's talking about
He's saying the governor Cuomo doesn't want people to take the Pfizer vaccine because what he really wants is for everyone to get his much
More dangerous and deadly mRNA vaccine that'll come out later
Thanks to Bill Gates the normal attenuated vaccine is bad
But Cuomo wants to hurt people more so he insists they wait until an mRNA one is ready great plan
That's a fun story to tell dum-dums
But it really doesn't make sense when you realize that the Pfizer vaccine is an mRNA vaccine
If you know that then Alex is just saying that Cuomo doesn't want you to take an mRNA vaccine because he wants you to wait
Until there's an mRNA vaccine ready. It's nonsensical
Alex needs to try harder because this is just embarrassingly sloppy. There's not even a conspiracy to unravel here
It's just an instance where he clearly is making up details about this Pfizer vaccine because he knows nothing about it
And it would severely hurt his ability to support Trump if he had to explain why Trump was trying to take credit for an mRNA
Vaccine something that he specifically and repeatedly has said is going to kill everyone
Yeah, this is the time for him to stand up and really be the leader that they need right now. Yeah
Yeah, also, let's remember that this vaccine that's being touted by Pfizer
They're saying that it has a 90% success rate, but that's not been validated by peer-reviewed study yet
It's way too early to scream from the rooftops that this is the answer to the prayers
It's promising and I do hope that things continue to look good
It's kind of a sticky situation and someone like Cuomo is in an unfortunate position to have to be
You know the person who has something to say about this potential vaccine a leader
Yeah, it's not even available and he's already being called out for like not wanting to give it to people yet
You know sure
This is really just the way that anti-vax people flip the narrative when they know that they can't really argue the vaccine anymore
Their game of being staunchly opposed to any and all vaccine is great when there isn't an actual vaccine candidate
Once there is they know that opposing the release and distribution of the vaccine is tantamount to them saying that they support the continuing
Deaths of thousands each week from COVID-19. It's really hard to defend that one in a conversation
Yeah, and most of them particularly the ones who are media grifters know that they can't be successful
Trying to publicly argue that position and it will hurt their bottom line
Mm-hmm, so you see what someone like Alex does he lies about how this vaccine from Pfizer is one of the less dangerous ones and
Pretends that there's a conspiracy against Trump
Among anyone who would say like hey, maybe it's premature to widely release this one still need some more tests on it
It's all garbled. It's garbled. It's nonsensical because the point isn't the point. Yeah
Yeah, you you you if you think that there's something about this
That's like the vaccine is actually relevant to the argument that's happening. Mm-hmm. That's why you get confused exactly
That's yeah, that's the issue
Yeah, it's just a bunch of shit spinning around in the fucking toilet as it spirals down into our collective sadness
Yeah, that's a poetic way to put it. Did you read that in Assassin's Creed Valhalla?
So we're done with the night, okay, his show is not good
It's it's it is what it is. Not nearly enough caravan. That's the only thing I'm interested in totally exactly
So we get into now the videos that Owen has released. Okay for the caravan. Excellent on front
I'm sorry on the 9th on
November 9th Owen sits down and he breaks down what the the trip is gonna look like God here is the itinerary
I can't wait. This is a map and on this map. You're gonna see little roadways. Oh see beautiful
Okay, so we are launching the stop the steel
Caravan and it is going to be launching from Austin, Texas right here tonight at 5 p.m
And what we're going to do is we're going to drive right down here into Houston
But we're going to have our first stop tonight at 8 p.m
Then we got a long drive ahead of us and we're going to go all the way here through Louisiana
We may make a stop maybe in Lafayette or something link up with some people through Mississippi
All the way through here down to Florida into Tallahassee. This is where we will be on Tuesday evening
First of all, this is a severe schedule. Yeah, Alex said they were gonna go slow. You heard that
He said they're gonna go slow. This is brutal
They're talking about getting from Austin to Tallahassee and basically a day's time if they're leaving Austin at 5 p.m
They should have no problem getting to Houston by 8. It's about a two and a half hour drive
So I would guess that shouldn't be an issue. Yeah, the next leg of the trip is a concern
Owen seems to be a little loose on the details, but according to his itinerary, which they've posted online
They're set to be in Baton Rouge, Louisiana by 11 a.m. On Tuesday
It's good that they didn't choose New Orleans since that would have been an extra hour to add on to the drive
But still this is a four hour drive
Assuming that they get to Houston on time, then they have a rally. Are they gonna stay the night in Houston?
They could probably pull that off. So let's say that they have a two-hour rally then go to bed
Get up and get on the road by 7 then they could make it to Baton Rouge by 11
Sure, then they gotta have a Louisiana rally and then get to Tallahassee by 8 p.m. For another rally
That's an approximately 7 hour drive
So if they're giving themselves two hours in Baton Rouge for the rally and everything that they're doing it could work out
But that's fucking tight. That is tight. It's almost like they're expecting everything to either be nothing or
That everyone will plan things for them. Yeah ready to go ahead of time when they get there
It's it's sloppy from a production standpoint
Anything goes wrong anything anything goes wrong their entire trip is behind
But compounded but does it matter? No, of course not if they get to
Tallahassee at 9. Yeah, no care. So no it the stakes are low
But also the setup is terrible true true true true
The next day is a little bit better paced on Wednesday
But this is a very very poorly timed route and it does not suggest that they had a lot of time to plan
So anyway, here's what happens on Wednesday then on Wednesday
We're gonna head north like this right up through here link up in Atlanta with some friends. That'll be on
Wednesday and then Thursday, we're gonna head up to North Carolina hit Charlotte head into Virginia
This is a little better spaced out
The first stop of the day there on Wednesday is 3 p.m. In Atlanta, which is only four hours from Tallahassee
So that leg should be totally fine. The next stop of the rally is in Columbia, South Carolina at 8 p.m
That's another three hours on the road. So as long as they limit their stay in Atlanta to two hours
This should be possible. That seems like what they did. They gave themselves two hours. Yeah
Yeah, then on Thursday, they do not go to Charlotte
In fact, they don't go to Charlotte at all
The next step is Raleigh and then there's another three and a half hour
I'm sorry, that is another three and a half hours in the car, but that rally is at 3 p.m
So they should be able to make that one fine after that
It's on to Richmond, Virginia for an 8 p.m
Rally, which again should be no problem and then the next day is in DC so they can get there whenever they fucking want
Really, this is a horribly designed trip. That first day must have been brutal. Yeah, like I've been on the road
Yeah, yeah comedy shows totally it's stuff like when I was looking at that like whoa. No, yeah
Oh, no
No
I've been seven hours and like you're adding on time to get meals and to go to the bathroom and
Unexpected things just always happen. Yep. So it just seemed like I would not want I mean
I want to go along with this, but I wouldn't want to be the ones doing it
No, I wouldn't want to be like responsible for anything. No, and it was clearly planned in in about 45 minutes
I wouldn't be surprised if they didn't
Account for time zones and all of this shit. Oh
I didn't when I was planning out like how many hours apart they are. I didn't even think about that
Think we might find out if they did too. So Alex is there while Owen is giving his
His little like here's where we're going. Sure. Sure. And here's how that video ends quite abruptly
So, all right more coming there in pole wars.com. I want Troyer leads the attack the peaceful attack the peaceful attack peaceful
peaceful attack
Very important peaceful attack. What is that? Get the fuck out of here. It's the you talk love and punch
Yeah, so we're going to turn the other cheek right into their fucking faces
Mm-hmm. We get to 5 p.m. Uh, Owen Troyer goes down to the state capital course
He's got some Patriots there got ready to send him off in style
Alright, ladies and gentlemen, Owen Troyer here live
Owen Troyer here live which camera am I looking at? All right, Owen Troyer here live
We are at the Texas State Capitol building behind me. We've got a lot of great Patriots out here that are sending us off
We're gonna be heading to Houston tonight
Owen has a great group of Patriots. They're sending him off in Austin as you can clearly hear the exact
There was browsing cheers. Yeah in the background. Yeah, Jordan
I'd like you to guess how many people are there for Owen send-off and I will give you a clue
Okay, I do have an exact number you have an exact number. All right, so
If it's not an estimate, I think we're gonna go with 13 people it's 9 it's 9
And there are 9 people there and in their hometown at the send-off event for their cross-country barnstorming caravan
That's the type of thing that happens after a wedding night and you're being sent off by all the drunk people in the bleary-eyed morning
It's absolutely the saddest picture you can imagine and fuck do I admire?
I admire Owen's attempt to keep a stiff upper lip and pretend that this is a great turnout. He's doing great
I'm pretty sure that's everyone who is there too because when the live stream starts there's actually only six people behind Owen and they have
To corral the other three to get into the shot to make it look like there's more people there
People out of a Denny's
It's sad man, but it's amazing. It's my favorite genre of entertainment
This is like this I could watch this forever this kind of thing
Oh, it tried to stay brave in front of completely obvious sadness
It's just it's just it couldn't be more blackadder like it is just pure pure
Stupid. Mm-hmm. It's amazing. So here's uh, here's a little bit of Owen talking about where they're about to head off to
We'll be at Hermann Park
Miller Hill we want to try to be there by 8 p.m
We may be running a little late, but we should be there by 9 p.m. At the latest
It's your first leg of the man. You can't start late
You can't start late and especially with that in pretty simple way between Austin and Houston
You're not making up time as you go along. I mean if you're worried, yeah, if you're worried about that, that's bad
Yeah, that's not good
Also
It's fitting that they're having a rally in Hermann Park in Houston because that park is named for George Hermann who donated a bunch of
Land to the city, but also fought for the Confederacy. Sure. Sure. So it's kind of right where right where they would
Yeah, you'd think they'd be so we get to Owen talking about
You know this this seems like a comedy show guy like a promoter
Uh-huh, like maybe a local show sure a guy who booked you. Uh-huh, and there's no one there
Oh, that's Ellen has that vibe that's going on. We know that we'll be in Houston tonight tomorrow
We're gonna be going through hopefully we'll have a stop in Baton Rouge. We'll be in Tallahassee, Florida tomorrow night
There's gonna be a big turnout there. It's gonna be a big turnout in Tallahassee
I know there's wait until next week. Wait until next week. Oh, man. You should have been here
Yeah, there's an hour before you were here. Yeah thousands of people last week was packed man. Sorry, I don't know
I don't know what happened this week. Yeah, so Owen doesn't really have much to say
So he starts talking to people and here's here's the first fella
So we've got a lot of people out here. So I want to ask these people why it's so important
In fact, let's get Richard Reeves up here. Come here Richard. Come here
Okay, come here Richard
Richard Reeve is a info wars guest. Yeah. He is a old friend of Alex's. This is not someone high profile
This is maybe an employee high profile. Oh
Celebrity sending us off to him. They have a big media presence too. I'm surprised Joe isn't there
You know Rogan should be right there. He should be he's in Austin exactly. Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Hmm Joe Joe
Well, you know look Rogan's not there that would have definitely given them quite a spotlight yes
They do have a lot of media there though. Sure. We have multiple news media out here
Of course, the local media will never show up ever but they you know
There could be a fire right outside their front door and they wouldn't report on it
So that's no big deal
but this is gonna get national attention as
Long as you make it important as long as you get excited as long as you realize that this is the final level
Well, I don't know if there's multiple media outlets
But I mean, I guess it depends on what you'd consider a media outlet extra extra 14 people exist in space
Mm-hmm. There might be a blogger there. Yeah, Richard Reeve might have a website could you could say infowars is there?
I mean in a sense the internet is national. Yeah
So Owen's gonna leave. Yeah, the interviews are what they are. They're pretty boring
He's gonna leave but he gets interrupted. Hmm. We've got to get to Houston. So we're gonna we're gonna we're gonna take off from here
Are we still alive?
All right, yeah sure go ahead so what is it called when a radical feminist star
God, oh facial hair after protesting president Trump
impeach buzz
Didn't even get good laughs there from the that crowd
So this is a guy who got interviewed by Owen earlier who comes back up tell an anti-feminist joke
Yeah, yeah to to sad
response from the gathered
This kills this kills is my clan meetings. Wasn't everybody loving this
So now Owen just like I we had a we got that joke was good
Now again, we're gonna be driving we can't facilitate lodging and meals and everything
But if you just stay the course with us eventually on Friday, you'll land in DC with us and then Saturday's a big day
There's gonna be millions of Trump supporters
I think in DC to stop this deal. So are you guys ready to make history, huh?
Are we ready to make history and save this country? That's where we're about to do
So god bless the Patriots god bless America. God bless Donald Trump. God bless everybody that made it possible. Let's hit the road
We'll see you at the stop the steel caravan
Fucking William Wallace shit right there man Wow today we declare our
our
Independence Day
So based on that you would expect that this thing is going
awesome
Jump absolutely. So you might be surprised to find out on the way from Austin to Houston. Yeah. Yeah. Oh something goes wrong
Oh, it needs to call in to infowars to complain
So I had to come on here and do this update because we're having mass problems with
communication and this is because of the censorship now
We don't have to pontificate on the mass
So tech censorship that we're enduring but because of that we're not allowed to promote our events on mainstream news
They'll never talk about our events on TV news
We're not allowed to exist on Twitter or Facebook or Instagram or YouTube or any of that. So all we have is our platform
That's it. That's all we have
So I had to call in and interrupt your broadcast tonight because this is the only place I can promote
What we're doing the stop the steel caravan. I hate to risk sounding uncaring about Owens problems
But isn't he describing a challenge that they have to be aware of? Well in advance
Spanning half the nation and you need to get people to a very tightly timed series of events in various cities
Isn't coordination and messaging your number one concern you were gonna do a direct mail campaign
But we realize there's some issues there, too
I just refused to believe that Owen got out on the road and only then it hit him that he'd been banned from Twitter
So he can't tweet about their next stop and it turns out parlor. Isn't that great?
It's outstanding really Owens been out of studio on the road for like an hour and he's calling in complaining about not having a Twitter
Account, this is absurd. I love it. Mom. I'm running away
Did you notice mom? I don't have any money to get a bus ticket. Yeah
Yeah, so it turns out that I mean like they did know that they weren't on these social media sites
But they kind of over bet on parlor sure being good not a surprise and maybe it's not good
I guess parlor is becoming so popular right now that it's just being
Overwhelmed and over inundated with people on it and it's just failing miserably. I can't put out any updates on parlor
Quite frankly, it's extremely frustrating because that's what we were gonna use to promote this thing
But it looks like we're just gonna have to call in here and give people updates. And of course, we're banned everywhere else
So hopefully parlor can get its stuff together. Otherwise, I may have to try to get back on the gab
And try to promote and give updates via gab. Wait, wait, you're not on gab. Why aren't you on gab man?
Why aren't you on gab? Oh, I thought like a lano and did you do you realize the gab is too toxic and not fun
Dude, oh even you realize that I was on gab, but then I got hounded by all these fucking Nazis
Yeah, they keep calling me like a like a shill for Israel. Yeah. Yeah, huh? I don't like it when you get abused online
Has anybody ever noticed that there's a lot of abuse online. Hmm. Somebody should do something about that
Yeah, so you might go back to gab
I think they get their shit resolved and they still posted updates on parlor
So I tried to get an account with like fake information, but they need an actual phone number
Of course, and I'm like, I'm not I'm not giving my phone number. I don't know
I saw some updates and it looked like things were great. Yeah, I'm sure I'm sure so Owen Owen
the only thing he can do is plug on info wars and then Wednesday Atlanta
Greenville, South Carolina and then Thursday, Raleigh, North Carolina and Richmond, Virginia
And then of course Friday and Saturday in DC. So this is the latest now again
Owen has plugged a rally in Greenville, South Carolina. That's not on any of their caravan itinerary surprise rally. This is weird
What's also weird is in a video they posted on Monday
There's a map that says they have stops in Atlanta and Columbia, South Carolina on Wednesday
But then on Tuesday, they posted a map that omits the Columbia stop
It's very confusing with or without parlor problems and Owen saying Greenville isn't helping
It kind of makes sense for the tour to go to Columbia though because that's the state capitol and the rest of these stops except
For Houston are all state capitals and it's obviously Columbia. He just keeps fucking up. He said Greenville said
Charleston on the last one
Part of me thinks that maybe that's just because all these rallies are really up in the air on a moment-to-moment basis
It could be you know, like oh it's on this map this time and then we got a phone call
It's like we can only get four people to go to the VFW
You still want to come and they're like, I don't think we should so now that Owen is called in to complain about how he
Can't promote things to Deanna Lorraine. It's now time to get his ass to Houston at this point
I was really needing some context some additional footage or information than just the infowars content and luckily
There actually was a self-styled journalist who had decided to come along and document their trip. Fuck. Yes
You genius now granted this person was an infowars fan god damn it
So the turn there's not much footage like it's still edited down videos, but it's something
Oh and because it's an infowars fan you end up with interviews like this
Feeling good and running on pure adrenaline
Faith in God and love zero fear and we're on a mission of divine
proportions
Show our support for our country
And we're here to make sure we'll never ever submit. We'll never submit to the communists
In case you're curious Wow, the guy you just heard is the same guy who told the anti-feminist joke during Owen's send-off wild
Anyway, this is from a channel called just another channel and the guy who runs it is a dude who's called into Alex's show
In the past I've forgotten his name, but he's a dude who you could basically call an infowars employee
Except they don't have to pay a contractor
He's got some videos from the tour that I was able to consult for context
From his video of the Austin send-off
I was able to see Owens video from another angle and it's just as depressing from any angle as it was from straight on
I'm not fully convinced that some of the people in the video weren't there explicitly with Owen
So saying they had an organic turnout of nine people might have been an exaggeration. Yeah. So anyway, this dude is
following their caravan this this guy from the just another channel boy and this weird dude who told the
Anti-feminist joke I had hates communists is he's also he might as well be our eyes in yeah our way in
Oh my god. I
Mean, I guess it just happened too fast
I feel like if they had actually planned this with like a tour manager and stuff
Somebody would have been able to pitch to like Vox or something like we're gonna embed with this whole thing
I would happen to like it. Yeah, I would do it. Yeah, of course if if there had been enough lead time
I might have risked blowing cover or whatever. Yeah, I'd be like guys just please I give me you know
I'm good at creating. Yeah, like I could write an amazing thing about going along the you know, I'd be fair
Yeah, yeah to to fair to fair to fair. Yeah, I might make Owen look fun
The Dapper Nazi Dan wrote the Dapper Nazi. Oh shit
Uh, yeah, so we're in Houston, uh-huh
we've got now two streams of information the info war stream and this other weird dude sure who's going along with him and
Here is Owens clip in Houston
So Owen has arrived in Houston and he says the turnout is bigger than expected
Things are a little bit more difficult to assess in terms of the turnout in Houston
But that's just because it's nighttime
There's no doubt that it's more people than were in Austin
But it still looks pretty thin low bar
If I had to guess the number I would feel fairly comfortable in the 100 to 150 territory
That's more than I would have it either if I was owned much much higher than that stretches my belief
Yeah
the just another channel video kind of cheats to make the turnout look a lot bigger by recording the walk from a parking lot to
Owens location in fast motion making it appear that all the people that they passed are there for Owen sure and because it's sort of
Shaking all over the place. I can't keep track of any
Yeah, I don't know if those people were there for Owen or not, but you know, it's a public park
Yeah, even if I give Owen the benefit of the doubt and go with the high estimate of the turnout
It's still an embarrassing failure for info wars
If they presented themselves as scrappy upstarts then a hundred people showing up to a rally is great
But that's not their brand Alex insists millions upon millions listen to him world leaders. Listen to him
They've swung domestic and international elections. He has a million-dollar high-tech studio
They should not be drawing this poorly
Yeah
If you're a talented but relatively unknown comic and you can draw a quarter of a house that is nothing to feel ashamed of
If you're a headliner who's been in the business for 26 years and you can't fill a room you should stop booking gigs
Yes, it looks bad. Yeah. Yeah, you're gonna wind up at the Comedy Shrine in Aurora
With me and me. Yeah, so Owen's got some good news to give this collection of Patriots in Houston
I know when I have some good news
To give an eager crowd I'm speaking to through a megaphone
I'm really quick to get distracted and to trump impressions and rambling about multiple cars in the caravan
It's so amazing how the instinct to pad for time and tease things out for no reason. That's not just like a show tactic
No, it's just the style. Yeah, it's in the info war style guide
I that reminded me so much of do you remember have you ever seen the Kurt Russell speech in miracle?
That is exactly how motivating that was that Owen just taught not very that no, it's quite. Yes
Okay. Yes, incredibly motivating. Yeah
I have a working theory that if you work it in four wars for long enough you lose the ability to get to the fucking
point
You just can't you have to like something else
I would believe that Alex can truly infect you with something that you'd like can't get out
You know, like there's a serious virus that he can break into you the virus of bad habits. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, so we get to the good news. Finally. Sure
Biden lost, Pennsylvania
That's a great thing to say to get a crowd to cheer for you. Yeah, I would say that every time
Yeah, you get a big cheer. It's not true, but you get a big cheer, you know
So the good news that Owen was teasing out is that Boa?
Biden had lost the electoral votes in Pennsylvania. This is not true nor was it true then so this is sad
I was curious what the deal was here and where this news was coming from and thankfully I didn't have to look far
Because a source is provided in the video from just another channel here again
Was that weird dude who told that anti-feminist joke who I've now learned is named Tom
Yeah, what's the news? It just broke. What's going on with those states?
I'm real clear politics announced that they took the electoral votes away from Pennsylvania and
That immediately takes him away from having the votes
Actually Trump is winning and he is
So this is got from real clear politics apparently, okay. So the issue here is that there's a confusion in terms
What these guys are presenting is that real clear politics is reporting that Pennsylvania has taken away
The electoral votes from Biden thus putting the election back into play
What they're actually claiming whether it's true or not
Is that real clear politics was withdrawing their projection that Biden had won Pennsylvania's electoral votes, which is a different thing
There's a bit of a misunderstanding going on here that was exacerbated by social media
And of course Rudy Giuliani Rudy tweeted out the real clear politics had taken away their prediction of Biden winning
Pennsylvania on November 9th, which is the news that all these people are responding to her
However in the real world real clear politics had never called a winner in Pennsylvania to begin with
Their president Tom Bevin tweeted out on November 9th quote. This is false. We never called Pennsylvania and nothing has changed
The idea here is to pretend that there's some media outlet in this case real clear politics
That is swung things away from Biden and towards Trump because this creates the illusion of momentum
With no tangible victories and no real hope to point to it's important for these assholes in the right-wing
Propaganda sphere to create their own fuel and this is one of the ways they do that
Yeah, you can see how even when on the road when doing something that's supposed to be fun
Oh and can't help but spread false and misleading information. It's all these people are equipped to do. Yeah, that's a real bummer
Yeah, but I mean if you want to get a cheer, that's a great way to do it
It's like if you're a stand-up. Yeah, and you're like, let's give it up for the troops. Sure
Hey
White staff. Yeah
So around this point I started to get a little bit lost in flights of fancy
I felt like Tom had really given me an assist with that one since Owen didn't cite a source and yet I had no
Idea who Tom was I'm getting information from Tom. He was just a weirdo in this guy's videos clearly along for the long haul
Essentially he was doing exactly what I wish I was doing documenting this utter nonsense, except he believes all of it
I bet he's actually Zach. I bet he this is my deep-throat reveal
Okay
He's actually Zach from
Space Force if Tom was gonna be doing all these things that I wish I was doing I felt like I should get a better
Sense of who this guy is figure it out figure it out. Who is this guy that I find myself feeling jealous of?
Luckily the just another channel videos use his full name and I was easily able to find his YouTube channel
It turns out that Tom is basically an open mic stand-up comic and his bits are what they are
Having been through it and done hundreds and hundreds of open mics and lived through the process of trying to write and work on jokes
I really don't have an interest in shitting on comics who are on their path
I will say however that I don't expect a Netflix special anytime soon
Ah, I'm not gonna take up our time making fun of his dude stand-up
But I can't not mention this on October 29th of this year
He posted a video of himself doing stand-up as Shao Kahn from Mortal Kombat
That was like two weeks ago. He's on stage
And I'm using the term very generous. Yeah in a full costume. Uh-huh. And here is one of the bits
The COVID fatality rate is at 0.0001%
The Shao Kahn fatality rate is at 100%
You're good! You suck!
That's really not good. Nailed it. Nailed it. Landed it. That's not good
But I've seen so much worse
It's a lot of commitment to get a Shao Kahn costume. To get one Shao Kahn bit. No, I meant the costume. Yeah
No, that's what I'm saying. He got the whole costume for one Shao Kahn bit?
Oh, I mean like it's a longer video than just that joke. That's brutal. Yeah, I didn't watch all of it
There's only one Shao Kahn bit you can do and you did it
That was about where I was like, I don't care. You got the costume. Alright buddy
That is fun because I can see myself in a bar
Like the hidden shamrock or something
Drinking at the bar and it's like me and a couple other comic friends at an open mic
And he comes up and Shao Kahn and we all turn and look at him and we're like, hmm and then turn back to our drink
Look, that's exactly what that guy is. Oh boy
Doing that, huh? Over committed. Alright, this is an open mic, but okay. Probably should have worked on the writing
Try pretending you have a Shao Kahn costume
Hey, what if I were Shao Kahn?
Now here's a brilliant joke
If you have a good joke, you don't need the costume. No, you don't need a costume
If you don't have a great joke, you do need a costume. Yeah, you got to sell it and this still is not good
Anyway, that's the guy who's along for the long haul
The shrine yeah, so here we're back to Owen and in Houston and
And he tells he tells them this to give them a real sense of meaning in what they're doing
Pennsylvania and they already would have called Georgia, North Carolina, Arizona, and Nevada for Biden
So you heard Alex
Claimed that like Trump fighting is because he saw them in Austin and now Owen is trying to give the audience that same
grandiosity, yeah, yeah, they're like you you this hundred people showing up at a park in Houston is the reason that the
globalists took
electoral votes in Pennsylvania away from Biden as these men
Later in their life shall sleep wondering what will become of me shamed that they were not here with us on this
St. Crispin's Day
So Owen predicted there's gonna be millions in DC. Good luck. They saw you come out here in Houston and they have the algorithms. They've already plugged in the AI. They know that there's about to be over a million Americans in DC this weekend.
And so guess what? The corrupt mayor of DC has tried to lock the city down. When? When? I got bad news. I got bad news, Mayor Bowser. We're plumbing in a million strong and you ain't gonna stop nothing.
USA! USA! USA! USA! USA!
An unsurprisingly large percentage of Owen's speech in Houston is the crowd breaking into USA chants
Which honestly I thought were kind of satirical when I was younger, you know
I felt like a high number of the people who are doing USA chants were mocking
Yeah, like making fun of the people who would just stupidly yell USA
Isn't that, like, a long-standing trope of somebody inexplicably, like, crying,
U-S-A! U-S-A!
Yeah, I feel like they've reclaimed it.
Yeah, yeah.
All in all, this is a pretty uninspiring speech.
By about minute four, you can kind of tell that Owen doesn't really have much gas left in the tank.
Just trying to prompt chance and talking about very not true news from Pennsylvania, that's basically it.
Here's a little taste of him from about minute five, where it just seems like he's fallen back on, like,
eh, platitudes, whatever.
Many who we thought were allies will abandon us on this journey.
Many who we thought were allies will stab us in the back.
But that's okay.
Because we're all we need, we're all we got, and we're going to D.C. to let them know that we still run this country,
and it's time for politicians to hear us!
Yeah!
Woo!
Okay.
And I say unto you, Steve Bannon will deny the cox crow three times.
So at this point, the rally ends, and I start to realize, first of all, these turnouts, I mean, granted, they were the first two.
Sure.
They're not good. Houston was better. Still not good.
Could be better.
I realized that I had really overthought things when I was talking about their itinerary.
They do not need two hours in any of these seats.
No, they don't.
They're not doing anything.
Always just coming in and yelling at a bullhorn.
You guys, we can do this!
And next stop, alright, we're gonna get out of here!
You guys keep on fighting the good fighting stuff.
Yeah, I was thinking there was actually, like, you know, we're gonna coordinate, we're gonna meet up with some people.
Totally.
It's nothing.
Of course not.
It's just, ah, show up.
There's just another channel guy will go around and videotape some people.
Yeah.
There's another group that's following them called the Hippies for Trump.
Of course.
I don't know what the fuck is going on with these white dudes with dreadlocks.
It's not surprising. Not surprising.
Yeah, these seem pretty high.
Yeah, this sounds like it's a hastily slapped together publicity stunt, Dan, and I'm just starting to think that it might be.
And I love it.
So, Owen goes to bed, and we wake up, and again, I will never know if David Knight covered this on his show.
But we jump in now on the November 10th episode of the Alex Jones program, where he's bent out of shape about a globalist named Klaus Schwab.
Okay.
Coming up, globalist Klaus Schwab. World will, quote, never return to normal after COVID.
No more police, no more meat, no more travel.
You'll be lucky if you're alive. Wait till I read it.
And you're gonna enjoy it. You're gonna bow down. You love it.
Klaus Schwab is the head of the World Economic Forum, and he wrote a book earlier this year called The Great Reset.
Some of the ideas in it were further explored in that online presentation that we discussed on a past episode, so we don't need to get too deep into it now.
That's what we talked about on the video that I did with that dumb Catholic guy, yeah.
This book is not Schwab saying that you can't have meat anymore or any of that bullshit.
It's a complex examination of interconnected forces that have been disrupted or altered by the coronavirus,
and it attempts to find possible solutions, as well as guess at some trends that might be expected to be seen.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just don't care about Alex's inability to read anymore.
He's someone who can't be trusted to get the point of a young adult sci-fi novel,
so it's really crucial to understand that when it comes to something like a book like this, he truly can't handle the material.
Yeah, he doesn't realize that his teacher was not actually an alien.
In the book, the teacher was an alien, but not all teachers were aliens. That wasn't the lesson.
Don't give him goosebumps.
When Schwab discusses how things are never going back to normal again,
he's saying that the state that we were in in early 2020 is not a state that we're working to return to.
We can't be, because that's impossible.
The idea that we have some kind of quote-unquote normal isn't a real thing.
And wherever we end up, that will be the result of decisions that we're making now,
how we respond to the challenges of the pandemic, as well as various aspects of life that it affects.
Honestly, from what I've read about the book, it seems like one of the largest points he has
about how things will be different in the future is that there's going to be a trend away from globalization.
The thinking is that one of the things that makes the virus response so difficult is that everything is interconnected,
so it's very hard to slow things down in one area of life without affecting every other one,
and this you would expect to lead towards a less-connected world,
because it would give more, I don't know, ability to have one thing fall apart.
Well, I think the one thing that conservatives have absolutely dominated as far as messaging goes
is this idea that it's even acceptable to talk about an older time as being normal or static.
Like, at no point, like, oh, let's go back to when America was great or anything like that.
The 1950s were great. It wasn't fine. It was constantly in flux then, and then it changed,
and it's going to keep changing, and there's nothing you can do about it.
That's just how it is. How can we even have a conversation where people are like,
let's live like we did back then?
Yeah, so you can take this guy saying we're never going back to quote-unquote normal,
and Alex can pretend that that means that there's no police and meet and travel anymore.
And what he really means is something that the future is unpredictable,
and we have the ability to make better decisions now.
Although this is terrible, what's happening right now, disruption,
and there are occasions and opportunities for us to do things that are better.
Dumb-dumbs. We're tired of saying I told you so. Listen to us before you do the dumb thing.
Again, I stress Alex Jones is unable or unwilling to wrestle with complex ideas.
So what he does instead is that he takes his fantasies and bizarre notions,
and then he presents them as researched, studied fact.
He's dumb, but being dumb isn't something to shame someone for.
It's that he makes his living through the weaponization of his ignorance,
which is something that is just repulsive, and I cannot forgive.
So in this next clip, Alex goes out to break really weirdly.
And listen to this. Mic down for this, because I want you to pay attention.
I am dead certain that he meant to plug, and I think you'll agree with me.
This is absolutely supposed to be an ad pivot.
We're going to go to break. Now, I know you're going to do something.
We've got to stay on air now more than ever.
I'd hope Trump could win, and we could hopefully turn the tide back quicker.
But you know, Revelation, you know what's going to happen.
But we've got to build and be faithful and wake up as many as possible,
and it'll get so bad that even those that are delusional in the end will wake up
when they're being forced to be euthanized, when their children are being taken,
when half their neighbors are dead from the vaccine, and they'll just finally go,
oh, what's  and by then, it'll be drone armies, robots, nerve gas,
helicopters flying over, nerve gassing everybody, because they've got a mop-up plan.
So they're going to hit us with different waves of bio-attack over the years,
locking us down tighter each time.
And then, by the time they hit us with the real weapons,
we'll be so absolutely outnumbered, outgunned.
But it won't matter, because humans are very strong when we start to fight back.
And it's just going to be one hell of a savage war.
My God, it's just going to be  most of the people on Earth will be dead at the end of this.
Hope you all enjoy it.
World government's coming to kill you and your family.
And they are celebrating it with enjoyment.
And all the little yuppies in Austin are dancing in the streets
and running around screaming they love Satan.
And they do.
And so their God is going to hurt them so damn bad.
All right, Paul Joseph Watson's coming up on the other side.
Infowars.com. Spread those wings.
One hundred percent.
I'm certain that a couple points during that, he had meant to jump to an ad.
Totally.
And Alex was like, ah, fuck it, I'm going to ramble about everyone going to die.
There were at least four times where I guarantee I was supposed to hear,
and that's why we need your support.
And that's why we need your support.
That was supposed to be there.
Yeah, and what further reinforces that is that as soon as he comes back from break,
he does a plug.
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure that he was just like, ah, fuck, I blew it.
Anyway, Alex talks to Paul Joseph Watson, and I don't care.
I only have this clip in because it demonstrates that this is the next day,
and Alex still doesn't know that that Pfizer vaccine is a mRNA vaccine.
Cuomo and Oliver saying don't take it, it's dangerous,
because this is a classic vaccine.
I'm not saying take it, but Trump did it, so if you want it,
you're in fear to end the lockdown.
It's the excuse to end the great reset.
That's why Trump checkmated him.
But they're saying, no, don't take it now.
You've got to take Bill Gates's mRNA vaccine a hundred times more dangerous next year.
So they're completely transparent now.
Yeah.
So I guess Paul Joseph Watson doesn't know the difference either.
Who cares?
Why would they look it up?
Alex made it up on the spot.
He was just guessing.
There was a 50-50 chance maybe he was right.
Sure.
Why not ride with it?
So in this next clip, Alex discusses lying to a woman that he saw in public about masks.
That's a great idea.
And then he proceeds to gaslight the shit out of her.
Great.
By the way, people are in such fear that I ran into a lady a few weeks ago that I know,
nice lady, and she's been wearing a mask for months, and I said,
are you always going to wear that?
Because Bill Gates said he wants you to wear it for ten years.
And she started crying.
And she said, don't be mean to me.
And I said, I'm just talking to you nicely.
But people are so emotional about this.
Man, you are an asshole.
It's because everyone is so emotional.
That's why everyone always says you're attacking me and then starts crying.
It's because of them.
It can't possibly be that every time it has something to do with me.
In this sort of meant-to-be heroic story of Alex's, he seems like a giant prick.
He's a dick.
Yeah.
So, speaking of people who suck, Roger Stone shows up.
Sure.
And I will say, I'm pretty sure he's drunk.
I think he's day drunk.
I hope so, yeah.
He has a giant cigar.
Halfway through the interview, he puts on a big pair of glasses, sunglasses inside.
Yeah, no.
He's slurring a bit.
He's doing the whole thing.
He's lost his job.
He's not getting a new one from anybody.
He's got his part and Trump's gonna lose.
Might as well fucking enjoy the rest of his life, yeah.
Roger Stone is a smart political operator.
He says Trump still has a chance.
We still have a chance to stop this steal.
He joins us from Florida.
Roger, thank you so much for taking time out.
Go ahead, sir.
So, he has his plan for how this could still work out.
Uh-huh.
He's doing operation.
Hey, look.
Biden hasn't won yet.
And people who say that he has, right?
They're similar to another group that's in denial about something.
Okay, okay.
And the deeper you dig, you know that not only do they like Holocaust deniers, despicable
people, they kept insisting, no, no, there is no evidence of fraud.
They trot out Romney and Bush like anybody's gonna be impressed with that.
So, people who are not buying your arguments about election fraud are similar to Holocaust
deniers, which are repulsive people.
Tell Alex about that, because he seems to hang out with a bunch of them.
There are a lot of people who deny the Holocaust, but they're denying it in a good way.
Not like this election denial.
I don't know if there's any single source of entertainment that I've viewed in my life
that had more Holocaust deniers on it than in Four Wars.
Cheers?
I'm not sure about the percentage, but I would say if you exclude the History Channel,
because they have all those documentaries.
They're all Nazis out there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's so them, though.
Like, their language is always the fucking most disgusting they can possibly think.
And it goes both ways, too.
It's like Mitch McConnell would reference Martin Luther King Jr. in a speech about how
he's unveiling a bill to bring back slavery.
Like, that's how awful they really are.
You're not wrong.
So in this next clip, Roger kind of rewrites the party swap from the 60s.
I don't think he's making a whole lot of sense.
The South and the Deep South have been a bedrock of support for Christian conservative values.
They used to be democratic in the old days until conservative Democrats saw the error
of the left wing, now communist, infiltrated Democratic Party and their other corporate
handlers.
And they had already moved to Ronald Reagan, Richard Nixon, Donald Trump in droves.
Also, you have a great southern military tradition here.
It goes all the way back.
We have a great southern military tradition.
It goes all the way back to the beginning of the United States.
We're huge military people here in the South.
No idea why I'm bringing that up right now.
Just tossing that out there.
This is just indicative of that very standard sort of belief in the anti-communist wings
of the right wing sphere, that is, these civil rights movements were really just communist
nonsense.
For Roger Stone, one of the people who helped create the southern strategy, built entirely
on whipping people up about race, for him to be like, they saw the error of their ways.
Fuck you, Roger Stone.
So Roger, he has his plan.
There's a narrow way to victory, and he hints that it has something to do with electors
or something.
Sure.
I don't think patriots understand that the last chain in this process is the legislature
certifying who the electors who will go to the electoral college are under the US constitutional
system.
But they are, in fact, they are who we're shooting for, if you understand.
Yes, sir.
Not interrupting, because I want you to get it all out.
I mean, yes, the electors are-
Eating a sandwich.
What his argument is, I think, is that we can use these legislatures to force electors
that will vote for Trump, even when they're supposed to be pledged to Biden.
They're faithless electors and all that stuff.
I'm furiously disgusted with this.
You cannot spend a year telling me that this is life or death and we're fighting the
devil and then be like, well, if we can use the vagaries of the fucking constitution to
trick our way into the presidency.
No, no, no, no.
You can't like then be like, no, no, no.
Oh, you didn't read us his rights before he got elected president.
And so now we're like, no, you don't get a 12 hour fucking Cinderella solution to
this fucking problem, okay?
Not when it's the devil.
Yeah.
So Roger, I will say there's reasons not to take him too seriously.
Sure.
And this is definitely one of them.
You have a whole second level here where Sidney Powell and Tom Fitton have correctly talked
about the hammer, a very invasives federal essentially surveillance abuse which had corrupted
and been able to manipulate votes through a scorecard program that was specifically
designed to work through the back doors of the state.
Roger's on some Dennis Montgomery shit.
He's on the hammer and scorecard stuff.
I think the worst part of that is he's telling it like he half remembers what it's supposed
to be about.
I think he's fucked up.
Yeah.
And then he's just filling in the blanks where he doesn't remember this stuff.
Like he doesn't know what it even is.
I don't think he cares.
He doesn't know that it's supposed to be.
Yeah.
He's like, and then they change votes with it and it gets, it's invasives.
It's an invasives thing.
Yeah.
So he's promoting the stop the steal stuff and it's like, you're involved.
I know you're involved.
It's the same name.
It's you.
It's a bunch of your associates.
You own the domain.
I don't know what's going on here.
You're making some money off this somehow.
I'm sure of it.
Totally.
Um, but anyway, this is my favorite.
This is such good comedy.
Uh, I could not have written this myself.
Okay.
The universe had to create this for me.
Uh, this is Alex's last question for Roger.
That's right.
I have one more question.
Roger.
What does Trump need to do?
Warning.
If you're drowning in debt, you can't afford.
I got one last question for you.
What is Trump?
I'm getting the light.
I'm sorry.
What does Trump need to do?
Every time.
Imagine that Alex, like, every time, imagine that what he's saying is true and that world
leaders listen to his show.
Yeah.
Alex is talking to Roger Stone.
Trump is watching.
What's, what's the last thing I need to know?
What does he have to call into the show to get the rest of it?
And Alex is going to be taking a nap, so he's not going to be able to get through to him.
That's why he always misses the part that he wants to hear.
And Alex is just done with the show, so he's napping and Trump can't get him.
Oh man.
That's brutal.
Yeah.
So Roger's gone.
Uh, and uh, if you, yeah.
Jordan.
Yes.
I mean, you're not in a city where you could.
That's true.
If you were in one of the cities along the route or near the caravan, if you don't join,
you're crazy.
That's true.
I was going to be in Tallahassee tonight about eight o'clock.
That's the real rallying point.
We're counting on folks.
We went through Florida.
You know, Florida loves liberty, gas up the car, drive up the next few days with us, stay
in DC for this event.
If you don't, you're crazy because this is all about visuals and it's all about going
up there and it's all about standing for freedom.
So we'll see you in DC separately.
We are running the emergency sale.
It's all about visuals.
Sure.
That's very clear.
Yeah.
We know.
So, uh, Owen is back on now and, uh, he'd like to give a little interview from the road.
Sure.
He's in a van, a moving van.
Okay.
Uh, he describes kind of what's going on and I'm like, I don't understand how this is any
different than a coup.
What you're describing is a coup.
Okay.
So you've had Donald Trump, the president of the United States declare he's won.
You've now had essentially for all intensive purposes, Mike Pompeo, the secretary of defense
state claim he's won and you have about 70 million Americans, I think millions of which
could be in DC this weekend claiming Trump won.
Right.
So you have Trump declaring himself the winner of an election that, uh, the sort of consensus
is that he didn't win.
Sure.
You have his secretary of state, uh, lackey saying, eh, he won.
Right.
And then you also have large groups of supporters who are very angry, right.
Who are saying that he, none of that proves that he won.
All of those things are exactly what you would expect in the case of like someone who lost
claiming that they won.
Right.
But.
It's a sting operation.
Hey.
Come on.
It might, it's the, it might be, it might not be, who knows, they've forgotten about
that now.
I mean, it's literally a group of people getting in the car, trying to grab more and more supporters
in order to essentially put siege to the white house until they fucking take over the country.
With bull horns.
Yes.
My favorite thing.
I know that I said that, uh, that last clip with Roger, where it got cut off.
Sure.
Favorite thing.
This is probably the finest moment.
Maybe of this whole episode.
Okay.
It's possible.
All right.
So Owen is just complaining about voter fraud and what have you.
And then this happens.
We'll say, wait a second.
This isn't right.
They see them counting in Pennsylvania and.
Well, we lost Owen decided to buy into a delicious, cheesy hamburger.
By the way, I've never been into a hamburger.
It tastes so good, but all this news has just been broken.
What is this?
This happens a lot.
I mean, this happens a lot, but this is, I think the first time or maybe it's one of
the few times that Alex has been forced to like, actually just be like, I was eating
a cheeseburger.
I'm sorry, guys.
No, a cheesy hamburger.
Thank you.
Yeah.
He would never eat a cheeseburger.
He simply likes his hamburgers cheesy.
Yeah.
He's interviewing Owen.
Feed goes out.
Ah, shit.
Ah, you caught me.
Yup.
I got to own up to it this time.
Nom, nom, nom, nom, nom.
You know, big old cheeseburger, cheesy hamburger.
But his defense for it is like, honestly, this is the best cheeseburger I've ever eaten.
So frankly, I'm doing you guys a favor by eating this cheeseburger.
Someone's got to do it.
Somebody has to.
It's too good.
Yeah.
So now Stuart Rhodes shows up.
Oh, great.
And he thinks that what needs to happen is that Trump's got to declassify everything.
Ooh, that'd be fun.
Well, I think he's on the verge of doing what I've been calling on President Trump to do
for at least six months, which is to classify all the dirty secrets and throw them out in
the street.
That's why it's awesome to see Don Jr. saying that just the other day.
He posted on Twitter, declassify everything.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I should have agreed.
You've been beating the drum for months.
Weaponize this scene before the election, declassify it, destroy Brennan as a foreign
agent, destroy Hunter, destroy Biden now, and Trump notes this has only moved.
And that's why they're now calling for a coup to remove Trump because he's finally moving
towards victory.
Continue.
So I guess the idea is that what they now want is for Trump to prove all their conspiracies
for them.
Yeah.
Which I'm sure he's going to do.
I personally would love it if he just declassified all kinds of shit.
That of all the things that he could do as a spite move on his way out of office, that's
the one I'm most in favor of.
As long as it wasn't like really very strategically targeted, like if it were like alien shit
or whatever, you know, like just something that like...
Start going down the hill, Kennedy, the whole thing.
Yeah, absolutely.
Let the chips fall where they may.
Fidel Castro was actually a CIA agent the whole time.
I want it all.
The Roger Stone files.
Exactly.
That one's probably not coming out.
So Stuart Rhodes says this, and I feel like I'll like it, but my only response to this
is that's not cool.
Is we have men already stationed outside DC as a nuclear option in case they attempt to
remove the president illegally, we will step in and stop it.
And we're going to be there to also help secure the coming rally this Saturday and your caravan
coming in.
So I've got good men on the ground already.
We've been...
Did a lead recon there last week and we're sorting out where we're going to be staging
and we'll be there.
We'll be inside DC, we'll also be on the outside of DC armed prepared to go in if the president
calls us out.
Stuart, can you not feel history happening right now?
I mean, it's happening right now.
Hoo boy.
Yeah, that's not good.
No, that's really fucked up.
Yeah.
I, Stuart Rhodes, leader of the Oath Keepers, have an army of armed men ready.
Hoo boy.
Yeah.
I'm going to be honest, it sounds, uh, sounds real blustery.
Yeah, a little bit.
I'm going to go with he's cosplaying on this one.
Yeah, most likely, but it's such a scary prospect.
Yeah, totally.
I still feel the need to take him a little seriously.
Yeah, no, cos people, cosplayers with giant heavy swords, even if they're heavy, they
can still hurt somebody.
It makes me uncomfortable.
Fair enough.
They don't have guns.
Guns are worse.
These guys do have guns.
They have guns and they're worse.
So the thing that I think is really funny about this interview is that Owen earlier
said that Bowser, Mayor Bowser, was trying to keep him out of DC, and apparently that
was in reference to, like, COVID restrictions and stuff.
Yeah, you have to quarantine maybe?
Yeah, yeah.
And in Stuart Rhodes' interviews, like, nah, we've had guys there a while, like, you know,
I don't have to do shit.
Okay, great.
Great.
So that got punctured.
That entire narrative.
I do appreciate that.
Yeah.
So now we're done with the 10th.
The show itself, again, not very good.
Alex's show is not satisfying in many ways.
There's still little things that come up.
Alex eating a cheeseburger, Roger Stone probably drunk doing an interview.
Did he make a, when he was eating the cheeseburger and got caught, did he, like, make a face
to the camera?
Did he mug to the camera with, like, a little...
Unfortunately, there isn't video of him eating the cheeseburger.
Oh, that's so disappointing.
But there is, um, just, like, it's Owen's shot, and then the camera goes out, and then
a big Sony logo pops up.
It's, uh, not great.
The three-dimensional pipes.
Yeah.
So we pick up with Owen on the road, and he's on his way to Baton Rouge.
Sure.
And that means red stick in French.
Okay.
Uh, Baton Rouge, Louisiana.
Owen arrives.
Okay.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, Owen Schroyer here from Infowars.com.
Stop the steel caravan in Baton Rouge, Louisiana.
This is our first stop of the day before we get to Tallahassee, Florida, this evening
where we're expecting a bunch of people, and so I'm not sure where, uh, our people may
be out here because there is no real parking lot for us to station, and they have kind
of the Capitol grounds shut down, so we're gonna drive around a little bit and see if
we've got a caravan that's looking to join us out here.
Otherwise, we're gonna have to just pick a parking lot.
Owen can't find his people, which is a bad sign.
We didn't plan any of this.
No.
That's what he should be saying.
These are things that all went wrong logistically because we were very confident that we had
planned everything, but we realized just now, oh, that's right, we're very dumb.
An important part of meetups is where.
Where is the first question, usually, that you want to take care of.
You can't text anyone.
There's no Google Maps.
Just we're in a parking lot.
So Owen finds the folks, and I would say that his response is tepid.
Hello, Baton Rouge.
Info Wars is in the house!
That's a solid clap.
The globalists thought that they destroyed America, but we're not dead yet!
From what I can tell, there was a turnout of about 25 in Baton Rouge for Owen's arrival.
But only one of them had hands with which to clap?
The other ones were holding like Gadsden flags and shit.
Owen's speech and appearance in Baton Rouge is incredibly boring, so I checked in on the
coverage on the Just Another Channel.
It was useless, too.
It was just that Tom guy doing a bad Cajun impression.
Of course.
I would say that this stop on the convoy was a waste of time for both us and Owen.
It was a zero.
But while he's there, Owen bangs the gong that is labeled Biden lost Pennsylvania.
I think we've got enough court cases, enough wins coming.
Did you see they already took Pennsylvania from Biden?
This is probably not a good question to ask, because I'm sure that they feel this way all
the time, but how dumb must Democrats feel when they celebrated that Biden won and now
he didn't win?
How dumb do you think they feel?
But how dumb do they feel?
They probably don't feel that dumb.
They voted for him in the first place.
So yeah, I'm not sure if they can really sense their dumbness there.
They like their feelings.
You said this was a sting operation, and now you're telling me that I should feel dumb?
Just a couple days ago, you reported that this election was a fake election, it was
a sting.
A huge scoop.
Yeah.
Strange how I feel stupid about that.
I feel real dumb, Dan.
So Owen talks to the people who are there, and one guy comes up and he says he has a
good idea.
We had a million people in DC and a million people all across this country getting up
on freeways, putting the banners over it, having 10,000 people see that every hour.
We don't need the media.
We don't need social media.
We can do this ourselves.
This is a multi-front battle.
If you're not going to DC, you pick a bridge, you get on it, you do it, you do it every
day.
That's what's got to be done.
There you go.
We are the media now.
We've taken the bridges.
Uh oh.
They got the bridges.
Wait until someone tells them about town criers.
We're screwed.
If they've got, can they put like little paper cups inside of the fence on bridges to kind
of spell out a message to us?
Wait for them to learn about pamphlets.
Yeah.
They're the media now.
They got bridges.
All right.
So Alex is-
I got a Shao Kahn joke for you.
Oh boy.
Okay.
Let me see if I got, I can get this one right.
Something something Goro.
No, no, no.
Biden's victory is brutal, but the turnout at these rallies is a brutality.
As good as that other dude's.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
Owen is acting like he just had a bae-ballity.
That wasn't even a joke.
No.
This was a statement.
Alex is there in spirit in this Baton Rouge rally and Owen asks the audience for a message
to Alex.
Just say something to Alex Jones, because I'll tell you, you know, I've worked with
Alex for a long time and he's really tied into this thing.
It's hard to even understand or comprehend how tied into it he is.
I see the torment he goes through.
So just give him a little word of encouragement as we see America through this final battle
to save our Republic, guys.
Just tell-
The hippies for Trump loves Alex Jones.
So those are the hippies for Trump who've been along for this whole tour.
We prefer sound bites.
Your words are going on too long.
So here's here's another.
This was a fun little message to Alex from the audience.
We love you, Alex, we don't need to fact check you like Joe Rogan did.
You didn't even know you had the documents, you know?
You are the John the Baptist of this movement.
You were laughing over another guy saying you're the John the Baptist of this movement.
Oh, no.
Oh, boy.
Oh, yeah.
There's nothing funnier than we don't need to fact check you like Joe Rogan.
We don't need to fact check you like Joe Rogan.
Oh, such a harsh fact checker that Joe Rogan was.
And that's kind of the problem with like doing it halfway is because then you have the appearance
of Alex coming out of that unscathed and it's like, oh, well, Joe did his best.
He did.
He gave he threw everything against the wall and Alex stayed standing and that is a really
bad optical thing to give Alex.
Now, I hate to say this, but this next clip is probably going to piss you off.
Sure.
This is probably I mean, because you're a lib, you know, this is really probably going
to be like...
Is it another Shao Kahn joke?
No, but it's going to be like, you're going to just the hair on the back of your neck
is going to stand up.
I'm going to punch my wall.
Probably.
Okay.
Absolutely.
All right, guys.
You want to upset some liberals that are watching this right now?
Oh, yeah.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America.
So they recite the pledge and then attempt to anger the libs.
Oh, guys, guys.
It's funny when they don't actually know or meet any libs.
Sure.
This weird like created version of the libs is being like, oh, they're so terrified of
the Pledge of Allegiance.
They respond to the pledge like vampires do to garbage.
Yeah.
Is that what's going on?
Who are you people?
Yeah.
We're like, they just can't get this like, we're just like you, man.
Nobody's mad at the Pledge of Allegiance.
It's just boring.
Probably unsurprisingly, though, this does end in a prayer.
We pray right now, God, we pray that you hear this prayer, that you raise up Donald Trump
to continue to be our king, God.
We're standing in unity right now.
We come together in the name of Jesus Christ, God.
Father, we pray that you come against all demonic attack.
We're praying for Trump to remain king.
Good.
Good stuff.
Hi, this is me, God.
I would choose someone who can stand better.
So the turnout in Tallahassee, which is the next stop on the tour, it doesn't appear to
be much better than the previous events, but again, it's nighttime, so it'd be pretty difficult
to gauge the exact numbers.
I would say that there, you know, it could be absolutely, I would be shocked if there
were 200 people there.
That is kind of the ceiling I would go to.
It's a great turnout for an indie band, but it's a terrible turnout for Info Wars.
Some of the individual closeup shots don't look too bad, but the people are packed in
pretty close, and also, if you watch the video, you're going to notice something glaring,
and that is that literally no one's wearing a mask.
That's something that our friend Tom is actually pretty stoked about.
This is Trump country here.
It's great to come to Florida, no mask mandate, none of that bullshit, it feels like freedom.
It's a totally change of energy.
You go into gas station, go into a restaurant, go into Walmart, nobody says nothing.
That's right.
Absolutely unrelated, Florida is the state with the third highest number of COVID-19
cases and the fourth highest death count.
It's like if Typhoid Mary was actually a political movement.
If you're Owen, you could probably feel a little bit better about your arrival in Tallahassee,
but not because it's amazing, but because the other events were so bad, they were so
dismal, that this is kind of like, okay, you have some stuff you can work with here, it's
still way less than it should be if all the other things about what you do, you say about
what you do are accurate, but fine.
I'm not too mad.
It looked like people were having a good time in Tallahassee.
So they go to bed and we wake up and November 11th comes along.
And again, I don't know if David and I covered any of this.
I'll never know.
Okay, fair.
We get to Alex's show and I was expecting like some big news from the road.
Totally.
David, we get something altogether different.
And Steve Pacenik's coming on.
Get the fuck out.
He's the guy that said two weeks ago on the show, they were going to fire the Secretary
of Defense and they have the CIA and others.
Did you hear they all got fired?
Steve is coming on.
He said two days ago it was a STIG operation.
I don't care what he said two weeks ago, maybe he got something right two days ago.
He said this whole election was one big STIG operation.
And David Knight said he's a CIA operator.
You can't walk away from that.
He was there to trap you.
Why are you having him back on?
Who are you people?
Do you talk?
This is outrageous.
Send a text message from time to time.
I want to throw something.
I thought for sure Steve would be on time out.
Forever.
Yeah.
Turns out you can fuck over Owen.
It's not that big of a deal.
You can say anything on War Room because no one's watching.
Yeah, I think it's such a small audience that there aren't really any stakes to it.
And that's why David Knight can choose to have Steve on or not because he has a tiny
audience to it.
It doesn't matter.
And he can shit all over Owen because who gives a shit anyways.
So Alex gets caught up talking about how Black Lives Matter or Aunt Jemima, and it's pretty
offensive.
Well, well, you're not.
So when you see Black Lives Matter and they all look like Aunt Jemima, they are folks,
they are literally Marxist, Leninist, Satan worshipers who follow Mao Tse Tung and say
they hate men's very existence and the only good man is a castrated man.
And their main sacrament is no families, for black people especially, and that black men
have their testicles removed.
I'm not making it up.
Because, see, they can't outright kill all the black men so they just cut their balls
off.
All right, when we get back, I'm going to break all of this down for you.
He doesn't.
He doesn't end up breaking.
Was that something that the syrup was pro that we weren't aware of?
I don't know.
Okay.
I think this is all just weird racism.
Weird racism.
Yeah, I think that's what's going on there.
So in this next clip, Alex, I gotta say, in terms of satire, he's not good at it.
In terms of these set pieces that he does, not good.
No.
This is about as well done as a joke has ever been on his show.
Wow.
This is where he declares himself president.
Is this a Shao Kahn joke?
No.
Oh.
He declares himself president.
Okay.
And I think, I feel like this was all right.
While you're really freaked out that you've seen Joe Biden announcing himself as the president-elect
and having the nerve to put up a big sign behind him saying it, and the whole media
and even Fox News announcing it, when under the law, it's a fraud.
But that's what these scammers are trying to do because their past hoaxes have failed.
But I've got some good news for you.
Ladies and gentlemen, the 46th president of the United States.
That's right.
Here we are, ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you.
It's not Donald John Trump.
He was a 44th president.
God rest his name and the annals of history.
It's not Joe Biden, the Chinese communist globalist agent.
No.
All you've got to do is be a media outlet and then announce that you are allowed to
announce the winner and that no one else is.
And then you just announce whoever you want is the president-elect.
And so you just have a dark blue background with the presidential seal on it and some
white font.
And you are the president-elect, 46th president of the United States, Alexander Emmerich Jones
of Texas.
Before you say anything, hearing that a second time, I take it back.
That wasn't good.
No.
Went too long.
Yup.
Overexplained the joke.
Totally.
As usual.
You know what I was remembering that made me think it was good?
It was the lead-in.
Yeah.
The lead-in was all right.
No.
Because it was serious.
And then it flipped to being a joke.
The music cue was at the right time.
It was good.
Yeah.
That was what tricked me into forgetting that it went way too fucking long.
The window dressing at the start kind of gives you a little, but, oh boy.
That's such a terrible, like, okay, we've announced that I'm the president and you know
that because I've simulated what a normal news outlet would look like.
And you know that you can do this because there's a blue background and on top of the
blue background there's a logo and in front of the logo there's a flag and in front of
the flag there's an eagle.
And oh, the music's ended.
Are you guys like this joke?
Yeah.
The music's ended.
Is this joke really working for you?
This is SNL, right?
Yeah.
I would say that it's a rare day in Austin when the cues at InfoWars work and that might
have blinded me.
That's true.
And it has some problems with the voter fraud and people not believing their stories.
Sure.
They had all these whistleblowers come out from the USPS about post-dating ballots after
the election saying that they were from before the election.
My brother-in-law, who I wouldn't even say is right-wing or left-wing, he's more pragmatic,
he was fighting mad the day after the election watching somebody postmark 50 of them or so,
working with the post office.
I don't care about Alex's dumb brother-in-law, however I do want to touch on this whistleblower
from the USPS that Alex is referring to.
This is the subject of Project Veritas's latest pile of shit video, a guy named Richard Hopkins.
Hopkins claimed that he was instructed by his postmaster in Pennsylvania to backdate
ballots that came in after the election.
His testimony has been used by many in far more official avenues to claim there's solid
evidence that illegal ballots were coming in.
However, the Inspector General of the USPS spoke to Hopkins, and Hopkins told them that
quote, the allegations were not true and he signed an affidavit recanting his claims.
Project Veritas started a GoFundMe and quickly raised over $130,000 for Hopkins, even though
he's clearly making shit up to be used as the basis for right-wing, dictatorship-enabling
propaganda.
Of course, Veritas can claim that he was coerced into recanting his story and he said that
he didn't.
And then this could just be another one of those things that's totally believed by the
dumb-dumb audience, but there's no real evidence at all, and the people involved are seemingly
acting in ways that are exactly what you would do if you want to keep a grift going, but
also want to cover your ass from legal exposure.
Sad stuff all around.
Hi, uh, Mr. Hopkins, come on in here.
I just want to talk to you about voter fraud and the alleged abuse that you witnessed.
I didn't say shit!
Oh, why didn't you say shit?
Is it because you could be hit with a federal crime perhaps?
I'd like to recant.
You'd like to recant that?
Was that coercion or just you realizing there are consequences?
I'd like to avoid all consequences, now flash forward to a little later, I didn't recant
anything!
I don't remember recanting anything, but I sound that way.
Please give me my GoFundMe money.
No kidding.
Oh boy.
I would not be surprised if that GoFundMe gets frozen.
Anyway, Steve Pachannik comes in and he's there to complain about John Brennan.
So where do you want to start, Dr. Steve Pachannik?
Let's start with the fact, this is very unusual what I just heard Brennan do.
I mean, it was one of the stupidest interviews he's ever done.
Did he claim that the election was a sting?
That's a pretty stupid interview.
That's a dumb interview.
I would feel real stupid if I gave an interview where I said that.
No, he doesn't say that.
He's, uh, Brennan was talking about how like, you got to get Trump out of there.
Like he, he's a caged lion, basically, he's a cornered lion.
You don't know what he's going to do during this lame duck period.
So he was just sort of, uh, you know, it's close to anything that Alex says that is pretty
close.
You know, like in terms of the globalists are encouraging the 25th amendment.
Yeah, John Brennan was.
I am too.
Yeah, absolutely.
That does not mean that there is a massive elaborate conspiracy to trick Trump into getting
hit with the 25th amendment.
This was just a commentator saying on public television, uh, hey, uh, Trump's a fucked
up dude.
We've learned he's a fucked up dude.
Hey guys, uh, I don't know if you've been alive for the past four years or if you have
ever read any history, but you realize that wannabe dictators don't leave on their own
accord, right?
It generally does not happen.
You have to remove them.
It seems, uh, it seems like, you know, and, and like even assuming that everything goes
fine in January, like there's a lot of damage that can be done before that.
He's got to go.
I'm not, I'm not saying that I a hundred percent agree with that just based on like how much
more trouble that could cause and the fact that January is coming.
Uh, but I understand, uh, Brennan's perspective.
Like I don't, I don't know.
Anyway, Steve is somebody who Alex says has been in the CIA.
Uh, Steve would beg to differ.
Now although I was accused of being a shill for the CIA, I've never been in the CIA.
Accused by whom?
Uh, maybe an enforced employee named David Knight.
Uh, yeah.
So Alex has said many, many times that Steve was in the CIA.
I guess Steve is not.
If I were Alex and I were interviewing him, I'd be like, wait, you've told me that you
were a lot for years.
So Steve was on the war room with Owen on the fifth, I believe.
And he said that the whole election was a sting, they watermark these ballots and it's
all like, ha ha.
They played into our hands.
Something that if you were to claim and would later discover was completely false, dumb
information, it would haunt you for the rest of your career and you would never be able
to get a job and let alone be some sort of presenter on the show again so soon.
Well there's this technique called hand waving.
Ooh, I like hand waving.
Here's Steve's attempt at that.
Trump is very much in control.
This is what I said before.
This is Sun Tzu.
He's watching the game, manipulating it, and you don't see it.
I told you we set it up, whether you believe in the watermarks and that, that's not relevant.
It is.
It is not relevant.
It's very relevant.
It is suddenly from, from we know where every single ballot on the planet is to it's not
really important.
Yeah, believe it or not.
It's no big deal.
Come on.
I'm not a CIA guy.
It's a minor detail.
It's one of those things.
Whether or not this election was a set up operation, minor detail, minor detail, whatever.
What a fucking, what a dick.
Pretty amazing.
It's unfair.
So Steve has a belief that Trump is going to win the electoral college.
Sure.
Tell people your, your, your, your weather forecast.
Rain.
What I said years ago on your show, we did a sting operation on Hillary Clinton.
She didn't succeed.
We allowing Biden to be president for 40 or 60 days.
And it's over December 14th, it will be over.
The electoral college will declare that Trump won.
Trump will come back in and this is a period of turbulence that would be expected in admitting
he's getting ready with riot police to shoot looters.
Well, Jesus, we got a pretty solid prediction there.
We can check back on that.
December 14th, huh?
Yep.
We'll see about that.
Well, I will.
I do like that.
I think they're very kind.
I think that's like, is that their version of a make a wish?
Like we're going to let him be president for 40 to 60 days.
We're going to give him that fun.
And then obviously we're going to do a coup and have to kill him, but he's going to have
a really good, nice time.
So Steve's making some specific predictions and also hand-waving away the ludicrous nonsense
that he said.
If you think about the watermarks too hard, you're, it's a minor detail.
Now I will say that this next clip, I've never agreed with him more.
You know, remember we're an alternative media.
There's no reason for anybody to believe me or believe you.
Totally agree.
Totally.
100%.
Totally agree.
Agree.
There is no reason for anyone to believe you.
I would argue.
There are many reasons for the opposite.
Yeah.
I would say that in the, in the pro con column, you got zero pros.
The interview ends pretty uneventfully, which I was kind of disappointed by.
And uh, I feel very confused, uh, betrayed, flummoxed, I can come up with more words if
you like, but I don't have my thesaurus handy.
Maybe that's a more fitting punishment for Steve is to take away his big swings.
Well, I mean, this is a pretty small swing except for him saying that, you know, like
we are allowing Biden to be, well sure, sure.
Yeah.
That's not an interesting swing.
No, no, no.
Yeah.
It's very close to the boring middle of info wars.
And I got kind of excited when this happened.
Steve, we really appreciate you.
Thank you for all the time.
Thank you.
And God bless.
You know what?
I just, I kind of did a false start there, a false ending.
Come back.
I got one more question for you.
Then phone calls.
And then we got Jay Dyer taking over.
I got a serious question because everybody's talking about election fraud and watermarks.
And I know those exist, the Secret Service 30 years ago had it in printer ink and I know
all that stuff.
So that's a real thing.
I wanted to get your take on that.
Try to have a Steve Pagenik.
He does not.
Bottom of the ninth, two outs.
Is Steve Pagenik going to get one more chance to swing the bat, Dan?
He does not.
Oh, damn it.
I thought he had one big swing left in him.
He doesn't even really ask the question directly at all.
They just want to talk about how great it is that Trump's firing people even though
he just lost the election.
Sure, sure, sure.
Trump is just axing all these people at the Pentagon that are civilians and bringing in
all these war heroes right now.
And again, I see the pucker factor in MSM.
They are visibly scared.
I've got videos of them learning that Trump's winning states are like cussing on air and
panicking.
I mean, I just want to see more of this because it's our country.
I don't like authoritarianism.
I don't like military doing domestic actions unless a military and a foreign power is attacking
me that I want the military in there and I cheer it on.
I mean, we didn't bring ourselves to this point.
The globalists did.
I just smell their destruction.
I smell blood right now.
No.
Well, you're a good bloodhound.
I mean, you're Sherlock Holmes in that way.
I don't mean it facetiously.
Holy shit.
Wow.
Yeah.
Wow, Stevie Peas.
That's our biggest swing of the night.
No, this is.
I will guarantee you my career and my future, Trump will be the next president of the United
States for the next eight years.
Not only four years, it will be eight years.
All right, Steve.
All right.
He hit a line drive single.
He's guaranteed on his career that Trump will serve the next eight years.
Great.
Cool.
All right.
I'm not a fan of authoritarianism, but I do have a guest on who's saying that Trump is
going to destroy term limits, so I just want you guys to know.
And have lost this election.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Or something.
Anyway, this brings us to the end of our episode, and we'll pick things up on Monday with what
happened in the evening.
I gotta know.
We'll find out what happened in South Carolina, Atlanta.
Yeah.
I guess North Carolina after that.
Virginia.
This is why we need somebody, like this needs to be documented 24 hours, because we've already
seen so many stupid things that you know had very interesting and angry conversations.
I almost guarantee most of them didn't.
I bet it was incredibly boring.
Really?
There's no way that they were like, oh, we can't do this rally here, and then they had
a furious argument together?
No, I'm sure Owen would be like, okay, sir, and then, you know.
That's fair.
I would bet if you wired their car and you had the actual footage, it would just be hours
of them singing 99 bottles of beer on the wall.
All right, who else has a Shao Kahn joke?
Who's up?
Did you see Rand Paul's Twitter?
Guh.
Yeah.
You know, no one can get in this bus.
It's Outworld.
That guy wasn't on the bus.
He was along with the other independent reporter.
Oh, okay.
All right, all right, okay.
But yeah.
I'm excited to see what happens, because I do think that there's a tiny bit of momentum.
If you look at the Tallahassee turnout, it was definitely better, and I think that they
do better at night, also, so I think they should learn their lesson from that.
Don't do daytime rallies anymore.
People still work, I guess.
I'm excited to see if it keeps growing a little bit, although I hope it doesn't, I mean.
That could be a...
I've done too many tours where it's like, you have a couple first bad shows, and then
your third show, you're like, oh shit, there's 70 people there, this is a good turnout, everybody
was great, we partied afterwards, this whole thing is turning around, and then your next
show, there's two people from fucking Finland, Dan, Finland!
They were from Finland!
How am I supposed to do shitty jokes to two people from Finland?
Probably tough to find common points of awareness.
It wasn't good.
I don't know, I'm interested to see, I would like to, I don't know what I would like.
I mean, I just want this to end without any violence or anything.
Yeah, me too.
That's really all that I'm particularly invested in.
If this story ends up with this being a complete dud, and like, embarrassing, awful, that'll
be pretty funny.
If this ends up growing and growing to the point where they get to DC and there's a lot
of people, and it still just is a rally, that's fine too, that's a story, that's an interesting
story.
They had humble beginnings.
They did!
A couple people in Austin.
Almost make me believe that Owen's speeches did inspire people.
No, certainly not.
Very much not.
Maybe other people's social media posts.
I, you know, I could see that as a story and I'd be fine with that too.
Oath keepers shooting some people is not the story that I want to see.
As long as we can avoid that, I think we can have a lot of fun with the Dan's Caravanity
Project.
Fairytale ending.
Fairytale ending, alright.
We have every policy wonk in DC show up and surround their rally, all of them holding
their phones, and when the rally is sad and everybody kind of slinks away, they all, I'm
sure, simultaneously press the button on their phones, and 200 phones scream out, whoa, just
like that.
That's what I want.
Or I'll play, I'm a policy wonk.
Yeah.
Do do do do do.
Yeah, so I mean, we'll see what happens.
I'm thrilled that we were able to do this, because this could not wait.
And there's just too much material for one episode.
So I, you know, there was a part of me that thought like, hey, we could just leave it
all for Monday, but then maybe we wouldn't have gotten that weird appearance from Roger
Stone.
Gotta get Roger on there.
Steve Pajanik comes back and pretends, hey, it's no big deal, I said it was a stick.
Unfair.
Unfair that that's how you can operate in the real world.
But we will be back, Jordan.
Indeed we will.
Until then, we have a website.
We do have a website, it's knowledgefight.com.
Yep, we're on Twitter.
We are on Twitter, it's at knowledgefight.net, go to bed, Jordan.
Yes, we are on Facebook.
Indeed we are, we'd like to download iTunes review, and if you could, please find a local
charity or bail fund in your area to help out people doing God's work.
Yeah, we'll be back, but until then, I'm Neo, I'm Leo, I'm DZXClark, I'm Daryl Rundis,
I only do standup in a Shao Kahn outfit.
Or Goro.
Or maybe Baraka.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan, I love your work.
I love you.