N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am SWEATING
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledge fight
knowledge fight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
saying we are the bad guys
knowledge fight
Dan and Jordan, knowledge fight
Riddle her, riddle her, riddle her
I need, I need money
Andy and Kansas, Andy and, Andy and
Stop it, Andy and, Andy and Kansas
Andy and, Andy and, it's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding
Hello Alex, I'm a 15-color, I'm a huge fan
I love your work
knowledgefight
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're couple dudes, like to sit around, drink novelty beverages
and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are Dan
Jordan
Dan!
Jordan!
Quick question for you
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today Jordan is very simple
Vinegar
Vinegar?
Yep
Just vinegar?
Moving on
Yep
End of podcast
I believe that this segment is called bright spots
not explain your bright spots
That's fair
I've been looking for salad dressing replacements
I'm trying to eat a little bit better
and I accidentally stumbled upon some interesting vinegars
like a strawberry rosé vinegar
Interesting
And it's fantastic
I will agree that is an interesting vinegar
Yeah
Had that on a salad, had it on some chicken
and now I've decided that I'm going to explore the wonderful world of vinegar
Yeah, why not?
I didn't realize that there was such a diverse world of weird vinegar products
I thought it was just vinegar
Can you...
Yeah that makes sense though
Yeah
Vinegar isn't like ketchup, it's not just like a thing
No, but there are also a bunch of different ketchups
Yeah, but there's ketchup
Right
You know?
Sure
You know what I'm saying?
Not really
Okay, fair enough
There's champagne vinegar in the cabinet that I'm excited to break into
I've not tried that yet
And then what did I order?
I ordered one online that's a chamomile tea vinegar
I'm never not going to enjoy your willingness to put both feet in the pond
before you have any idea how deep it is
The pond is full of vinegar
Yeah
I enjoy it, we'll see what happens
It's the vinegar week
Yeah
What about you?
We're going to do 500 vinegars this week
No we're not
And we'll get back to the seltzers here soon enough
Sure, sure
My Bright Spot, Dan, is unfortunately also food related
But it is also a gratitude towards our listeners related
Oh that's nice
I got that peanut butter for our 500th episode
The fog, something in fog
Fit in fog I think
Fit in fog, yeah
I keep saying Phineas in fog but I think that's a Nickelodeon or two
That's something else, that's Phineas and Ferb I think
Yeah something like that
And it is excellent
I bet
It is spectacular
It's spec-tacular
There we go, nicely done
Thanks
No it's just that like, oh shit I forgot what it tastes like when it's made out of real things
You know like when you eat Jif you're like this is borderline all sugar and fake peanut
It's pronounced gif
Yeah nicely done
That's probably a hacky joke
No it's pronounced skippy I think
Oh
That's what I say whenever people say it's Jif
I mean what about like a lot of grocery stores they have the things where you just put the peanuts in and grind it up yourself
Totally, yeah
Do you ever fuck around with that?
No, why would I want to work?
Why would I want to work?
Alright
I go to the grocery store because I don't have a peanut farm, not because I want to
Talk to my boy Jim
I don't want to moonlight as a peanut farm worker
Talk to my buddy Jim
Jimmy Carter
That's him
You know the guy?
I've heard of him
Okay
Well that's good, I'm glad you're enjoying that peanut butter
Yes, thank you very much Bex
So Jordan, today we are having a very exciting time here
Yes
It is time for the thrilling conclusion
The dramatic conclusion
To Dan's Caravanity Project 2020
Now Dan, this is Caravanity Project 2020
Alright, alright
Today we're going to be talking about November 11th, the evening of Wednesday until
Whenever
This weekend's nonsense in DC
So we'll see what happens as Owen Schroyer continues on his great big convoy down along
Oh boy
The south and up the eastern seaboard
Okay, here we go
And, yep
So we'll get to that here in a minute, but before we do let's take a moment to say thank
you to some folks who have signed up and are supporting the show
So first, John M, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you John
Thank you
Next, Cara M, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks Cara
Here we go
Next, Simian M, thank you so much, you are now policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks Simian
Oh related
Next, Gunner D, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you Gunner
Next, Chris D, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks Chris
Next, Kate
No Last Names
No Lastgui
Just Any Kate
Kate, thank you so much, you are now policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks Kate
And, I voted third party in 2016, sorry and never again, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, that stuff.
Yeah.
And finally, I'd like to say thank you to a couple folks who donated on Elevated Love
and we appreciate that very much.
So, Kit and Laura from Cincinnati, thank you so much, you are now a technocrat.
Bianca C, thank you so much, you are now a technocrat.
And Evan M, thank you so much, you are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey mate, that's fantastic, have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
Alright, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this Watson, alright?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much Kit and Laura out in Cincy.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you Bianca and thank you Evan.
Yes, thank you very much, all of you.
If you're out there listening and thinking, hey, I enjoy the show, I'd like to support
what these gents do, you can do that by going to our website, knowledgefights.com, clicking
the button that says support the show, we would appreciate it.
We would love it.
What you could do is you could dip a knife into a big old jar of generosity.
Just dip a knife in there, pull out some crunchy, just creamy generosity, spread it all over
the bagel of a local charity or bail fund in your area.
And top it with some really weird vinegar.
Yeah, absolutely.
So Jordan, I have two out of context drops from today's show, so we'll do one now and
one in a little bit.
I, because I'm a Christian, cannot kill you just because you're stupid.
Fair enough.
Seems good.
Let's see.
I support this prohibition on killing.
Now I'm going back through my Bible to see how many people were killed because they were
stupid and it's a lot, but I don't know if it was post-Christ.
And I don't know if it was specifically only because they were stupid.
Yeah, that's fair.
So Jordan, when we last left off on our previous episode, Owen Schroyer and his merry band
of Shao Kahn impersonators and hippies for Trump were about to roll into Atlanta, Georgia.
That was Wednesday the 11th.
Alex had just wrapped up his show where Steve Pachana came in to claim that whether or not
you believe the 2020 election was a massive sting operation planned in advance to catch
Democrats stealing votes, it's a small detail whether you believe that or not.
What is important is that Trump is going to win and then apparently he's going to get
a third term because these dudes love America.
One thing that's crucially important to understand as we continue exploring this caravan is that
at a certain point it stops being an Infowars caravan and it starts being Infowars within
the larger space.
I'm comfortable judging Owen and Infowars for their crowds in places like Tallahassee
and Baton Rouge because those are specifically Infowars caravan events, or at least appear
to be.
Once they reach Washington DC, they are now becoming part of something larger, which is
the combined work of a network of loosely affiliated grifters.
The plan for the weekend has been for everyone to show up in DC and form the Million Maga
March.
I call it Griftpocalypse.
It's fair.
This effort combines the Infowars caravan with Ali Alexander's Stop the Steal campaign,
as well as Brandon Straca's Walkaway nonsense and whatever the fuck Mike Cernovich is doing
these days.
Beyond that it's attracted the legions of Oath Keepers, Proud Boys, and members of many
right-wing gangs who are less interested in hogging the spotlight.
According to an article from Friday in USA Today, the only group that had a permit for
the event is a group called Women for America First.
Quote, Amy Kramer, chair for Women for America First, said her organization is not coordinating
with any of the other groups planning simultaneous events.
This is really interesting because according to a recent article in Mother Jones, Women
for America First were on one of the main websites for Stop the Steal, www.stolenelection.us.
Donations that people made to Stop the Steal through that website end up going to Women
for America First, and the site was used to promote rallies branded as Stop the Steal.
Great, great.
Anyway, it's a load of bullshit.
Griftpocalypse it is.
Yeah, it's a load of bullshit to pretend these people aren't coordinating.
But that's not even an argument that's really worth having, I think.
The point is that the end result of these rallies will be the combined efforts of a
whole cadre of weirdos.
And so even if we get to the end of this and there is a big turnout in DC, we have to keep
our eyes on the ball and remember that had nothing to do with this stupid road trip.
No, not at all.
Not at all.
It's because fucking evil Steve Bannon, Nick, furied us into the Avengers of Grifters.
More or less.
That's what happened.
So here's our second out of context drop.
We've never lived in more historical times.
This is one of the most historical points in history, except when Jesus Christ was walking
on the earth.
That was more important.
Okay.
All right.
Yikes.
Let's see if we can name other historical figures who have...
Can't do it.
None?
None.
Is just Jesus?
Jesus right now.
Jesus now.
Okay.
He's even saying that 1776 wasn't a big deal.
All right, but what about Genghis Khan when he died an entire empire?
Small potatoes.
Okay.
Fair enough.
Small potatoes.
Do you see that march in D.C.?
Fuck.
It looked exactly like hundreds of thousands of Mongols riding horseback with their amazing
bows.
That shit was nothing.
Yeah.
Oh, fair enough.
So the 11th November.
Sure.
Owen Troyer arrives in Atlanta.
Owen Troyer here from Infowars.com.
We have just landed in Atlanta, Georgia, and we are on our way right now to the Capitol
building where we have Patriots, Trumps and Mortars, Infowarriors gathered as part of
the Stop the Steel caravan.
There was no reason for me to pull this clip.
Nothing happens in it.
I only decided to start with this because the opening of the video in Atlanta is surreal.
You have Owen Troyer poking his little head out of the sunroof of the Infowars tank with
a handheld mic, talking about how they're heading to the Capitol while driving down
an empty street.
There's no reason for them to choose this presentation.
All it does is make the audio terrible, since even if Owen has a windscreen on his mic,
he's still using a regular microphone while hanging out of a moving vehicle.
It's just very bizarre.
No, it was really easy to understand what he was saying the whole time.
It was infuriating.
No, it was great.
This video's real bad.
No, no, no.
Pop out of there to empty us.
Yeah.
That's what you want.
Empty road.
Yeah.
It's the Stop the Steel caravan, and right now it is very successful.
It looks like we may stop the steel, but we've got to take this thing right to Washington,
D.C.
There's one thing that's suspicious in its absence from this shot of Owen hanging out
the top of the tank, and that's any indication that there are any cars behind him.
You would think that if the caravan is as successful as Owen is claiming, they'd pan
around to show the giant convoy, but nope, just Owen talking to no one, driving down
an empty street.
That's a great metaphor.
You know that I'm Mr. Caravan Fan, Mr. Caravan, if you will, but I found it incredibly challenging
to jump back into this stuff, entirely because how poorly produced this Info Wars video is.
Owen doesn't arrive at the Atlanta rally until eight minutes into the video, and the entire
time up to that point is just him with his head out the sunroof repeatedly saying, Atlanta,
we're in you.
It sounds more like that after the end of a week at camp, they always have the slideshow
with the... There's always a clip of somebody being like, and that's why we love camp, and
when there's swelling music around it, everybody's like, yeah, that's great, but if it was just
him silent to emptiness, you'd be like, this is a bad camp.
If I went to that camp, I'd probably be into a well-made version of Memories from Camp.
Sure.
I still wouldn't be into it if it was poorly made, and that's how I feel about this.
Even if I were into Info Wars and I thought Owen was cool, I'd still be like, guy's got
to do better than this.
This is eight minutes of Owen saying nothing, hanging out the roof of a tank.
This sucks.
It's like the worst version of Mission Impossible.
I don't understand.
They didn't need to keep it for time or anything.
There's no reason for this to be in there.
It's so distractingly bad.
It's just hubris.
I think it's just hubris.
They just think any idea is the best idea at the time.
Their attention span is nothing.
Well, I would argue that it's more likely that they think that there's something badass
about him driving around out the sunroof, and I would argue it does not look that badass.
No.
It kind of looks just like, I mean, it looks fun-ish.
Eh.
You got wind in your hair.
Yeah, I saw it on Mythbusters one time.
It was great.
Sure.
I don't know.
It made this a chore.
So on his way, I mean, whether or not he's badass or not, leaning out the roof of this
here tank, he does end up at a stoplight, and there's a guy at the stoplight.
There's something so fucked up and, like, immediately deflating about a tank at a stoplight.
It's pretty sad.
How dare you be stopped by light?
You're a fucking tank.
Leading a convoy.
Yeah, that's weak shit.
No.
Get the fuck out of here.
Well, he obeys traffic laws, and he tries to do a little bit of, just do a little crowd
work with the guy who's standing, waiting to cross the street.
And so that's our plan, and that's why we're in Atlanta here today.
How are you doing, sir?
Me too.
Atlanta.
We are here.
Stop.
The steel caravan has arrived.
Hey, how far out are we?
Less than a mile.
They are out of gas.
There is no enthusiasm left in this fucking thing at all.
I am trying really hard to stay excited about this, and they're not doing it.
They're bored.
Yes.
They realized a couple of days in it was a terrible idea.
They're not having fun.
We went to Baton Rouge.
We drove seven fucking hours, and there were ten people there.
What are we doing?
There's nobody there.
Sucks.
Oh, man.
So Owen thinks-
See, this is when you want to be on the RV.
Yes.
This is when you want to be getting the conversations and bird's eye view just right there.
Beautiful.
So Owen thinks he's funny, and so he has a bit that he wants to do.
And this is like, I mean, I guess this is exactly how comedians do it.
You polish things up at open mics before you try it on a real crowd.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, no, that makes sense.
And for Owen, the open mic is sticking his head out the top of a car while no one's listening.
Oh, that's fair.
I think the Democrats are actually still voting, guys.
Are the Democrats still voting in Georgia, or have they stopped yet?
Do we know?
I think they're still voting, because Biden's not ahead yet.
So there's no one there.
Wow.
He's just talking to nobody.
Brutal.
See-
Now, hold on, hold on.
This is a Shao Kahn joke, sir.
Well, maybe your mood will change once you hear the crowd within the background.
Try this on an actual audience.
Here we go.
I think the Democrats are still voting, guys.
I think the Democrats are still voting in Georgia.
They haven't stopped voting yet, because Joe Biden hasn't been put in the lead.
So they're going to keep voting here in Georgia until Joe Biden gets the lead, but I don't
think it's going to work.
Good stuff.
But I don't think it's going to work.
Good tag.
All right.
Good work, guys.
So, you know, that sound wasn't that great, but I can't throw too much shade at the turnout
at the Atlanta rally.
It's still south of 200 people, but that's really good for an Infowars event that's taking
place during the day.
Yeah, that's not bad.
So far, their daytime rallies have been very, very sad, and this at least looks like what
you might call a group of people.
There were some strange signs in the crowd.
One was just a big queue with the where we go one, we go all slogan.
Another was, quote, Trump's coup d'etat is already underway, which kind of implies that
Trump is leading an overthrow of the government.
I really don't think they get how that sounds.
That seems to either be a counter protester or the opposite of what the messaging is supposed
to be.
I don't know what's going on.
Overall, I would give this Atlanta rally a solid meh.
Decent turnout when we grade on a curve, but full of suspect weirdos and nothing really
interesting at all.
It kind of feels like this was an event that might have been planned already and Owen just
crashed it, since there's definitely some people there who seem to be confused by his
arrival.
Sure.
The video on Infowars is titled, quote, Democrats send operatives to start violence at rally
in Atlanta, which I don't see in the video itself, and even if there were violence in
the video, their claim that they were operatives sent in by anyone is completely manufactured
and not substantiated in any way.
I think the title is in reference to a young woman who drives by and yells that Trump isn't
president anymore, which is the closest I could see.
Just scary stuff.
Yeah.
At a certain point, another guy with a bullhorn threatens Owen's dominance with a we don't
want pedo Joe chant, but it all resolves peacefully.
Oh, that's good.
Yeah.
That's good.
I would hate to see infighting at these.
I imagine they're Democratic operatives.
That's gotta be somebody in the movie who's like, they're green, it's their first operation
in the field.
You know, they've been on the desk for a few years.
Everybody else got injured, so now it's their chance to shine, and they're like, we're sending
you to a rally with 200 people to cause problems.
Uh, oh no.
We're gonna go send you to Agent Provocateur, something that needs no Agent Provocateurs
to get out of control.
Can I try and solve terrorism or something?
Next time.
All right.
So the video from just another channel also doesn't really show any violence.
There's a little bit of yelling between a few people at one point, but it's unclear
what the context is, and then there's a long segment where the video maker and his friend
Tom, who's now our friend Tom, complain about how someone is flipping them off from a nearby
window.
It's pretty sad.
What is wrong with these people?
It's very bummerly.
Oh, I love triggering the lip.
He's giving me the finger!
And they're just like making heart shapes with their hands, and the guy's like fuck.
Fuck you.
So the Atlanta rally was at 3pm, and unlike past stops, this one included what appeared
to be a little bit of an actual march.
I have no idea where they were going or why they were parading, but it seemed like a new
development compared to previous cities.
I don't think they did either, Dan.
From there, Owen was off, because he had to arrive in Columbia, South Carolina for an
8pm rally.
Sure, sure.
Infowars only posted a one minute video about South Carolina, which seems weird, because
from the just another channel footage, it seems like that would be the most useful for
them optically.
Sure.
It was nighttime, the turnout was pretty good, and there were some college students yelling
at them, creating the sort of tension and victimhood they desire in their optics.
Operatives go to college, spend $40,000 to $60,000, and then they're undercover enough
to shout obscenities, yeah.
In the video on Infowars, we get a shot of the caravan itself, and it's really hard to
tell how many of these cars are actually along with them, or if it's just traffic.
Assuming that all these cars are part of the convoy, it's like maybe 10 to 15 cars, which
is nothing to sneeze at if you're an indie band or something, but it's really sad for
day three when you're Infowars.
Yeah, that's not good.
That's not a convoy.
Turnout was alright in Columbia, South Carolina, but again, it's easy to overestimate because
it was nighttime.
They ended up taking a big group picture in front of the Capitol building, and I think
it's about 150 people, probably.
Sure, sure, that's nice.
Yeah.
Good for them.
In the evening of the 11th, things took a turn for the ugly, as the Infowars caravan
came under attack.
Uh oh.
We have a video posted on Parler, trucks were throwing milkshakes at the convoy, and here
is the report.
Well, here we are on the Infowars caravan still.
I think we're like 20 cars strong, 30 cars strong right now.
I'm in line with everybody.
I'm like five cars back behind the Infowars riot wagon, or armored vehicle, whatever you'd
like to call it.
I actually just had a trucker throw something at me, and it exploded all over my truck,
some sort of nasty milkshake or something.
A nasty milkshake.
There was a young girl driving in a Pontiac, and she cut the trucker off, and he started
flashing her, and threw something at her, and it hit me.
So I'm getting attacked because other people in the caravan aren't driving well.
But yeah, I don't know, I've got a million miles, at least, traveling back and forth
across this country, and I've never had a trucker throw a milkshake at me.
So that's definitely a new one.
Oh, that's nice.
This is rather interesting, but anyway, we're on our way to DC, and I'm going to have to
get a car wash at some point, and wash all that shit off my car.
You can actually see several of our guys up here ahead of us.
You don't get to use car washes.
Driving this caravan stuff is pretty crazy, because people are slowing, and then speeding
up, and slowing, and then speeding up, and then people are trying to cut us off and doing
all kinds of crazy stuff.
No shit!
It's wild driving in caravan, guys.
I hope you're all staying safer than me, not getting any dramas.
People were pretty quick to point out that the reason for all the things this guy is
describing is because they were basically clogging the interstate.
Yeah.
They had 20 cars in a row in the passing lane, which is at best dumb and selfish, and at
worst pretty dangerous.
They did what?
They had it in the passing lane?
They were on the left side of the road.
As a Chicagoan, that upsets me more than what they stand for.
When you do a convoy like this, there's no reason that the cars all need to actually
travel down the highway in a line, but that's what they seemed insistent on doing, which
is stupid.
Of course.
Plus, they were doing this convoy at night for no reason.
This was the leg between Columbia, South Carolina, and Raleigh, North Carolina, which is about
three and a half hours drive, and the North Carolina rally was at 3 p.m. on Thursday.
There's no reason to night drive that one in a convoy 20 cars deep.
That's just asshole behavior.
Oh, God.
Luckily, everyone survived.
You don't get to use a car wash.
You're a rugged individualist.
You have to find a fucking hose.
You don't get to use all of these creature comforts if you're trying to sell yourself
as the fucking revolutionary that you are.
I would like to...
Sheik Ravara didn't fucking wash his shit in a fucking washing machine.
I'd like to shift your criticism.
I don't care whether they use car washes or not.
Fine, I get that.
I would like to say you don't get to complain about someone throwing a milkshake at your
car.
That I agree with.
Grow up.
That I thoroughly agree with.
Yeah.
So yeah, everyone survived, and now we jump in on the 12th on Alex Jones' show.
Because again, who knows?
David Knight might have had full coverage of the caravan, and it'll be a mystery lost
to time.
Much like, who built the pyramids?
Was it the aliens or was it Egyptians?
It was not the aliens.
We'll never know.
What if David Knight covered it back then?
Non-white people can also build things, turns out.
But what if the equivalent of David Knight covered ancient mysteries, and we'll just
never know because it was so boring.
Yeah, that's possible.
That's possible.
If you wanted to hide true information, you give it to David Knight and no one will ever
know.
If you want to have really fun, interesting, fake information, give it to him and it'll
bore the shit out of me, which is normally what happens.
So anyway, here is Alex attempting to make some analogies, and I apologize in advance
for the audio quality on this show.
They were saying, Alex, why are they having people that have moved out of California vote
for Biden when Biden was already going to win the state?
Well once you're already flipping everybody's votes and already stealing, you keep stealing
to stay in power.
Why?
That's why nobody can win as a Republican in California.
They already got it.
They already got it in California unless you had like an 80% victory because of the fraud.
That's why there was 87% turnout.
We never had anything near that in the US, usually 55, 60% because people went out to
vote against Donald Trump, Biden, and they just got cheated by the computer.
So that's coming up.
But again, people are like, well, why would they cheat in California if they've already
got it?
Because they already cheated.
It's like saying- You're a genius.
If you've remarried and your new wife's pregnant and you're like, well, why do you have an
18 year old son?
Well, I got another woman pregnant before.
There's no third dimensional thought here.
Why are they stealing stakes they already got?
Because they already got them.
What?
I mean, let me use another example.
Yes, please.
Let's say I'm slaughtering cows.
Okay.
All right.
And I'm about to slaughter a new one to put it in my deep freeze.
Of course.
And people ask, well, why do you keep the other deep freeze going that's got some of
the last cow left in it?
It just doesn't even register.
See, once we start thinking third dimensionally, we can defeat the globalists because they're
operating third dimensional.
We can operate fourth, fifth dimension.
Are they?
Many plays out.
And that's what we do here at Infowars.
I don't know if Trump plays 3D chess or 5D chess, but I know I do.
So I listened to Alex a bunch so I can help you out here because that was a garbled mess.
Sure.
Yeah, that was great.
I got the point really well.
Did you?
Yeah.
Well, let's see if you did.
Okay.
Well, what I think is that Trump basically won almost every state, but there was fraud
all over the place.
Sure.
There was even massive voter fraud in California, which people he talks to can't understand.
They don't understand why the globalists would steal votes in California when California
consistently votes Democrat.
Alex's explanation is that California doesn't actually consistently vote Democrat, and the
appearance that they do is only there because of the voting fraud that's already and always
going on there.
They were stealing votes in California because they're only in power in California due to
all the votes they always steal.
This is not that complicated of a concept that he's trying to describe, and yet Alex
struggles to come up with two really bad analogies.
The first is getting married and your new wife is pregnant, but you have an 18-year-old
child, which is from a previous marriage.
This analogy doesn't make sense because each pregnancy would be an unrelated event, whereas
the imaginary voting fraud would probably only be able to be pulled off by the people
in California because the people committing all the fraud are in power and covering it
up.
They're having kids because they've already always been having kids, Dan.
We'll get to that.
The previous fraud facilitates the current fraud in the California example.
The way to make this analogy actually work would be to imagine a scenario where the new
wife allows Alex to impregnate her because she's so impressed that he has an 18-year-old
son.
That would make sense.
Something about his son needs to implicate the current situation, and in the existing
analogy, that's not the case.
With the California stuff, the idea is that they're stealing the election because they
always do.
So it's possible that another way to make this analogy work is for Alex's response to
this person to be that his new wife is pregnant because he only gets romantically involved
with women, he's gotten pregnant.
Yeah, that would make sense.
Then the analogy would work.
That would make sense.
The second analogy Alex is trying is that he's slaughtering a cow while keeping what's
left of his previous cow in the deep freeze.
This also doesn't make sense based on what he's trying to say.
This would be a good analogy if he were trying to argue that Democrats kept deep frozen votes
from the last election to use in this one because they won by such a wide margin last
time so they had leftovers or something.
Are they reusable like that?
I mean, in terms of keeping cows in the deep freezer, that's how that might work.
I would put the votes in a plastic bag so they don't get wet.
Smart.
Neither of these analogies help clarify his point, but Alex insists this is somehow third
dimensional thinking, whatever the fuck that means.
Really the only thing that these two analogies have in common is a sense of time that whoever
Alex is talking to seems unaware of.
The child from a previous marriage analogy involves a person who doesn't realize you
could have had a child with someone else in the past.
The cow butchering example involves a person who doesn't realize that the cow in the freezer
will eventually be eaten in the future.
The only thing I come away from this convinced of is that Alex is really bad at analogies,
and the people he talks to on a regular basis must have a difficulty with really elementary
concepts, maybe even object permanence.
Have we tested Alex on object permanence?
We tried to play peek-a-boo?
I would be interested to know exactly what extent his object permanence lasts to.
I assume it's more than peek-a-boo.
Okay.
But is it like six months?
If anybody who's involved with the Sandy Hook trial is listening, on the stand, test his
object permanence.
Here's what you do.
On the first day, hold up a sign, and then see if he remembers that there was a sign
in the room.
Anyway.
That would be fun.
Yeah.
So, in this next clip, Alex discusses the cycle of history.
He has some interesting theories about this, but it's pretty simple, based on his assessment.
Okay.
What happens throughout history?
Good question.
Stuff.
Governments get power, whether it be in ancient China or ancient Middle East, or ancient Mesoamerica
or ancient Europe, and routinely, they have periods where there'll be whole kingdoms,
whole civilizations of thriving people, and just suddenly, there's no one left.
And this archeologist go there, there's archeological digs in Germany, archeological digs in Mexico,
everywhere.
Archeological digs in Africa, and they'll build a civilization, and then within a hundred
years, everybody's dead, and they find them all sacrificed.
The final phase, eaten by the priest class.
Sure, sure.
Yes.
There is a demonic force, ladies and gentlemen, that's trying to depopulate us, and they're
announcing it publicly.
I'm going to break it down on the other side.
This is the most important broadcast in the world.
This is the cycle of history.
Wow.
I wish there was some way that every archeological dig throughout history found some sort of
recording or a tablet or something, and it's all just the same Alex Jones ideas.
Like every civilization has been ultimately destroyed by somebody like Alex Jones.
Someone who thinks that all history is a cycle of decadence leading to the priest eating
everyone.
There's had to be somebody in ancient Rome just running around screaming like, the priest
class is eating people.
They're eating people.
Almost certainly.
Ah, ah, ah.
Yes.
I would say that maybe in crueler times they had less of an influence.
Sure, possible.
Because they couldn't ever-
There's so much cruelty.
Well, because they could never get to a point where they would have a radio show.
Sure, that's fair.
You know, people would just like-
Kill them.
Yeah.
And I'm not saying that's the ideal solution.
No, I don't think so.
I do guarantee that this sort of mentality has probably existed throughout all cultures.
Yeah, I would probably argue that most governments-
I mean, it's just paranoia, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, on a basic level it's all just like sort of imaginative, creative paranoia.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, I suppose you could probably make a very good argument that every civilization
ultimately collapses when the perceived corruption of the government equals the actual corruption
of the government.
Hmm.
Do you know what I'm saying?
I hear what you're saying.
I don't know how I could test that in the moment.
I don't know how I could test your theory.
Okay.
I'm not sure-
Let me give you an analogy.
I slaughtered a cow.
Yep.
Alright, move on.
Deep freeze?
Next one.
No, I understand what you're saying.
I think it's an interesting thought, but I don't know if I fully agree with you.
Yeah, no.
I don't know if it's accurate, but it's an interesting thought.
I don't know if I fully agree with me.
Well, it's well said.
It sounds really great, doesn't it?
It sounds almost like an aphorism.
Yeah, it really does.
Yeah.
Society collapses when the perceived corruption matches the actual corruption.
You could see that on a pillow.
It sounds like something somebody smart would say.
Yeah.
Never mind, I take back my comment because now it's pillow worthy.
Yeah, yeah.
So it's probably not true.
No.
No, definitely not true.
It's probably economics.
Yeah.
I worry about it being bullshit because it sounds good.
It sounds so good.
Yeah.
Yep.
Speaking of things that are bullshit-
Shao Kahn jokes?
Caravan, at some points, more than 400 cars, some join, some leave, is on its way right
now and is in North Carolina.
There's absolutely zero chance that there have been 400 cars in the caravan at any point,
and I would be comfortable betting that there wasn't even a total of 400 cars throughout
the entire thing.
I would go so far as to bet that the combined turnout for the events that have happened
up to this point on November 12th are barely more than 400 total people.
I would agree.
This is insane levels of hubris.
Yeah, there aren't enough people in the cars themselves.
It's not like there's four people to a car where if you guys could all afford your own
individual cars, there would be 200 cars.
Yeah.
No.
There's five guys.
I'm offended that there probably are 10 cars.
That to me is shocking and scary.
What are you guys doing?
Three of the cars are probably Infowars employees.
Another one is the guy from Just Another Channel.
Another car is the Hippies for Trump.
They're not busy.
No.
This is their dream.
We want to live the hippie lifestyle while also supporting a political mandate that is
trying to actively kill us.
My grandpa followed the Grateful Dead around.
I'm following Owen Schroyer.
Oh, man.
Oh, that's real bad.
You know where the best place to get drugs is?
The parking lot of an Owen Schroyer show.
Who's my real dad, mom?
Well, back in the 2020s, Owen Schroyer came through South Carolina and we spent one magical
night together on the Infowars caravan.
And here you are.
Like 70-year-old people with Infowars caravan tattoos.
Where were you, man?
Oh, man.
You should have seen it.
There were upwards of 50 people.
If you can remember the Infowars caravan, that means you weren't there.
You sad bastards.
Oh, God.
It's a bummer.
It's just a bummer.
It's such a bummer.
Anyway.
Oh, man.
Let's get back to house.
What did you do?
I followed Pat Robertson around for a summer.
What?
I do love the idea.
All right.
We can't live in 18 different versions of that exact same joke.
We jump back to Alex and I will say that there is one thing that Alex is pretty consistent
on.
It's something he's very wrong about.
And that is that he does not exaggerate things.
He talks about that a little bit here.
I've thought about doing this broadcast for 26 plus years.
You always think about what could be your last broadcast.
I'm not saying this is my last broadcast, but I need to just let you know, I need to
explain something to you that I don't exaggerate any of this, okay?
Most of the time it's worse than I'm telling you.
And this could be our last broadcast next week could be, but the zone we're in right
now, the internet kill switch they've got, they can hit telecommunications as well.
And we're in the prime zone for them to assassinate Trump, set a nuke off, anything.
Well, good thing you don't exaggerate.
Never ever feel safe.
I don't exaggerate things, but if you spend one single moment in safety, you're an idiot.
Does this mean that this is the actual last broadcast that he's been teasing doing to
play after he's done?
If he's never exaggerated anything.
Because that would imply that he's already quitting.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's very weird.
I don't know what's going on because he's talking about this sort of like it could be
his last broadcast.
It's not.
He's on tomorrow.
No, obviously.
It's on the next day, but like I want him to do that fucking mythical last broadcast
already.
Yeah, it has to.
Yeah.
How can you say I don't exaggerate things and then say this could be our last broadcast
knowing full well that you've got at least several more months in the, you know, like
you're very an asshole.
Your very exhortation for money is in and of itself an exaggeration.
Yeah.
Cause you're an ass.
Um, this, this sort of thing though, this extremeness is, is really escalating here
in this, this stretch of time.
I guess maybe Alex is disappointed in the care event cause he's talking about like,
you know, a nuke's going to go off, Trump could get assassinated or turn off the internet.
Why not?
Uh, he basically in this next loop just says, head to the Hills guys.
It's over.
I have been under such stress knowing that we have a chance to stop this and save billions
of people.
And the stress has been on me that I, Howard Stern made jokes about it and it's a funny
viral video, but I had three molars collapsed the last two months.
I mean, all my teeth are literally crushing and falling out of my face.
Uh, I have to wear those fucking pills on it and I'm not feeling sorry for myself.
My spirit is absolutely lashing out at this and in fighting and God really last night
said to the Holy spirit to me to comfort me and to say, listen, this is the way it's going
to be and it's your job is just get people ready and you've done your job.
Now you just need to get them ready.
So I'm just going to tell you it's all over folks.
The best thing you can do is get to the countryside somewhere and try to dig in because it's all
just going to get worse.
Holy shit.
The only thing that differentiates Alex from someone like Jim Jones is that Jim Jones was
specific.
Yeah.
Also not for nothing.
Like you even responded to this being passionate doesn't result in grinding your teeth to the
point they fall out of your head.
However, that's one of the most common symptoms of stimulant abuse between that pretty much
everything about how Alex acts and the fact that Joe Rogan tried to get Alex to talk about
his problem with Adderall on their last episode kind of makes the picture come into focus.
Alex might as well be like a high functioning coke head.
Yeah.
This is, this is the, it all makes a bit more sense when you imagine that, Oh yeah, he's
on stimulants.
Yep.
That's a disappointingly simple answer, but probably the correct one.
Yeah.
Well, I don't think it makes a, uh, I don't think it explains everything.
Obviously there's still a whole bunch of ideas that are bad and it certainly doesn't let
him off the hook for his behavior, but it does make it like a lot of things that don't
make sense do make sense when you consider like, Oh, he's just on drugs.
Yeah.
That's about right.
Billions are going to die and you got to head to the Hills.
Sure.
Alex needs you to know billions are going to die.
He doesn't exaggerate though.
Billions are going to die.
Oh shit.
They're going to release mass bio weapons and kill billions of people and I don't just
say that you will watch billions die with blood pouring out of their eyes, their ears,
their mouths.
Okay, cool.
I mean, you're, you're going to watch absolute mass extermination.
We didn't stand up for the children.
We didn't stand up for God and we rejected Christ and Satan now is coming into the earth
and I'm not trying to be negative.
Everybody wants to hear all this positive lies.
All you can do is get right with Christ.
I can just tell you right now, we can hold them back.
Trump may still prevail, but we've seen the model of the devil's attack.
It's exactly what revelation says, but now we're in it.
We are now entering Satan's first big lash with his plan and he'll keep going and going
and going until he makes war on the saints and overcomes them.
It's going to be really difficult to go back to normal after that.
Um, no, we're living in the biblical end times.
There isn't like a really easy way to walk back.
We're in revelation because revelation doesn't include like false starts.
Guys, I got some good news for you.
They closed the third seal.
They closed the third seal back up, guys.
We've only got to deal with seals one and two.
Let's get to work.
Especially, there's going to need to be a lockdown to deal with all these goddamn plagues.
We have a special seal sealant and uh, yeah, get the fuck out of here.
Yeah.
It's troubling.
It's troubling because like it feels like the only move after this is go away or become
a doomsday like full on religious preacher.
Yeah.
I don't.
They did all that stuff when Obama was elected to those, the biblical end times.
I kept hearing about that.
No, that's true.
That's true.
But I heard about the biblical end times an awful lot.
Sure, but probably from biblical end times preachers.
Well, yeah.
They can be wrong a bunch of times.
That's true.
But they can't transition to something less extreme.
You know, like they can say we were wrong or whatever.
Sure.
I mean, they could become a hot dog then.
These are the blood moons.
This is the real, you know, like you can do that.
That would be fun.
Like look, last time we thought we knew it was up, but this time blood moon.
Yeah.
But you can't be like, ah, the world is going to end.
I know it's coming.
And then be wrong and then be like, well, what you really need to do is focus on your
alderman race or, or whatever.
Or like, it's really tough to desensationalize from the point of end times.
Well, I mean, that's again, like the idea of, of like, all right, we lost this one.
Devil's going to win, but we got to focus on the midterms in order to defeat the devil
again I guess.
Right.
And the other problem too is if you are an end times type, end times always got to be
coming.
Yeah.
End times cannot be here.
No, it's really bad when it's here.
Yes.
Yeah, that'll fuck you up.
The money is in end times being coming down the road somewhere.
Totally.
It really screws things up when it's here.
And I think Alex is going to, I don't know, I see this as a bad decision on his part.
So Alex gets to talking about galactic laws, contract law for aliens.
Sure.
This is really stupid.
This is fifth dimensional chess, huh?
This is fucking stupid.
I don't know all the timelines, but are the globalist always tell us what they're going
to do in their internal documents that are public, but they don't promote them, but it's
a metaphysical rule.
They got to tell you what they're doing.
Kind of leave the plans laying on the road side.
So you have a chance to read the fine print if you can find it, kind of a public notice.
That's why you have public notice that they're going to take a piece of property or public
notice they're about to tear something down or public notice they're about to take a park
away from you.
Because they have to give you notice because you have metaphysical, spiritual rights, unalienable
rights to challenge that.
This is common law, this is galactic law, this is God's law, and even the devil has
to follow it.
This is a comically childish and stupid view of morality, and I would just like to take
everyone who claims that Alex is smart and he has good points and ask them what they
think of that, because that moral system that Alex is presenting is really hard to defend
if you want to look at human history.
It's simple enough to say that everyone who deprived people of their unalienable rights
went to hell after they died.
Like Thomas Jefferson.
Uh, yeah, that's kind of a problem.
Alex would have to then either say that slavery doesn't violate unalienable rights or a bunch
of his heroes and ancestors are in hell.
But leaving that aside, looking at the actions that are ascribed to the devil in traditional
Christian lore, I don't see where he's warning people what he's going to do before he does
it.
In the Garden of Eden, it's God who tells them not to eat from the Tree of Knowledge.
If God hadn't done that, then the serpent would presumably have done the exact same
thing it did in the story and convinced Adam and Eve to eat the fruit.
The serpent didn't do anything except a manipulative, evil act.
The part where there was a warning came from someone else entirely.
So in order for this to make any sense in Alex's moral conception, the morality or immorality
of your actions can be determined by other people's actions.
This would imply that it would be very wrong for me to punch you randomly and without warning.
However, if someone were to tell you Dan is going to punch you when you go to his house,
then my punch would be completely fine, because someone else let you know that it was coming
and you chose to come here anyway.
In fact, in this conception, it could be argued that me punching you is never immoral in and
of itself.
If my punch is morally correct when someone else warns you and morally incorrect when
they do not, the actual distinction is the warning itself.
That's where the moral weight lies, so it becomes a matter of the other person doing
something immoral by not warning you.
My punch doesn't matter at all.
So then, what if no one else knows that I'm going to punch you?
Then apparently I have to tell you ahead of time that I plan to punch you, and then if
you come over anyway, you've consented to being punched.
This is stupid for a number of reasons.
To what extent do I need to make sure that you're aware that I'm going to punch you?
You have to serve people before you punch them.
Is it enough that I mumble it to you as you leave, knowing that you'll probably not hear
me or forget by the time we end up getting together to record again?
I think you have to put it in a movie.
Is it enough for me to write, I'm going to punch Jordan the next time he comes over on
a piece of paper that I taped to a lamppost two miles north of my house, knowing that
you'll never pass that lamppost?
That's how Arthur Dent got that bypass.
Could that satisfy the metaphysical condition, even though there's literally no way it could
ever impact your behavior?
Ask the Vogons.
You could say that the warning was there if you wanted to look for it, and it's really
your fault that you didn't find that lamppost, it was right there in the open for everyone
to see.
To what extent does the person the thing is being done to need to be aware of the thing
that's going to be done to them?
This is a question that Alex cannot answer, because no matter what the answer is, shit
doesn't make sense.
If the standard is informed consent, then the globalists need to be doing way more warning
than they're doing right now, and honestly would probably need to get literally everyone
to sign off on their plans, knowing the implications of what they're agreeing to, so it obviously
can't be that.
If the standard is that the person needs to believe the warning, is that possible, that
you need to believe it?
Because even if that's the standard, I still don't think you deserve to be punched for
coming over, whether or not you believe the warning.
You might not believe it, someone could say Dan's going to punch you if you come over
and you'd be like, ah fuck you.
But you understand that this line of thinking makes perfect sense because of the way that
all of these people have to deal with hell?
Like okay, if everybody that doesn't accept Jesus Christ into their heart is going to
hell, Jesus didn't get his message out for a good long while to the rest of the world,
so all of those people, despite never having heard of Jesus Christ spend eternity in hell
just because God was like, nah geographical product placement.
So your argument then has to be, well there's evidence of God all around you, so you should
have known that God was real, and obviously Christ, if there's a God there's got to be
a Christ.
So it's still your fault, and that's why hell is justifiable to people who've never heard
of Christianity.
That might be, I think that you're trying to bring too much sense to it, and I'm trying
to deconstruct this from an ethical perspective.
I'm saying that you've deconstructed both fairly well.
Well see, here's what I think that Alex would say the standard is.
He would say that the standard that you need to achieve is that you need to publicly admit
this somewhere, so even if you do it in code that's only decipherable to a genius like
Alex Jones, that's still good enough.
I struggle to see how this qualifies as warning people in an ethically meaningful way, for
the same reason that my message taped to a lamppost doesn't seem like it could reasonably
be seen as possibly impacting your behavior.
I mean, you know, Dan, we're dealing with Satan and God.
There's obviously a lot of wiggle room in the rules.
Those two guys aren't known for absolutes.
Alex is talking about human behavior too.
Oh shit, well we're fucked.
In order to make this morality work, it must not be the would-be victims of the crime that
are required to be warned about what this person's going to do.
It must be a thing where the act of writing it down and putting it out there is to serve
as a notice to God of their intentions, but what kind of sense does that make?
Also what are the consequences for breaking these supposed galactic laws, and why should
the devil be concerned with any punishment?
He's already the fucking devil.
Disintegration.
It's the punishment he fears most.
Well then what?
Okay, so he does that and then he disintegrates, great, there's no devil anymore, hooray!
Well, but God would have to create another devil, otherwise his prophecy wouldn't come
true.
See, again, here's where I'm really struggling with Alex and all this bullshit.
You understand that for your actual religion to not be bullshit, you have to have the end
times.
You can't stop them.
You can't delay them.
It's God's moment.
He chooses.
There's no way that Biden is going to affect God's plan, otherwise your entire religion
is nonsense.
Yeah, and you can't vote on the devil.
You can't vote on the devil!
I'm assuming Job would have had a different vote.
This is the moral system of a child, and honestly it's embarrassing to hear him try to explain
his beliefs.
It also kind of makes me sad to hear how small his vision of the divine is.
It's the same kind of bummer I get whenever I hear people on Project Camelot talking about
like alien contracts and stuff, it's like ugh.
Come on.
Are you saying to me that even if we get beyond the stars, we're never going to get past the
point where a signature is going to hold the entire universe together?
It's still just going to be a signature.
Yeah, and God is trying to get the devil on technicalities or something.
Exactly!
Alright.
Aha!
We have him on a Rico case!
Yeah.
So, at this point, Alex does something incredibly familiar.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are back live, broadcasting worldwide again, we are back live broadcasting
worldwide.
I am your host, Alex Jones, very, very thankful to be here with you today.
And I believe I'm connected, I believe I'm live, but, okay, we're going to rebroadcast
for a while, and I will be back because I've got to reset and go into this.
No, I'm cool now, I've got to reset, I can't do it, so there's too much going down here.
So, as I was saying, I've got some really important news we're going to be covering
here until you get reset.
And I sent you guys a lot of videos, I sent you guys a lot of things.
And so, the first thing that I'm going to want to play is whatever you guys want to.
I'll be back in a little while.
What?
What just happened there?
This is an important announcement.
So I was thinking about this and wondering, what the fuck is going on?
Yeah.
Alex is in DC now, he's already arrived in DC, so you lost the bet.
So he's freaking out trying to do this show remotely, and it sounds like shit.
Like there's a lot of audio crackliness, it's just terrible.
And honestly, even beyond that, his heart is not in it.
So he freaks out a little bit and he goes to rebroadcast, it honestly wasn't surprising
to me at all.
It honestly seemed like a prudent decision.
The only real question to me is, why is he hosting at all?
Good question.
Then it dawned on me, there's probably no one else who can host.
Schroyer's on the caravan.
David Knight is definitely not a primetime candidate.
Well, I think David Knight, he has his own show, and he had a heart attack like a year
ago.
Oh, that's true.
And his workload, for his own sake, I think it's great that he's not taking on unnecessary
burdens, but I think that he would probably not be the person who would, and he's not
gonna move product.
And Millie Weaver is gone forever, Deanna Lorraine is terrible.
She's too green, probably for the main show.
Same problem with Harrison Smith, like he can fill in on the War Room because no one's
watching that, but actual Owen show, or I'm sorry, actual Alex show, seems like it's probably
no good.
Millie Weaver is gone, like he can't talk to Mike Adams anymore.
No, of course not.
All the fourth hour fill-in hosts are either, like, they wouldn't do it, or, how are you
gonna have three and a half, four hours of Gerald Cilenti?
It's too much.
Are those the funeral bells?
Because I can hear Roger Stone's name coming right down the pipe.
He's day drunk.
That's true.
He's fucked up.
See, now that's what I want.
I want three hours of rambly day drunk Roger Stone.
I do not.
I listen to it.
I do not want it.
Fair.
There will literally be no one left at Info Wars who's able to fill in for Alex.
It's interesting, in a way.
He's kind of reached the pinnacle of success, but at the same time, he's right where he
started.
He's got a giant business with a ton of employees, but he still needs to do everything himself
because everyone sucks.
He's the president's biggest cheerleader, but he's still ignored and cast aside in favor
of more seemingly acceptable right-wing commentators, same as it ever was.
I feel like you should realize that the path he's on leads nowhere, and it never has.
It started with him being alone, and it's going to end with him being alone, and good
luck to you, buddy.
Except there's some good news.
What's that?
He goes off air, and he comes back, and then he starts talking about having cancer, and
I was like-
Wait, what now?
I was like, wait, do you actually have cancer?
It's like, nah, I don't have cancer.
Oh, okay.
Just the only way I can talk to you is from the heart and where I'm at before I hit all
this news.
I am devastated.
It's not just that I've learned that I have cancer, and that I'm dying.
It's I've learned we all have cancer, and we're all dying.
I don't literally have cancer, though you have cancer every day, and your body kills
it with your immune system.
Oh my God.
Okay.
All right, buddy.
All right.
You didn't even need to add that shit.
No.
Just say I don't have cancer.
But I could always be fighting off cancer any moment of any day.
That weirded me out, because I kind of felt like, oh, that makes sense, you have cancer.
I don't know.
I would believe it if he was like, I have terminal cancer.
Oh, well, yeah, okay.
Shit.
Well, no wonder you want the world to end.
Yeah.
Your narcissism is experiencing it that way.
You don't want to go alone.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, no.
Unfortunately, that is not the explanation.
Not unfortunately, I don't even know how I would put it, but that's not the explanation.
He just thinks that everyone's going to die.
But you should know, he's not happy to report that.
Sure.
I'm sitting here last night and this morning, thinking about what I'm going to say today
on the air because of all the announcements and all the statements that have been made,
confirming our worst analysis and then some, and I don't feel good coming on air, telling
you that we're all dead.
But I want to explain to you the reality of this, and we'll do it next segment because
I'm very emotional right now.
Sound like it.
Yeah.
Yep.
Very emotional right now.
Oh boy.
All right.
I don't want to, man.
And now I just, now that we kind of get more of the gist of what he told his kids at the
breakfast table, you're going to watch billions die is like not a good morning.
Kids, you got to head to the hills.
No kidding.
Hey, we can do remote learning as far remote as we need to be.
Hey, look, I got some John Birch society books.
That's all the book learning you need.
So yeah, I mean, we're all going to die and Alex takes no pleasure in reporting that.
That's nice of him.
I think he kind of wouldn't be reporting that if Trump had won the election, which is weird.
But it turns out the election stolen.
They stole this bigger than Dallas in front of everybody.
But Hey, if you catch somebody in your house with the safe or in your house with the computers
or in your house with a silverware and then the family heirlooms, do you have a right
to take it back?
Damn right you do.
And so they are panicking.
They're saying have a coup against Trump all over the news.
They're saying he's insane.
He's crazy because he's not going to let them have this fifth attempted coup against us
separately.
You've got my commitment to burn the candle at both ends here, ladies and gentlemen, and
we're fighting hard here.
We need your financial support info or store.com bringing a caravan up here and flying here
with the crew and all.
We love you.
We appreciate you.
Info or store.com bringing this caravan up here is a shockingly pointless and spent a
lot on gas for no reason.
Yeah.
No grammar.
I do.
I do appreciate the, the if you know, if you catch a robber in your house, you know, that's,
that's good.
If you catch, you know, you have a right to defend yourself, et cetera.
But if instead of doing that, you're a, you lose something and then you drive to DC and
murder someone who has, you've never met before and who's never been to where you live.
It's not quite the same as a robber.
It's not the same thing.
No, I would, I would argue it feels similar to Alex.
It does though.
Yeah.
Cause of metaphysical laws.
Sure.
Um, so the Alex is, you know, I think you can tell also from that clip that the audio
has not gotten better.
No.
And so Alex gets really mad again.
Of course.
I'm on the road.
I'm here in Washington, DC.
I'm having a lot of technical difficulties, but I'm just gonna stay on here as best as
I can.
They're on the break.
We'll try to fix the big muddy signal.
I'm getting blessed in my ear, but that's okay.
That's why I like to go just with a laptop, just straight Skype.
It's like clean.
You got this big fan dangled thing.
It looks like a space shuttle over here and it's just, it just hammers the hell out of
me every time.
I got to make an executive decision.
I'm going to rebroadcast.
I'm going to plug in all this.
I'm going to laptop because, uh, yeah, it'll take a while, but it's okay.
You know, we're real, we're real transmission there.
I'm just trying the best I can here.
I'm not complaining either.
It's just, uh, God, the whole country's going to hell in a ham basket, man.
I feel it.
We're still having broadcasting issues, so of course the entire country is falling apart
naturally.
Isn't, isn't my shitty set up just indicative of the state of the world?
Isn't it strange that me, Alex Jones of Info Wars would have issues with my phone connection.
Hey, I constantly have these tech issues that plague me in studio and out and every time
I try and take a phone call from somebody and now here I am trying to broadcast from
DC and I'm having problems, it's somehow I'm surprised by it.
It's a shock and the world is clearly going to hell.
Totally.
I will say that it's not, it's interesting that there's, this happens twice on this show.
Of course.
Uh, I think I don't, I don't recall the last time he's done this twice, um, but he ends
up vamping until the commercial breaks, so he doesn't actually have to storm out a second
time.
Um, but he ends up leaving early.
Of course he ends up, uh, he's got more fun things to do.
Yeah, yeah, definitely.
Yeah, totally.
He's wearing a hat, got cattle.
So that's what it comes down to, how I'm out riding the range, which I wish I was doing
checking the fences.
I might be wearing a Stetson, but I don't, I'm not lucky enough to get to do that because
my country is in so much damn peril, but I can't like Hank Williams Jr.
I like to ride my horse and shoot my gun.
Every boy's work she's never done, now the rest of the song goes.
That Lord has certainly made a lot of beautiful women out there, honey.
Wow.
Harrison Smith is going to be taken over, ladies and gentlemen, and I'm tempted to pop
back in, but, uh, I won't, I was here mentioning all this news.
All this information, this unfolding hell, there's been so many people in this hotel
room walking back and forth.
I can't even remember what the last clip was.
I was going to play.
Well, what was the next clip guys?
I was going to get there.
That's right.
That's where I wanted to go.
So this is a great ad for brain force.
Um, you know, these sort of new tropics, these supplements that give you focus and clarity
and the ability to really stay on task.
Yeah, and the ability to disintegrating.
That one's also a real eye opener.
The ability, like when you talk about mental fog versus clarity, you're talking about the
ability to do a radio show in a hotel room where there are other people present.
Yeah.
God, just, anyway, Harrison Smith takes over for like the last half hour and I think that's
about right.
I think that's, that's about what he can handle.
He's boring as shit.
He's terrible, but give him a little time.
Yeah.
Get his feet wet.
Give him five minutes up top.
He'll start the show.
Yeah.
It's that kind of thing.
Yeah, for sure.
It's that, it's that, uh, that standup show.
It's like, all right, I want you to get some experience, but we still have to move some
product so we have to keep the audience happy.
So Alex is going to do most of it, although he's not going to do much.
No.
So, uh, that night or that day in a caravan activities, it was really stormy that day
for Owen.
So he talked to an underwhelming group of people in the rain in, uh, in North Carolina
about how the election was stolen.
Sure.
And honestly, by this point, the charm of the caravan caravan had worn off for me.
It's redundant.
It's unimpressive and ultimately it's too obvious what the game is.
This is all about creating the optics of taking your dumb show on the road, arriving at a
much larger event and then giving yourself credit for the turnout at the large event.
Yeah, totally.
It's honestly pretty disappointing.
There was such great potential for this road trip.
In the end, it's really forgettable.
Yeah.
I tried to find an angle of something interesting.
We talked about the open mic comic who did the Shao Kahn impression.
I tried to see if there was a human interest angle in here somewhere, but there just isn't.
They had the opportunity to do something really interesting and compelling, and instead they
did exactly what Infowars always does.
They produced a cookie cutter performance that was meant to create profit and gather
attention while funneling support to larger fascist movements.
I'm really disappointed in them, but I also know there's not really anything else they
can do.
The only thing that's even close to interesting in this stretch is they did a damage control
video in Raleigh where Greg Reese and some other employee discuss how someone gave them
a book with a Nazi bookmark in it.
Their angle, naturally, is that this was an agent provocateur leftist who was there to
make Trump look bad, although I would argue it's equally possible it was just a fan who
gave them a Nazi bookmark in a yoga book.
After the Raleigh stop, they added on to Richmond, Virginia, and honestly, it's a fine turnout,
but it's more of the same.
My highlight is that a guy is playing the trumpet there while the crowd sings the national
anthem, and a shot of the trumpet player happens to include a historical marker in the background.
This was actually shot on the site of the 1863 Richmond Bread Riot, which is kinda fitting.
The Union forces had hurt supply lines for the Confederacy, so prices of food had increased
in Richmond considerably.
From History.com, quote, on April 1st, a group of poor working women held a meeting in a
Baptist church to organize a demonstration against the rising costs of food.
Mary Jackson, a 34-year-old mother, and Martha Ferguson riled up the audience with tales
of rampant speculation and price gouging happening in the markets.
Soon, the mob was angry enough to agree to meet the very next day outside the Capitol
building and extract bread and justice from the men in charge.
The governor initially refused to meet with them, but then when he did, he was unsympathetic,
so the mob went on a tear and started rioting.
They stole food, but also luxury goods, until the riot police arrived and were prepared
to fire.
The reason that I think this is fitting that this ridiculous display was on this same site
as the Bread Riot is because the aftermath of that riot was that the Confederacy tried
really hard to keep it quiet, since they knew that word of this internal chaos would raise
the morale of the Union armies.
These videos are really things that Owen in Infowars should try to keep quiet.
They're out there yelling about how this is the end of the country, and this caravan's
the last battle, and these are the crowds they can draw?
I don't know if that raises my morale, but I think it should hurt theirs if they looked
at it honestly.
Like, this is not impressive stuff.
Yeah, I wouldn't like it.
If I was doing that in any capacity, like, even, like, I went on tours where I made negative
money.
I think I've only exclusively done that.
I think I broke even one stamp.
Maybe.
Maybe for me.
But yeah, if I was doing this in any...
Like, this would be bad for me on an amateur tour.
Like that's the level of bad this is.
Yeah.
You might be able to get a little bit of b-roll from this for a larger thing.
Yeah, that's true.
Like the camp video?
The wrap-up video?
Yeah, maybe.
But yeah, it's not...
No, this isn't good.
It seems to me like this is them throwing everything they've got, the most extreme language,
the most immediacy possible, and it's still incredibly underwhelming.
And I would be embarrassed of that if I were Infowars, and if I were Owen.
I would treat this like the Confederacy treated the Bread Riot, and I would not have the Trumpeteer
standing right in front of the memorial of that.
Hide it.
Yeah.
Oh boy.
So we jump to the 13th, Friday, and Alex is back hosting his show again from DC.
From DC.
That would have been really funny if he'd gone home.
Yeah.
Fuck it.
We can't...
I can't do it from here, and nobody is home!
Trump called yesterday, but I was napping.
Yeah.
And I can't call him back.
He drove by the hotel, and he stopped by, and I was napping, and he just couldn't get
in!
They wouldn't let him in because he didn't have a room!
Yep.
Classic hotel staff.
Classic hotel.
Yeah, it would be funny if you left, but instead he stayed and then just did nothing.
Yeah.
Except for yelling to a bullhorn.
That sounds right.
But here he is talking about what has happened on the caravan, and you would know that this
wasn't true if you were keeping up with the caravan.
How would I know?
Well, we caught Antifa on the way here following us from Florida up into Virginia, now in DC,
posing as patriots in handing out white supremacist literature.
So that's going to be their main mission tomorrow.
We actually caught them on video red-handed, and we actually intercepted their communications.
We love you, Alex!
Through a source.
Here's our Nazi stuff!
Through a mole.
I'll sell them.
We've infiltrated them.
We're planning to dress like MAGA folks at the march tomorrow, be wearing their red baseball
caps backwards, and wearing camouflage pants is how they're dressing.
So Alex is just making all that up.
And the only thing that's real is that book that someone gave them with a Nazi bookmark
in it that they've decided is leftist agitators.
And now he's turned this into they have a mole, and Antifa followed them from Florida
up through the whole convoy all the way up, and there's plans for in DC, they're going
to show up with backwards MAGA hats and camouflage pants, and they're going to hand out dirty
literature to everyone to make the patriots look bad.
So dumb.
I can think of few things that would do more for the cause than Antifa joining that Infowars
caravan as agent provocateurs.
I just don't think there's anything else that could be done for the movement that would
have that much effect.
I don't think I've heard anybody but me talk about this.
The caravan is just for them and us, isn't it?
I'm not positive that I've seen any angry tweets about it or anything.
I think I saw a couple people posting about the milkshake from the truckers.
I think I saw a little bit of jokes about that.
But in terms of this, I don't think anybody gives a shit except for them and me.
I don't think Antifa's following anybody.
It's really annoying that you spend all of your time whipping up white supremacists to
fight for you, and then you're like, I don't know where all these white supremacists come
from.
Must be leftists.
Must be Antifa.
Come on, man.
You've spent so much time loving these guys.
Let's just move on.
It's a little much.
Just say it.
It's not going to alienate 48% of the country.
It's not going to alienate the people who are still listening to you at this point.
Exactly.
If you can ramble about the literal devil all the fucking time and say all this nonsense
bullshit and people don't leave, just mask off, man.
Just toss a sig heil out there who fucking cares.
But even if he does do that, these listeners, Nazi or otherwise, need to recognize that
their lives are over.
And so because their lives are over, it's time to go yell at the governor.
OK, when you're tuning in, I want everybody to understand your life is over, as you know
it, until you fight back.
We need people every day surrounding the governor's mansion where Governor Abbott is.
If he's in a restaurant eating, you don't go up and threaten him.
You go up and you say, sir, we know you're being blackmailed.
We know the lockdown's permanent.
Be a leader and stop it.
We need to start his recall.
Smash cut to Alex complaining about people yelling at Trump officials at restaurants.
A bunch of leftist provocateurs, yeah.
Also, there are 20 states in the United States where a governor can be recalled, and Texas
is not one of them.
In order for Alex to do his plan about recalling Governor Abbott, he would first need to find
justification for a new law in the Texas Constitution and then get a law passed by the state legislature.
It would be a cumbersome process that he's not up for, and honestly, it would probably
just be easier to wait until he's up for re-election and then field a fringe-ass candidate to lose
to him and probably split the vote so a Democrat ends up winning.
Also, Governor Abbott's not being blackmailed.
He's still an incredibly far-right politician, just not far-right enough for Alex.
He's failed Alex's purity tests.
It's not illegal to write a law that just says Governor Abbott can never be governor,
right?
Abbott out.
Yeah, no Abbott.
No Abbott's forever.
Yeah, that might be an interesting law.
I would be interested in that law.
I think it would get challenged.
Someone would file a lawsuit.
On what grounds?
I'm not a lawyer.
So in this next clip, this clip's a little bit long, but I kept it in because it begins
with Alex talking about how he's not into offensive violence.
And then it's quite a ramble about a bunch of nonsense.
But I think I needed to play, it's two and a half minutes long, but the reason I wanted
to play this whole chunk is like, if you listen to this, it's sort of an ABA kind of structure,
where you have the A theme of offensive violence, then B is kind of just random talking points,
spaghetti up against the wall, and then you return to what the thesis of the initial thought
was.
But by that point, your brain will, if you're not paying attention, you'll kind of already
have forgotten that that's what he was talking about.
And this happens quite a bit, but I rarely play full clips of it, just because it's long.
And I don't want any offensive violence, but I see a lot of talk online, people saying
time to dust off the muskets.
Here's the issue, existentially, and I'll give you these clips of the big news.
Under common law, under common sense, you cannot come with experimental dangerous vaccines,
whether they be safe or not, and they're not, they're deadly, and it's obviously the takeover.
These people have liability protection, they have long histories of killing people with
vaccines.
They are eugenicists that want to depopulate you.
When somebody says, I want to depopulate you, and he's spent hundreds of billions of dollars
he got from big foundations and the robber barons to get control of the world health
system and most nation state systems, he's been thrown out of over 20 countries, Gates,
has been, he's in another 140 or so.
Thrown out of 20 countries.
When you've got something of that matter through a plate glass window, and he says he wants
to do this, and it's what he comes out of, Cold Springs Harbor and the eugenics, and
then he's coming, violating the Geneva convention, violating the Nuremberg code, violating international
law.
If the Nazis were coming to give you a deadly shot or take your kids away, you don't just
have a right, you have a duty to fight them.
So they've already shut down the communications almost everywhere.
Now they're coming.
Now they're going to beta test in Canada and Europe in this round and in California and
in New York, dragging people out of their homes, beating people up that don't wear masks,
taking people's children away.
The UN said that was the goal.
It's already happened in Australia and Spain.
Now it's happening in England.
And they're just normalizing that vans come, cops have guns.
You disappear.
And then again, if they say you have COVID, these are leftist doctors at extermination
centers, not guillotines.
They say, oh, he had COVID.
And now you're going to see people take it to the COVID centers.
It's already happening in Australia.
People die in these.
You're totally healthy.
They take you.
They go, oh, he got sick.
We had to innovate him.
And yeah, he died after two weeks on a ventilator.
So they strap you down and the comics Chinese do this and they put it down your lungs and
they kill you.
And they sit there and laugh at you while you're dying.
And they turn it up way higher.
Like a lot of the old folks in the blue city areas where they have these killer eugenics
doctors, they're, they're, they're in cult bioethics boards, like, like Ezekiel Emanuel
saying he wants to kill old people.
He runs this.
He hires for decades, all, all these boards, these are psycho killers.
And even the medical association said, why did you give people twice the pressure you're
supposed to?
And there's like, because they got to get kill numbers.
So they're coming to kill you.
They're coming to kill you.
So you kind of, you kind of get what I'm saying.
He starts with the presentation of like, there's a lot of people who are saying, clean off
your rifles.
And then he gives the appearance of saying that, no, you shouldn't.
And that is good for him because he can sort of point to that as being like, this is me
pushing back against the idea of offensive violence.
Totally.
Now the next two minutes is him saying a hundred fucking different things that you can't keep
track of all these various little bullshit pieces.
No, Ezekiel Emanuel wants to kill everybody.
Totally.
Yeah.
Cult, cult leftist doctors.
Bioethics boards.
Psycho killers.
Do cults create bioethics boards?
Is that a thing I didn't know about?
That's what the new Assassin's Creed is actually about.
God damn Templars.
And then it gets to the end and the message that he's trying to drive home is they're
coming to kill you.
They're coming to kill you.
This is the answer to the beginning of it.
This is him saying, there is no such thing as offensive violence now.
It's not a question of that.
Like existentially, this isn't even a question we need to worry about.
All violence is defensive.
You got it.
But he doesn't need to actually say that if he structures the argument this way.
And if anybody tries to say like, Alex, you're advocating for people to dust off their rifles
and fire at people if they feel like they're vaccine pushers.
A bioethics board is coming for them.
Or someone is telling you to wear a mask.
They're trying to get you to...
Offensive violence, so anything you do to that person is defensive.
And if anybody tries to say that Alex, this is what you're saying, he can point to like,
I said that there's a lot of people who are saying clean off the rifles and I was pushing
back against that idea.
Alex, you are one of them.
You just did it.
The larger context of it is the coward's way of saying exactly that.
Just shoot people.
There's no such thing as offensive violence.
But if you do commit one of those crimes, I will say that it's a leftist who did it.
And that it was offensive.
And then they also handed me a fucking book with a Nazi book market and followed me from
Florida.
Yeah.
Jesus Christ.
So in this next clip, Alex talks about a conspiracy that I'd like to see him substantiate at all.
And the police come and say, you're not allowed to criticize the lockdown and arrest them
and disappear them.
And by the way, a lot of these people, we need to try to get them on Daria.
Remember that Swedish couple was panicking and they come and she was organizing a demonstration
and they arrested her husband.
They'd never been seen again.
Last time I heard check on them, same thing in Australia.
They've disappeared.
Thousands of people, members of city councils that said, no, we're taking a military base.
Some were never seen again.
What?
There's a big difference between you not checking.
This is what I'm saying.
This is object permanence.
Yes.
If they still existed, we would have heard about them in the news again.
Yeah.
Since we haven't heard about them in the news.
They've never been seen.
They've been killed.
They've been disappeared.
That's the explanation.
Yeah.
That's really sloppy.
That's all it takes.
Yeah.
I would assume.
I have not seen my delivery driver for the Chinese food that I got last night for 24
hours.
And I'm thinking about filing a missing person.
That's scary.
I would assume that if city council members were being disappeared, there would be openings
on city councils that were very suspicious.
We would at least have elections.
We'd have a runoff.
Why?
Because we elected somebody.
Oh, somebody disappeared.
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
Would you update their Wikipedia page?
One thing that would happen there is paperwork.
Sure.
Yeah, definitely.
You'd be able to point to something.
Definitely.
There would be paperwork.
Conspicuous in its absence from any of this is any proof.
And when Alex says there's this Swedish couple, they've never been seen again.
We should look into them.
Like that tells me you haven't.
Yeah.
And you're making that up.
Would you say it?
Yeah.
So Alex goes to calls.
He takes some calls.
And one of them he offers a job to.
And this guy is somebody who he'd previously offered a job to.
And he's like, hey, you said give me a half hour show or something.
And Alex is like, oh, yeah, man, we're going to start that up soon.
He's still planning on starting that show with callers up soon.
But yeah, so here's what this caller's theory is about what the Dems are up to.
I feel like the left is winding up their people.
They projected this win so that when Trump does win on the day of the eclipse with December
14th, when it all gets sorted out, I feel like this is going to create bedlam in the
streets.
And that's why I feel like they're going right into the COVID news now to create a lockdown
scenario and all those leftist areas to lock those people down, to suppress them even more,
so that they go crazy when Trump wins to really stoke this civil war.
And I feel like that's that's really what they set up so that I totally agree with you.
I totally agree with you, sir.
What else do you think's coming?
I feel like what you were saying about the bio attack thing.
I feel like just just going with God here and looking at the alignment and God's handiwork
here.
Just there's a great conjunction on December 21st.
Oh, my an apocalypse.
Wow.
It's back.
I'm sick of conjunctions.
Eight years later, it's back sick of conjunctions.
So that eclipse that's happening on December 14th isn't going to be visible in any part
of North America, but they will be able to feel it.
It's only going to be seen in South America, parts of northern Antarctica and some of southwest
Africa.
I have no idea why that would be significant in the United States, but go off, whatever.
It's an eclipse.
Eclipses are global events, Dan.
It's the sun and the moon and they're doing a whole thing.
They're spinning all the time.
I grow weary of these sorts of ideas being brought to Alex's attention and being like,
I fucking agree.
I fucking love it.
Totally agree.
I'm right.
They're knocking leftists down to whip them up into a frenzy.
So whenever Trump definitely doesn't steal the election and wins it outright, they'll
be whipped into an insane frenzy and start the civil war.
And they knew that all of this.
They knew all of it.
They knew they had to do all of this right now because the stars are aligning and there's
an eclipse on December 14th.
It's the eclipse.
They got to do it.
You know what I grow weary of?
Anybody who dares take this shit seriously.
Anybody who has the pretense of like, no, he actually has some really good ideas.
He's really, he's right about more than he's wrong about.
Yeah.
Go fuck yourself.
Fuck yourself.
You never listen to this show.
If you listen to this shit, you'd be like, Oh, God damn it.
Anybody, anybody.
I challenge them.
If they think that Alex is more right than he's wrong.
No kidding.
Explain away.
Tell me, tell me about how eclipses are part of the fucking plan.
And every civilization's ended because of priests eating people.
Yeah.
In only a hundred years.
And all of the people are dead.
To be fair, sometimes it was like a hundred years.
Okay.
There's different time frames.
Sure.
But it always ends up with a human barbecue.
Every civilization that's turned its back to Christ, Dan.
Totally.
It falls apart.
Yep.
So instead of just handing off the baton to Harrison Smith on this episode, Alex has
a little bit of a fancy maneuver and that is he has Ezra Levant from Rebel Media come
on to host for a couple of segments and then Harrison takes over.
Nice.
So Alex still gets to leave early.
Nicely done.
Ezra Levant is coming up very excited.
I'm going to interview him for a segment that I'm, he's a great talk show host, his own
right with Rebel Media.
He's going to take over two segments and then we're going to have Harrison Smith and Owen
Schroyer hosting from DC.
Harrison's back in Austin, Texas.
The interview is not very interesting at all.
And the only other clip Alex has on this show before he leaves, I think is interesting in
any way as this.
But man, I, let me tell you, Trump won on a landslide.
Everyone I know believes Trump won black, white, Hispanic, old, young.
I mean, it's like 60% support Trump.
Everybody knew Trump was working his ass off.
No one votes for that dead zombie Biden and Kamala that had half a percent support Democrats.
Everyone hates them.
That's why the globalist chose them because they're such weak puppets.
They can control them.
So I think we have 60%.
It's just, we have to convince ourselves that we are the majority and start not complying.
This is in reference to a caller who's like 3% in polls believe Trump won the election.
Yeah.
Alex is like, I think we got 60.
I think it's a hundred percent.
Yeah.
Oh Jesus.
So, um, he talks to Ezra Levant.
It's un-consequential and then the show wraps up.
I think what, what frustrates me the most is that the principle reason that Alex and
the conservatives like Trump is because he's a dick to libs.
Yeah.
Lib tears.
Did it never occur to you that that would motivate libs?
Right?
Uh, yeah.
Like say, say, okay, fine.
Say that nobody's voting for Biden.
The principle factor of your guy is making a lot of people hate him.
Yeah.
That's motivating.
And then when you add on like the existential danger that he presents to vulnerable populations,
you can probably galvanize quite a bit of support that way as well.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
It's all just dumb.
Yeah.
Anyway, on Friday the convoy arrived in DC and at that point it's really kind of pointless
to discuss it as it being its own thing anymore.
Yeah.
From that point on the caravan just became another group of participants in the larger
very sad display in DC.
Here's a little clip of Owen, uh, I guess this is their point now.
Okay.
Yeah.
I've been trying out a new chant actually on this road trip.
You guys want to try this with me?
I think everybody agrees with this.
I'm not sure.
So if you, if you don't agree with this, you can just hang your head.
Government sucks.
I don't know what they're doing.
Oh man.
I don't.
Oh God.
Yes.
We've been wildly obsessed with electoral politics for the last little while and yet
here we are trying to overturn an election while yelling government sucks.
I just, I just, you guys don't understand anything.
Well, I mean, if you want to be anarchist, go for it.
No, of course.
But don't do that.
But they don't want to be anarchists.
They hate anarchists.
God.
I hate these people.
Yeah.
A government that is not fully in line with exactly what we want in a way that represses
the people we don't like sucks.
That's the real chant.
Non-nazis suck.
Yes.
On the one hand, it's only fair that I congratulate Owen for being able to get to DC theoretically
on time.
Lost me 50 bucks.
In hindsight, this was a miscalculation on my part because I thought that they were actually
planning to do things in the cities that they went to, not just drop in on ongoing rallies
for about 15 minutes before leaving.
They were able to achieve their goals on their trip because they had no goals.
So I guess I just overestimated the project.
You put together that time schedule where I was like, yeah, I would say two hours is
about right for a rally.
You know, you're going to go do some glad-handing.
Maybe you want to see something in the town too.
Totally.
Like it's awesome to go around America.
Maybe you go like, and I know from the times that I've been on the road, like there's just
unexpected shit.
Like you might have to take a shit.
You might have to pull over at a rest stop for a couple minutes and sometimes you might
get lost.
How many times have you been on the road and been like, we're 10 minutes, we're 15 minutes
off track.
It's the doubling back.
Now you've lost half an hour.
It's the best.
Yeah.
You might even stop and see the world's largest blank.
It's the best.
I think that they probably weren't on time for most of it, but they did end up pulling
it off and the trip ended up.
So like, congratulations.
I mean, but they set the bar so low for success.
I had more ambition for them than they did.
Of course we did.
That's kind of sad.
This is why we're here.
Yeah.
With that congratulation out of the way, I have to say that this was one of the most
pathetic, dismal, embarrassing, and childish weekends I've ever seen in this country.
The prelude of Alex's completely pointless and poorly attended caravan tour is what made
me pay closer attention, but if not for that aspect, I think I might have given this entire
million MAGA march nonsense a pass in terms of attention.
Fuck it.
The turnout on Saturday was in the tens of thousands, but nowhere near their goal of
a million people, and well below the 400,000 plus who came to DC for the 2017 Women's March.
It doesn't even come close to the turnout for Jon Stewart and Stephen Colbert's rally
to restore sanity and or fear back in 2010.
There are two pieces of the puzzle here that are important to recognize are both true and
seem at odds with each other, but are not.
The first is that this rally was a horrible failure.
The turnout wasn't even close to what the organizers and propagandists like Alex would
have wanted, having built this up as their last fight for the country.
The fact that they did a poorly attended caravan leading up to the march only serves to highlight
how thin the support for their cause is in other cities around the country, even in the
more conservative leaning south.
Their attempt at creating optics of the country speaking out in support of Trump has really
only proven that their best shot isn't even a fraction of the people who will come out
to support reproductive rights or civil rights protections.
There's gonna be excuses for the small turnout, and there'll be pictures that do look like
million people, but they're far less.
There have already been a ton of attempts to use pictures from the Women's March or
the March for Our Lives protests, which have been erroneously claimed to have been from
this weekend.
Naturally.
There have also been edited videos of Trump supporters being attacked, where the context
of them initiating the violence was left out.
These will be the attempts to salvage what the Trump scammers can from this utter failure
of a rally.
The second piece of the puzzle is that the turnout was still way too high.
And that's because this rally was explicitly radical.
This was not a political rally, in the sense that like a march supporting the Second Amendment
or a march protesting a tax hike might be.
The only reason this rally was happening is that these people decided to show up to say
they don't want to follow the rules of the country anymore.
Whenever there's a new president elected, the side that doesn't win will often hold
demonstrations, and you're likely to hear people chanting stuff like, not my president,
and I bet you could find small pockets of people in those protests who insist the election
itself was invalid and the results aren't real.
This weekend's rally was an entire rally that just consisted of that small pocket, which
is now, I guess, the right wing.
This rally was a collection of really fucked up weirdos.
Alex Jones had the Proud Boys giving him security, apparently one of whom had a Pinochet did
nothing wrong shirt on.
The Oath Keepers may or may not have had men stationed around the city in case shit got
hot.
Great.
Nick Fuentes and his grippers walked around as completely normal participants in the affair.
QAnon weirdos were all around.
Naturally.
This seeming contradiction is the same thing that haunted every stop on the caravan.
In every city, the turnout they got was minuscule compared to the way they present their audience.
Every event they held would be considered a flop by anyone who seriously had the self-image
that they do.
But they don't mean it when they describe how popular they are.
It's kind of a joke.
They know they're lying, just like Alex does when he says there were 400 cars in the caravan.
That's a lie for the benefit of the listener in the middle of nowhere who thinks they're
hearing dispatches from the front line, not realizing that they're being deceived to sell
them pills.
They don't care that there's no one at the actual rally, because on some level everyone
at Infos has to know that in a sane world, no one would show up at their rallies.
Nine people showing up to send them off in Austin is more than they deserve, based on
their credibility, work ethic, and integrity.
Indeed.
This is the same dynamic at the DC rally.
The turnout is a disaster, if you're looking at it as a sincere attempt at a political
rally.
If you're looking at it for what it is, which is a collection of people living in a completely
fractured reality that's at odds with our reality and sees our reality as hostile, then
the turnout should be terrifying in a wake-up call.
Any event that would allow people like Nick Fuentes and Alex Jones to speak on their stages
is not a political event, and I worry that some people there, or some people who might
have seen coverage of the rally, they might not understand that dynamic, and how extreme
the stuff they're seeing actually is.
I don't know what to think about what the future holds, but I do have a couple of main
thoughts that came up.
The first is that Alex's messaging to his audience is completely out of sync with his
public behavior.
In this period where he's going to DC and joining in this rally that's trying to reinstall
Trump as the president of the country, he's simultaneously telling his audience that there's
no hope and everyone's gonna die, so everyone needs to head to the hills.
This messaging is discordant, and it kind of gives you the impression that his primary
focus is attention-seeking behavior and selling survival food buckets.
The second is that we are about to be entering a period where fantasies and alternative realities
on the extreme right are going to be coming into large-scale conflict with what I'm going
to call reality.
As more and more excuses for why these fantasies aren't coming true become unconvincing, the
need to escalate will be ever-present.
Whereas before, in his earlier career, Alex could justify his conspiracies by pointing
to the Federal Reserve, now in the era of Trump, in order to make anything he's saying
make sense, he needs to evoke the literal devil, end-times prophecies, outrageously
complicated and nonsensical conspiracies, and insistences that everyone he doesn't like
is a pedophile.
Without strong forces pushing in the opposite direction, this road only leads to deeper
extremism.
There's no point where someone like Alex will be like, all right, good job, we achieved
our goals.
If he ever reached his impossible-to-attain goal of eliminating all the globalists, I
would bet everything that I own that he'd magically find a new sect of neo-globalists
and just knock me down with a feather, they all happen to not be white.
What I'm saying is, I'm worried.
Well, I mean, extremism on the right has always been there, obviously, they're the right,
that's kind of their position.
But in electoral politics, you used to be able to give them a bone, like, oh, George
W. Bush lowered the marginal tax rate.
That's like a little pressure valve.
We gotta win.
The president gave us something, we elected him, and we got the win that we were looking
for.
Now, all of the wins that they want are either imaginary, and so cannot be achieved, or impossible,
and so also cannot be achieved, or we'll kill everyone, so hopefully will not be achieved.
Well, even the imaginary- So there's no pressure valve, you know, other
than violence, really.
The imaginary and the impossible ones, the practical real-world versions of them are
exactly what it would look like if someone were taking authoritarian rule.
Exactly.
It would be like the prosecution, targeted prosecution of the leadership of the opposition
party.
Totally.
Yeah, we want Hillary to go to prison.
That's not going to happen, guys.
Right, yeah, yeah.
The real-world version of any kind of thing that would be like, ah, yes, we've gotten
what we want, would be-
Public execution, you know?
So it's like, there's no pressure release valve.
And if Trump, if the right hadn't have weaponized imagination, then they could have been like,
oh, well, Trump put up fucking, he dropped environmental protection, so we win.
But nobody gives a shit about that on the right, they just want fucking murder.
If Alex wants to try and continue his brain, he should just be focusing on the fact that
Trump got out of the TPP, or whatever, and stay on that talking point and be like, let's
build from there.
But he can't.
And your messaging on the right was never economic anxiety, it used to come off that
way, but now it's just full-on racism.
So you can't even be like, oh, well, we got out of the TPP because of economic anxiety
or anything like that.
It's like-
Well, you might want to tell the Times that.
Yeah.
I think that it's really worrisome, just the rally itself in DC was worrying.
This is an attempt to take over fully the GOP, with these scam artists, these Trump
scam folk.
Yep.
And I think that's probably wise of them, I think it's the only thing they can do.
It's their best shot now.
Yeah.
Although they'll end up in a turf war with QAnon soon enough, and then they'll fracture
the party and then Democrats will win every election moving forward.
That's probably our, the most likely outcome of that in the long term is they will eventually
kill each other.
They'll destroy themselves from within.
Or at least diminish their own electoral power.
Sure, sure, sure.
But I meant metaphysically, metaphorically, not, you know.
But that's like the long term.
The short term is fucked up shit.
Yes, yes it is.
It's always fucked up shit.
Yes it is.
And it's very scary.
Fuck.
Yep.
Oh, well.
Anyway.
Hey!
Much like everything on Knowledge Fight, this Caravanity project has started fun and
ended up depressing.
So great.
The good news is, though, in South Carolina they did find a homeless man with a computer
chip in his hand, but they couldn't get footage of it.
He gave him that Nazi book.
Exactly, there's the problem.
That's what happened.
So I resent this so much.
They ruin my fun.
I just-
Wanna have fun!
They just don't understand how to do anything.
Yeah.
Anything.
How much fun would it be if one of the videos is just like, Owen being like, alright, we're
gonna go to this North Carolina, we're gonna go to this Raleigh event, but you know what?
While we're in town, I'm gonna try and find the best hot dog.
Totally!
Something!
Anything!
Some personality other than we're angry.
Yeah, yeah.
Wham!
We're angry and we're sensitive.
Yeah.
That's it.
Like we're angry and we're like, please don't hit us with milkshakes, god damn it.
You gotta suck.
Gotta hit the car wash.
Yeah, oh man.
Anyway, thank you all for joining us on this Care of Vanity project.
Yes, indeed.
I think that I need a day off, and so I think we will be back at the end of the week.
Yes.
I think we'll have an episode on Friday this week.
I believe so, yeah.
Because I also just don't think that Alex is gonna be, like, back to putting out some
content that I can cover in time for Wednesday's episode or anything.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I don't wanna, look, sorry guys, everybody out there, sorry, I don't wanna cover Alex
going on Tim Pool.
Yeah!
I don't wanna cover.
I don't respect Tim Pool enough to deconstruct an episode of his squirrely ass.
Plenty of people told me that Alex was on Tim Pool and I was like, who the fuck is Tim
Pool and why would I give a shit?
Yeah.
He's somewhat relevant to the worlds that we cover, but I just, I find him so insufferable.
And also he seems like somebody who might bother me.
What type of douchebag is he?
He seems like the kind of guy who might email me.
Oh, who's gonna try and fuck you.
If we do an episode about him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I just don't even wanna deal with that.
Okay.
I don't wanna wake up some day and see a notification to Tim Pool wants to debate or something.
I just don't wanna do it.
So yeah, I don't know, I don't think I'm gonna do that.
But maybe sometime in the future, maybe as sort of a look back thing, but there's no
immediacy.
I have no interest in covering it the same way we might cover Rogan.
Yeah.
Anyway, we'll be back at the end of the week, but until then we have a website.
We do have a website, it's knowledgefight.com.
Yes, we're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at Knowledge Underscore Fight and I go do Ben Jordan.
Yep, we're on Facebook.
We are on Facebook!
It's a dollar show, right?
Revive to use this.
And if you could, please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work.
Yep, we'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo, I'm Leo, I'm DZX Clark, I'm Daryl Rundis.
I am that trucker who threw a milkshake at the dude in the caravan.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.