N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Damn, Ed, Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledgefight, knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying, we are the bad guys.
N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight Dan and Jordan, knowledge fight.
N-N-N-Knowledge Fight Need money, need money, need money, need money.
N-N-N-Knowledge Fight Andy in Kansas, Andy in Kansas.
Stop it.
Andy in Kansas, Andy in Kansas, Andy in Kansas, Andy in Kansas, Andy in Kansas.
It's time to pray.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex, I'm a freshman in college, I'm a huge fan, I love your room.
Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fed, I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're couple dudes that sit around, drink novelty beverages and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones.
Oh indeed we are, Dan.
Jordan.
Dan!
Jordan!
Quick question for you.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today is, uh, Socratesian.
Socratesian.
In that it is, uh, know thyself.
Oh, it wasn't just the word Socratesian.
No, no.
It is the, uh, the Oracle of Delphi.
Okay.
Uh, whatever the fuck.
I'm thinking about myself.
Yes.
Um, because I, I started to think about, uh, stuff earlier this week and I was thinking
about like, what do I know about myself?
And I'm like, well, I like spicy stuff.
Sure.
And I just so happened...
That's a good starting point.
I just so happened to have a spice challenge sitting around that we were going to eat on
camera.
Yes, yes!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The nuts.
No, it wasn't the nuts.
It was the, uh, the white chocolate bar.
Oh, the white chocolate bar.
Oh, shit.
Lightening, I believe, is the name of it.
And I bought this white, uh, this white chocolate bar that has a bunch of chilis in it.
Sure.
Because I was like, uh, hey, that sounds interesting.
Second, they were giving, uh, meals to charity for every bar that they sold.
Sure.
So it was sort of a charity drive.
I was like, I'll buy this.
Eh, eh, eh.
And we'll try it and we'll have some fun.
Yeah.
Now, it was sitting on my counter and I thought to myself, would I enjoy this without an audience?
That's a good question.
Would I enjoy this spice, like, crazy hot thing without the added element of people
watching me eat it?
Sure.
Can I enjoy this without it being content?
And now we get to know thyself.
Exactly.
Yes.
I don't like spicy stuff that much.
Because I ate about half of it alone and I thought it was terrible.
It sucked.
Aw, damn.
I don't know if I'm getting older or what, but, like, it was unpleasant.
I found it to be too much.
It hurt.
It's all punctured.
You don't like fucking spicy things.
You don't like seltzers.
You're not gonna like vinegars anymore.
I do like seltzers.
Just some.
All these plants are alive.
They're all fake.
They're great.
All this shit is bullshit, dad.
It's all about worms now.
Is anybody even actually listening to this show?
Nope.
Is this just you and me?
I have all these sock puppet accounts.
Are you trolling me with the greatest troll it is?
I have fake addresses I'm sending buttons to, yes.
That is what's going on.
No.
That's a good scam.
I still really like spicy stuff, but I don't like really spicy stuff, I think.
I think that, you know, I don't know, maybe it was late 20s, early 30s, I was in a real
extreme spice kind of place.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And now- Got your picture on a wall everywhere.
Sure.
I've achieved.
Yeah.
I've achieved something.
Yes, yes.
And I think that maybe it's just over for me, for the extreme spice.
So I will be getting a hot, as opposed to an extra hot, at the Thai place in the future,
and I think that's okay.
I agree.
That is okay.
That is my bright spot, is accepting that about myself.
I like it.
How about you?
My bright spot, Dan, is piano solos.
Okay.
Piano solos is my bright spot.
Well, actually, this is a mix of a great bright spot and a bit of a sad note.
I was listening to- The outro to Layla?
Very, very sad.
Nicely done.
I was listening to Yoko Kanno play the piano solo on Adieu from the Cowboy Bebop soundtrack,
and it's a really, really good piano solo.
Second only to the outro from Layla.
It's very Thelonious Monk in its syncopation.
It's really, really good.
And then I was thinking about my favorite pianist of all time is Keith Jarrett.
Okay.
Do you know who Keith Jarrett is?
I do not.
He is a jazz pianist who will give these literally hour and a half long improvised piano concerts
where it's basically just him for an hour and a half, and he's fucking-
Just tickling the 88s.
Riveting.
His music is beautiful, and he is incredible.
He's a dynamite performer.
That's great.
And I just found out that he had a stroke.
Oh, no.
Yeah, and he's lost the ability to use his right hand, or I can't remember.
It's one of his hands, though, so he'll probably never play live again.
Maybe not.
Maybe he'll be the Def Leppard drummer of piano.
If anybody could do it, I'm telling you, he is incredible.
So I'm pouring one out for Keith Jarrett's hand until such time as it recovers.
That's very sentimental, and we're wishing the best.
Yeah, if you get the chance, listen to one of his live albums.
I want to transition into a less sad thought, more of like, why my brain is bad.
I was thinking the whole time you were talking, we've had pianos for a very long time now.
I can't imagine anyone's doing anything new with them.
Fair.
You're telling me about how great he is.
Okay.
All right.
I was like, yeah, I think we've done the piano stuff.
Let's start talking about numbers.
How many keys does a piano have?
88, baby.
How many different possible combinations of 88 over any number of measures are there?
Well, I mean, some of them don't sound good.
That's why you're looking for the good ones, man.
Right.
But we've had a lot of time.
Sure.
Just because there are an infinite number of possible combinations.
You say that.
It is because it's true.
Yeah.
I think I might be done with all music.
We did it, guys.
Yeah.
Wrap it up.
We got all the music we need.
Now, see, here's why my brain doesn't work again.
You're like, let's talk numbers.
I'm like, yeah, wait, we've done everything we can with numbers too.
What about the set of infinite numbers?
I'm in a weird head space.
A set of whole numbers is infinite.
Anyway, Jordan, today we've got an interesting episode to go over.
We're talking about November 16th and 17th, 2020.
Dan, this is 2020.
Sounds good.
Whoa.
That's right.
Holy shit.
We're doing it.
Wow.
You're leaning into the end of the year.
I finally reached it.
It's 11...
How many...
This has been what?
11 months.
It's been 11 episodes since you started doing Dan, this is 2020.
I got to accept it sooner or later.
Yes.
It's just how it's got to go.
Sometimes submission is what you need.
Sometimes you need to submit to the universe, and when the universe insists on saying this
thing, you just kind of have to accept it.
I'm going to be honest.
It feels a little bit like the end of 1984 with this bit here.
I just love the government now, Dan.
Great.
I'm Dan.
This is the government.
So, this is a stretch of time that I think is a little bit of a stopgap.
We're talking about the beginning of this week, Monday and Tuesday.
And there's a reason.
And our Monday episode will pick up on Wednesday and go through the rest of the week.
And everybody who's listened to this probably already knows, Alex has gone down to Atlanta
because there's a protest in to do, and he's got to try and stop the steal.
He's on his... and I kind of feel like that's an extension of the caravan.
Alex went down to Georgia looking for an election to steal.
That's what's happening here.
Well, yeah.
So I just... hold on to that thought.
Okay.
Alex is going to Georgia and doing all this stuff.
And I kind of... it's not obviously part of the caravan, and the caravan went through
Atlanta on its way up to DC.
So they've already just been there.
But it kind of has the same spiritual energy of like Infowars on the road.
Right, right, right.
It's a bit of a sequel.
Yeah, so Monday we'll have the sequel of Alex's adventure in Atlanta.
And this is this interstitial period where Alex is back in Austin, in studio, and complaining
a whole bunch.
It's kind of like Steve Coogan and Rob Brydon in The Trip.
Sure.
Yes.
So we'll get down to business on this episode, but before we do we've got to take a moment
to say thank you to some folks who've signed up and are supporting the show.
That's a great idea.
So first, Gap Tooth Killah, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk!
Thank you very much, GTK.
Thank you so much next, Andrew G. Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Andrew.
Were you about to say Andrew Dice, Clay?
WK!
Okay, I gotcha.
All right.
Next, another lunatic.
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, another lunatic.
Next, Bill and Virginia Warren.
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Bill of Virginia.
Thank you. Next, Creator, and it's spelled C-R-E-8-H-E-R.
Thank you so much. You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Creator.
Thank you so much. Next, Dave.
Thank you so much. You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, Dave.
I like a good Dave.
Yeah, for sure.
Serengeti.
Do you like the movie, Dave?
No, not a fan.
Ooh.
Had nothing to say and followed up to it.
Nope, nope. We're good.
That's fine.
Next, Tiger High Eats License Plates and Chicom Globalists.
Thank you so much. You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
That stuff.
And finally, I'd like to say thank you to a couple of people who donated on Elevated Level.
We appreciate that very much.
So, Chris E., thank you so much. You are now a technocrat.
And Sarah McAfee, thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate. That's fantastic. Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right, we got to go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much, Chris.
And thank you so much, Sarah.
Yes, thank you very much to the both of you.
If you're out there listening and you're thinking,
hey, I enjoy the show, I'd like to support these gents.
You can do that by going to our website, knowledgefight.com,
clicking the button that says support the show.
We would appreciate it.
Indeed, we would.
Or.
Or what you could do if you find yourself filled with a generous spirit
and you need to express that.
Find your way over to a little device that has 88 keys on it
and play one of the 10 approved songs that Dan allows.
And then use that generous spirit to express music in a way
that gets you to local charity or bail fund.
I lost it a little bit at the end because of your bitter rage towards pianos.
You think there's actually 10?
How many would you bet?
Six.
Six?
Anyway, here's an out of context drop from today's show.
Sounds good.
God acts through math, and math tells us that the Democrats cheated.
This is just logic.
This makes sense.
You can't refute that.
I'm just real done with God.
He acts through math.
So in this first clip where we start off the show,
Alex, boy, I think on our last episode,
he had to go off air or threatened to go off air twice.
Indeed.
He's now switching it up and just going off air as soon as the show begins.
I like it.
We have massive breaking news.
I actually have to go off air for a few minutes and talk to some insiders.
I'll leave it at that on how the Clintons are now stealing Georgia,
preparing to criminally certify it and how serious the situation is.
But we have a path forward.
First, I want to play a little bit of my speech yesterday.
Again, I'm your host, Alex Jones,
and my speech from Saturday at the million Trump march
that now they're estimating may have had close to a million people at it.
It's historic.
No, no, no, no, they're not.
No, they're not estimating that.
Who is estimating that?
Him, Alex's.
They is doing a lot of work there.
So Alex is getting this information that they're trying to steal Georgia.
And so as we know, by the end of this, Alex will head to Atlanta
to meet up with Ali Alexander, who's doing the stop the steal thing.
Doing great stuff.
And I wanted to stop you before you started talking about Alex going to Georgia.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because I've written a song.
Now, I'm sorry for stepping on.
You are one of six songs.
I do think that this episode is not as good as I want it to be.
There's not as much happening.
Alex is kind of just talking about how Georgia needs to.
It's on his mind.
Yeah, nicely done.
And now it needs to they need to take it over and what have you.
And so I thought as a bonus to the audience and to the people,
yes, I would write my own version of The Devil Went Down to Georgia.
But about Alex and Ali Alexander.
Do you have accompaniment?
No, no.
I want to get a piano.
Certainly not.
Oh, damn it.
I might want to do some mouth sounds.
OK, all right. I'll take that.
Alex went down to Georgia.
He was looking to stop the steal.
His sales were down.
His staff's a clown and the situation is an ordeal.
When he came across this young man spinning a yarn and spinning it hot.
And Alex jumped up on top of his tank and said, boy, let me tell you what.
I guess you didn't know it, but I'm a bullshit artist, too.
And if you care to dare, I'd like to work with you.
Now you spin a mighty fine yarn, boy, but give the Texan his due.
I need your skills to sell my pills, but I'm still better than you.
The boy said, my name's Ali and it might be unwise,
but I'll join your scam to make some clams because I only have shameful allies.
Meter was a little off.
You know what?
I'm going to give that one to you.
Thank you.
Perfect so far.
Just keep on rolling.
Ali rising up your theories and push your talking points hard
because there's profit to make in Georgia and Alex is a blowhard.
If this works the money and re-noun are all yours,
but if you don't you'll end up working for wars!
Alex mumbled about his obsession with the unborn and flyer.
I might have taken that one from the top.
I'm going to be honest with you, you just don't get this from other political podcasts.
You just don't.
Alex mumbled about his obsession with the unborn and fire flew from his fingertips when
he gripped his tiny bullhorn and he pushed the talk button and there was a static hiss.
He'd forgotten to replace the batteries so it sounded something like this.
As Alex fumbled, Ali said, your tech problems are sad, old son.
I know you have a million dollar studio, but let me show you how it's done.
Fraud in the votes.
Run boys, run.
All you have to do is say dominion.
Pretend QAnon shit is solid info.
Is Roger Stone pulling my strings?
No child, no.
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do,
Alex got a miss- I didn't think there was any way there was
another verse.
There's a, there's a conclusion.
Sir, you are going for it.
There's a conclusion.
Your commitment to this is fucking fantastic.
There's a story being told here.
No, I, I'm with you.
Alex got a misty look in his eye because he knew he'd met a friend and he offered Ali
his tiny bullhorn, handing it by the speaker end.
Ali said, can you call Larry Nichols about that congressional blackmail?
And I done told you once, you son of a bitch, stop extending the Easter sale.
So, that's, someone put that to music.
Before the show, you were telling me, you know what, it's been real hard to do any kind
of thinky work.
You've been struggling.
Why'd you do that?
Now I realize that it's just been the song.
It's just been the song.
That took me maybe half an hour.
Uh, yeah, so someone put that to music.
Alex went down to Georgia.
Looking to stop the steal.
DJ Danerkey is going to turn that into an absolute banger.
We're going to get what number one on the billboard charts.
So, uh, the Democrats, they're trying to steal that election in Georgia.
Why?
They already won it though.
Well, they're going to steal it.
And they better be, you know, Thursday apparently is the deadline.
We're recording this on Thursday.
Oh shit.
I have been on the phone with people in the Trump campaign.
I've been on the phone with a lot of different top political strategists and for all intents
and purposes, this election could be over for president Trump Thursday, last Thursday,
hold on.
He'll still not leave office because the fraud is real, but it will give them perception
that the election has been certified and it'll make the road towards the lighthouse for the
second Trump term.
And I was taking our country back very, very hard.
Yeah, no shit that will, that will make things more challenging.
Yeah.
Yes.
The process continuing to move along as it's supposed to will make derailing the process
more difficult.
My car being turned into a cube will make it difficult to drive from here on out.
Yeah, that's true.
That is, that is true.
Having your wheels taken.
Yeah.
It's a hindrance.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
Having my feet cut off will really make it harder to play football.
Yes.
Yeah.
So Alex is not the only one who's heading down to Georgia.
Of course, Ali Alexander is, is going down there.
Sure.
Some other noted weirdos.
Right.
But Alex thinks that everybody needs to go to Georgia.
Sure.
And I would like to just point out again, I don't, I don't want to keep beating a dead
horse and I love that caravan.
The caravan went to Georgia.
Yes, it did.
And it was, and it was wildly successful.
You already did.
No, no, no.
It was wildly successful.
And so they need to do it again.
Sure.
Okay.
You better start getting on the plane or in the car and heading to the capital of Georgia.
Can't remember what it is.
That is all unfolding right now.
Too many black people live there.
Because we can force the legislature to force the governor to order an emergency session
and not certify it.
The legislature must stand up now with the governor who works for the Clintons, not just
his chief of staff is the problem.
That's coming up next segment.
I got to refuel though here.
We need funding.
Yeah, no shit.
Of course.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I find this unconvincing, uninteresting.
Yeah.
I'm a little bit blown away by the, the level to which they're willing to embarrass themselves
without actually.
Are you talking about Rudy?
I'm talking about the whole, the whole, the whole kitten caboose.
They're all teaming up to make everything a sick joke.
And it's weird me out because that suggests to me that we're going to have to escalate
from sick joke to full on military takeover or, or they're just going to, I don't know.
You know, he's not just going to go.
You notice how I escalated.
I wrote a parody.
Yeah, exactly.
He's not just going to go.
It's not just going to go.
So here we go.
Let's ride this.
I don't know why everyone's acting like we can just wait and he'll just go.
Well, I think that's one of the good re like the reasons why I'm really glad that our show
is about Alex Jones.
Yeah.
Because at least I know he's full of shit.
I don't know what's going on in terms of other places and that's very scary to me.
So I'd rather not have, uh, you know, an opinion that people take too seriously on it because
I could be wrong.
Right.
I could misinterpret something with Alex totally fine saying he is full of shit, full of shit,
trying to get attention and push extremist views.
We can handle that.
Yeah.
And then along the way, sometimes there's something really fun.
Like look, Hey, it's always fun to write a parody song of the devil went down in Georgia.
True.
It's been done a lot.
A lot.
Cause it's great.
Yeah.
Another thing that's fun is when Alex says things like this.
Imagine a doctor who episode where the Daleks are always little robots rolling around like
R2D2 saying, exterminate, exterminate.
But it said, they said, hello, my friend, I'm here to test you for the COVID.
Oh, sorry.
You've got it.
You've got to go away.
That would be a very different villain.
And now they actually in Japan and Europe have Daleks.
They look just like Daleks, right out of Dr. Who, whoever signed it copied a Dalek.
Sure.
And they come up and stick a swab up your nose.
And if you don't, an inner hatch opens up and a gun comes up.
I want one of those.
I want one of those right now.
I want a swab to gun transfer out of one barrel.
I love that so much.
All right.
So there's this robot that's going around and it's programmed, I guess, because he's
not saying that someone's captaining this robot.
I assume the robot comes up to you and it's supposed to swab you and somehow it's in its
programming that if you refuse, it shakes you down with a gun.
It threatens you with a gun, presumably not shooting you if you then agree to get the
swab.
No, of course not.
It's traditional carrot and stick.
All right.
Here's your swab or here's your gun.
Turns out you're going to choose the swab in the end.
Carrot, carrot, stick, swab, gun.
It's all the same.
It's all the same thing.
I think...
Why would you even need...
I would prefer a knife.
If it just switched from a swab to a knife and it's like, one of these is going up your
nose today, you choose.
These machines would be made by doctors who I assume would not prioritize gun.
All right, the head of the Mayo Clinic is a real gun nut.
Yeah.
All right.
So we're developing this robot that's specifically to test people for COVID to make it so people
don't have to risk getting exposed to run tests.
I feel like you didn't answer my only question.
Of course it has gone.
See?
Now we're in business.
I will green light anything.
This is amazing.
It's in the news.
I'm going to need a citation on this.
I'm going to need a source.
If anybody...
I looked it up, I could not find information on this.
Although I think what he's referring to is that there are robots that are used for COVID
testing.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
In a number of countries, they've rolled out some models of these and I think he's combining
that with, there was a crowd control robot in China from maybe last year that they were
working on that would give little shocks to people to try and corral them in different
directions.
An R2D2 shock, yeah.
Yeah, I think he's mixing up those two things, but the mental image is so funny.
So if I take this swab, no, I will not.
What about now?
Now here's the thing that tickles me the most.
This is what tickles me the most.
The inside hatch.
The gun comes out.
That's what it is.
It's so great.
Yes.
That's what it's so great.
It's a perfect image.
It's so fucking funny.
It's the hatch.
Yeah.
Does it, does it shoot out with a cartoon, like spring, like boing.
Yeah, of course.
It's got a robot hand.
Yeah, exactly.
Stick them up.
And then it takes your wallet.
Oh boy, yeah.
Alright, I'm here for a showdown.
So this has been the fun part of the show.
Meet me at high noon.
So now Alex gets into like what, uh, you know, his sort of Georgia story line.
Okay.
And this is the big story.
Lawsuit.
Georgia Secretary of State signed a legal deal with Democrats challenging how ballots
are processed.
A law is going to be processed after and allowing mail-in ballots to be counted without actual
proof or signatures being confirmed and it just goes on from there.
This is another classic case of Alex getting a Trump talking point that's factually incorrect
and then it's spiraling out of control when he's recovering it into something else altogether.
In this case, Trump tweeted about how the, how Georgia was stealing the election and
that there had been a consent decree by the Secretary of State that quote, makes it impossible
to check and match signatures on ballots and envelopes, et cetera.
Trump went on to say, quote, they know, uh, they're, they knew they were going to cheat,
must expose real signatures.
This dude's tweeting like a detective in a shitty noir film who's just been shot, scrawling
on a piece of paper, must expose real signatures.
Anyway, I have no idea how a consent decree would make it impossible for people to compare
signatures, but I guess that's the best Trump's people can come up with to keep people like
Alex busy and keep people funneling money into that stopping of steals.
Sure, sure.
In reality, according to the Associated Press, the state absolutely requires signatures to
match.
The issue comes down to this quote, a lawsuit by the Democratic Party, which led to the
agreement, argued that minorities were disproportionately affected when they had their ballots rejected.
Among other things, the settlement set steps for local election officials to notify a voter
by phone, mail, or email in a timely fashion about problems with a signature.
Are they really trying to tell me that a state governed by Kemp has not done enough voter
suppression?
It's an interesting angle.
Right?
Yeah.
It's like he didn't win the election because it was free and fair, Dan.
Some have said that.
Like maybe if there were paper ballots, we might find out that the results might have
been different.
It could be.
Yeah.
And this is just another legal challenge that Trump's camp is making, trying to block the
finalization of the election, but it's going to get thrown out just like all the others.
The only thing I find really interesting here is the dynamic where Alex can't even really
understand what the issue is.
Alex thinks that it has to do with deadlines and votes without signatures, but that's not
the case.
The legal challenge has to do with whether or not the Secretary of State had the authority
to make the changes that were made, which were designed to create more oversight and
better handling of signature matching.
The suit doesn't seem to even take issue with the actual change that was made, just that
it was allegedly made unilaterally and without proper approval, which is pretty deep in the
weeds in terms of legal challenges to an election.
I'm not surprised Alex doesn't know the details on this.
I wouldn't expect him to, since being aware of how much of a Hail Mary this is would probably
be bad for business.
Can you imagine if that's what did it?
I believe that right before we started recording, this challenge got thrown out.
Yeah, of course.
I believe, if I understand the headline I just saw correctly, I believe this case has
just died.
It got thrown out the moment the judge realized that it was written in colored pencil.
Wow.
So, can you imagine if that's what, if all of a sudden they were like, oh, the Secretary
of State didn't do it right, so Trump is president again?
That's not how it goes.
No.
That's not how it's going to work for anyone.
I wouldn't assume it would.
So obviously, knowing that this is weak, Alex recommends the right course of action, which
is investing in gun robots.
I lied.
It's not.
Everyone must go to the capital of Georgia now, and you must surround the governor's
mansion now.
I'm coming.
I'll be there.
And I'm bringing Roger Stone, and I'm bringing a bunch of other people.
That's what I'm doing behind the scenes.
And I'm calling the damn White House, and I'm telling Trump he needs to go and get on
a frickin' airplane and land at the capital of Georgia and go into the governor's mansion
and stop sitting there and letting his lawyers do it.
We need to see people power, and this will do it.
Yeah, that's a great idea.
Let Trump storm the governor's mansion.
I think that's a great idea.
It would look cool.
I think the only thing that would be better, so that one is a great idea, and he should
definitely do that.
And then I think everybody in the Senate should stab him once.
I do love the idea that he's like, I'm coming to Georgia, and I'm fucking bringing Roger
Stone with me.
Who cares?
I want him to be like, and we're going to settle this election by single comment, combat.
Choose your champion for we have Roger Stone in this corner.
And then the camera pans over, and he's got a lampshade on his head.
Complaining about Elliot Spitzer or some shit.
Yeah, I'll fight whoever you fucking want.
I don't give a shit.
I will only fight if Elliot Spitzer's dad will come against me.
Where's Bongino?
So Alex has a little guest on this episode.
It's not a great sign.
All right, Enrique Torrio is an awesome American.
Oh no, that's not good.
He's the leader of the Proud Boys, and he was there helping provide security in DC for
us and did an incredible job.
So Enrique Torrio, guy who's the head of the Proud Boys, is on.
Cool.
See, this is the thing that I'm talking about.
How is it that we have the juxtaposition of Rudy Giuliani melting like a fucking candle
in front of us with Enrique Torrio being like, what if we killed all the leftists?
Like that's, you can't have both.
Here's what's interesting.
Enrique Torrio is clearly trying to learn a little bit about PR, because he's doing
some heavy lifting on this appearance, trying to give the, like, hey, we just like to hang
out.
You know, the Proud Boys, we're just like a drinking club.
We just like to have a good time, and hey, we don't just let anybody in.
We do extensive background checks on people like Rufio Panman, based stick man, did extensive
background searches, whatever the case.
He's trying to make it look much more respectable, and Alex is actually the one who's kind of
ruining it.
You know, when somebody, when a man's down, I don't want to keep attacking him.
These are people that attack women and children, and then as soon as you let them up, they
attack somebody else.
Yeah, of course.
Once they assault somebody, I think a good, some broken ribs will teach them.
So Alex seems to be the one who's pushing this towards even more extreme, and it seems
like a nerd talking to a bully, like interviewing a bully, who's like, oh, isn't it fun how
you kick their asses?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a good thing you're not bullying me.
You were kicking those guys' asses.
Yeah, it's great.
That's great.
Well, you know, when I beat people up, I kind of, you know, once they're down, it's kind
of, that's the end of the fight.
No, you should keep kicking them.
Yeah, Jesus.
Yeah, it's very strange.
Alex is kind of pushing.
You know, what we're trying to do is just show that we're a group of normal people like
everyone else.
I mean, we have our own political beliefs, but what we do is we get together and we just
share community, just like we do.
I think you should kill people.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey, Alex, we've gotten so much bad press, um, and a lot of our members turn out to be
real crazy.
Nazis.
Well, that's one word.
Well.
We do a lot of background checks, but apparently not on that kind of thing.
No, no, they can name a fuck ton of serials though.
That's important.
Exactly.
Look, here's the deal.
We're trying not to do all that shit publicly, all this stuff about kicking people when they're
down.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're trying to look different.
I know that the Oath Keepers and your buddy Stuart Rhodes kind of lean into that.
We're going to kill you stuff.
Sure.
It's great.
We're different.
Alex, Alex, buddy, there are two ways to go.
We're going underground, my friend.
We're going to survive and then we'll kill people again in 10 years or four or whatever.
We'll be, we'll make it through this.
We're not going to go out here all Nazi guns a blazing today.
And Alex is like, what if we're Nazis?
I think if I had to guess, I think it's just like glass half full, half empty in terms
of the DC rally.
I think that Alex is trying to play it like half full, like we are going to take over
the world.
Sure.
There was a million people there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whereas Enrique Torrio, it's probably like, yeah, it was a lot of people, but it wasn't
that many.
We can't take over the world with this many people.
Not enough.
Yeah.
So maybe try and put on a face of respectability.
Or invite general Petraeus and see if he'll do us a solid boom.
So Alex is impressed that I, I don't know if this is actually true.
I think it's not, but Alex thinks that no one has ever infiltrated the proud boys.
I don't think that's true.
But he has a theory as to why, and I think it's pretty funny.
I don't know how you guys have kept your organization pretty much infiltration free and how you
guys have done such a great job in the organization.
How do people get involved with proud boys and how are you keeping the organization in
infiltration free?
I mean, I guess you look at Antifa, they all look like devil-worshipping vampires.
Can't name any serious.
They're total cowards.
I guess all you guys look pretty macho.
Yeah, they're too macho to infiltrate, you know?
Yeah, leftists are, we just can't look macho enough to infiltrate the proud of us.
Too much soy or something.
Yeah, that's our issue.
Yeah.
So I think that Alex has a pretty consistent thread going of just like really gaslighting
his audience about the crowd size.
He's talking about like it's straight up, maybe even a million people there.
Real tough to sell.
Yeah.
And then something even more tough happens.
Police estimated upwards of a million bigger than Louis Farrakhan's event.
Incredible.
We're getting Gavin McGinnis lined up, dealing with some Skype issues.
Oh boy.
Oh, that's a surprise.
First of all, Skype issues, not a surprise.
Second of all, not a surprise that now we're getting Gavin on.
Oh man.
We're, we're really trying to infiltrate the proud boys, I guess.
I have this, I had this interesting experience while I was listening to this episode and
it was largely, oh, okay, we're just going to interview a bunch of people with the proud
boys and extremists and all right.
I'm not interested.
Hey, who else wants to start a war?
You want to start a war?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm not super interested except for just to say like, yeah, okay.
I haven't, uh, Gavin and Enrique are talking to Alex and the whole conversation is largely
about everyone's got to go to Georgia.
Yeah.
It's like, okay, I think this is bad, but I also don't respect Gavin at all.
No.
Uh, I don't, I don't, not really.
He's not interesting.
He's not funny.
He doesn't say anything.
Um, so are they trying to drum up like support from the proud boys?
Like, Hey, we're focusing on the proud boys.
The proud boys need to go to Atlanta.
Is that like the, the idea here?
No, I think they're just trying to show a stiff upper lip and sort of like, we're going
to be, you can come to Atlanta because the proud boys will be there to fight with you
in case shit goes bad or something.
I think that that's kind of a lot of the message.
Yeah.
Stop being a coward.
You'll have, they'll have your back.
Right.
Um, so Alex asks Enrique to define the moment that they're in.
He keeps doing this with people, every single guest.
He asks to define the moment.
Okay.
Uh, and then something very, very familiar happens.
Enrique Tarrio has taken over proud boys, Gab McGinnis started as an idea to promote
family and men and fraternity and unity for American men and American men are under attack.
But now the globalists are so scared of it.
You've gone through the fire.
You stood up at hundreds of Antifa events for freedom.
You defended so many people.
What would you call Enrique Tarrio?
This historic moment we're at right now.
Guys want to put his mic on for him, go ahead Enrique Tarrio.
Sorry, that was my fault.
Oh, that's our fault.
Go ahead.
It's your fault.
We don't care.
We love it.
Technology back and forth.
Go ahead.
Ooh, that happens multiple times.
Guys.
I think there's some mic muting issues.
Uh, I'm not entirely sure.
Oh boy.
Anyway, uh, Gavin shows up and we're not going to listen to too much of him because I find
him, uh, unsufferable.
Odious?
Yes, that too.
Uh, but, uh, I just wanted to say that I'm thrilled that he's decided to give up.
We proved it this weekend that we are on the side of what's right and they are on the side
of what's wrong.
And if you can't see that now, I give up.
Congratulations.
Good, good, good.
Please, please give up.
Didn't Gavin come on Alex's show like a year ago saying, fuck this, we're done, give up.
What's the point?
Yep.
Nothing, nothing expresses, uh, you know, just like leader more than any time you lose
moody deciding to quit moody lash outs.
Yeah.
That's how I want to, I admire it.
Yeah, absolutely.
I do not.
I, a lot of people would listen to that and say, I would die for that man.
Anyway.
Fuck, uh, fuck Gavin.
Uh, Owen, Owen Troyer, leader of the caravan comes in and they talk about their huge crowds.
Owen, you did the caravan through the South up to DC.
The police that we talked to estimated, cause I was saying 200,000 that day, cause the police
were saying 200,001 spot.
Turns out that was three and a half miles.
People going back to the beginning of it.
Three and a half miles.
They're estimating 800 to 800,000, a million people, and then Antifa attacking at night,
getting their asses kicked, all of it.
What would you describe this moment in history as well?
From the images I've seen sad.
I think that this had more people in attendance than the million man March.
From the images I've seen sure of your caravan.
I've done standup for larger crowds.
And I was a failure.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Yep.
Uh, I don't know.
Oh boy.
I don't care about relative size to the million man March either.
They seem really hung up on that.
They really want to make sure that this March is better than other black people's Marches.
It seems like a- It's bigger than Louis Farrakhan's March.
Why did you choose that one?
It seems like a sticking point.
They brought it up a couple times.
Yeah, it seems very important to them that- I would ask you, Jordan, how do you define
the times?
How do I define the times?
How do you define this moment that we're in?
I would say pathetic.
It is sad.
I would say that the human race has responded brilliantly and terribly.
At the same time, to the point where, man, I'm really hoping we lose 98% of people and
get the reefs back.
Do you know what I'm saying?
The 98% of reefs lost?
That's a tragedy.
That's not great.
So Owen has had a revelation lately.
Sure.
This doesn't seem like a revelation.
Seems like very similar to catchphrase of Ben Shapiro's kind of.
Great.
I would say that party politic is emotion over evidence.
It's emotion over evidence.
Same thing with the mainstream news, emotion over evidence.
We live in reality.
A million people out there.
Nobody got COVID.
Nobody got sick.
I'm riding back in the airplane.
Everyone's fine.
Laughing about the dumb mask thing.
They almost kicked me off a plane floor, but we won't go into that.
It's far too soon to know what kind of effect that DC rally is going to have on COVID rates,
but it's not too soon to discuss broader trends that we've seen from past events.
If Trump's rallies throughout 2020 are any indication, Owen may have to eat those words
in the future once data is available.
A report released in October by the Center for American Progress said, quote, analysis
by the Center for American Progress finds that about half of the president's 22 campaign
rallies held between June and September were followed by county level increase in COVID-19
cases suggesting the events may have led to community spread.
I don't have data on the recent rally, nor does anyone yet, but I mostly cut out that
clip because I have a hunch that Owen's going to look pretty bad in hindsight as will this.
It's like crazy from, from like five blocks up to the Supreme Court, you're, you're packed
in like sardines.
I mean, there's, you can barely even breathe.
Poor choice of words, I would say there.
Oh Jesus.
So we end the 16th and we jump into the 17th and this is, this was really strange at the
beginning.
First of all, Alex screws up his, his whole thing, this whole time period between the
election and the inauguration.
What do you, what is it?
79 days of hell.
Yeah.
It's a countdown.
Day after the election, 78 days of hell left.
Yeah.
Alex screws it up.
Goes backwards on it.
It is now day 64 of the 79 days of hell.
Communist China and its new allies are desperately trying to overthrow the election of President
Trump.
I understand that it's an easy mistake to make, but no one cares about this except you.
This is not caught on.
It's not great.
It's not, no one's going to remember 10 years from now, oh, you remember the 79 days of
hell.
You're the one who's pushing this really hard.
You have to actually get it right.
You can't say we're on day 64 now.
There is only 15 days of hell left.
There's a little bit of a, yeah.
Oh, is hell going to end on the 30th?
He's trying to count down, but he messed up.
And that's fine.
It is fine.
But it's not.
No, of course not.
This is his baby.
Anyway.
Yeah.
There was a weird sound and I don't mean like poor quality sound or anything like I really
felt like Alex is, it sounded like he was reading a commercial at the beginning of this
episode.
And now the mainline Republican party has awoken to the truth of the new world order
and world government and Tucker Carlson is a fancier, more well-produced version of Infowars.
Not because Tucker Carlson's copying yours truly, but because the world has awoken.
Yes, the enemy's striking back hard, but my friends, when it comes to the culture war,
when it comes to recognizing the UN and its true aim of world government depopulation,
we are winning.
So didn't that, I mean, that seems, that sounds like a promo.
Yeah, that was a movie trailer.
Yeah.
That was pre, that was LaFontaine all the way.
And I was really thrown by it because it just seemed like, what is going on?
And then he goes to a couple of like prerecorded reports and I realized he just wasn't there.
That was prerecorded.
Oh, that was, okay.
Yeah.
Alex shows up 14 minutes into the episode.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you so much for joining us.
I've got plenty of important stuff to cover.
I don't normally start the broadcast with five minutes or six minutes of Tucker Carlson,
but he knocked it out of the park.
So yeah, Alex shows up late, I guess he was getting more information about Georgia or
something.
Sure.
There's an interesting dynamic that's going on and I think that though Alex is crazy and
all this stuff is nonsense, I think he's benefiting from QAnon quite a bit.
Yeah.
Cause you know, you remember the dynamic that existed, you know, in previous times between
people like Fox News and Glenn Beck and Alex Jones.
Alex Jones justified Glenn Beck being crazy because he's like, I'm not Alex Jones.
Exactly.
He was able to sanitize himself and make himself seem more palatable to a wider audience.
Yeah, he was a bullshit launderer.
Yeah.
And because there was someone who could be like, I'm not that guy.
I'm stepping on that guy in order to make myself look respectable.
I think Alex now has QAnon to be like, I'm not QAnon.
That's fair.
That's a fair point.
And because everything has just gotten so much worse in terms of public discourse and
people filtering information, like I think, I think he's able to like take advantage of
people thinking that like there's only one person who's wrong at any time or whatever.
Not realizing QAnon and Alex can be wrong.
Glenn Beck and Alex are both wrong.
You think, uh, you think QAnon stuff is going to, uh, become leaderless and they're going
to be like, eh, maybe we'll go back to Alex Jones.
No, I don't.
Well, I don't know.
I don't know what to predict of it, but I think that most of those people are too
pilled to go back to Alex.
Too far gone to go back to the light stuff.
Yeah.
I think they would find it a little bit disappointing.
Sure.
They would find it ungratifying.
Yeah.
So even though Alex is late, starting the show 14 minutes in or whatever, he did say
that he has some important stuff to talk about.
Of course.
Now generally when he has important things to talk about, it's bizarre fantasies.
Right.
Notions.
Of course.
Things he's misremembering.
Half baked anything.
True.
Yeah.
And my, one of my favorite things is reporting Twitter comments as if they're news.
That's good.
Another comment on Twitter said half the PM and the future head of the state of our country
have been openly promoting the globalist world economic forum, great recent initiative for
months already, but I cannot find a single mainstream media article in Canada that has
mentioned or discussed it because you're a slave.
You're not supposed to see all that info.
You're supposed to be preconditioned to the UN world government takeover slogans before
you ever consciously understand what it is.
So this is really standard bullshit, but I think it highlights something that's really
interesting within like Alex and his rhetoric.
Sure.
You can easily find articles discussing the ideas presented by Klaus Schwab in references
by name to quote the great reset in media going back to early this year after his book
was published.
Just a simple Google search shows that before July, there were articles in Vanity Fair,
the Hill, the Financial Times, Forbes, and plenty of international outlets.
This is the same thing as why aren't there any Muslim voices denouncing terrorism.
You didn't look for it.
You assume it's not there.
And now you're making out a conspiracy out of the idea that you haven't found anything.
There are plenty of people talking about these ideas.
They were just not places you were interested in.
They weren't in publications that you maybe normally read.
The Hill is publicly available.
It's there.
These articles are there.
If you wanted to, if you had any interest, that discussion's there.
No one's hiding anything from you.
You can type questions into the Google search bar.
True.
So if he's like giving you one of those rhetorical questions, like how come no one's talking
about this, you could type in like how come no one's talking about this and you would
have to fill in.
Right.
I think that what's going on is a mis-phrasing of what they believe or what they experience
as the problem.
Sure.
They want these ideas to be yelled on the front page of every paper.
That is what they think they merit.
It's so important.
Exactly.
In the same way that all of Alex's conspiracies whenever it's like the media's not covering
X, Y, or Z, like there's an article about why you're wrong about this everywhere.
You can find it if you want.
They just want this, like the coverage.
The same thing with like no one covers like Trump being good and you can find articles
and publications about good things Trump's done.
It's just that no one is bowing down and being like, oh Trump, you're the king.
They're not covering it the way you want to.
They're covering these ideas in a real world way as opposed to your way.
And because that isn't, your view isn't being shouted from the rooftops, it's experienced
as a coverup.
And that's just not, that's not accurate.
Yeah.
They're not saying what I want them to say, so they're not covering it at all.
Exactly.
And I'm not going to look for the articles that would prove my point wrong.
And that's bad for business, Dan.
Well, the thing that's really sad about it is like, I'm only talking about this phenomenon
right now because Alex is reading someone's tweet.
Like that's, is there any bad take you can't find on Twitter?
Like you can find, like that's the situation.
That's the corollary to your lies about the piano.
Bees are too good.
Wait, I bet you could find that.
Yeah.
For the environment.
Exactly.
Shit.
Fuck.
There's no oil executive somewhere who hasn't tweeted out like let's kill all the bees so
I don't have to deal with flowers anymore.
Trying to think of a take that isn't on there.
Candy sucks.
Someone doesn't like candy.
Nope.
Definitely there.
It's all there, man.
It's all there.
If you want to find a bad take, you just search it into Twitter.
Air tastes bad.
Of course it does.
Do you know where air comes from?
The sky.
And your butt.
Exactly.
Comes out of people's butts.
That's the only place air comes from.
So anyway, Ali Alexander shows up.
And this clip is actually really interesting too.
Like in the same way that last clip really demonstrated this sort of phenomenon of like
not looking for evidence and then claiming there's absence of evidence of something.
This is another really interesting thing that Alex and his people do quite a bit.
We're really appreciative of all the grassroots work out there, but stoptheseal.us features
our coalition partners and we're always willing to work with anyone.
Okay.
Roger.
There is a phenomenon where then people go get permits.
Right.
And then they take over and then say it's their event.
Exactly.
We don't care about the event or our name.
We care about winning.
We care about winning in the Electoral College and getting Donald Trump above 270.
You know, I happen to be a strategist, so I'm working with all of these folks.
Yeah, we did have a vendor who secured the permit and then decided, oh, well, Alex can't
speak and this person can't speak and that person can't speak.
And then this shill should speak and this rhino should speak and then made lies about
the Trump family.
And, you know, that's going to come out later.
But you know, we're not going to tolerate our movement being hijacked.
That's right.
I mean, I talked to the White House.
Trump, you did too.
The White House is going to come to find out these people are running it.
So that's the reason these ladies are a problem.
Right.
And then in our Georgia event, I announced that and now they're coming to take it off.
So now they put out a flyer that they're going to Georgia and they had Georgia featured as
a blue state and they misspelled Georgia.
And so so you you and I were first to announce on our independent channels, we're marching
to Georgia.
And again, it's not about we don't give a damn about credit credit.
These people come to us like you really care about.
Right.
And then they do media.
And it sounds like there's a problem with those disgusting freaks because, you know,
they don't present well.
Look at these disgusting freaks.
They're responsible for all they did.
They told you about a stolen election.
When Owen Schroyer got up to speak, he's saying four more years, Trump on the election.
They tried to jerk him off the stage and even won a saying that he really won.
So what's going on is that women for America first, that that group got the petition or
got the permit.
Yeah.
And they organized the actual event.
Right.
It had a list of speakers that didn't include people like Alex.
And well, they organized the event.
Well, there were a lot of people who also decided to descend on Washington at the same
time.
Sure.
But party crashers don't organize the party.
Well, party crashers are actually more integral to the party than you're willing to.
There is no party without the crasher.
That doesn't sound true, but I guess I have to believe you.
I don't have any evidence.
Look, why isn't anybody talking about this kind of stuff, Dan?
I find this fascinating because it's the same thing with like, okay, yeah, freedom works,
Americans for Prosperity, Koch money, Koch funds, like Astroturfed a ton of the tea party
in its early days.
And then Alex glommed onto it and then accused them of taking his movement over.
Yes, of course.
And that's exactly what he's doing here.
Yeah.
And they won't let them hijack their hijack, Dan.
Somebody's crashed this thing in DC and they rightfully probably were like, this is going
to be tough to deal with.
I understand maybe Alex speaking, but Alex's buddy, I don't know about this.
And then they have the temerity to get on this show and accuse the people who are the
actual organizers of stealing their event.
The balls.
And then to be like, they don't present well.
I just like, like Alex does, I really want to like have these clips available just whenever
I'm just like, oh, women for Trump.
And it's like, man, you guys don't get it.
The moment you step out of line, you're no longer for Trump.
You're just women to them.
And you know how they treat blank, just women.
It is kind of shocking to see, like, so fast.
You could not have organized that event, Alex.
You could not have.
We saw the caravan.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Saw what you were capable of.
The combined work of a ton of grifters added to the population that came to DC.
But the actual event and people having a reason to be there was done by the work of the people
who you were impugning.
Yes.
And that's why, like, if you're on the right, so stop trying.
Just stop it.
Yeah.
Stop organizing these things.
Just stop it.
The people who want to come and get up there and yell and make you look bad and steal all
your thunder are going to shit on you later.
Yep.
Yeah.
You're being used.
Yep.
Every time.
Oh, well.
Anyway, Alex.
No, these are my friends.
They're not your friends.
Alex is talking to Ali and he wants to know why is Georgia so important?
Now recap why Georgia is so key.
Robert Barnes is there.
Everybody that's smart has been telling me for weeks, you're absolutely right, the White
House agrees.
George is key.
How you doing there, buddy?
So we got a long pause here.
Alex?
Alex, we lost you.
Alex.
Alex, this is mission command.
Alex, wake up.
Ground controls have made you tough.
Weird.
All right.
So then it goes to commercial.
I thought that was really strange.
I mean, the feed just went out.
Yeah.
And I don't know what happened there.
They don't address it when they come back, but...
Too much flute.
But here's the thing.
I know that probably online that didn't happen.
Sure.
But I'm listening to it through the feed that goes to all of the radio stations that play
Alex around the country.
This is what's syndicated to shortwave too, so whoever's listening, it just cut out.
Which is...
That's not good.
That's an audience you care about.
That certainly, it's not great.
They could really fix these problems.
Maybe not.
It's doable.
I don't know.
But why?
That's a good point.
Anyway, Alex wants to know, where's Trump?
Where's Trump?
Hiding.
Ally!
Howard, he always was.
Ally Alexander, tell me where Trump is.
I hate you guys.
Let me ask you this question.
Why aren't we seeing a lot of Trump?
Because that's his bully pulpit power.
He still has.
Why has he been so...
We saw it tweeting and saying, I won the election yesterday.
That's not enough.
I mean, he should be in Georgia.
He should be having rallies.
I keep hearing he's going to have these rallies.
When do those come?
So the rallies were going to come and then there was a compromise reached inside the
White House.
So I'm just...
It's my first time talking about it.
And what they decided was until these cases start making their way through the courts,
Trump does not want to position himself where the courts can hold a tweet against him or
a rally against him.
And so his tweets are very concentrated.
Counterpoint.
Alex just said that he tweeted the other day that I won the election.
There is that.
The Democrats are everywhere declaring victory fraudulently, calling him a dictator, but
he's afraid to speak out.
Right.
That's ridiculous.
And it is ridiculous.
No, that sounds right.
The courts held during the the ban, the terrorism ban that was described as the Muslim ban,
they held a tweet against him.
DACA, they held a tweet against him.
So Trump is trying to play the legal strategy smart.
Counterpoint.
Trump tweeted, I won the election.
Yeah, that is a really smart strategy, I think.
Counterpoint.
Trump tweeted something about Antifa scum.
Yeah.
He seems to be.
Your story doesn't hold water, Ali.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You can make up all the fantasy fiction that you want.
But Trump is a giant, cowardly loser.
And I assume you guys are going to start killing all of us immediately.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Trump wants to get out there, man.
He wants.
He does.
No, he wants to play golf.
He wants to get out there.
He wants to do his rallies.
There's plans to do rallies.
See?
In the meantime, stop the steal.us.
We will keep posting rallies every state capitol, your noon, your local time until the electoral
college meets.
And maybe after that, maybe after that, maybe we never give this country back to them.
He keeps calling it the electoral college, which is fun, but, uh, I don't care who gives
a shit.
Yeah.
But it's like this thing is like, what he's doing is, Hey, yeah, Trump wants to come out
and say hi to the people.
He wants to be the figurehead, but he can't be, he's got to play it smart cause the courts.
So for now it's just me.
Here's my website.
Wow.
Fund us so we can have demonstrations at every state capitol and never give the country back.
Whatever that means.
See, I, I get it.
And I understand why everybody is like mocking this and I get why people are writing so many
op-eds and all this stuff that's like, Trump can't do a coup and this is just a grift and
all that stuff.
But it's like this grift is gonna run out.
They don't just stop it when the grift runs out, they create a new grift and whatever
they need to do.
Whatever they need to do, they will do to continue that grift.
Right.
It's not a joke, man.
It is primarily a scam that people like Alex and Allie are running.
Sure.
But the scam, if taken seriously, it's super dangerous.
Terrifying.
And in the past when it's been a scam that's hurt civilians and normal people, you know,
it's awful and it is what it is.
But now it's a game where you could hurt the whole country.
Yeah, the world.
And yeah.
Yeah.
The world.
Yeah, it's too much.
Now, I've had a theory for this whole time that Allie Alexander was working with Roger
Stone on Stop the Steal because it is the same name as Roger Stone's alleged poll watching
organization from 2016.
And I didn't need to actually do any further research on it.
They just told me he was.
Nice.
Allie Alexander, a great political analyst and also publisher, is here with us.
He's been a tireless fighter with Roger Stone starting Start the Steal a Few Years ago with
Roger and then Roger's handed the baton to him.
Roger's going to be in Atlanta, Georgia tomorrow.
I'm going to be there tonight.
Okay.
So I was right.
Yep.
This is all connected.
If Alex is to be believed, which he's usually not.
True.
But this seems like something that makes total sense.
Yeah.
I mean, it's Roger's domain.
He was licensed, he registered it, and now he's taken his cut.
Yep.
I have no doubt he's taken a cut.
Well, and here's the thing.
If this is a conspiracy, all conspirators can be charged with every aspect of a crime.
Rico.
Exactly.
So, if Allie follows through with his plan.
Okay.
Roger might be in trouble.
Good.
I'm going to just leak out our plan, Alex.
They've talked about doing, oh, we're going to elect Joe Biden and do a virtual inauguration.
Good.
Then Alex and I will fill the streets with 5 million patriots.
And Trump will be there and we'll inaugurate him, doesn't it?
We'll inaugurate Donald Trump.
Because the Democrats said they were going to do that if Trump won.
Yeah.
That they would just break the victory up.
When?
Well, we're not going to break it up.
We're going to reconstitute it.
Who said that?
If you guys want to act as insurrectionists, well, then we know how to deal with that.
But we will bring tents.
We will bring trucks.
We will bring cars.
I agree.
And now is the time after Georgia to start occupying DC, period.
So apparently the plan is occupying DC, which you're going to get bored of very quickly,
Alex.
You have no ability to run anything like this.
No, no, no, no.
You have no interest in anything that, especially once the cameras stop, like one of the things
about those kinds of occupations is that they get boring after a while.
People might cover it for a bit and then there's long periods where there aren't cameras, there's
no attention and you don't have, you're not built for that.
So no, you're not going to do that.
But assuming that you do, you're not going to get 5 million people to come to DC.
No.
That is not going to happen.
And let's imagine what's going to happen if you try and inaugurate a second president.
No, that'll work.
No.
Dark Pope.
It'll be fine.
We'll have two Popes.
Somebody will dig up Biden's remains and put them on trial.
It'd be great.
I'm fascinated by trying- I'm just remembering my medieval warfare
history.
I remember people writing down, sieges were our favorite part.
You know?
That four months of waiting for supply lines to catch up, sitting there going hungry, not
fighting anybody, just sitting there in a tent.
I think Alex wants his listeners to do that while buying survival food from him.
Exactly.
To keep rations.
Of course.
And then Alex will show up with a bullhorn every now and again and take credit for everything.
Like medieval kings fighting a war.
Sure.
Yeah.
So let's try and think about what in the real world would that look like if Alex- I mean
first of all, it's a leap to imagine five million people would show up.
So let's stipulate that five million do show up.
Sure.
Now they decide they're going to inaugurate Trump though he lost the election.
Well.
What happens then?
I guess we divide up territories?
I mean, I don't know.
The mind reels.
Steve Pachanik might get a job.
I'm telling you, I'm just telling you.
We just got to isolate him.
We give him, we give him all Alaska.
It's the biggest state.
The old werewolf treatment.
Exactly.
Take all of these, take all of them and say, you know what?
We agree with everything you're doing.
We love what's going on.
There's a lot of resources in Alaska.
We're going to say- But what about the good people of Alaska?
We're starting a pilot program.
We want to put your ideas into action, but we're not sure because they're not tried and
tested yet.
So we want to move all conservatives to Alaska and you guys just work it out there and then
bring it back to us whenever you're ready.
I feel like this is not fair to the people who live in Alaska.
Oh, that's true.
Yeah.
That is definitely true.
Oh well.
The moon.
We'll give Alaskans Hawaii.
Ooh.
And then we'll give Hawaii to Japan.
Wait.
This is going to get out of control.
Now I'm trying to rebook everything and it's trouble.
So let's leave that aside for another day.
All right.
Alex gets it.
He's been doing on this episode his Brian Stelter impression, which is not a good impression.
That one's great.
Now it's really funny because apparently it's not his.
Brian Stelter goes, there's no evidence and they have none and they shouldn't be on air.
Don't go watch them because we have hours and hours of evidence a day.
It's ridiculous.
You know, Mark Dies would be proud of that impression.
Well, I mean, I'm not saying Mark ripped me off, he's done a great job, but I was already
doing it.
I believe that.
Okay.
I don't.
I don't either.
Alex stole Brian Stelter impression from Mark Dies.
Sad.
The thing that always makes me feel like an alien to these people is what they laugh at.
Yeah.
Like, was that that funny?
What did you laugh at, Ali?
What did you laugh at?
Was it just that he did a voice?
I think so.
And if so.
Ooh.
Yeah, well, I mean, I think that that was one of the challenges of doing standup was,
first of all, not thinking the things that I said were that funny.
Sure.
That's a big challenge.
And often the audience agreeing.
Yeah.
And then, you know, things that I saw other people say that weren't all that funny and
audiences thinking they were hilarious.
Sure.
You know, people have different senses of humor.
There's no accounting for that.
Totally.
And it's bewildering.
Yeah.
I'll tell you a few that the stuff on InfoWars that is humorous to those folks who are on
as guests.
It's worse than anything, most things that I've seen at comedy shows.
Yeah, it feels alien.
It really does.
Because in comedy, you know, you've seen every kind of, I've seen the gamut of people trying
to be funny all across the board.
And even they have nothing, there's nothing like this.
This is just a series of people who only understand each other and laugh at these weird things
that are just divorced from reality.
Yeah.
It's wild.
I mean, so much of comedy and so much of what you find funny is the ability to understand
sort of shared perceptions or shared ideas.
And I think once people have such fractured realities that they live in, it makes sense
that humor wouldn't translate at all.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Between them.
Yeah.
That's sad.
How could you make a joke about the sun rising if they're like, we've never seen the sun and
it's dark all the time.
And you're like, okay.
It'd be tough.
There's no shared point of commonality.
So in this next clip, Ali yells that he's signing his death warrant and he's going to
fight this thing all the way to his grave.
And so all of these guys, I'm so proud to be working with you, Alex, and you, Ed.
We've got to rush the gates.
We've got to be the barbarians that rush the gates in the castle, or we're all dead.
It's really that simple.
So I'm signing my death warrant.
It's liberty or it's death.
Alex, I think you're in the same boat.
Oh, I'm total commitment.
Every cell in my body is commanding me to take action.
I'm not in control.
I just remembered when he got sued by Chobani and Alex said, I will fight this.
I will win or I will die.
I will win or he settled a week later.
I'm real sorry about that stuff that I did.
I will win or die.
That's you know what?
A error of my ways.
Look, Hamdi Ulukaya, I am so sorry that I said those things about you.
Please don't sue me.
Uh, okay.
Alex, whatever.
Oh boy.
Anyway, uh, Ali leaves.
I guess he's got to head down to Georgia for Alex to meet him down there.
And Alex takes some calls and this is such a fucking performance on Alex's part.
I believe that what's going on here is that Alex thinks that this caller is nuts and he
doesn't want to talk to him.
So he decides to pretend to be mad about something else.
Dave in Nevada.
You're on the air, Dave.
Yes.
My topic is predictions on the coronal mass ejection, uh, brain shifts and the report.
You see, you know, we're not screening your call.
You're actually on air live right now.
Sure.
Oh, put you on hold, put you on hold.
Listen, I have a thing, I put you on hold, I have a thing about callers.
I love you to death, but I'm not other talk shows where I pre-screen you for an hour.
Want to have you a clean phone.
You want to tell us what you're calling in about a scrape.
Once you get on air, you tell us what you want to cover.
You don't have to ask permission, sir.
He wasn't.
He was telling you what his topic was.
Coronal mass ejection.
His phone sounded fine compared to the callers that you generally have on this show.
Real easy.
He wants to talk about predicting coronal mass eject ejections, brain chips.
Yep.
And I think Alex was like, I don't want to fucking talk to this dude.
Nope.
I want to get mad at him for no reason.
Exactly.
And then it continues.
Once you get on air, you tell us what you want to cover.
You don't have to ask permission, sir.
If you ask for permission, I will hang up on you.
That's the one rule is no censorship and no screening.
Let's try again, Dave.
I love you.
Go ahead.
You're free man, brother.
It's okay.
This is going to sound like numerology.
Okay.
You just asked for permission again, dude.
Don't do it.
Did he?
Just go.
He did not ask for permission again.
He's he was giving a caveat that this is going to sound like numerology, but I was more preamble
than anybody else.
Yeah.
That was, that was softening the numerology that was about to come.
This is going to sound like numerology because it is.
But if I say this is going to sound like numerology, maybe you'll think it isn't.
Yeah.
Maybe you'll think that I'm more of a rational actor in this whole thing.
I think just as like, yeah, all right, I don't want to do this.
I don't want to take whatever this guy's saying seriously, but you know, whatever.
I'll just get mad about my weird idea about anti-censorship of phone calls.
Yeah.
Very strange.
Sure buddy.
So Alex takes another call and this guy wants you to not take a vaccine.
And then thankfully Alex starts talking about his idea of this karma and the whole sort
of thing about like, you need, the globalists need to trick you into doing things for moral
reasons.
Galactic law.
Sure.
And Mike down for this cause you might get a little confused cause it's confusing.
Fair.
But this is perhaps the only thing that like really fascinates me about Alex anymore.
This idea of his bizarre ethical system.
They can dial up the radiation and they can inject you with anything they want to.
You got to make sure that you don't take anything that, that, that they're pushing out and don't
feel they can spray it on you, but metaphysically they get the bad karma.
They believe from it.
They need you to agree.
They can pressure you, but they need you to agree so they don't get at least the instant
karma.
It's how the dimensions work.
I don't understand it all.
They know it's a law.
So do I.
You make somebody do something.
You get instant karma.
You get interdimensional karma when you die for sins, even if you manipulated the field
or however it works, but they need to trick us to go along with it and at least acquiesce.
That's their satanic operation.
They need us like in the garden to agree to it.
Does that make sense?
No, not, not, not one bit.
Nope.
So if I understand correctly, instant karma isn't after you die.
That is like now.
No, it's instant karma, right?
Which is real.
So, but I don't think that history backs that up.
No, it does.
No, it doesn't.
I don't think it does.
What about all the monsters who died in their beds?
Oh, but you missed out all the instant karma that did happen.
Oh, sure.
Like they stubbed their toe?
Exactly.
Great.
Yeah.
Instant karma.
I don't think that this works.
I think you're going to have a really tough time explaining how this system has ever operated.
Sure, sure.
Human history.
Sure.
Especially if you go back to like times when, like feudal times.
How did instant karma work back then?
When life was cheap in the back ages.
So do you remember, so there was a, I can't remember, but it was, I can't remember if
it was Roman or if it was not, but I feel like in my head it's Roman.
The metal bull.
Do you remember the metal bull?
The golden bull.
And they would put a human being inside the bull and light the fire underneath it, making
that person burn alive inside of the bull while the king laughed.
I feel like you're talking about Game of Thrones.
No, this is not Game of Thrones.
It's real.
Okay.
And that guy absolutely had diarrhea that night.
And that's what happens.
Instant karma, Dan.
Sure.
It's, it's tough.
Yeah.
It's tough for me to wrap my head around this.
Now Alex seems to also be saying that even if you manipulate the system and get people
to do things of their own volition, you'll still have bad sin karma after you die.
Of course.
Well naturally.
What?
Haven't you seen the scoreboards that follow us around everywhere and sit on top of our
left shoulder?
Am I the only person who can see the scoreboard?
I think so.
Oh shit.
Cause this makes perfect sense to me.
You and Alex.
If you look at this scoreboard right over here.
I'm a little bit, I'm a little bit worried about the real world application of this moral
system.
Sure.
I'm a little bit worried about it.
For one, if you believe this moral system and then let's say you violate someone's free
will and then there's no instant karma.
Oh my God.
I must not have violated their free will.
Uh oh.
There we go.
This could teach you the wrong lessons.
I wasn't instantly karmad.
So furthermore, furthermore, here's the biggest issue.
You know what?
That kind of implies is that anything that you do, if God doesn't strike you down for
doing it, it must be okay until after when you find out, well, but then it's not like
instant karma.
It's just bad.
It's not that bad.
No, no, no.
Whatever you did to somebody they must've been fine with or else God would have given
you instant karma.
Of course he would.
So the fact that you're still standing and don't have, what the fuck?
I think my biggest issue is that they can quote pressure you.
Yeah.
Now what does that mean?
Wow.
What are the limits of pressure?
They can pressure you into agreeing with them, but they'll still be in trouble after they
die.
They'll just not have instant karma if they pressure you.
So they can just, they can just torture you endlessly until you agree.
What if they send a robot with a gun and a little...
Cause I would say that's not pressure.
Is Dalek pressure?
I think that's the question.
I think Alex is saying that it is, but it's absolutely not.
All right.
If the globalists have to get you to agree to do things, Dalek's with guns is not pressure.
That's force.
That's pressure.
No, it's not.
That's just pressure.
Now, if the gun actually kills the person, that's instant karma.
But as long as you're just pressuring them with the threat of shooting them.
The threat of the gun is not pressure.
Not instant karma, that's pressure.
That's an inappropriate level of pressure.
Well, see, that's why I don't like when he says pressure.
I think it is debatable, you know, the whole idea of like, did I make you do something
cause I pointed a gun at you?
Sure.
Like if I make you rob a store when I'm pointing a gun at you, are you morally culpable or
should you have gotten shot instead of...
Sure, sure, sure.
Actually, this is a stupid conversation.
It is.
Of course I forced you to do it.
Yeah.
Naturally.
You got a gun on me.
Yes.
So the robot with a gun is not pressure, that's force.
This moral system makes no sense, but I want Alex to talk about it for an hour.
Honestly, I think even a robot with a swab is maybe force.
A robot comes up to you with a swab?
That's a little bit intimidating.
I mean, it's weird.
If there's no gun, it's not force.
You could just then walk away from the robot.
It's not Rosie the main robot from the Jetsons.
But if it's a Dalek, you can outrun it.
Close a door.
No, Daleks can fly.
Not these ones.
Not real ones.
Alright, well, I'll have to call Matt Smith and see what he can do about this.
Anyway, I just want Alex to do a fucking whole special episode about this weird moral system.
Gotta.
And I'd love him to do like a call-in show where people can ask him questions to refine
some of these ideas.
Absolutely.
I want him to have a chalkboard.
I think it would fall apart so fast.
I really want him to try and explain it.
I really do, because it is bonunkers.
So now Alex takes another call, and something happens that happens more than I would like
to admit, and that is this caller tells Alex about a dream he had.
Oh, of course.
Thanks, sir.
I'll take my call, brother.
Yes, sir.
Alex, I just wanted to reiterate a dream I had approximately 16 years ago.
A dream goes like this.
I had crossed a gigantic cavern.
I don't know how I crossed it.
I didn't know where to go.
And I laid down on my back.
I looked up to heaven, and I saw a blue spiraling light, and this blue spiraling light turned
into like a tornado.
And out of that blue spiraling light, a dove formed, a blue dove.
And I felt liquid love raindrops going entirely through me.
And a voice like a trumpet spoke to me and said, a moment is only for a moment, but a
moment lasts forever.
And Alex, this is America's moment to stand up.
If this moment is missed, this moment will pass forever.
There's a shelf life on it, and kudos for you for going to Georgia today.
They're right.
It's a dimensional jump point where they've liquefied the energy field for the future,
and we have to remold things now.
What are those words?
They've liquefied the jump gate?
What are you talking about?
Of course.
Fuck off.
They liquefied the jump gate.
I had a dream that I was skateboarding last night.
Anyway, this guy apparently-
I got to tell you about a dream I had 16 years ago, so I was 17 years old, and I had this
dream-
Look, I love you.
You're my best friend.
I don't want to hear your fucking dream.
No, no, no.
You want to hear this dream.
It's really incredible.
No, no.
So I had this dream, and there was this cat, and it was climbing up a tree.
You know like cats do.
And then I saw this blinding light, and so did the cat.
And you know the cat saw it because the light blinded the cat so much that it fell, and
it was holding onto the tree just by its bare paws.
And a deep, booming voice said, hang in there, kitty.
And I just always hung onto that, Dan.
Well, it's a meaningful thing.
It's a meaningful thing.
I like the idea that some people are going to maybe protest outside capitals and be like,
the time is now.
I mean, or else why would that guy who called Alex Jones' show have had that dream 16 years
ago?
That's ludicrous.
I just want to reiterate a dream I had 16 years ago.
Is the last sentence I want to hear anyone say ever.
I have to assume Alex in that moment was like, I'm so mad I freaked out at that caller earlier.
I should have freaked out at this guy first.
God damn it.
I should have saved the freak out.
I blew it too soon.
Anyway, we have one last clip, and it's sort of an intro to our Monday episode.
Well, I'm on my way, and I'm not the devil, just a little bit, but I love Jesus.
And so I'm on my way to Georgia, and I'm going to be with Roger Stone, Ollie Alexander, and
so many others fighting the steel.
Very exciting.
Join us Monday on Knowledge Fight as we discuss Care of Vanity Project part three.
The Texan went down to Georgia.
He was looking for a stop the steel.
So I'm excited about that kind of, I'm excited about the idea of like, I'm playing by my
own rules.
Like, we're going to cover this show, but I think a bottle episode where we talk about
his time in Georgia makes more sense than us covering Wednesday at the end of this episode.
Agreed.
Like the caravan, perfect two-parter.
Makes total sense.
Absolutely.
And let me tell you something.
I shot on it a little bit, but that was a very well-written parody song.
Thank you.
That was very well-written.
It was a good parody song.
I will be genuine for this one moment.
This is very nice of you to say.
I will admit, in hindsight, there were some meter problems.
There were a couple big ones.
That's the problem whenever you write it out and you don't sing it, you know, perfectly
in advance.
Yeah.
I mean, I might've reread it.
Anyway, I think that this was a little bit of a preamble episode in some ways.
I feel like this was getting ready to go to Georgia.
And it's this, he's just got back from DC and now he's about to leave again.
There's this weird middle place where it's like, fuck, I don't know, I'm going to hang
out with Ali Alexander and all the Proud Boys.
Yeah, it's a layover in the airport.
Yeah, kind of.
But it's his home.
Yeah.
He is a nomad for the 79 days of hell.
He is a man adrift running around the country, hither and yon, trying to find attention wherever
it might be.
He is going to have to do that, I guess.
Yeah.
That's like what he's got to do.
I will say, on the one hand, I'm glad it doesn't come off as desperate.
I guess.
I was being facetious.
Anyway, we'll be back on Monday, but until then, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
You bet it is.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledge underscore fight and at go to bed Jordan.
We are on Facebook.
And if you could, please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work right now.
Yeah.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
We accept all callers except for censored.
I don't know how to do this one.
I fucked up.
Sorry.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.