N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledgefight, knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys, knowledgefight.
Dan and Jordan, knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
Hey everybody, welcome back to knowledgefight, I'm Dan, I'm Jordan, we're a couple dudes
that sit around, drink novelty beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh indeed we are, Dan, Jordan, I have a quick question for you, what's up, what's your bright
spot today?
What's your bright spot today, Jordan, paradoxically, very strange, unexpectedly, social media.
Social media, the thing that you have left as soon as you finally realized after eight
months that you should have been gone from it two years ago.
Yeah, I don't like social media in a lot of its manifestations, permutations, because
I find that it just doesn't match with the way my brain works.
Not no shade on people who do enjoy it or like Twitter and Facebook and stuff, I just,
it's not for me.
As I've gotten older I recognize that it's confusing, I don't like, when I was running
the knowledgefight Twitter account, and it became a thing where it's like, I know I'm
using this, everybody who listens to the show knows I'm using this, so if I post promo stuff,
it feels dirty.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It feels like, I don't know, it's a good aversion to self-promotion, but.
I understand.
Anyway, the reason that I'm throwing a bright spot to social media is I started to think
about like, what are ways that social media can be used in ways that are fun and not dumb,
and everyone keeps asking for pictures of my plants, and so I've started an Instagram
account called Plant Underscore Fight.
Alright, alright.
Where I'm going to post pictures of plants.
I like it.
And so far people have enjoyed it, I've posted a picture of the quinoa so far, and periodically
it will feature different plants from around Dan's wild kingdom, but I figured it's not
connected to the show, it's not too intrusive on my personal life, and it felt like that
nice sweet spot, and something that people enjoy.
People like seeing these plants.
Yeah, I think so.
I think so.
Yeah, so I think maybe this is a function that social media can serve, although I still
think most of it's trash.
Here's what we'll do.
I'll make an Instagram account for my two dogs.
People have asked for me to post pictures of your dogs.
Yeah, I'll go with Westies Underscore Fight will compete to see whose, I guess, growing
things are better.
I'm afraid that your dogs are cuter than most of my plants.
I think I'd probably lose that Underscore Fight.
But I'm not as popular as you, Dan.
I don't know about that.
Oh yeah.
So what's your bright spot?
My bright spot today, Dan, is back to Assassin's Creed Valhalla, but it is a specific reference
in Valhalla that I particularly enjoyed that came out of nowhere, which was a reference
to One Punch Man.
Do you know about One Punch Man?
Vaguely, yeah.
Yeah, so One Punch Man is a manga and an anime about a very depressed guy who can defeat
anything and anyone in one punch.
Yes, I believe you've told me about this.
Yeah, and he's so existentially destroyed by that, like how bored and awful it is to
be the ultimate power in the universe, I guess, that he's just a real bummer all the time.
And there's a perfect reference to that in Valhalla, where you have to fight a guy who
will always defeat you in one punch, and he's a real bummer about it.
People could have guessed that was going to be the spoiler.
Well, yeah.
It's a reference, yeah.
So it's very, very, very funny.
That's nice.
I enjoyed it.
It's my little Easter egg.
It's nice to be surprised by a little reference in there.
Sure.
Ah, it's good.
I have a gripe.
I don't know what the deal is, but I lost a bunch of time on Valhalla.
Did you have a corrupted save where you kept falling through the...
No, I had a bug, though, that I ran into.
Ooh.
And that was... maybe this is just one of those problems that happens when you play
games when they first come out that I'm not really used to.
But there's a mission at a certain point where, without any spoilers, you talk to a guy, and
then you've got to get to another city.
Sure.
You've got to take a boat to get to the other city, and every single time after I talked
to this guy, the boat would spawn in the middle of land.
Like, just as if it were a horse.
Sure.
Just in the middle of a path.
I can't do anything with this.
And so I had to go back to my most recent autosave file, and it had autosaved so many
times while that boat was still there.
Sure, sure.
You restarted, like, 50 times, and all your autosaves wound up getting you back to where
the boat was.
So the last save before that was a great mistake.
Four hours.
Yeah.
It was very frustrating, but it is what it is.
Yeah, I had the same thing happen on one mission.
All of a sudden, every time I loaded the save, the entire screen would just start shaking,
and then my character would just fall directly through, and then fall forever until she died.
And that was it.
Even great games, you know, sometimes there are little problems.
Eh, launch date, release bugs, it happens.
Yeah.
And you know the other thing that's really exciting for me, too, is that, like, I know
that Age of Calamity, the Zelda game, Hyrule Warriors, has come out.
Oh, it has.
And I haven't even, I haven't even touched it, or got it, I haven't even thought about
it.
You don't have time.
No.
And that's a nice feeling.
Yeah.
To know that that's there.
If I ever, uh, ever.
Sure.
Because it may not ever happen.
You've got another 80 to 100 hours to put into balance.
If I ever finish with Valhalla, then, uh, you know, Age of Calamity is there waiting for
me, and that's a nice, comforting feeling.
Yeah.
Anyway, I had second bright spot there.
Yeah, that is great!
So, Jordan, today, uh, we've got an interesting episode to go over, um, uh, Alex went out
of Georgia.
Alright.
Um, shout out to the, the couple people, uh, made audio versions of that.
Yes, they did!
They did!
My parody song, which is.
This is very interesting.
This is a new level of fame for me, that, uh, I'm quite frankly uncomfortable with,
but I think is delightful.
You've reached a lot of people.
People have put, uh, put my parody song to music.
Honestly, I think a lot of people were expecting a sequel today.
Um, I don't know if, is there a sequel to The Devil One Time in Georgia?
Uh, yeah.
Not a Charlie Daniels version.
No, no, no.
Well.
But there's a million different.
Well, in that case, mine was a sequel.
That's true.
Uh, no.
There is no sequel.
Uh, I figured, you know, can't force it.
Um, but Alex, uh, he went down to Georgia, and I, I will say that, uh, this experience
was not what I wanted it to be.
Um, it lacked a lot of the charm and the fun of the caravan.
Sure.
Um, and that's because the caravan allowed me to paint a picture.
Right.
Whereas, in this case, it's kind of Alex, the picture's painted.
You realize every time we get excited for something, we're talking about people who
turn every good thing into shit.
Yeah, yeah.
We're, we're, we're getting excited about the potential, um, that never gets realized.
We are the fucking Lucy, or no, we're Charlie Brown.
Every time they set up that football, and we're like, we're gonna fucking do it this
time.
Yeah.
We're gonna kick it.
It's gonna be a caravan field goal.
It's gonna be amazing.
And then they slide it out from under us again and again and again.
Yeah.
It's, it is unfortunate.
So, um, there's still some fun to be had along the way.
And I actually had a number of interesting, uh, things that I want to bring up and discuss
in the course of this.
Uh, we're just going to be talking about November 18th, 2020, um, Dan, this is 2020.
Oh, hey.
Oh, you're still alright with it.
I told you, we're still alright with it.
It's too late.
I've accepted it.
I also want to say that when I, uh, uh, discussed this on the last episode, I was actually stuck
in my craw a little bit.
I said that you were submitting to the bit, and I don't actually, that was not the right
choice of word.
I meant surrender.
Surrender is the word.
That was the word I was looking for.
Surrender is a good word.
It bothered me.
For like an entire day that I couldn't come up with that word.
You ever have something stuck in your craw?
I was laying in bed and I was like, I meant surrender, dammit.
Um, so, uh, the reason that we only have this one day is because, I mean, I think the trip
to Georgia is pretty unimpactful.
I think that it's, it's repetitive in nature, what Alex does when he's on the road.
And at the same time, there's enough stuff that happened during this episode that's worth
talking about that to try and force it and do like the whole rest of the week would have
ended up with like a six hour episode.
Still hasn't pulled a computer chip out of that homeless person.
Still has not.
We're on eight months of not pulling the computer chip out of somebody.
Yeah, I'd like to, there's so many running tallies.
How many days has it been since Rand Paul has refused your challenge to debate?
We're getting up to, uh, close to 150.
We are currently on day four of the scourge of, uh, gun toting Daleks running around the
streets.
We are in, like, there's a lot of tallies.
There's a lot of things to keep an eye on.
Yeah.
But you know what I'd like to keep an eye on?
What's that, Dan?
Uh, my gratitude and our gratitude for the folks who have signed up and are supporting
the show.
I like it.
So first I'd like to give a shout out to Kayden, that's with a C. C-A-Y-D-E-N.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Kayden.
Thank you.
Next, Joe the fourth with Roman initials, I-V.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Joe the IV-th.
Thank you.
Next, Da'Rin and that's D-A-R-I-N.
Uh, thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Da'Rin.
Thank you.
Next, Taylor D. Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Taylor.
Thank you.
Next, Taylor Daines?
Uh, uhh, sure.
Ok.
Next, Zoe P. Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks Zoe.
You ever get into a Zooey Zoey argument?
No.
Good.
Okay.
Next, this fella asked me to say how I thought his last name was pronounced.
And I know that this was just because it looks like Wiener.
Sure.
But I knew it was Wiener.
Maybe, maybe...
Sometimes it's Wiener.
I think it's rarely.
I mean like Matt Weiner, isn't he the guy who made Mad Men?
Sure.
Isn't that Matt?
Yeah.
I might have the first name wrong.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Something like that.
Yeah.
So anyway, Jason, thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Jason.
You ever get into a Wiener Weiner argument, Dan?
Yes.
That one I have.
Next, Quasar the Corgi Star.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks.
Cue the CS.
And finally, I'd like to thank you to a couple people who donated on an elevated level from abroad.
Ooh.
So first, Jan from Denmark.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
And Mirjum from...
This is a name that I'm not going to be able to handle.
You're going to do this.
Hammond Lina.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate.
That's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
We got to go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much to our representatives from Denmark and Hammond Lina.
Yes.
Thank you very much to the both of you.
I look forward to your correction about the pronunciation.
It'll be great.
Yeah.
It's pronounced quokka.
Probably.
Yeah.
So if you're out there listening and thinking, hey, I enjoy the show.
I'd like to support these giants.
You can do that by going to our website, pressing that button that says support the show or...
If you are experiencing any kind of malaise or perhaps existential crisis, what you should do is fill yourself with a generous spirit.
Channel that chi energy all the way up into your fist and punch a local charity or bail fund, but metaphorically and with generosity.
All right.
That works.
So Jordan, this is the reverse of the caravan.
Mm hmm.
This is and I don't know why I didn't see the Navarock.
I don't know why I didn't see this in advance.
I'm so blind.
I'm so blind to like what's actually going to happen.
Sure.
Because like Alex going down to Georgia, it's like, this is exciting.
Alex is going to be rampaging it, but I forgot that that means that Owen is going to be hosting the show and like, I forgot that like, oh, it's the flip of the dynamic from the caravan where Owen's out on the road and Alex is, you know, throwing to him in the field.
Now we've got, God, I was just like, as soon as you get into it, you're like, oh no.
How does, how does Owen try and really pull off three hours?
Well, one of the ways he does it is he mostly plays a live feed of Alex and Ali Alexander yelling in Atlanta on this episode.
That's smart.
There's a lot of that.
Yeah.
So thankfully there's that.
Sure.
And I will say I appreciate it.
And the episode starts with Alex doing a little bit of a message.
This is the mark of the beast out of Revelation.
It's not coming.
It's here.
And so many of the big Baptist churches and Catholic churches are putting in the QR codes and doing all the same thing because they're not churches.
They've been taken over by this system.
So it's going to all get rapidly worse very, very quickly.
So Alex has got some fear of QR codes.
She wants everyone to have, I don't know what he thinks QR codes are the thing that's been around for 15 years.
It's been around for a while.
And in the real world, they're just an advancement of the same idea behind a barcode, which is used by many retail outlets.
I say many because if you don't want to use barcodes and UPC scanners to ring up products, you don't have to.
No, you do.
It's compelled by the mark of the beast.
You don't have to.
No, it's compelled by the mark of the beast.
It's just efficient.
The main reason I pulled this clip was to illustrate how deep into the nonsense Alex is to start this show off.
The second reason I included this clip is probably more important and it's to use this as an opportunity to explain how people like Alex are broken records trying to make everyone afraid of everything for no reason.
QR codes are something that Alex is trying to scare his audience about, and interestingly, if you look into the history of the thing that preceded QR codes, the UPC barcode, you'll find hysterical people doing the exact same thing 50 years ago.
According to an article about UPC history in Wired, quote,
when the first UPC scanners arrived in the early 1970s, according to various IBMers who worked on the project, there were protests at grocery stores even though the codes appeared on coke cans and jars of applesauce, not right hands and foreheads.
I love Christianity.
And in the year that followed, an urban legend arose, warning gullible types that the number 666 was hidden in each barcode.
Some of these paranoid types noted that there were often sixes in the barcode, which were in fact arbitrary, but it doesn't matter.
Again, from the article, quote,
Early test films of the scanners were labeled with the letters F, G, and H, and some saw this as proof that the code would wind up on more than just coke cans, assisting the H stood for head and the F for forearm.
Sure.
People do this, it's inevitable, because change and the future are both scary things.
The more complex a system is, the greater possibility it has in terms of productivity and effectiveness and ability to help people live better lives,
but as that complexity increases, the theoretical damage that it could cause go up too.
A simple example is just the internet.
The ability for people to communicate and digitally interact over great distances, it's revolutionary in terms of information flow and directing charitable assistance to places that need it,
but it's created a gigantic tinderbox that could explode at any time.
For instance, back in 2013, the Associated Press's Twitter account got hacked,
and a fake tweet was posted about two explosions going off at the White House that had injured President Obama.
This wasn't true, but the effect on the stock market was real, and it's the byproduct of a volatility that would not exist without the ability for information to travel exceedingly fast.
Almost every technology you can imagine can be slotted into this kind of balance.
Having a centralized power company in your town relieves you of the burden of having to run a generator yourself,
but also, if there's a bad storm in your area, your whole block might end up losing power for a while.
The complexity of emerging technologies provides benefits, but also increases the problems when something goes wrong.
Alex is just one in a long, long chain of hysterical idiots yelling about how some new-ish, not even that new, new-ish, invention is the end of the world.
He's rambling about QR codes just like his forefathers, who protested barcodes outside grocery stores.
It's a real bummer that John of Patmos really maligned a more efficient system.
Like, maybe if Satan were less of a—like, God is kind of a Luddite in this scenario, right?
So the Antichrist is like, hey, let's give everybody a mark so we can do the whole thing.
You can do commerce, you can do all this stuff.
Yeah, I get that that can be abused, but it's still a more efficient system, all right?
God is out here like, let's give everybody free will.
Fuck that noise. That gets everybody complicated.
See what we're talking about with Twitter? People are jumping out there, lying, ruining the stock market in two seconds.
Put the mark of the beast on everybody, forehead, call it a day.
All right.
Yeah, that's my plan.
I lost myself entirely in that speech. I was like, all right, yeah, let's do that.
You have a hypnotic power today, Jordan. I'm worried about it.
So Alex is on the scene in Atlanta with Ali, and the beginning of the show is what appears to be a pre-recorded—
or it could have been live, I'm not entirely sure—thing of them just sort of yelling about this stuff.
Yeah, yeah.
And Ali has some big news to break down.
This is just one example of dozens that have already come out in the last day. This is just now breaking in Georgia, where we are.
Just this morning, it is breaking news. David Shafer, the Georgia Republican Party chair, tweets this.
One of our monitors discovered 9,626 vote error in DeKalb County hand count. That is in Atlanta.
One batch was labeled 10,707 votes for Biden and just 13 for Trump, an improbable margin even for DeKalb standards.
The actual count for the batch was 1,081 for Biden and 13 for Trump.
Had this counting error not been discovered, Biden would have gained enough votes from this one batch alone to cancel out Trump's gains from Fayette County, Floyd, and Walton.
Folks, we have to audit the vote, and we have to check the signatures in Georgia. That's why Alex Jones and I are here.
So Ali is reporting based on a tweet that was posted by David Shafer, the head of the GOP in Georgia.
But it's a very misleading tweet designed to be used by bad faith actors like Alex and Ali to fuel their machines that they're trying to use to overturn this election.
Naturally.
Basically what happened was this. They're conducting this recount in Georgia, and during the recount someone made a recording error.
That is to say that they mistakenly put down over 10,000 votes for Biden and 13 for Trump, when in reality the total was just over 1,000 for Biden and 13 for Trump.
This mistake was caught in the recount, and that's what Shafer is yelling about.
Sure.
This counting error was not made in the initial automated count of the ballots, only in the recount, so it does not actually affect the totals for the state at all.
But that's the impression that Shafer's tweet and Alex's coverage are designed to leave the audience with.
Sure.
The idea is supposed to be that their sleuths uncovered 9,000 votes from the actual election for Biden that were erroneous, when in reality someone involved with the recount made a mistake and the process caught it before it actually was a big mistake.
Yeah, that'll happen.
The DeKalb County CEO released a statement that basically said that they were unable to verify the claims of this error, but to put it in my words, even if everything Shafer said is true, it doesn't matter.
Quote, based on Chairman Shafer's Twitter storm, I was a little surprised by the tone of this statement.
Chairman Shafer, okay.
No, I was more about the Twitter storm part.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Based on Chairman Shafer's Twitter storm, the alleged vote error was discovered, reported to DeKalb elections officials, and corrected prior to the transmission of the official audit report to the Georgia Secretary of State's office.
If the scenario occurred, as Chairman Shafer alleges, this is evidence that the checks and balances established by Georgia Secretary of State Brad Raffensperger to ensure the accuracy of the election results performed as designed.
As is always the case with Alex and Allie, this is a dud, but it's a dud that they're probably going to use as a piece of evidence of fraud.
Sure, forever.
Yep.
And it's not just Georgia, baby!
It's not!
Somebody during the recount accidentally put an extra zero, and then they found it, and now it's all over.
More or less.
Yeah.
Okay, cool.
But it's not just Georgia.
Thanks, America.
It's also Michigan.
Sure.
So breaking news, Allie, on the situation that is just explosive, like out of a Hollywood gangster movie in Michigan.
Tell us about that.
So in Wayne County, Michigan, that's Detroit, the Republicans, two Republicans and two Democrats sit on the canvassing board.
The Republicans decided not to certify the election, but under duress and threat from hundreds of thousands of tweets, the leftist Antifa, BLM, they reluctantly agreed under the condition that the Secretary of State would do an audit.
We are in legal and constitutional limbo as we don't even understand what that means, what are their rights.
No, you don't understand what that means.
So we have this bullying from the left against people who just want to certify clean elections, not bad elections.
What Allie is saying is inaccurate, but let's pretend for a moment what he's saying is true.
That would mean that the Republicans on this council he's talking about were willing to certify an election that they felt was fraudulent because people were mean to them on Twitter.
Yep.
I'm sorry, Allie is saying that like it's an understandable thing, like the leftists are just too mean on Twitter, they had to certify the results.
Well, when you say mean things, that's how the American Revolution started.
Sure, there was the taxation thing, but George was like, these guys are a bunch of dicks, and they were like, well, we got to tear this place down.
Yeah, I mean, it's like in the Declaration of Independence, cyberbullying comes up a lot.
How dare you write letters to us?
Allie is saying, like the people tweeting stuff, this mean stuff, it's like the equivalent of having a gun to your head, which is ridiculous.
If it's your job to make sure the election is fair, and your decision-making process is in any way affected by what someone on Twitter says, you've proven exactly one thing, and that is that you're not qualified for your position.
Yeah.
The Wayne County Board of Canvassers met to certify the election results, and things broke down on a party line.
With the two Republicans, William Hartman and Monica Palmer, voting against certification, and the Democrats voting for certification.
At issue was the number, there was a number of precincts that had an unexplained discrepancy in vote totals.
According to the Detroit Free Press, quote, most of them recorded discrepancies of three votes or fewer.
In 2016, there were similar discrepancies in voter totals, and Jill Stein's campaign had pushed for a recount.
This recount was ended by a court order before it could be completed, but after the election was over, the state of Michigan did do an audit,
and it found that a vast majority of the unexplained discrepancies were easily explainable by human error,
and that, quote, many of the problems encountered in Detroit are attributable to a lack of proficiency using EPB software, or the mishandling of provisional envelope ballots.
They found in their audit that votes were accurately counted, but that there were mistakes made in terms of being able to correctly match each vote with its ballot,
because of these various human errors.
It's incredibly likely, almost to a point of certainty, that this same phenomenon is present here in the 2020 election.
Ultimately, Palmer and Hartman agreed to certify the Wayne County results when the Democrats on the board agreed to do an audit of the votes,
but apparently, Palmer and Hartman didn't realize that the audit would be literally impossible to do prior to the certification of the election,
and so they tried to recant their certification, which is something they can't do, so that's where things stand right now.
Oh, you know, you can recant a certification after an election. That's how it always works, Dan.
The cynical-minded fellow out there might think that the real reason that Palmer and Hartman decided to recant their decision to certify is that Trump called them personally, but what do I know?
Oh, that'd be crazy.
Now, Ronna McDaniel, the Republican National Committee chair, is calling for Michigan to adjourn their board for 14 days to get to the bottom of these very serious, or possibly wildly overblown, issues.
At the point of us recording this episode, we don't know how this is gonna shake out, because the board in Michigan is set to certify on Monday, which is in the future from us right now.
Great.
All signs appear to indicate that, like Georgia, they will certify the results, but this world is fucking insane, so I am not going to take anything for granted.
Yeah, come on, why not?
But the reality is that there were precincts-
Let's get a nice Andrew Johnson in there to help take us over.
Couldn't hurt. Could hurt, could hurt, could hurt.
What's the wrong with it? No, no, no, no, no. Whenever there's a fraudulent election, you want an Andrew Johnson to come back in there.
Well, there were issues of voting discrepancies that are, to an extent, normal.
Sure.
And that is something that's being weaponized by Ali, and one of the ways that he's doing it is just outright lying.
They're still calling for an audit, but they did go ahead and say they're going to certify it, because things were, quote, out of balance at a record level.
So they're out of balance at a record level. I think it was double from 2016 to now.
That's just categorically not true.
Alex and Ali are making this stuff up, knowing that no one in their audience will question them or go consult the 2016 audit, which I would bet anything I own that even these two dudes don't know exists.
It'd be really hard to find. You'd have to Google it.
It's not hard.
And then you'd read it.
That part might be hard for them.
Have you read things before? That's hard.
The Detroit Free Press said this of the unexplained discrepancies in Wayne County in the 2020 election, quote, of Detroit's 503 election day precincts, 85 recorded unexplained discrepancies in the vote totals, as did 94 of the city's 134 absentee voting counting boards.
Most of them recorded discrepancies of three votes or fewer.
If you consult the 2016 election audit conducted by the Michigan Department of State, you'll find that, quote, the Wayne County Board of Canvassers reported during the post-election canvas period that concluded November 22, 2016, approximately 392 precincts appeared to be out of balance.
If you combine the in-person and absentee counting boards from 2020, you have a decrease of 213 out of balance precincts in this election compared to four years ago, not double.
Sure, sure, but that's by 10,000 each time.
Sure.
Every single one of those is an accidental adding of 1,000.
No.
And these numbers probably sound high, and they kind of are, but these are almost entirely indicative of minor human errors that do not actually affect vote counts.
But they do lead to accounting problems.
For instance, the audit report discusses the case in 2016 of Precinct 152, where the sealed ballot container, it only had 50 votes in it at the end of the night, but the rules indicated that 306 votes had been cast.
This was because poll workers had accidentally left the rest of the ballots in the tabulator and failed to put them then into the sealed container.
Sure.
It's a problem, and it will lead to a discrepancy, but it doesn't actually have any bearing on the vote tallies or mean there was any fraud.
Most problems that you will hear people like Alex yell about fall into this category, and I would be willing to venture a guess that in a few months, whenever there is an audit of this election, which Alex will ignore by that point, you'll find a lot of similar human error issues.
Sure.
I mean, have you ever counted to 1,000 and then counted to 1,000 with two people over your shoulder, six feet away from you, going like, no, that's one more for the other team.
Like, of course you're going to get three wrong.
I mean, look, in Mario Party 6, I think, there was a little mini-game where you had to remember the order of fruits.
Yeah.
Yeah?
You had to remember four fruits, usually.
And sometimes my friends got it wrong.
Of course.
Well, I mean, granted, we were high as hell when we would play it, but still.
Sure.
One time, my buddy Swearengen, it was a bundle of grapes was the thing he had to remember.
I think it was grapes, and he pluralized it, and he got it wrong.
You went off on it.
No, he got it wrong.
Oh, that's right, because the game does it for you.
Yeah, because it was the voice.
It wasn't like a Scattergories argument that everybody got into.
It was that weird period where the, I think it was the GameCube, had a microphone that you could have, like, a couple voice commands.
It would recognize, so you'd be like, banana, grape.
Sure.
And he got it wrong even though he had the right...
Because he said grapes.
I think so, yeah.
Lives on in my memory.
Forever.
Anyway, yeah, my point is that people can make mistakes.
People make mistakes.
The larger point here, though, is that Ali and Alex are completely wrong and absolutely just making up that there's record levels of precincts being out of balance.
They have no idea what they're talking about, and the actual numbers are the exact opposite of their narrative.
There wasn't record discrepancy, and if you go by the strict numbers, there was a 54% decrease in precincts reporting unexplained discrepancies this election cycle.
Seems like progress.
Yeah, that would make sense considering for the, like, three months up to the election everybody was constantly screaming about how there's no possible way that this would be a fair-counted election, so everybody went so fucking overboard.
Well, and because of those discrepancies that happened in the 2016 election, there were probably a lot of conversations about little things that could be done to limit...
Well, I think that, I mean, obviously you'd like to see that number even lower, but that much of a decrease from one presidential election to another seems, like, pretty good.
I don't know.
I mean, let's say we've got, what is it, almost 150 million votes cast, or over 160 million now? Something along those lines.
And we have, what, it's 50% of the counties in Michigan in 2016 reported fewer than three, three or fewer.
Like, that's a vote tally of discrepancy less than a thousand.
In Michigan, that's ridiculously...
Yeah, and reading over this audit, they were discussing that, like, the really bad ones are ones that had over three.
Yeah.
And that, you know, it leads you to recognize that these ones that are out of balance aren't out of balance by, like, a thousand.
No.
That would be egregious.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That would be, like, national alarms going off.
Totally. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it's severe when there's three or four votes that are...
Somebody added a zero, and it's a story for months now, you know?
Well, yeah, and it was, you know, in a recount, and it got caught before anything...
Sure, sure.
Before it had any impact on anything.
Totally.
So, anyway, these are kind of the big sort of election fraud narratives that they got, and both are just like, oh, here's the real story.
I understand where your lies are coming from and the spin you're putting on, but it's just... it's flimsy.
As is this.
Ali has some things he wants to complain about.
The Pennsylvania Supreme Court.
The Pennsylvania Supreme Court in a 5-2 decision said it doesn't matter that there were no Republicans in some of these polling locations.
It's fine.
That is not true.
Well, that sounds true.
Here's what's going on here.
Trump's legal team had argued that their poll watchers in Pennsylvania were not allowed close enough access to voters, vote counters, excuse me, in the Philadelphia Convention Center.
Because of many factors, perhaps most importantly COVID-19-related social distancing, the poll watchers were kept behind a barrier approximately 15 to 18 feet away from the first row of canvassers.
So the workers would have a safe area to come and go as needed, like they had to go to the bathroom or whatever.
The Trump campaign argued that this was not appropriate, and a lower judge reached a compromise where they could set the barrier at six feet.
Then Trump's campaign filed a lawsuit claiming that the votes that were counted before the barrier were moved were, uh, they shouldn't count since the watchers didn't have appropriate access.
The matter reached the Pennsylvania Supreme Court, who ruled that the initial distance was appropriate for the requirements in the election code, and to mandate that the distance was too great would be the state encroaching on the county's right to run its election through the Philadelphia County Board of Elections.
That does sound right.
Yep.
They vacated any previous order and denied the Trump campaign their requests.
Oh, that's fair.
This is not what Ali is reporting.
No.
The Supreme Court decided that it was fine that the Republicans had no poll watchers, which is not at all the issue that was before the court.
He's lying about it because it sounds better for his side.
Sounds way better.
Yeah, because he's a liar.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This same strategy has been employed by Trump's legal team, including noted weirdo Jenna Ellis, who said, quote,
It's inexplicable that five justices on the Pennsylvania Supreme Court would conclude that watchers observing from distances up to 100 feet away is reasonable.
And then she pulled out her slide whistle and went, boop!
No, downward.
Boop!
Yeah.
Okay.
There is no evidence that this is the case at all.
In fact, the only reference to 100 feet in the court decision is, quote,
The campaign contends that the board set up imposing a barrier and having some tables in the area over 100 feet away from the edge of the security fence,
effectively deprived its representative of the ability to be truly present and effectively eliminates the representative's ability to perform his or her role of ensuring openness and transparency in the electoral process.
That idea only exists as a thing that the Trump legal team claimed but isn't substantiated.
I like that the Trump legal team could just be like, yeah, we're claiming that 30 different drone bombs killed all the Republican in the United States, and nobody is talking about that.
Nobody's talking.
And the Pennsylvania Supreme Court isn't even going to certify that the election was stolen since all Republicans are dead now.
Sure.
If you look at the findings of the suit, you can find out what the maximum distance from a person the watchers would be.
There was a 15 to 18 foot divide between the watchers and the first row of tables, then from the suit, quote,
A designated area of the convention center was divided into discrete sections, each devoted to various aspects of the pre-canvassing and canvassing process.
Each section contained three rows of folding tables, each table separated by five to six feet.
Even if you assume that, like, each table takes up six feet on its own and you use the high end of 18 feet for the initial barrier,
you still end up only with a distance of 54 feet from the barrier to the furthest table.
But of course, you know, also people could observe from different angles.
Sure.
Anyway, my point here is that you can easily see how talking points get created out of this.
For someone like Jenna Ellis, she can claim in a suit that people are 100 feet away, and then when the suit gets thrown out,
she can claim that the court determined that people 100 feet away is totally fine, and that's not necessarily accurate.
No, they can make any claim they want.
But this is how you can spin this case rightly being rejected.
Yeah.
And as for someone like Allie, you know, he doesn't have to worry about things like getting disbarred or anything,
so he's free to just make up anything.
Yeah, why not?
Which is what he's doing.
Yeah, go for it.
It's great.
Well, there's just no way, I'm blown away that at no point in time do any of these courts just be like,
we're holding you in contempt for this dumb argument.
One time, hold them, it's pathetic. It's pathetic.
It's a shameful thing to be a, I can't imagine being a judge reading one of these things and being like,
my job is valuable. How could you possibly think that?
I mean, you see how long it took to like disbar Larry Klayman, though.
Exactly.
Or like get him suspended.
They'll do anything to avoid telling each other that they're doing a bad job.
It does seem that way.
Yeah.
So there's a plan in Georgia, and it's not a fiddle contest, but Allie has this plan that he's going to lay out.
Alright.
He's one of these guys who really likes, I think he fancies himself a Bond villain.
Sure.
He really likes to lay out his plan.
Okay.
We're in Georgia, tell folks about what we're doing the next four days in a row at high noon.
So at high noon at the Georgia State Capitol, Alex Jones, myself and other patriots are here,
and we are marching and we are telling the Secretary of State, stop, don't certify.
The chances of that happening are zero.
But we might stop the deadline that happens 24 hours after that, and that's when Governor Brian Kemp,
who's been wobbly on this whole issue, then has to certify the election from his office.
So...
MWAHAHAHA!
That was less nefarious than some of the other times, but like he's being a little blunt.
I kind of appreciate that.
There's no chance we're going to achieve this goal.
We're going to fail, but maybe we won't fail later, even though it seems like planning to fail from the beginning
would suggest that we are going to continue to fail.
Listen, every day at noon we're going to be marching for something that is not going to work.
And then, maybe after that, the Governor will do some...
And by the way, Kemp did certify.
Yeah, well, of course.
That also had a zero percent chance of working.
You fucking larping pieces.
We're going to high noon! Get the fuck out of here.
Get a job.
Guns blazing.
Get a fucking job.
He has a job. This is it.
Yeah, well, get a different one.
Well, he might have to, because even Ali recognizes here that if Brian Kemp, if he certifies...
If even Brian Kemp isn't on our team...
We might be fucked.
We're fucked.
When he signs a piece of paper certifying the election, it puts a Democrat slate of electors to the Electoral College.
We cannot have this happen.
If this happens, our remedies in court then become next to nil.
Well, that's where we are now. You've lost Georgia.
Move along.
Let's get Alex to Philadelphia or something.
Let's get him in a fight with Grady.
Yeah.
These fucking guys.
I wonder what the next state will be.
Alex went to Arizona.
He went to Georgia.
This isn't going to work in Georgia.
What's next? What's the next state?
I don't know.
With the weakness of all of these legal challenges...
They're not going to get less desperate.
These are already incredibly pathetic.
What happens when all of these fail?
They have to do something and it's going to be even more desperate than what it is now.
I think it's got to be go to D.C. again or something.
Yeah, it's got to be something like that.
Or maybe Lexington and Concord, because you know how much they love the Revolutionary War stuff.
So maybe try and recreate that. Go down to Boston or something.
I'm waiting for them to be like, okay, we're going to head to South Carolina.
There's a couple forts around.
Oh boy.
We'll just see what happens.
I got a crazy idea. Alex is going to occupy the Alamo.
I don't think that's a bad idea.
This is my destiny.
Leave him there.
Sir, we have a group of tourists coming through. We're going to need you to leave.
I'm part of the exhibit now. I am Colonel Travis.
That would be great.
Late career change for Alex. Living museum display.
Instead of going around with his Mark Twain show, he's just like, I am Colonel Travis.
Yeah, he could just drink.
I think it would be great.
So now we get to Owen helming the show in studio.
He's sort of just giving a little talk over the footage.
He gets surprised by a little someone he sees hanging out with Alex.
And Alex Jones is right there on the screen.
Bullhorning the state capitol building in Atlanta, Georgia.
I think that's Nick Fuentes to his left.
Rob Dew there on screen as well filming.
Yeah, Nick Fuentes is hanging out with Alex down in Georgia.
There's Alex Jones and a Nazi standing next to him.
So I think we're doing great.
Having a great time.
I think we're doing great.
So Owen is just throwing to this video as much as he can.
Sure.
The globalists have been caught red-handed, engaged in massive fraud.
And the people know.
And the people will not accept this fraudulent election.
And just like in other countries, they're none of them.
We need a new election call in the disputed states.
Wild.
Stop the steal. Stop the steal.
Ah yes, such a great constitutional plan.
Ah.
It's called for new elections in the states that your hero lost.
This is really stupid, but for the first time in a long time, Alex makes sense.
He's back to being in an opposition role to the rest of reality, which is where he belongs.
Yeah.
It feels...
Yeah, yeah, I...
They just know they want fascism.
Well, they've kind of had to be blunt about it now.
They can't, like with the election results in Michigan, like, okay, okay.
I get you.
What if we just throw out all black votes?
How about that? Does that count?
Would we still have an election there?
Is that still good?
But Alex seems right out on the street.
Yeah.
More what I'm talking about.
You know what I'm saying?
No, no, no. He's home.
Yeah.
He's home again.
I compare things to wrestling a lot, but that's because there's a lot of similarity to the
distorted reality that exists on Infowars and in the WWE.
To get really basic with things, there are good guys and bad guys in wrestling.
The good guy is the face, the bad guy is the heel.
The ultimate goal of a feud is to have the bad guy anger the audience,
whether it be by cheating in matches or having a shitty personality or whatever,
to the point where the audience wants to pay to see the face kick his ass.
There are variations in some middle grounds, but this is the basic dynamic.
There are character types that only work as a heel or a face,
and trying to make them work in an opposite alignment does not play.
A cocky showboat who thinks they're too hot works as a heel but not as a face,
because the things that they have to do to play their character are inherently annoying.
The exception to this would be Shawn Michaels, but he was a once-in-a-generation talent
and rules don't apply to people like him or Stone Cold or The Undertaker.
I gotcha. It's fine. We can move on from that.
Similarly, the scrappy tryhard wrestler who refuses to quit does not work as a heel.
The audience watching a person take a horrible beating and still kicking out of pins
makes them cheer for the underdog who won't give up.
The giant they're fighting has thrown everything they have against them and they just won't stay down.
People love that shit, to the point where it's such a powerful thing
that it was used to turn Stone Cold's face in his match against Bret Hart at WrestleMania 13.
Bret went into that match as the face, and the two had a brutal match
that resulted in Bret getting Stone Cold into his submission hold, the Sharpshooter.
Stone Cold was bleeding profusely from the face, and he refused to tap out to the Sharpshooter,
with Bret ending up winning when Stone Cold passed out in the hold.
It left an iconic image, and that performance, where he refused to give in,
made it impossible for crowds not to cheer for Stone Cold, and thus he had to be a face.
Consider that previous to this his gimmick had been that he was a homicidal redneck
that was inspired by the emotionless serial killer Richard Kuklinski, aka the Iceman.
Who among us has not turned face after being like, I like serial killers?
Less than a year prior, he'd broken his former tag team partner Brian Pillman's ankle,
and then was trying to invade his home to continue attacking him,
which led to Pillman pulling out a gun on television to protect himself,
which was super fucked up and really scared people at the time,
because, well, the feed cut out right as Pillman was pulling his gun.
Okay, well that's not good.
No, and Stone Cold was rushing into the house.
That's not good.
Anyway, the point here is that there are characterizations that only work in certain contexts,
and Alex Jones only works outside any connection to power.
Everything becomes incoherent once he's trying to make excuses for the president who he supports,
but everything is still a conspiracy, just a conspiracy that doesn't involve the president,
and everyone who blindly supports said president.
It's nonsensical, like trying to boo a wrestler who has too much heart to give up.
It doesn't make sense.
This, I think, more than anything else, has made me feel substantially better since the election,
and I wanted to take a moment to address that levity that we probably have on the last couple episodes.
It would be easy to get the impression that I don't think that Alex is as serious a problem anymore,
or that I feel like the work is done now that Trump is out of office,
and I want to make sure no one—
Strongly disagree.
I want to make sure no one thinks that that's where I'm coming from.
Yeah.
It's my job to watch Alex Jones and critique him,
and for a long time he's not made actual sense from the standpoint of what his character is supposed to be,
which is infuriating.
Yeah.
He's supposed to be the only person who can see through the elaborate communist plot to take over the country,
but he's apparently also supposed to be the guy that has the president's ear,
but he's also the guy who's mad that the president isn't doing everything he says.
It's convoluted.
The truth teller persona needs to be someone who is ignored, or is listened to by people who are perennial losers,
like Ron Paul.
If you don't do it that way, too many unanswerable questions come up that penetrate the facade.
I'm grateful to be able to study Alex Jones during this period
where his persona was completely out of sync with the reality he's trying to present,
but I'm also incredibly relieved to re-enter a world where he's back where he belongs.
Time will tell if he's able to pull off the transition back to that place,
where he gets to yell on the street and everyone, you know, chants and stuff.
Time will tell.
But if he can, I have a hunch that there's a lot of money to be made off semi-red-pilled folks
who find themselves unsatisfied by Fox News but think QAnon's insane.
Yeah.
I think that Alex could have a pretty fucking profitable time if he's able to thread the needle back.
I can't believe that we're positioned in a place where it seems like all of these right-wing people
are just going to slide back into their positions, but we're going to have a higher tolerance for it.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, it could be a situation where some people are going to come out of this more sanitized to normal reality.
People like Mitt Romney, Marco Rubio might come off with a sheen of sensibility
because they're not saying Trump should say he's the winner or whatever.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then other people might, I think there's going to be a drastic reorganization in terms of media folk.
I think that so much radicalization and so much, you know, nonsense has happened in the last four years
that I don't think most people are going to be satisfied by Fox News.
The audience that they have catered to I think might have progressed past the point of what they're able to create.
Yeah, they radicalized them beyond a point where they can control or satisfy them.
It feels like that's a real possibility and that could be an amazingly huge market for people like Alex.
If they're able, like I said, if they're able to thread the needle.
And I think he wants to, I think he would love to because he loves money.
Yeah.
And he also seems to be having just a blast.
Listen to this.
This is Alex like, you know, I don't remember how free willy ends.
But I imagine that it ends with that whale getting to swim in the ocean.
Sure.
Free.
Yeah.
I think he jumps over the kid too.
Yes.
He's very majestic.
And it's really moving to see him like, you know, swimming.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is kind of like Alex as free willy.
Okay.
This is just free willy.
I want to salute and commit her by the shot of her today.
It's going to get bigger and bigger as papers around the country see this.
And I know on Saturday, you're going to be out here with at least 10,000 people.
But I know to all the millions watching, we love you and we appreciate you.
And we'll never give up on America for this new world order takeover.
Yeah!
He just gets to say nothing and people get excited.
Yeah, that's great.
It's awesome.
That's great.
He never gets to hear cheers whenever he's on the show.
No.
And he can just yell catchphrases and people get excited.
Yeah.
And I want to salute all of you that came out here today.
You are just the beginning of the Second American World Order.
You all are pioneers in the next wave of the Republic.
Alex Jones has been right about everything.
Come on, Alex.
You don't need a job that bad.
All right.
We don't even need to.
Look, look, look.
Even Alex doesn't want to hear that.
99% of the time, kid.
He says it.
You don't tell him that.
Yeah.
Alex can just yell these catchphrases.
People get really excited.
And then when he runs out of breath, he'll have someone like Ali there to tag team the
mic with him.
It's great.
It's perfect.
That's Alex swimming free in the ocean.
Yeah.
It's a little, you know, I can understand that.
It's a little bit the difference now between doing an online comedy show for people watching
a screen versus going and doing a live stand-up set.
You're not going to get those same laughs, man.
You go out there and do it live.
That's the juice.
That's the way it feels good.
Yeah, perhaps, perhaps.
So Nick Fuentes is there.
That's the downside of doing it.
That is a huge problem for me.
Yeah.
Downside of doing live comedy is you might get booked on a show with Nick Fuentes.
That's true.
All right.
So he's there.
And he seems like this dude's scary as hell because I can kind of see what his program
is right now.
And that is, so earlier he did his thing where he brought like his, his griper movement.
Sure.
And they started trying to embarrass Charlie Kirk.
Right.
And Turning Point USA at all these live events.
I mean, I don't know.
I feel like they won.
Yeah.
It seems like they pretty much beat the shit out of Turning Point USA.
I don't know how, how effective Turning Point USA is.
And also another point, a point of that is also that like Charlie Kirk is getting older
and his whole appeal as a college ambassador is maybe a little bit less sensible at this
point.
But whatever the case, I do think that, you know, he set his sights on them and whether
he's responsible for them having a waning influence, he's now I think moving on to the
GOP.
Sure.
I think that there's a target on like the actual Republican party.
Yeah.
And I know that a lot of people, their mentality would be like, let them fight.
I understand that.
But also I think if you let them fight, you run the risk of like, okay, well any gains
made by people like Nick makes this a even more Nazi-ish party.
Yup.
Anyway, he's not happy about the GOP.
The Republican party has failed us.
We know there was a fraud.
We saw it on election day.
There is no question about it.
And since election day, we have heard from our Republican representatives, absolutely
nothing.
Mickey Haley has said nothing.
Dan Crenshaw has said nothing.
Marco Rubio in fact supports Biden stealing this election.
So what you have here is more or less them getting ready for Biden to win the election.
Right.
And then their focus will turn to inter GOP conflict.
This is sort of the model of the Tea Party, you know, where the fringe inside taking over
the party.
Yeah.
Seems like they're just doing it again, but the figures that are doing it are even more
extreme.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And great.
And I look forward to that because this cycle doesn't seem to just repeat itself and get
worse as it goes along.
No, it's a testament, I think, to the true level of contempt that the GOP party operatives
have towards their voters is just like, we're going to lie to them, essentially take them
captive to our bullshit, and then we'll be able to control them forever.
And then we'll leave them sitting ducks to demagogues like these assholes.
And then all of a sudden you lose control and the mob comes after you.
And you're like, no, we don't even need to worry about them.
The mob is just so stupid though.
You know, Nick Fuentes is going to remain on the fringe.
He's never going to come in here.
And in 20 years, you know, Supreme Leader Nick Fuentes is going to be great for us.
Ugh.
So I'm worried about Nick Fuentes in the sense that, like, this guy is a real shithead and
he's young and clearly...
His box has fewer air holes in it than Alex's and Alex got rid of all of his.
He has plans, you know, that's what makes him worrying to me.
Though I will say that sometimes he has ideas that just don't make any sense.
We want Trump! We want Trump!
And if we don't get him, the trucker strike that is coming up this month is only the beginning!
Yeah!
I'm not sure if Nick understands his political alignment very well, but he should realize
that it makes absolutely no sense for him to be calling for a strike of anything.
He's either a paleoconservative or a libertarian depending on when he's answering the question
and both of these political philosophies are super anti-union and super anti-strikes.
We want Trump! We hate unions!
And we want every trucker in United 541 to stand with us and strike against their horrible oppressors!
Yeah. Typically libertarians view unions as an extortion racket,
trying to get in the way of the freedom of an employer and an employee
freely agreeing to terms of trading money for labor.
They would likely support a worker's right to withhold their labor if the terms were unfair,
but they would definitely, and I mean definitely,
be way more passionate about supporting a business's right to replace that worker
with someone who would accept unfair terms.
That's what freedom is about, after all, according to libertarians.
We are together recognizing that in the face of an overwhelming government entity
the only method of fighting back we have is to unite together
and all of us utilize our power to neutralize their power
and that's what we call libertarianism.
Great. I don't see any possible way for Nick Fuentes to coherently call for a trucker strike
in order to force Trump into office.
If the truckers were to strike over their disapproval about an election,
Nick's political belief set should require that he support the trucking companies
bringing in scabs to do the work these truckers refuse to do.
It doesn't matter because this isn't a statement that's meant to make political sense,
nor is it even something he can pretend would be effective.
This is a line he's throwing out in hopes of incitement.
He's trying to pump up the crowd and planting images in their head of their side
throwing the country into chaos with truckers refusing to work
unless Trump is installed as president is exciting.
It's exciting for them.
I mean that's the classic fucking takeover playbook though
is to utilize all the power of the stuff that you hate
to get yourself into power and then close the door behind you as fast as you possibly can
so other people can't unionize.
Sure.
Like that's how you do it.
Yeah.
That's the game man.
So they're out there and it's fun enough but there's also lulls
and when there are lulls Owen's got to talk and
Oh that's not good.
Here he says something very unsurprising.
Looking at the crowd here as they begin to march into the building
people who were on the caravan with me last week who are still part of this.
So Americans are ready to go.
They are not going to let this election be stolen from them.
There are people you recognize from the caravan because you were in Atlanta.
I don't understand.
No they were in the cars the whole way.
So the people who are info warrior types in Atlanta
are very likely to come to both of these events.
Oh I don't know if they have that kind of scheduling freedom.
I'm certain most of them are unemployed.
That's not fair.
So Owen gets talking about this Dominion conspiracy.
Oh that's great.
Love me a good Dominion conspiracy.
Man he believes just the dumbest version of this.
You know record. It can all be done off location. It can all be done remotely.
It's all been proven.
That's why they run with these systems.
That's why they tested it with Hugo Chavez in Venezuela
and then when it worked to steal elections for the communists in Venezuela it went nationwide.
You don't think that had something to do with
You know it's so historic.
Never mind sorry.
So for the record Hugo Chavez died in 2013 and won his last election in 2012.
So I guess the theory here is that this company stole the 2012 Venezuela election as a test run
then eight years later paid it all off with the US election.
This naturally raises the question of why the globalists didn't just use it in 2016
but we're playing with conspiracies so let's not bring real questions into it.
They weren't ready yet.
Chavez had just died in 2013. They weren't sure if it was going to work out.
Three years prior.
It's a mourning period. Have you not read about international and intergalactic contract law?
So the conspiracy that Owen is spinning is made out of combining details about two different companies
and then insisting you've proven something suspicious.
The two companies at issue are Dominion and Smartmatic.
Part of the way this conspiracy is presented is to claim that these are the same company
or that Dominion owns Smartmatic but that's not the case.
They are unrelated.
Smartmatic is a company that's provided election technology in Venezuela
but they actually have a history of calling out voting problems like they did in August 2017
when they found that the results of the constituent assembly election had been altered
which they knew because their system is tamper evident
and set to quote self-report any attempt to interfere with it.
Dominion has nothing to do with Venezuela so the ability to connect Venezuela with Dominion
relies on connecting these two companies which are not connected and are actually competitors.
It's important to remember here that the game that these people are engaging in is not to make a coherent point.
Their goal is to create a perception where they're right and everyone's out to get them.
In this case, the connection to Hugo Chavez is really telling
because it's not about a connection that's real.
It's about tying this whole thing to a right-wing boogeyman.
The anti-communist right-wing view Hugo Chavez as one of the world's greatest evils
so involving him in this conspiracy is essentially, I don't know, fan service for weird right-wingers.
I'm surprised they haven't just picked a bunch of the different left-wing governments
America's tried to topple over the years.
Why not?
No, no, no. Because Hugo Chavez is high profile.
Oh, that's true.
And he's a figure that most, like, Fox News watchers would be familiar with as a heel.
As a boogeyman, yeah. As a heel, if you will.
Yeah, so he's almost the perfect person to use as almost like a signifier.
And he's dead so it's not like he's going to come at you.
Sure. I don't know how he would sue anyway, but...
I don't think he was interested in suing Dan.
So in this next clip, this is where I just kind of lost my patience with Owen.
We're going to pick up the live stream from the Capitol again in about a half an hour.
I've got other news I'm going to get to as well as video reports in the meantime.
Boy, I mean, it's just so...
Do I go down the fake pandemic and everything they're doing with the torture, psychological torture?
I'm speaking as a producer here.
Infowars is currently in a no-win situation.
You basically have two main event players in the entire company with Alex and Owen.
Owen sucks and all that, but compared to the rest of these zeroes, he's basically Dominique Wilkins,
which I say because Alex is in Atlanta.
There are two roles that currently need to be filled.
One is in studio and one is remote.
And because there are only two people who can reasonably fill those roles, they have to do those jobs.
With two roles and two people, there are only two possibilities of how to organize things,
which is both trash in terms of presentation.
One option is having Alex in studio and Owen on the road.
This is good because Alex is much, much better as a broadcaster, and he knows how to move the products.
And he can say nothing passionately for an hour.
The downside, however, is that Owen is not a draw, so you end up with really lackluster, disappointing remote events.
Even on his best day, Owen can't get a crowd revved up like Alex.
Alex is old school on a bullhorn, and Owen is just a pretender.
The other option is what we have here, where Owen is in studio and Alex is on the road.
The upshot here is that you probably get more compelling video from the road,
because Alex is probably drunk, and he knows how to get people pumped up.
More people are also going to show up, naturally, if Alex Jones is somewhere,
compared to if Owen Schroyer is there.
He's a sideshow.
Yeah, so if the goal is optics of large crowds, you really need Alex there.
At the same time, you run into problems with the show itself, because Owen's just not that good as a host.
It's so goddamn boring, and I can't imagine he's moving any pills.
He says something like,
we'll get back to the feeds of Alex and Allie in half an hour,
and all I can think is, well, here comes a shitty half hour.
This is a substitute teacher showing a movie.
And the movie is Alex yelling into a bullhorn, and sometimes that movie stops.
Yeah, and you're like, what do we do now? Let's play Heads Up, Seven Up.
No, let's listen to Owen talk for a half hour? No, fuck that noise.
It's a tough situation if you're in charge at Infos and you have to figure out how to assign roles,
but if it were me, I would never have Alex out of studio.
He may draw a bigger crowd, but there are going to be a ton of people in Atlanta no matter what,
and Owen isn't as exciting as Alex, but combined with Allie Alexander and Nick Fuentes,
it might end up not being as poorly attended as the caravan.
You need Alex in studio for multiple reasons.
The first is that he's the only person exciting enough to make this dumb show watchable,
and thus make people more likely to buy the pills.
There's a financial reality that Alex is better for business as the host.
Then, on top of that, the whole point of Infowars right now is that shit is super dangerous.
Antifa and Black Lives Matter are trying to kill all the conservatives.
Remember a few months ago, Alex said that China and MS-13 had teamed up with the Democrats
to take out conservative talk show hosts? Legitimately, no.
He did. In hindsight, that narrative makes a lot more sense
if we imagine that Alex is just an out-of-control stimulant addict.
Yeah, that would make sense.
Anyway, I would advise Infowars to lean into this whole thing and make the studio feel like Alex's bunker.
The whole point of his career is supposed to be that he's the oracle,
the only person in the world who can see directly through the globalist plans.
The literal devil has been trying to enlist him since he was a child
because the devil knew that Alex was special and he was a psychic.
If you expect me to believe any of that, you have to protect that person at all costs.
The psychic who's the only person who knows what the globalists are going to do before they do it
is way too valuable to have out on the street yelling into a bullhorn with a couple of young enterprising bigots.
Yeah, that's not the best military tactics I would suggest.
No, no, no!
I would say.
Now that Infowars has become something so comical and hyper important,
it's time for them to get right with the script.
Alex is supposed to be this all-important guru, so he needs to start acting like it.
The studio's already established as having guns everywhere and being super well protected,
so Alex should only be making appearances from there.
Owen is the young gun, the warrior in the fold,
so he needs to be Alex's proxy on the streets, willing to risk it all
because he knows that his muscles and physical form are all that he has to give to the Infowar.
That's true.
I'm going to move on now because I'm getting lost in flights of fancy
about the ideal direction for Infowars to go in the future,
and again, as we touched on at the beginning of the show,
we keep coming up with better ideas for them and then they just don't do it.
I've got you beat by a mile.
No, no, can I tell you one of my other things before you do it?
Sure, sure, sure. Go for it.
So they like to try and present Harrison Smith as like the smart research guy.
Sure.
So I just had this image of him like every single fucking time you're on camera,
you'd be peeking out from behind a comically large book.
With glasses all the way on the tip of your nose.
Yes, and wear a fucking robe.
Yeah, totally. Totally. What are we doing here?
Like, why not?
Bring Joe Biggs back in and have him always have grease on him somewhere
because he's like a mechanic type or something.
Yeah, look like a monk.
He's a monk in there. He's got the...
Joe Biggs has been fixing cars.
Yeah, always, always been fixing cars.
Turn this into an episode of Taxi.
That's what I want. Danny DeVito should be hired by Infowars.
Why not? At this point, just fucking, like, nothing that they say is real,
so why not make all the characters actual fun characters?
Yeah, that'd be fun.
Christopher Lloyd could be involved. He's still alive.
Alex, I know you're listening. I don't think you're listening,
but if you're listening, I will quit doing this show in order to produce
the next season of Infowars.
I've got you beat by a mile, Dan, and it's...
I'll bring you in as a co-executive producer.
It's easy. It's easy.
How can Alex be in both places at once, you ask yourself?
Why are you wasting money on a fucking tank when you could have a hologram?
Yeah, that's interesting.
Harrison Smith comes with you, puts the little hologram Alex on the floor.
He's got a fake bullhorn. He does the whole thing remotely,
maybe does a little moonwalk.
I assume that they're going to mix the Michael Jackson hologram
with his to look a little bit better.
With a record, you'd still need a recording, though.
That's true.
Alex's time would still be strained that way.
I could sing Beat It for a while.
Yeah, you certainly could.
Beat it.
No one wants to be defeated.
Show them how funky...
Give them a hologram saxophone, just...
I could see it.
So, yeah, I just think that there's intrinsic problems with people
in the roles that they're in.
Like, they can do specific things to a certain level of competence.
And unfortunately, Alex can do multiple things,
but the other people he has can't.
And the only way to maximize everybody's skill sets
is to have them all start playing characters.
And in order for this to feel right, Alex can never be out of studio.
I know that he wants to be, and it is, like I said,
his free willy natural environment to be out there yelling into a bullhorn,
but that's not his place anymore.
Yeah, right. I mean, it is a little bit, though,
that none of them really understand who they are,
because they all think that they're way better than who they are.
Yes.
They all think that they're Paul Revere or some shit.
Everyone who works at Infowars is Lance Stevenson.
They think that they're fucking Kevin Durant.
Okay.
But you're still Lance Stevenson, okay?
You're gonna blow in Lebron's ear.
That's your job. That's all you've got.
It's not gonna score 20 a night. It's just not gonna happen, man.
You're a dick. Play your role.
It would be better, I think, for everybody if they did play their roles.
Totally.
And, God, it would just be more funny for me, too.
It'd be great.
But then that goes back to everybody would have to have
a base level of competence that just simply doesn't exist.
And we can't wheel it into existence.
But they could if they focused.
Okay, then everybody requires a base level of focus that does not exist.
The reason that Owen probably hasn't gotten better at going out
and doing these road things is because he also has to do the war room.
Right.
He has to wear these multiple hats.
Obviously, if he spent all his time focusing on, like,
all right, how do we manipulate crowds to the best of our ability?
Sure.
That shots work best in field pieces.
Right.
If he really studied his craft and really tried to hone that,
he could be an amazing tool for Alex to use
while Alex is the guru in studio.
Yeah.
Doing what he does best.
Right.
And if he had other employees that he had just work in specific areas
to be like, you are the person that I need to cover tech shit.
Sure.
Because I don't understand tech stuff.
Right.
You, Harrison Smith, you have glasses, you look like a dweeb.
Yeah.
We need you for that.
Do it.
Step into it.
Yeah.
It's kind of what Alex tried to do with, like, Mike Adams.
Mm-hmm.
Whenever there's a health story, we got the health ranger,
you know, that can be the reliable voice on that front.
Sure, sure, sure.
He needs that.
He needs the people who fit the tool,
or are the tools for the jobs that need to be done.
Yeah, but that would require Alex to have any interest
in in-house talent development, which it seems he has strenuously avoided.
Well, yeah, because I think he's trying to go for these cheap pops.
Yeah, and no one is.
Someone like Ali Alexander or Nick Fuentes,
it's like, all right, you're trying to capitalize on whatever audience
they already have.
Exactly.
But they're also using you.
Yep.
And it's not going to work out in any kind of long run.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a bad strategy, and I hate to keep giving him advice,
but yeah, you need to develop some talent.
He hasn't.
And it's too late, probably.
Has anybody he's had on camera in our entire time period improved?
Do you know what I'm saying?
I think Owen has some, but that's because he was super green
in the beginning.
I mean, other than a more increased, I suppose, professionalism,
as opposed to being like, although at the same time,
he was like fucking Hammer and Sickle and all that shit.
I'm not saying he's good.
No, he's not good.
Okay, maybe Millie Weaver, but that's also just because
the first time we saw her, she was Rainbow Snatch.
That's true.
And that stopped.
It's hard to come back from that.
Yeah, no, I don't think that there's a lot of proficiency
and skill development going on at Info Wars,
but here's what I would say is one of the main problems.
It's such a singular Alex Jones-focused world that you have people like Owen
trying to host the show, and he's clearly trying to be Alex.
Totally.
I feel that, oh my gosh, you've got Democrats.
You know, I'm going to try not to yell and scream
and get frustrated today.
It's just Democrats are the most disingenuous scum
I've ever seen in my life, and it's just so sick.
That's just a bad Alex impression.
No kidding.
One of his fake breakdowns with long pauses for dramatic effect.
He's just doing the exact same thing that Alex does,
but it comes so falsely.
Yeah, it's way less believable.
Yeah.
He's a bad actor.
No, he needs to find his own lane, his own voice.
He's like a comic doing someone else's delivery, basically.
It's tragic.
Because you have stuff like that, and that just falls fucking flat.
And then it goes to commercial, and Alex is back,
and he's doing shit like this, and you're like,
holy shit, you're running circles around people.
Who do you think's up in that blimp?
I'll tell you who.
He's been sitting over us for like 30 minutes.
Brian Stelter, punky-dumpty, is out there surveilling us in that.
Listen, I'm not saying he's a child molester.
I'm just saying I wouldn't let him pick my kids,
and he looks like a child molester.
What are you going to do?
What is this, Aeon Flux?
Everybody's floating in fucking dirigibles above us,
watching everything?
What are you talking about?
Owen's in studio doing a bad Alex impression,
then you cut to Alex in the field.
He's accusing Brian Stelter of stalking him by blimp.
Democrats are just the most disingenuous people.
I think God is in a blimp shitting on all of us right now!
I mean, what do you do with this?
It is like watching Michael Jordan.
You're like, he's just too good.
Owen, just fucking sit down.
Sit down.
You're Horace Grant.
You're not even Scottie Piffer.
Get the fuck out of here.
There's a part of me that kind of,
I mean, Alex is wrong, and he's a monster,
but there is a part of me that if he's frustrated with his staff,
I get it.
Yeah.
They're not good.
No.
He can do all of these things better than them,
and I guess he should be able to.
Sure.
He's 26 years into this career.
For sure, for sure.
I mean, Owen started at Infowars in 2016,
so it makes sense that he would be better,
but it's embarrassing the level of better.
It is.
And he's doing a really bad job of fostering
and sort of mentoring them in terms of whatever skills they have
not being emphasized,
if only illustrated by the fact that Owen's just doing an Alex impression.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, it's like Trump and his whole administration and shit.
It's like, I just,
you bear the responsibility for hiring shitty people.
You do.
That's part of your job.
Yeah, that's the administrative responsibility.
Yeah, and if they're shitty, you bear responsibility for not improving them
or even seemingly attempting to.
Yeah, that's why there's performance reviews in a lot of normal work environments.
Yeah.
So, yeah, this is all Alex's fault.
Oh, sure.
I mean, the buck stops there,
but just in terms of pretending this is a chaotic environment
where it's just perform Alex's just running circles.
It's almost outrageous watching this episode,
the difference that you see.
Yeah.
It's like I want to give a round of applause
that he thinks Brian Stelter is stalking him in a balloon.
That is pretty great.
That's hilarious.
That's really great.
That's really funny.
Yeah.
Not as good as a Dalek with a gun, but it's still good.
No.
It's still good.
Yeah, I do like the image, though.
It's out of note.
Because I see-
Brian Stelter's got binoculars.
I see the Hindenburg level where it's a giant blimp
and he's down and he's fucking, he's got a ship's captain vibe to him.
He's doing that whole thing, looking out the window,
just leaning down, just being like that motherfucker again.
He's bought the hat that Alex wore on Halloween years back.
He's wearing it.
He's playing Flight of the Valkyries while-
Yeah, with one of those sextant.
I don't know.
Well, as we all know, Brian Stelter only navigates by stars.
Yes.
So, I mean, Alex is coming in with this just dunking on Owen,
being like, Brian Stelter's stalking me.
And then, he's so good at this that he's even doing commercials from the road.
He's doing commercials from- God damn it.
Right outside Atlanta is the Georgia Guidestones, ladies and gentlemen.
So, we're here covering all this, trying to stop the steal,
educating people about what's really happening.
And the only way I could bring a security team with Antifa
and Black Lives Matter threat here, and they're strong here,
the only way we could be here to cover all this
and to seriously focus on what's happening is your financial support.
So, I want to thank you all for going to Infowarsstore.com,
getting great t-shirts, books, films, water filtration,
and then all the great supplements.
These are the highest quality, highest end supplements.
When I forget to take them, I really feel it.
I'm sorry, it burns the candle at both ends.
And without DNA Force Plus-
So, yeah, he just goes into a net.
Yeah.
It's remarkable.
Effortless.
He even recognizes that probably Owen's not doing a good enough job
of pushing the product, selling things to keep things afloat.
So, he knows that it's his job to not only go out there to draw a crowd
to make the optics that they need to push this argument
that the people are demanding Georgia flip,
but he also needs to get on air and add pivot to try and sell pills.
I mean, the weight of the Infowar is squarely on his shoulders.
Yeah, I really don't understand how-
See, that's the other thing that I don't understand.
How is Owen not self-imb-
Like, do you think he watches clips of his own-
Like, when I was doing stand-up, I would listen to my sets over and over.
I would watch myself do sets, and I would critique my performance.
You know he doesn't do any of that shit.
But, like, what's the incentive to?
Exactly. Be good at your job. I feel like that's a good incentive.
I feel like Owen could probably make a pretty decent argument
that he's as good as he needs to be.
He has a show on Infowars.
Sure.
It's basically the top of the, like, commercial conspiracy bullshit world.
Like, in terms of that media, it's a job.
You get paid. You're on Infowars with Alex Jones.
Yeah, but that's like somebody saying, like,
oh man, I have always dreamt of playing triple-A ball,
and I made it, and now I'm done.
Like, don't you want to get to the show, man? Come on!
But the dark reality is, for him, this is the show.
That's true. Ooh, that is a dark reality.
Yeah.
Because, like, for us, we're looking at it, it's like,
oh, you could work for a real outlet.
That would be, like, the equivalent of going to the majors.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But that's not the way he looks at it.
That's true.
That's not the way the people in this sphere look at it.
The only place to go up would maybe be Breitbart,
and that's probably not even.
No.
Like, you could work for Drudge, but Drudge is out of pocket now,
so you can't do that.
Yeah, Drudge isn't a home for you.
OAN maybe, but that's kind of a lateral move.
And they don't want you.
Probably not.
Their hosts are boring, but in a different way.
They might want Owen, but not Alex.
Yeah, that's definitely true.
Well, you could work for Rebel Media, but then again,
that's another lateral move.
Sure.
He's about at the top of the mountain.
That's sad.
That is really sad.
Owen's peaked.
That's really, really, really sad.
I'm bummed.
Yeah.
I can't wait to have him pump my gas someday.
And to your question about, like, why doesn't Owen get better,
one of the issues is whatever you accept becomes acceptable.
And if you can get away with just doing this,
why not always do this?
Oh, man.
I still sometimes wake up in the middle of the night
and I'm thinking about bits that I've done
and been like, how can I improve those?
I'm probably never going to do standup again.
There are stories all across the nation,
including where I found this story today.
I was doing a deep dive into this where the headline is
from a black lady, goodwill ambassador,
who hates white people with the headline,
should white boys still be allowed to talk?
That's in the Dixonian at Dixon College in Pennsylvania.
You're allowed to be racist against white people.
Deep dive, Owen did on this.
Did he read it, Dan?
Well, there's a couple important points I need to make.
Okay.
First, this essay that Owen found today on this show,
he's complaining about, it was published in February 2019
by the student newspaper at Dickinson College,
a school with an enrollment just over 2,400.
It was written by a guest writer,
and it's obviously making a point that conversation in classes
in the writer's experience are dominated by white male voices.
Sure.
From the essay, quote,
in my time at Dickinson,
I've listened to probably hundreds of white boys talk.
It feels incessant.
From classes and lectures to the news and politics,
there's an endless line of white boys
waiting to share their opinions on the state of feminism in America,
whether the LGBTQ plus population finally has enough rights,
the merits of capitalism, et cetera.
The list of what white boys think they're qualified to talk about is endless.
Something very few of them seem to understand is that
their ill-informed, uncritical opinions do not constitute truth.
It's kind of funny, actually,
because the essay itself explains why Owen being offended by this essay is nonsense.
Is exactly why he is, yeah.
Quote, the second thing most white boys seem not to understand
is that they do not exist separate from the rest of the world.
You do not speak alone.
You speak with the weight of every other white man who has spoken over a woman,
erased the contributions of queer people from history,
or denigrated broken English as unintelligent.
No, no, no, no.
When a black person does something, all black people are responsible for it,
but as we all know, a white person is an individual and cannot be held against.
You speak with the weight of policies and laws meant to forever define intelligence
by how it measures up to the bros of America.
As is made clear in the final paragraph of this essay,
this is about Black History Month and how the writer doesn't approve
of overvaluing white opinions, particularly when it's to the exclusion
of other, quote, buried or ignored voices.
Speaking as a white boy, I don't take any offense at this perspective.
The style of writing seems to me very intentionally to be confrontational
because it's an opinion piece about how her perspective and voice
were being relegated as being less important than others,
so rhetorically it works for the writing to be kind of brusque.
Totally.
It's stylistically sensible.
No, as somebody with a partner who teaches high school, believe me,
white boys talk too much.
And I don't think, like, obviously this isn't this person making the argument
that white people should never be able to talk.
It's just a perspective of all this conversation on campus
seems so much about issues that are unrelated to their experience.
White males seem to take priority and precedence.
Now, the other thing I would say is that the headline of this is
Should White Boys Be Allowed to Talk?
And I know from my time when I used to write for my campus paper,
generally editors write the headlines.
This person who wrote this article probably didn't write that headline,
and she's being lambasted for the headline.
The headline is more extreme than the actual article is.
And if you're an editor trying to get more-
Exactly.
Then you would make an extreme headline so people would grab their attention.
Yeah, yeah.
It's, uh, I don't know.
It's a willful misunderstanding of the point that was being made in this student newspaper.
And the right-wing media did a cycle with this back in 2019.
They already did this.
Yeah, it's a yearly thing.
It's like Christmas season.
It's 21 months ago.
It wasn't last year.
Who said it was an annual thing?
It is a yearly thing.
It speaks volumes that Owen Schroyer decided to spend time on the show
complaining about this college newspaper opinion piece from over a year and a half ago
because he wants to whine about how bad it is and it's tough to be white.
It's just very sad.
I just want to throw things.
It's remarkable.
That length needs to be gone to.
Yeah.
I would argue that the person who is furious about an op-ed piece in a student newspaper
that is thousands of miles away from him is the saddest person.
Very sad.
Yeah.
Now, we go back to Alex out there, Bullhornin'.
He's chanting.
He's getting some chants going.
Sure.
There's some Stop the Steal chants.
Are we going to do any locker ups?
I feel like locker up never goes that style.
No, I don't think there's any locker ups that I heard.
But there's definitely some USAs.
Quite a few of them.
And then we get another surprise guest appearance.
Let's go back to the state capitol in Atlanta.
He's outside now with a big crowd, Bullhorning.
Special session now.
Hey, right guy?
Good job being here, brother.
Appreciate you, man.
Enrique Tarrio enters the picture.
Cool!
Enrique Tarrio and the Proud Boys have shown up
with Alex and Nick Fuentes
and Ali Alexander turning this into a
real fucked up place.
It's the Washington Generals of
conservative propagandists.
Yeah. But, so Alex is out there
he's got this special session now chant going
and I've been pretty, you know,
effusive in my praise
for Alex out on the street and his ability
to rile up a crowd.
But here is the point where I have to point out
that he is only human.
And he cannot get any chant going that he wants to.
Because things fizzle out a little bit
and Owen goes back to him
and there's a little bit of a different picture.
Let's go back live now, Alex Jones on the PA.
Joe Allen is a communist Chinese agent.
This is not a joke.
America is in grave danger.
Do you think he was trying to
start that as a chant? I think he was.
Man, that's a long thing to chant.
Well, yeah. With a bad meter?
That's not good. No, it's not.
I think he was. I think he was trying to get it going.
That's bad. And also you can just hear
there's just, it's flattened.
There isn't wooing anymore.
The rally is over.
Those things have a time limit.
It's true. People can only yell so much.
You can only chant for so long. Sure.
So Owen wants to make an analogy here.
He's talking about these globalists, right?
They're like bullies who steal your lunch money.
Right? But they don't want you
to talk about how they're bullying them
and how some people might bully them.
Their analogies are spectacular.
This analogy stinks.
I try to make analogies here.
Try. You try.
So people can understand.
Because I don't know if people can understand
what I'm saying half the time.
It's like, is it just in my head this makes sense?
Or is this translating on air?
If you're in the
high school lunch room
and there's a guy going around
stealing everybody's lunch money.
Everybody's like, where's all my lunch money going?
This is weird.
And then you're like, hey uh,
Steve over there
has been going around
stealing everybody's lunch money.
I gotta pause it real quick because
I didn't realize the first time
I listened through this that
he's imagining a scenario where this guy
is stealthily stealing everyone's money
as opposed to... Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a pickpocket.
This is a high school pickpocket bully.
Yeah, it's a high school bully cat burglar
pickpocket.
And then Steve comes up to you
and says, hey man,
don't say that. That's hateful against me.
That could lead to violence against me.
Well hold on a second, Steve.
You're the one that stole all the lunch money.
That's who the globalists are.
That's who the Democrats are.
That's who the mainstream media is.
They've stolen your country.
They've stolen your integrity.
They've stolen your freedom.
They've stolen your reality.
They've stolen everything.
They've stolen your future.
They've stolen your children's future.
They've stolen our education system.
They have taken from us
everything except the very breath
from our mouths and now they're
coming for that too with a stupid
face mask.
And so you just point the finger
and say, you've committed these crimes.
You've committed these atrocities.
You're trying to make us a slave.
You're lying to us. You're dividing us.
You're gaslighting us. You're instigating
us. You're doing it. And they say,
don't say that. That could lead to violence
against us. Well, you know what?
Maybe you deserve what's coming.
There we go. You ever thought about that?
Oh wait, they have. That's why they're so
scared.
Did you really think we would just take
actions?
You usually thought you could control the mobs?
No.
That analogy that Owen used
is not great, but I think I get the point.
Owen understands that his position
in life and his career is to be a stochastic
terrorist and work really hard
to inspire people to enact violence on his
enemies, but he doesn't feel like he's
wrong to do that because he's decided
his enemies deserve it, his imagined enemies.
That's not surprising to
hear, and honestly it's a theme that kind of runs
underneath a lot of Infowars programming,
but it's weird to hear Owen be so
blunt about those feelings of wanting mob
violence. Seems like a bad move.
You guys stole everything
and I want everybody to
solve this problem and you deserve
violence, so I think we all know how we want everyone
to solve this problem. It seems like a really bad move,
particularly because we've done this enough times
to know that should anything happen
they'll call it a false flag.
Also, it's almost
impressive to me how much that rant
felt forced.
The emotion felt ungenuine,
but in a completely different way than the falseness
of Alex's outbursts. Alex
is way over the top, growling
and fake crying, almost like a clown's
take on performing an emotion.
When Owen gets rolling, it feels way
too much like he's thinking in his head,
alright, now it's time to get intense.
You can almost hear him trying to figure out what to talk
about next. It's a really boring
version of insincerity, and I just
don't enjoy it that much, as
is style. Yeah, and as far
I'm sorry to say this, but
his voice gets real whiny.
In the higher pitches,
he cracks, his voice gets real whiny, and
so his...
YOU STOLE IT! AND YOU DID IT!
It just doesn't sell it to me.
I try not to be too critical
on those kinds of fronts because I
think that most... Says the man with the golden voice.
Yeah, but I also have,
you know, there are
types of emoting
that I can do where my voice is very annoying
to folks as well.
I think that a lot of people don't have... I call that
talking for me. People don't have
as much control over
the tonal qualities
of their voice as they want to
without a lot of work going into it,
so I always try and be
understanding on that front.
I mean just more in terms of the
things that are very easily controllable.
Right. You would think after four
years you'd get a little bit better at
faking an emotion if your job is
basically to create
and present emotions.
Yeah, I mean if your job though, as you
see it, is really just to do an Alex impression,
you know. That's the problem.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah. So
in this next clip, Owen writes some
fan fiction about Trump
and what he's up to while he's hiding.
Sure. And just listen to this clip
and ask yourself, how is this
any different than what people online
do with Q&A? Okay.
But you know what? I think what
President Trump is doing right now is he's giving
these people one last chance.
What? And he may have even given
them a day and just said, you know what?
I'm gonna go away. I'm gonna be quiet
for about
30 days.
And you guys can concede this election
and
you can stop lying to the American
people
and you can stop making
deals with the Communist Chinese and stop
working for the UN and the World Health Organization
and
let me be President.
Or you can
continue to tick off the Americans.
You can continue to tick
off the Republic
and I'll
unleash this beast. I'll unleash
this kraken. I'll let this line roar
and you can deal with that
instead.
Because that's where this is
going.
Yeah, it's a million
marchers in D.C. peacefully
now. Yeah, it's gonna
be thousands of people peacefully in Atlanta
this weekend. But let me tell you,
if you steal this election from us
and you put in a UN
Communist
corrupt criminal Joe Biden in the White
House, it's not gonna be a million peaceful
marchers in D.C. No,
no, no. Okay.
Okay, so if Biden is
inaugurated, we will kill. Yeah,
I mean, more or less. Good work, guys.
Thanks for your help. He's creating this
fictitious imaginary scenario
where Trump has given a deadline
for the globalists
to back down and stop pissing
off the patriots. And it's gonna be at high
noon 30 days from now.
Because he's such a good guy.
You have to give him that chance
to do the right thing.
And now this is where this idea
that Owen is just creating out of
his own fantasy. Isn't that the same thing the
globalists have to do?
Hey, interesting thought.
That is an interesting thought. Because that dovetails
in this next clip. Okay, here we go.
Yeah. Trump's giving him one
last shot. And of course
they're not gonna stop.
But see, just like they have to have that
metaphysical comfort,
just like they have to have that metaphysical
comfort of you accepting
the mask, you accepting the vaccine,
you accepting
the tyranny, you inviting the tyranny,
that gives them the metaphysical comfort knowing
they didn't force it on you. You accepted it.
Trump, we have to have
the same metaphysical comfort knowing that we
gave them the last shot too. Why?
Hey, we gave you one last chance
to stop it, stop
with the enslavement of mankind,
stop with the lies
that you're telling mankind,
stop all of it, stop the election theft,
you can stop it all right now. The censorship,
you're coming after all of us. And they won't
do it. But they've been given the metaphysical
opportunity now.
So there will be no
excuses. Okay, this is a problem for
me on a couple levels. Oh, there's a problem
on a lot of levels. The first is that
this is just a preemptive justification for
murder. Yep. Owen is telling the audience
that once Biden is president, that means
the audience's enemies have turned down
this imaginary last chance that Trump
is offering them to give up their wicked ways.
It's going to be tough to eat your neighbor
but take comfort in the fact that they deserve it
because Trump gave them the last chance. They had a chance.
They could have changed their mind at any point in
time. They've earned it. That's the function of this.
Yep. The second issue I have is with
Owen's understanding of Alex's bizarre
moral system. Owen seems
to think that it's about the globalists needing to feel
comfortable that they give you a choice, but
that's not what Alex believes.
Alex believes there are literal cosmic
laws that even the devil cannot break
that involve you not being able to act
counter to someone else's free will.
It's not that it's a comfort to know you
didn't force people to do something, it's a belief
system that involves instant karma coming
if you do. It's a necessity.
I worry that Alex
may not have fully explained this whole
system of how the cosmos worked to Owen,
which is troubling.
I get the sense that maybe what happened is that
Alex got pretty drunk a couple times and rambled
at Owen about this. He misremembered
some of it. This is all Owen remembers, yeah.
It's about comfort, not
the immutable laws of the universe.
Even in, why,
why, why are you
saying that you have to do
the same thing as the globalists?
Shouldn't you be like, we don't have
to do the globalists because we're not globalists?
If you're saying we have to do the same thing as the globalists,
that makes me think that you're actually globalists.
It's not the same thing, it just has sort of
similarities.
With the
globalists, they're
like, they have to
trick you into doing something. Sure, of course.
That's deceitful. With Trump,
this is straight up. How?
Because this is him being like, hey,
everybody knows everything, this is your last
chance. No, he would be straight up if he
said that, but instead he's doing these weird
esoteric legal challenges that don't
make any sense. He's saying it to the globalists
behind the scenes. Oh, okay.
According to Owen's imagination.
So then why do I have to die?
Well, you had
your chance. Okay, that's a good point.
I did have my chance.
You heard Owen imagine this
thing, and you refused to get it on.
Yeah, I had my
obsolete acquiescence, I guess.
Yeah, and I think that this also
highlights the other thing where Owen is doing a
bad Alex impression. Totally.
His version of Alex's stupid moral
system isn't interesting. It's even
more stupid and less interesting.
It's not interesting, whereas Alex seems like
it's based on some kind of
real fucked up
belief system that
I'm interested in unraveling. I'm not
interested in listening to Owen
miscommunicate it. Well, he clearly doesn't
share that nonsensical
belief. Of course not. He doesn't share it,
and I don't think he actually understands
what Alex is trying to convey,
and so he just sort of botches it.
But he is doing an Alex impression,
and apparently this is some piece of this
mythology that's important enough that
he feels like he needs to also include
it. Jesus. And it's just
blah. Yeah. So anyway, I was
about ready to say fuck all this,
but Owen, every time
I think I'm out, he pulls me back in.
Alright. Coming up in the
next segment,
we're going to be joined by Alex Jones and
by Nick
Fuentes, and apparently
Alex has a big announcement that he
is going to be making,
and he really wants me to emphasize that.
So Alex is coming up, huge
announcement next segment.
I am not positive there is a huge
announcement, but when I hear that,
you gotta stick around. Well, hello.
That would be cool if he was going to
sacrifice Nick Fuentes to Trump
and eat his heart in
public. Alex has shown
inclinations towards cannibalism.
I think that would work. I think I would definitely
give Trump the presidency if Alex
eviscerated Nick Fuentes and ate
his heart live on air. The only
thing that I think is kind of close to
like maybe this is his huge announcement,
because it's something I don't know if I've heard
from him before,
was he does say that
the Austro-Hungarian empire did
nothing wrong in the lead up to World War
I. Okay, that's an issue for
me. Somehow that's a new problem
that I didn't know I had to converse with
today. Well, I didn't, well we don't have to.
Okay, good. Because I don't think that's his announcement.
He does say that, and I got confused.
We
can talk about that another time if he brings
it up again. I would like to hear more. It could have been
a stray thought. He doesn't
elaborate on it. He
says it's all the British fault, their fault.
Sure, sure, that sounds right.
Anyway, that's not his announcement,
but it could have been.
Maybe it's that Nick Fuentes had the
speech of the day. Best speech out
there in Atlanta. And
like I said. Did he just hiss for 25
minutes? May as well have, but he hissed
in the right direction. And that is
at the GOP who aren't backing
up Trump. Again, Nick is
a guy who has a project.
And his project now seems to be focused
on being anti-GOP.
He's a usurper.
Mitch McConnell has said nothing. Nicky
Haley has said nothing. Dan Crenshaw,
Madison Cawthorne, all the people
hailed as the future of the GOP have
remained silent while people like
myself and Alex and patriots
like you coming out to the state capitals
have been doing all the work and fighting
for this. So we have to take the fight
to them no matter what happens with President Trump.
And let's
be clear. We know China
Joe's a bought and paid for
enemy. He's not even a traitor. He's just a robot.
But when you've got
Marco Rubio and
you've got the gay pirate
Crenshaw and all these
fake people doing
all of this, they are literally
worse than the enemy because they act
like they're with us when they're really
establishment folks. Yeah, so
it seems like this is the direction
that they will probably want
to go next with
their targets.
Obviously you can always keep Soros
and all that shit in the back burner.
But yeah,
ineffective, cowardly
Republicans in name
only can be the new enemy.
The turncoats who didn't support
Trump in his hour of need.
Guys, I agree with you. They were lying
to you the whole time. But in a different way
than what you think. They were lying
differently than you. Like it would
almost, I wonder, sometimes I wonder
like what would happen if the Murdochs
just like one day were like
hey, we
don't want everybody to be
killed. So we're just gonna announce
Fox News has been lying
to you this whole fucking time. It was
our idea. We wanted to get you guys
to do the bullshit that we wanted to.
Now, we don't want you to kill
everybody. Sorry. Someone would
find some investor in
News Corp and be like
well this is why they said that cause he got
bought off but it would turn into a
conspiracy of its own. It's never gonna change.
So I think that
Alex is really into this too
and I think it's probably
a really sound decision on his part
in terms of where to take the rhetoric.
Where to take the
narratives. If you want to try and shift
into some direction
going against the
ineffective
turncoat Republicans or whatever
is probably gonna be your best bet.
Because then you'll probably get
a little bit of the slack of
people on the left caring about
what you're doing. If you're attacking
the people they don't like
less mean comments on Twitter
are going to come in.
And you saw exactly
this model play out with
Nick Fuentes when he started attacking
Turning Point there was a lot
of people who were like let em fight
or there were a lot of people who were like
haha look at this isn't this funny?
And in the process they
passively or by
amplifying and laughing
at them making fun of
Charlie Kirk aided
in pushing and furthering
Nick Fuentes' goals. So I
think that this is probably if
you're just trying to craft like
what do we do next now that we know
there's no chance this is gonna
work out it's probably a sound thing to do.
Well I mean I'm gonna
I would say going back to their
terrible military strategy and then
update it for us here
when your enemies are
infighting it is a bad idea to
just let them watch or to just
watch it. That's when they're weakest. That's when
you destroy both of them. You can't
allow them to regroup
after defeating their inner
struggle in order to become even worse.
And the worst parts of
it probably entrenched during
that infighting. Then we saw
that in 2009 onward
with the Tea Party we are
going to probably see that
again unless and I don't know
what you do like I don't you know I don't
like to talk about crushing
because I think that that's kind of
I don't know violent imagery
and I'm not super into that.
I don't know what you do to push back against this
stuff but I do agree with you like
watching and laughing like haha they're
destroying each other is not
good when one of the parties that
is doing the destroying is
far more extreme than
and that's not to say hey we should defend
the mainline GOP. No.
It's just that neither of those is a winning
strategy. No I mean what we should do
is what the right has always done
successfully to the left and the center
which is exacerbate
whatever differences they have and force
them to destroy each other instead of just
the right never sits back and watches
us fight.
Fair enough.
But anyway Alex says he's going to take over
the GOP which is what he said
years ago and then he said he had and then
Trump did and now I guess they're
doing it again but
this is so lucky.
Nick starts talking about
his view of America. Oh no.
And the mic cuts out at
exactly the right time. Yeah I would imagine
so. You know who the rhinos are and we're
taking over the party. We are the people
we are the populist movement. How would you describe
the new right
or just the new populist?
Nazis. Well I call it America first
because what distinguishes us
from them is our interpretation
of what is America. In our view
what constitutes America is the American
people. It's not America
as its economy. It's not America
as its government. It's not America.
It's not America.
Alright we are
live right now.
We have Alex Jones and Nick Fuentes
our
transmission there. Our connection has been
interrupted. We will get them potted up.
If I were a producer and I were watching
this and I knew who Nick Fuentes was
exactly. I'm not saying that's what happened.
Red button! Red button as soon as he can!
He's about to say it's not America the republic!
Stop it! Red button! He's about to say it's not
America the country! If he's left
to talk about what he believes the
American people are
it's going to become
a little blunt what his beliefs
are. I'm not saying that someone
did hit the red button or anything. There's
equally possible that their tech issues
just suck so much. More possible. But if
I were there I would have done exactly that.
Totally. Because you can't risk
like that
game getting blown up.
You're just waiting for them to be like
and we're going to round up
all the people with mental health issues
and put them in the...
Who hit the red button?
Exactly. All immigrants have to go
and okay.
Well. Yep. Yep. Anyway
I thought that maybe that
trucker strike thing that Nick was talking about
was just trying to rile up the crowd.
It turns out he really
is in support of this. Which is weird.
That is weird. But then it's weirder
that Alex is too. Okay. Fuck off.
And I'll tell you I really like what I'm seeing
with this trucker strike that they're planning
later this month. I was about to say I've been meaning to
promote that for a week.
If the trucker strike, especially on the east coast
is shut down. They should shut down blue states
and blue cities. Hey you're shutting us down with the COVID
hugs. We're shutting you down. And they
should come to Georgia and other state capitals and
just drive around honking the whole
time. In fact truckers I'm calling for you
on Thursday, Friday and Saturday here
at noon every day. Drive around
the
the capital honking your
horns. Honk for us.
Nick is a child so I'm less interested
in his political philosophy making coherent sense.
Sure. Alex on the other hand should
definitely not be in favor of a strike
just because he likes the goal of it.
The means that's being used to achieve
the goal is the withholding of labor in an
organized fashion, which he totally
hates. It's interesting and kind
of ironic why this plan that Nick
is so keen on would never work.
The biggest reason is deregulation
and union busting in the shipping and trucking
sector. According to Snopes there
used to be two million truckers who were
members of the Teamsters and now there are
only 75,000. Great.
The institutional power that truckers had in the
70s from banding together and keeping
those unions strong has disappeared, largely
due to political influence of
people who Nick and Alex would be largely
in agreement with, at least as far as labor
issues go. God. There is
often big talk about
truckers striking because it brings to mind
a complete shutdown of food distribution
and the myriad issues that come along with it,
but the sad reality is that these
strikes don't really end up having any
real impact because they can't.
If you're a trucker and you want a strike
are you going to get the Teamsters to strike
to install Trump as president?
Do you really think that's going to work?
That's probably never going to happen
so if you're working in a union shop
that's not going to be a strike, that's going to
be you quitting. If you're an
independent trucker or maybe you work for a
smaller outfit that's theoretically on board
with this strike, you probably can't afford
to do it because there's no protection for
you. You have no weight to throw
around by withholding your labor since
whoever's hiring you can just hire somebody
else. If those tomatoes need to
get to Kansas and you're on strike to install
your fantasy king, great, good for
you, you're fired, and this other truck
is going to get paid to haul those tomatoes.
The only way this kind of
strategy could work is ironically
if the world was exactly how Alex
and Nick don't want it to be.
If the trucker's union was strong and
everyone in it could vote to stop work because
they felt the election was stolen, it would be
super fucked up but they could make a pretty huge
statement. The political movement
that Alex and Nick are a part of has actually
ensured that this can never
really happen. It is because
it's clearly them being like, well we would
love unions if they agreed with us
and for some reason we can't get unions
to agree that we should destroy unions
and I just don't get it!
Honestly, even if this could
possibly happen, this idea,
it doesn't matter. On this
day, when this episode is recorded, November
18th, the guy who organized this
strike called it off.
Probably because it was an absurd idea
that would only hurt the participants and achieve
literally nothing. Well there is that.
Yeah, I'm fascinated by
this abdication of their
political beliefs though.
I don't understand it. Their political
beliefs are we will do anything
to get what we want. So
that's why it always gets to me
whenever somebody's like, oh Mitch McConnell's
a hypocrite or any of that bullshit.
Their only political belief
is here is the thing that I want
and I will do anything to get it.
So there's no possible way for them to
be hypocritical in this fashion.
You know? That's their belief system.
I understand that with
people like Mitch McConnell.
I know that Alex
isn't any better but his brand is supposed
to be that he's better. His brand is
supposed to be, yeah, exactly.
I understand. And that's why it's just
kind of weird to me that like
I get it
but I don't get how you
don't get it. Not you.
No no no, I know. I know.
Anyway, Alex's traffic is way up because
of course it is. Because of course it is. During these sorts of periods
Alex ends up getting much more
traffic I think a lot of the times because people
want to see him drunk and crying or something.
There's a lot of potential
for something. And he said
this a couple times in the last couple
weeks. That traffic is way
up and no one's buying anything.
And that's sort of characteristic of either
artificial traffic or people
tuning in to be like, oh
something bad is going to happen. Yeah, we saw that
multiple times. Multiple times.
He's like, traffic is so, it's
triple the size but people aren't buying anything
and I just don't, yeah.
We are seeing four or five times the traffic
on the side. It's pissing off the
public. They don't know what to do. They've got
feds, FBI that come in the restaurant
sit down every morning we eat breakfast.
They put CIA stickers on our car
even in locked up garages. And they
just want us to know they're watching. Of course we know
that you're helping guide in the
end of America and the merger with the New World Order
because it's going to be peaceful and good.
But it's not. They're coming to sterilize our sons.
They're coming with 5G. They're coming to fry us and kill us.
That's their own damn admissions. They're going to depopulate
us. And so all you FBI agents remember
you're going to be thrown
to the wind just like all these
tyrants do. You're destroying America.
You're destroying everything. So I feel good
about what I'm doing and I'm not threatened and I'm not intimidated.
So I have a hundred feds follow us if you want.
You work for the shy comms and if you don't stand
with us you have that on your conscience. You have
God to face and God's real and God's
the real judge. We'll be right back. Wow.
Whoa boy. That's something.
That's intense. Yeah.
That's a bit. Alex's traffic is way
up and the feds are
following him and putting CIA stickers
on his car. I wrote that down. I'm confused
as to why they would do that.
Is that just a
gentle reminder? Hey guys.
We're watching. Just to let you know.
We can put a sticker on your car anytime
we want. Yeah.
I don't know if
the CIA isn't a prank. Do you think
it might be a bunch of kids?
It certainly could be. I mean I think
that or it could be people who used to
like Alex and now have decided he's a shill
or something. Could be. Or like you're in the CIA
we're going to label your car. Yeah.
I mean or it didn't happen at all in
Alex's imagination. Oh that's a possibility.
He's just making all this up. He's just making up a bunch
of bullshit. Yeah. Any of these things are possible
but what I think is not possible
is that the feds are following him
around Atlanta and putting CIA buttons
on his stickers on his car. Would you say that it's not possible
for the FBI to
be going around and putting CIA
stickers on Alex's stuff? I find it
implausible. Where would they even get those stickers?
I don't know if they exist. Exactly. So
Alex gets in this next clip to what I
think might be possibly his
big news but it just makes no sense that
this would be the big news.
We're here. I've got big news as I said.
The Austro-Hungarian empire. I want to start
getting into it now. The freedom
streak of those of us that were pro-Trump
pro-America. We don't
go away just if they steal this election from Trump.
And it's the fighting
the fraudulent election
that puts us in position to absolutely
now if you thought Trump put a
big dent in the New World Order.
We're just getting started. Trump is just one way.
So I guess his big
news is that
Trump isn't the end. Which is not
news. That doesn't sound like news at all.
It's not big. Especially considering
he said it in 2016 before Trump won
the election. He was like, listen, here's the major
victory for us. Trump isn't
the end of things. Yeah, this is just
a step along the way. Exactly.
I don't know. If there was some
sort of actual big news, it's not
gotten to at all.
It's just that we keep on fighting
and what have you. Sure, sure, sure.
And then Nick phrases this in such a
weird way. But it's actually not that weird.
It's really revealing.
What they've done is they've disenfranchised
73 million Trump supporters.
The president gained
10 million voters between 2016
and 2020. There's more Trump supporters
than ever. There's more patriots than ever
that are aware of globalism. The idea
that stealing the election from us
and canceling our votes and disenfranchising
70-some million people
that we go away after all
of that, if they just get through,
you know, they speed through the process, they
see Joe Biden, do they think then that
we just disappear into thin air?
Losing an election is not the same thing
as being disenfranchised. But this
is actually a really neat moment of clarity
for Nick, because it is the
same thing to him. He believes that
he's entitled to win everything, whether it
be due to the color of his skin or his
radical Catholicism. This is
the same mentality you hear
in that tape of Richard Spencer that Milo
released. In his rant,
Spencer said, quote,
like, this is never over. I win. They fucking
lose. That's how the world fucking works.
Little fucking Ks.
They get ruled by people like me.
My ancestors fucking enslaved
those little pieces of fucking shit.
I rule the fucking world. Those pieces
of fucking shit get ruled over, ruled
by people like me. They look up
and see a face like mine looking down at
them. This audio was allegedly
recorded the day after the Unite
the Right rally in 2017,
which Nick Fuentes took part in.
It's not hard to understand
that underneath whatever slick presentation
folks like Nick have, that rage of entitlement
is just below the surface.
It makes total sense for him to claim that
losing an election is disenfranchising
his side because he's entitled to
win. Would he ever think that
all the people who voted for Hillary in 2016
were disenfranchised? No, of course not.
Because they're entitled to lose
to someone like him. They're globalists
and they're evil and they should be
Yeah, it's very, it's very
fucked up. It's exactly what they
Yeah, they want a, well, I mean, if you want
a homogenous nation, then the idea
that losing
an election is possible is kind of silly.
True. And
I mean, like,
he's not going to be pressed on this on Infowars
because Alex doesn't want to open up this
box of worms, but
I mean, he believes that people who have, like,
immigrated here shouldn't
vote and stuff. Nick, Nick, I have
a couple of quick questions for you.
Do you want a white nation?
Wow! Okay,
follow-up question. Have you ever
heard of what happens to people who don't have
quote, pure blood in a white
nation? I've heard, I've- Nick Fuentes.
Yes, I've heard. Have you heard
what happens to people who
do not have pure blood?
That's a point that comes up
in a number of discussions that he's had
that I've seen. The point
about his last name being Fuentes.
Um, and
I don't know, I don't know, I don't think
he really deals with that. I don't think he wants to.
No. No. Anyway,
I think it's interesting
that, you know,
this is all very revealing.
This, the conversation
that they're having, whether it be
Owen being like, yeah,
mob violence, they deserve it.
Yep, hey, they have it coming. Okay.
Trump gave them an ephemeral
chance that they had no idea was happening
because he put it in a court
filing where he said
that demons were flying in
from Stargates to shit on our shoes.
Pretty blunt. All
of their specific points that they're making
about these, the various
states are nonsensical.
You know, Nick is just
talking about taking over the
GOP. I think he's probably
is the most singular focus. Yeah.
And I don't know if he actually believes
this or he knows that Alex believes
it and therefore it's best to
play into Alex's beliefs.
But he's presenting himself as also
fighting the literal devil. Sure.
We're fighting a spiritual war.
You know, don't forget, it's not about on some level
even Republicans and Democrats or
globalists and people, although it is
in some sense, it is about the
rulers and the principalities
of other realms, evil
versus good. That's what it's always been.
Other realms, other dimensions. The Bible's right.
Yeah. So I don't know if Nick
actually believes that or if he's
doing this to manipulate Alex. Sure.
Either is possible. But also
you see that Republicans or
Democrats, globalists or
people. Yep. That's the dichotomy
there. That's strange.
No, he's genuinely one
of those truly terrifying psychopaths.
You know? Yeah.
Like, he's a guy who
provides you, I would
say that 99% of the people
in the world you can actually
talk to. They're reasonable people.
But guys like Nick Fuentes are
that argument for like, you can't
talk to this. He's a
terrifying psychopath. Yeah, like a couple months ago.
This can only be handled by a
larger power, you know?
Like a federal, or like a
law, not God, obviously.
Like a level of
something, somebody needs to step in
because this isn't a like
one-on-one conversation that you can have with
Nick Fuentes. If you or someone in his life
you might want to try and like get him help.
Yeah. I mean like a couple months ago he got
he posted a video of him
going to like troll a Black Lives Matter
protest. Yeah. Where like
he had one of his friends had a sign that said, I can't
read. Yeah. Like parodying
I can't breathe. Yeah, yeah, yeah. He's the type of
person who does shit like that. Yeah. Like that's
just like, take the political stuff
out of it. Take the, take anything
out of it. It's just
antisocial
disgusting behavior. Mm-hmm. And
I don't know. Anyway
I think that what we saw a little bit
in that CPAC appearance is sort of
continuing.
It's not been as consistent
or direct as it appeared
it might be. Mm-hmm. Because it did appear that
Nick Fuentes was kind of trying to
like usurp.
Say a little bit. A little bit. Yeah.
And I think that he's taking up
a mantle here as more of
like actual leader
than Alex. Yeah. And that's kind
of scary but also like what are you going to
lead? Alex's kingdom
is illusory. Yeah. He doesn't really exist.
Yeah. That's the thing that I
was wondering. Like what do you want to be?
The next Owen Troyer? Good luck. No. I mean
we saw this on, his ambition is
clearly far outside. Way higher. Yeah.
Yeah. Way, way higher than being
a second in command to Alex. Yeah.
Which is kind of why. His project
involves using Infowars.
Exactly. Not being a part of it.
As a stepping stone. Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
He probably is almost even embarrassed that they
are the sort of people he has to use. He still has to.
Yeah, yeah. As soon as he gets outside
of their level he's not, he's not a
ladder up guy. Mm-mm.
Uh-uh. No.
Owen who? What was the
what was the name of the event
that they went to? The RNC
remember
when Alex got super drunk and couldn't give a
The deplorer ball? The deplorer ball when he couldn't even give his own
keynote speech. Yeah. Yeah.
Was that the one where? No, no, no. You're talking about
CPAC. Yeah. The deplorer ball is where he got really
drunk and peed on a tree. Yeah, that was a different one.
Yeah. Oh, good
time. Yeah. No, at
CPAC whenever Fuentes showed
up and clearly stole the show from him
Mm-hmm. Like even then my first thought is
like Alex, this is not
somebody that you can use.
This is somebody you should watch out
for. Yeah. This is somebody who's gunning
for you and if you can't see that
you're insane to me. Mm-hmm. You know?
Yeah, but Alex and him can
coexist as long as he follows
Nick. Sure. Yeah, like I agree.
And if the next season
and the next project is
destroying the GOP who won't
bend to their extremist
tea party will, then
the two of them could have common cause and coexist
perfectly fine. Sure.
It's just once
Fuentes in his like larger project
leaning towards Catholic fascism
Mm-hmm. Yeah. It becomes
more apparent. That's where him and Alex
might come to loggerheads.
Yeah. But that's a ways off.
See, that's the thing though. If you're Alex, you
have to see Nick Fuentes and
realize two things. One,
it's, he's
never going to bend to you. No.
That's never going to happen. Uh-uh. And two,
there's only two ways that goes.
Yep. You bend to him
and he disappears. Uh-huh. Those are the
only options there. And when he's gone,
when he disappears, uh-huh, he's planning
something against you. Yeah, exactly. Exactly.
Yes. What don't you understand about who
you, why don't any of these people know who
their friends are? Yeah. Every,
everybody who's run afoul
of Roger Stone, Roger Stone has tried to
destroy. Uh, yeah. You don't think he's
going to do that again? Yeah. You don't, what do you think he's going to be like,
well, I have some sentimental attachment to Alex.
Yeah. Get the fuck out of here. He used to be friends
with Larry Klayman.
And we saw how that went. Exactly.
Yeah. It's not, don't,
don't, don't get involved.
Ugh. So stupid. Yeah, and Nick
Fuentes seems like, uh,
I mean, like, just
quite frankly, slick.
Yeah. Intelligent. Mm-hmm.
Uh, able to- Razor focused.
Yes. Razor focused. To a level
that you just don't see generally
with people who are in the Info Wars here.
Yeah. Yeah, I mean, like, obviously
I agree with you. If I were Alex, I would be
terrified of him. Yeah. And work
to pretend- I would be trying to destroy him.
I would, either that or pretend he doesn't exist.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. One of the two. Totally.
But Alex can't because
Nick is fairly popular
in these right-wing worlds, and he has
uh, you know, whatever
amount of juice that he does and
groipers and stuff, and Alex wants a piece of it.
Yeah. It's just so weird to be
watching a Greek tragedy happen
and not have that, like, if you're
watching a play and you're watching a Greek tragedy
you're like, man, those characters have no idea
what's coming for them next. Well, see
but here's where I would take issue with that.
It's the same thing with me saying that, like,
Alex should only be in studio and Owen should
be his proxy. Sure. Like, that is what
they should do, and that is a way that it could
play out and it's gonna be disappointing when it doesn't.
Right. You looking at this as a Greek tragedy
is also probably not how it's gonna
play out. It's probably true. It's probably way less
interesting, uh, than it is.
Yeah, that's probably true. Because people
develop and people change over time
and honestly, I think the most
likely thing that's going to happen
is that
Alex and
Nick will have some
sort of an alliance and be able
to work together, attacking the GOP.
Yeah. And then, I don't
know, Nick can't help himself.
He's also a fucking extreme troll.
He's a lunatic. He's gonna do something
that ends up getting him kicked off
whatever streaming platform he's been relegated
to now, or whatever.
Like, he can't not push the
envelope. Yeah, that's true. And he'll
just be some sort of an extremist
voice. Uh,
next George Lincoln Rockwell or
some shit. Yeah, probably.
I just, uh, he's just one of those
guys who it seems like
he's that, like, dark
candidate in the GOP
that they cannot see coming.
You know? Like, they just don't see him
coming. They think they're completely
different people, and then Nick
Fuentes is there and they realize they're Nick
Fuentes. I don't know. I don't think so.
I think that that's
writing a supervillain story
where only a shithead, like a
really dangerous shithead exists.
We have a couple
last clips here, and
they're just a little check-in
on how Alex's operation
is going.
He did a money bomb a little while ago,
and he made a lot of money from that.
But then he also decided to
take a tank across the East Coast.
So that was a bad idea from a...
And then he's been flying all over the place
and he goes with, like, a large security detail
and then also has to broadcast
remotely. Jesus.
And apparently this hasn't been a great idea.
He can't afford to do the nightly show now.
He just canceled it for a week.
Because I guess within a week he'll be back in Austin
and the, like, manpower
will be able to
be moved. That's a thin
operation. There is, like, no...
If there's no one else to run
the board, you can't afford to pay
someone, I don't know, 20 bucks an hour
or something? You can't get
someone on, like, some freelance person?
Guess not.
Guess not. If that is the
difference between, like,
like, we have the money
for it, we don't,
that is a razor's edge.
That's real bad. I don't know if that's
actually true or not. I would assume that
it's just not worth it.
Yeah, that would probably make the most sense too.
Yeah. And it turns out it was
between that, cancel the nightly show
or get rid of David Knight.
It's just we don't have the forces
to be able to have folks to run the shows.
David Knight in the morning, Info Wars, my show
during the day, The War Room. I mean,
you know, which was it? Cancel the nighttime
show or cancel David Knight? Well,
cancel David Knight. We love him. So,
but if you get to a point where the funding gets cut,
David Knight goes away, or Ola goes away.
Please keep buying products at
InfoWarStore.com. This is a real
fight, 12th round, InfoWarStore.com.
Great products, big sale about to end.
Sean Rappaport, NoMoreFakeNews.com
taking over. God bless you all. We'll see you
in Georgia at the State Capitol.
...
Oh, here she comes.
Watch out boys, she'll chew you up.
It takes zero for us to suddenly
just start jamming a little bit.
Look, it's totally lit. It's brutal.
Brutal shift.
I have no... We're all gonna die.
I have no confidence
in the staying power of my organization
and I had to fire someone
whether it be the nightly show or
beloved David Knight and hey, you know what,
if we don't get money, Owen might be gone.
Get the fuck out of here Owen. Anyway, here's
Hall and Oates.
Here's a jaunty
sax outro for the show.
It's very, very jarring.
Oh man, they just heard us.
I've learned long ago, or
maybe I should have learned long ago and
learned fairly recently not to take anything
at face value with Alex's
financial talks.
So this may mean something, it may
just be a desperate ploy for money.
I don't know, but if
the nightly show is canceled for a week
because Alex is in Georgia, that
is not inspiring confidence in terms
of... Maybe Deanna
Lorraine just sucks. I mean, she does.
She does! So maybe they're just
creating a fake reason to be like Deanna.
You suck.
Yeah, we need to find a character for her.
I'm not sure what it would be. I haven't watched
enough of her to really know what character
she would shine as in the way that
Owen as the proxy on the street
Joe Biggs as the mechanic.
Monochromatic snatch.
Oh, I see what you did there. Thank you.
No.
There's nothing better than
making a little joke and having somebody
say, I see what you did
there. I just don't think that that
conception of a character was any good.
No, it was not. The parody of
the social justice warrior
archetype or whatever, it just
had no legs. Even a good
performer couldn't have pulled that off. I would say
don't try and retread those boards. That's a bad
idea. Yeah, I don't know.
Whatever. We'll see
what happens. Anyway, I was a little
disappointed by Alex in Georgia.
Just as a whole, I
think that it was refreshing
to hear him yelling in a bullhorn
and people yelling back. Yeah, that's great.
Getting people excited. That's good stuff. But you also
notice once you watch enough
of it that it's like, this is really one note.
Yeah. It's just that over and over again
yelling the same catch phrases, the
same sort of
little blurbs.
You wanna fight? You better believe you
got one! And then everyone yells, yay!
It's like him yelling his get-er-done
or whatever. It's kind of,
it wears on in a way that
you shouldn't be in Georgia for multiple days.
You should just be there
for a sting and then
get back to the fucking studio where you're needed.
Yep, yep. But
you know, it didn't work out.
No. Georgia did not work for
Alex. Again. Yes. Again.
And this is coming out on Monday, so we'll know
for sure, you know, the certification
status. Yeah.
But does not, oh I'm sorry,
I mean with Michigan. Yes. If they were talking about that earlier.
They were talking about Michigan. Pardon me, yeah. So we'll see you on
that one.
And I don't know, I just, I think this is
going to fizzle, and they're going to need to find
themselves on more solid ground.
And it appears to me that solid ground, if
they're smart, is
a new
Tea Party thing.
Attacking the GOP. Yeah.
Yeah, that would make the most sense. Yep.
So we'll see.
Ah, let's hope! Yep.
We'll be back, Jordan, but until then, we have a website.
We do have a website, it's KnowledgeFight.com.
Yep, we're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter, it's
UnderscoreFight at go2bedjordan.
Yep, we're also on Facebook. We are on Facebook
if you're downloading right to iTunes,
and if you could, please find a local charity or bail fund
in your area to help out people doing God's work right
now. Yep, we'll be back, but until then,
I'm Neo, I'm Leo, I'm
dzxclark.
I'm the Juiciest Ice Cube.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan,
I love your work. I love you.