N-N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Damn, Ed, Jordan, I am SWEATING
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for Knowledgefight
Knowledgefight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Shang, we are the bad guys, Knowledgefight
Dan and Jordan, Knowledgefight
Rattle her, rattle her, rattle her
Need, I need money, rattle her, rattle her
Andy and Kansas, Andy and, Andy and
Stop it, Andy and Kan, Andy and Kansas
Andy and, Andy and, it's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding us
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan
I love your work
Knowledgefight
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledgefight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're a couple dudes, like to sit around, drink novelty beverages
and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are Dan
Jordan
Dan!
I have a quick question for you
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, Jordan, is just a nice sort of glow
the post-holiday glow of having, we got to spend a little time
Oh yeah, indeed
the live stream put on by Cognitive Dissonance
It was great, raised a lot of money
That was awesome, congratulations
Yeah, it was really a great time, a lot of fun to chat with them
and to be overwhelmed, quite frankly, by the support of people donating to the Senate campaign
Quite crazy, honestly
And I started to reflect on it, I'm like, we did a terrible job of promoting this
I think there's some tweets and stuff, but we forgot to mention it on our last episode
because we recorded it in advance
It's too early, it's too early, it was a day early
We can't promote something more than a day in advance
Two days in the future doesn't exist in my bright spot
It doesn't exist for us
But yeah, it was nice to be invited, it was nice to be along for the ride on that
It was fantastic
How about you, what's your bright spot?
My bright spot, Dan, aside from us having a lovely holiday together
playing some board games and the like
You introduced me to ham
I did introduce you to ham, I cooked you a ten pound ham, Dan
Well, I didn't eat all of it
We ate less than two pounds of that ham
I come from a non-ham family, and so I have not experienced really like a ham steak
or like a slice of ham
Marinated in a little maple syrup, did all kinds of fun stuff
I couldn't really taste the maple syrup
Nope, I'm not good at cooking ham
But it was very nice, very, very delightful
It was a great, great holiday, but in order to tell you what my actual bright spot is, Dan
I'm gonna have to open up my correspondence cage
Just to be clear, we didn't have a big gathering or anything
We didn't, no
In case people are thinking that we had like a Thanksgiving party
It was the two of us
Yeah
As always
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Just in case people are thinking, ah, you're flouting COVID
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we're all, oh yes, me and-
Very careful, very careful
It was very, very small
I'm sorry, but go ahead
No problem
Yeah, I'm gonna go ahead and open up my correspondence cage over here, Dan
Click
And a new raptor princess, Kranat, created a cover for my book
Oh, that's great
Made a graphic design that is not just a great cover and a great design, but like really perfect
Uh-huh
It made me feel seen
It was really, really cool
I did see the design and it looks fantastic
It looks fantastic
And so that's awesome
Yes
I'm really happy for you and that's a really awesome piece of work to have been created
I have some issues with your correspondence cage
What about it?
Not a fan
What, what, what, don't you like about it?
Second, I have another problem
Was to open the lock
No, I got the sound effect
Click, yeah
I have another problem and that is you're naming someone a raptor princess
Yes
And you're not telling me in advance, so I don't have the clip here
I don't know
I don't have the drop
I can't just tell you to play a raptor princess clip
I feel like that's something that you have to also choose to do
Well, see, this is what we really need to talk about
And that is you should have made your own drop
Yes, I should have made my own drop
If you're naming someone a raptor princess, you need to come
If you're coming in with the correspondence cage sound effect
You really should have your own drop
I understand, you're right, I should have my own set of drops entirely
Uh-huh
Yes
I think that's a good idea
You really want to annoy me
If you really want to escalate this arms race of annoying each other, that is the way to go
That would be a great, that would be a great decision
So is that crannot, is that right?
Yes, crannot or craynot
Okay
Not sure the, it was a correspondence
And yeah, it's tough to know how vowels are long or short
Exactly
Yeah
On the page
Well, thank you
Yes, indeed
On, I know that this is a gift for Jordan, but I'll still thank you
I think it's pretty cool that that exists
Fantastic
So, Jordan, we got an interesting episode to go over today
Yes, we do
And we got a lot of, lot of bullshit, lot of, lot of business to get into
But before we do, uh, let's, uh, take a little moment say thank you
to some folks who have signed up and are supporting the show
That's a great idea
So, first, paganfilthisdustin, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, paganfilthisdustin
Thank you! Next, NateS, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Nate
Thank you! Next, DexterKW, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you, Dexter
Thank you! Next, Anna, no last name, no last initial
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Anna!
Thank you! Next, Simon Starian Firedoodle, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Mr. Doodle, I believe is what I'm going to be calling him.
Thank you so much. And then, RoCoCoLibertarian, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, RoCoCoLibertarian.
Next, Kat, with a K, Kat V, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks very much, Kat!
And finally, I'd like to say thank you to a couple of people who donated on an elevated level, we appreciate that very much.
So first, Elise Middlefart, thank you so much, you are now a technocrat.
And, ooh, tough one here, Donald Trump, thank you so much, you are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate, that's fantastic, have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
Alright, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, alright?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why are you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much, Elise Middlefart, and thank you so much, Donald Trump.
Yes, quite a situation for him to be like, well, the only way to take down the GOP people who are betraying me is to donate to knowledge fights.
Yeah, that'll do it.
That'll get him.
So, Jordan, today I found myself in a little bit of an interesting pickley conundrum.
Sure.
And that is that Thanksgiving happened and Alex was out of studio for the end of the week.
And so in terms of us coming back with something from Alex's oeuvre seemed like it was gonna be a difficulty.
Owen Troyer was in studio filling in.
Ugh.
I guess we could have maybe forced something out of like Alex's little, you know, hey how you doing videos.
Sure, sure.
Standing in front of a lake yelling about something or other.
But I just wasn't interested.
And so I thought like now is the time we gotta get wacky.
It's a wacky Monday.
It's time.
It's been a while.
What we thankfully have is I think that Carrie Cassidy, Swery Carrie, over at Project Camelot has given up on her paywall format.
I don't know if that's because enough people were generous or if, I don't know what the deal is, but these videos are all very available and I've not had to log into anything to get them.
I think Carrie missed our episode.
It's possible.
I think Swery Carrie was like, if they're never gonna do an episode on me again, I better make these free.
She missed us.
She missed the thing we've got.
So I guess there are anybody, you know, who's sort of newer to the show.
Whenever we need to take a break from Alex Jones, we like to look into the world of Project Camelot, which is a YouTube channel run by a lady we call Swery Carrie who interviews space weirdos.
Yep.
Various super soldiers, people who have been to Mars, people who are psychics.
She is a psychic herself.
Of course.
She hangs out with this guy named Mark Richards.
A little bit Pleiadian, but not a ton.
Well, maybe.
Maybe.
It's debatable.
Someone told her that who might be a racist alien.
He was definitely a racist alien.
And then he became Death.
That'll happen.
The Archangel Abaddon.
That's true.
There's a lot of lore here.
Her main source of information, her big sort of whistleblower is this guy named Mark Richards who is a murderer who was framed for murder because he was off planet at the time.
Well.
He was a sentient spaceship Minerva.
Indeed.
And his friends in the raptor beings.
Right.
Right, right, right.
Doing a mission of some sort.
Just to be clear, we didn't make this up.
Nope.
This is stuff we've learned.
We've observed this in the wild.
Yeah.
So, unfortunately over the time that we have looked at this, it was supposed to be just a pressure release valve.
Of course.
We've come to realize that Carrie is also very into QAnon.
They are dovetailing together our two shows.
And that kind of took a little bit of the charm away from it.
But, sometimes you still just need a hit.
You gotta go to the well.
Yeah.
So today, Jordan, we're going to be looking at a video that was released on Project Camelot on November 12th.
Which is a little bit of an election Q&A.
Okay.
Post-election Q&A.
Alright.
Okay.
You probably have some Q's.
I got some Q's.
Carrie's got some A's.
Out of CVAs.
Here's her introduction.
Hi everyone.
I'm Carrie Cassidy from Project Camelot.
Hi Carrie.
So, very happy to be here today.
But my guest didn't show up.
So, I guess she had some conflict or other and we'll have to reschedule.
I'm not sure what's going on there.
Anyway, so, I just thought I'd do a Q&A if that's useful.
I love it.
Now, I want to say that I do not think anything is bad about a guest canceling.
That shit happens.
No, no.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I only left that introduction in because it is the setup for a punchline later.
And I don't want to turn this show into a thing where you're yelling bingo all the time.
Okay, I'm not going to try and yell bingo all the time.
But I would like to see if you can figure out where the payoff to that joke is.
Okay, alright.
I think you'll be able to figure it out.
Is the guest that cancelled actually her?
No.
Is this a Fight Club scenario?
No, no, no, no.
Alright.
But there is definitely something that's like, wait a second.
There's literally no way this guest should have ever cancelled.
You'll see once it happens.
Okay.
Alright.
So, a Q&A would be nice.
Certainly, like I said, you got Qs, Carrie's got As.
Of course.
But it turns out this is even more than just a Q&A.
Alright.
This, what she started down this road.
A Q-Anon-Anay.
Ooh.
There's a lot going on.
I can say that, in general, I did have a precog dream last night, finally, about the outcome
so far.
It's an interesting dream that I had.
So, maybe I'll just share that and then you can go ahead and ask questions about whatever.
So, when I hear a caller on the Alex Jones show talk about their dreams.
Yes.
Not interested.
Uh-uh.
Boring.
When I hear Swery Carrie open up the show saying, I had a precognitive dream, finally,
about the election.
Fire in my heart.
I had a precog dream several days after the election, finally.
About what's going to happen here.
The election, yes.
And so, she gets into that right at the beginning, right at the top, and it turns out that she's
a good storyteller, because she sets the scene for what was going on before the dream.
Sure, sure.
In order to give you some context.
She had spicy foods?
Maybe.
That might be the truth behind the words she's using, but I'll leave that to the Pleiadians
to know for sure.
So, my dream, basically, was, and I had a very, they were shooting a 5G at me last night,
so, I know Trump doesn't have complete control over scalar weapons that are being used, and
so on and so forth.
So, I was up most of the night, on and off, and then finally fell asleep, I think, around
6 or so AM.
So, I mean, look, she was having 5G shot at her.
Scalar laser 5G attack.
No, I understand, and she was saying that, and I get that, fine, you were having 5G shot
at you, that's a happening.
Sure.
How did she know?
Because she didn't say what the effects of having 5G shot at.
She has 5G sensors.
No, apparently, not being able to fall asleep is a sign of 5G attack.
That's it.
Well, I mean, I've certainly been someone who's struggled with insomnia at periods in
my life.
Sure, sure.
A lot of times, I still, it takes me a long time to fall asleep.
It's frustrating.
It sucks.
I have friends who'd be like, I lay down, and two minutes later I'm out, and I get mad
at them.
I'm furious.
Because it'll take me an hour and a half, at least, usually, of just laying there to
fall asleep.
And it sucks, but if I could imagine that I was under 5G scalar attack, that'd probably
be more exciting.
Or it might make it harder.
It would up the drama.
I feel like it would make it impossible to sleep.
Yeah, because then I'm like, oh no, 5G.
Instead of going to bed at midnight and falling asleep at two, you fall asleep at six, and
you're worried about 5G attacks the whole time.
Yeah, maybe I'm glad I don't think this.
I think that's a good idea.
Yeah.
Now, the problem is, I've been outside your window with my phone pointed at you every
night, so that's why you've been having trouble sleeping.
Does your phone have that app, the 5G shooting app?
It does.
Wow.
Well, it actually emerges from a compartment in my phone.
That's important.
Yes.
Your Dalek phone.
Yep.
So this is the setting of the dream, 5G attack all night.
Of course.
And then she gets to sleep at around six in the morning, and here is part of the dream.
And then I had this dream in which I saw the television, and Trump had taken it over and
was showing, actually, individuals and indictments and individuals that had actually been killed
part of their indictments in, I guess, a military tribunal type of situation.
And it was all being announced to the entire public.
And I was very happy because these individuals were very dark and involved in hurting children
and the children in the underground bases, adrenochrome and all of that.
Sure.
Of course.
So that was the dream.
It was like a little movie.
It's quite a dream.
Quite a dream.
Carrie's a...
If I were a dream analyst, if you will.
She's dreaming about stuff she's read on blogs.
I wouldn't go with precog.
I would go with, you've got some really violent fantasies, lady.
Well, I think that she's tapping into the zeitgeist of a lot of the online extreme right.
Like, these are the sort of fantasies that get trafficked on message boards, and even
people like Alex engage in.
This idea of Trump righteously taking over and killing their enemies is what they desperately
want.
Yeah.
You know, I get bloodthirst to a point, you know.
Somebody was, whatever nonsense somebody wrote in like the Atlantic or something where it's
like, but we don't want to see Trump dragged from the White House.
Are you talking about Friedersdorf again?
No, I'm not talking about Friedersdorf.
The American people don't want to see Trump taken away from the White House.
He needs to concede like an adult.
And part of me is just sitting there going like, no, I would like to see him dragged
out by his hair.
I would like to see him dragged through the streets.
That would be great.
That's a little bloodthirst.
I get it.
I don't think it will, I don't think it's a good idea, actually.
I think the consequences of it are so much worse than whatever catharsis you get out
of it.
Exactly, right?
I can have that second level of thought.
I don't have the like, nope, the end bloodthirst.
That's all I need.
Yeah.
It's like, okay, let's imagine a scenario where Trump does take over broadcast television
and announces like he's killed all of his enemies.
Like, what happens next?
What the fuck kind of world are we living in?
Where the president is just like, I've taken over all beads of communication.
Well, just so you guys know, killed everybody.
I killed almost everybody.
Bill Gates got away on a white horse.
Too pale for me, guys.
Too pale for my blood.
So Carrie's talking real specifically about a person who has been killed in this dream.
Sure.
I'm not sure.
I'm looking, I'm scanning the chat right now, and I'm not sure what some of these questions
refer to.
If you're referring to my dream, the details were very visual.
So like I said, there was television on, I was seeing it, it was literally, the part
that it was on was a particular person who had been killed as part of the sort of, I
don't know, whatever you want to call it, indictments and certainly payback for his
crimes against humanity.
She doesn't say who?
She never says who?
No.
That's bullshit.
She had a dream, it was visual, so she saw the person.
Yeah, she had to have.
Conceivably.
And she knows that person's crimes.
Well, it's against humanity.
Yeah.
I would say that it's either gotta be Soros or Bill Gates, right?
I'm gonna go with Stelter all the way.
No, she doesn't hate Stelter nearly as much.
I think Stelter is in the dreams of all right-leaning people.
That's his power?
Yes, exactly.
That's his demon clown power?
Yeah, yeah, Stelter on 39th Street.
I don't think it's Stelter.
Stelter on Elm Street.
I don't know, man.
I don't know.
Maybe it's not a human.
Maybe it's a raptor.
It could be a raptor.
Whoa.
What if it's an alien?
Holy shit.
It has to be an alien wearing a human face, though.
It doesn't have to be.
Oh, that's a good point.
Yeah, because once Trump takes over the TV news and talks about how he's killed all his
enemies, it could be like, and some of them.
Ooh, man.
Take it one level.
Some of them are reptiles.
Look, it's fucked up if all of a sudden we hear that Trump killed all of his enemies,
but if at the same time he finds out that aliens are real, and he's killed aliens,
and we've got intergalactic treaties going on.
But Ike is now my Surgeon General.
What?
Nobody else can handle these raptor surgeries.
Gee.
So anyway, this person that she's talking about has been killed already in the dream.
Sure.
But she won't say who it is, and it's really frustrating.
It was interesting because it was literally about the fact that they already killed the
person.
So that seems quite adventurous to come forward in that way.
It does.
But that, in theory, is the plan, and they have said that they have killed certain people,
or it has been put out there.
Now, Trump, of course, has not said this yet.
So this was an official report, and it was clear that he had commandeered a television
station or maybe, and took the internet down.
No, but it was an official report in the dream.
In the dream it was official.
I understand, but don't say official report in the dream.
Oh, so Trump took down the internet?
How fucking scary is this?
He just took it down.
How scary is this?
And how much does this fit all of your nightmare versions of what the Democrats are trying
to-
No, this is a fantasy fulfillment dream.
Right.
Trump has taken down all of the internet, controls at least one TV station-
He's seized communications.
He's murdering people.
He's crippled your ability to communicate with your audiences and your communities.
And I'm so happy.
Great.
So this might've been a vision, this dream.
It might've been a dream, might've been a vision, probably a dream, probably a vision.
He says, or they say, the QAnon and so on and so forth, the philosophy behind it is
they want to show people.
So my last video I said, okay, fine, show us.
In other words, don't talk about showing us, show us.
I get the sense that there is a possibility that what she's trying to say is that her
dream was a vision that was granted by Q.
I am expecting something along those lines.
It sounds to me a little bit like there is a belief that Q can give you dreams.
How long can you wait on the whole-
For a vision from Q?
Well, not just that.
Well, I mean, obviously you can wait a long time for a vision from Q.
But, okay, she said last week, the philosophy behind Q is show people, which, bananas thing
to say about Q considering its track record.
But how are you still waiting?
Does she think the dream, she thinks the dream is a response to her saying show me what's
going on.
Yes.
Oh my God, we're all going to die.
Yeah.
And this is also two weeks ago, so this shit has not happened.
Oh boy.
Happened yet.
I think she did it.
This sucks because, okay, you don't have to yell bingo because the bingo is going to be
in this clip.
Okay.
There's no other way for me to set this up without it being obvious.
All right.
Okay.
I gotcha.
But afterwards, I'd like you to explain to me why this is the punchline to the joke of
the guest canceling.
Okay.
My guest, who was supposed to be here, she is actually-
The gate of gates?
An interesting woman, and she considers herself something of a time traveler.
She is also involved in researching, I guess, CV.
I'm not going to say the name.
And her book is going to be about that.
So, hopefully, we can get her back.
She was on my show a few years ago.
So, why is it really fucked up that this guest missed the show?
Dan, if you are a time traveler, it seems like you would, at the very least, be able
to make plenty of things on time.
You would never miss an appointment if you're a time traveler.
It really doesn't seem...
I mean, maybe you can't use time travel for this kind of mundanity, you know?
She had to go to get her hair appointment.
I would suggest that if you're somebody who has power over time and space and can manipulate
it to whatever extent you can, to the point where people say that you fancy yourself a
time traveler, I think that time is something that's on your mind.
I think that punctuality is probably a priority for you, even if your talents are imaginary.
I think I take issue with something here.
I think I let it go by the first time, but can you fancy yourself a time traveler?
Yeah.
You see, it seems like you either are or are not.
I fancy myself a man about town.
Now I understand that, but this is a little bit different.
How great did I never leave the apartment?
A man about town is very subjective.
Well, I also never leave the apartment, so I am not.
Do you leave this time?
No, I don't.
Okay, well then you are neither a man about town nor a time traveler.
Yeah, I think that your instinct to let that go is good because I don't know if you're
ever going to get to any further truth on it.
I like it.
Now, I will say that with this person who thinks they're time travel or who has a book
coming out about COVID, that book should have come out three years ago.
You would think, again, time travel being what it is.
Yeah.
Couldn't you have written a book to warn us about COVID?
Exactly.
Yes.
And Carrie says that she was on the show a couple years ago.
When it would have made sense.
That episode had better been all about COVID.
Yeah, that would be a good one to go back and check if she was like, in three years
I'm going to write a book about this shit, but just so you know.
Otherwise, I have some questions.
Yeah.
We'll check in on that and see.
What are you time traveling to do?
Have fun.
Well, that is a good reason to time travel.
Yeah.
I mean, there's certain sporting events that, I mean, obviously the classic thing is like,
gamble on them.
Sure.
But if you could go watch some amazing moments from like-
Totally.
Just feel the catharsis of this crowd just freaking out.
Right, right, right.
That'd be kind of fun.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Watch Jesse Owens run.
Yeah.
That'd be great.
Shove it in Hitler's fucking face.
So this guest didn't show up.
Mm-hmm.
And they should have because they're time traveling.
But Kerry mentions another guest.
Someone asks a question about Robert David Steele.
Mm-hmm.
Who is, of course, a real weirdo.
He has a lot of irons and many fires.
True.
He-
Does not, however, fancy himself a time traveler.
No.
However, he was the guy who was on Alex Jones' show and talked about how the globalists are
kidnapping children and taking them to bases in space.
Yep.
And enslaving them.
And then Alex got mad that everybody thought he believed it because-
He said, yep.
I believe you.
You are correct 100%.
And then Robert David Steele did not get invited back on Alex's show.
I'm surprised.
But he comes around Project Camelot from time to time.
This clip is very confusing.
I'd like you to listen to this.
And I think we have a little bit more to this story about Robert David Steele.
Okay.
I'm very interested in what's going on in his life.
All right.
You know, I understand that Benjamin Fulford has come forward saying that Robert David
Steele should be the candidate.
You know, I actually haven't seen the post, but this is kind of outrageous.
This.
He is always working under the orders of the triad.
And I have one video going back.
But first of all, the original video I did with him where he states what happened to
him, where he was threatened, and so on, and had to basically.
I think if he wants to stay in Japan and stay alive, he has to do what they say.
So now he's coming out against Trump, strangely.
So apparently Robert David Steele has turned on Trump, which I didn't know about, mostly
because I don't care.
Right, right, right.
I'm not going to follow along with what he has to think.
Far more interestingly, he lives in Japan, and in order to stay alive, he has to do the
bidding of the triad.
See, now, I wrote that down, and I'm struggling to really comprehend this, so if I understand
correctly, let me read exactly what I wrote down.
Works for the triad in Japan.
Now, that's Robert who?
David Steele.
Robert David Steele.
Former CIA agent, yeah.
I don't know if he was actually in the CIA.
I think that's just what he said.
Yeah.
Is that a move up for him?
Probably.
I don't know.
Look, dude, here's the thing.
I've listened to a lot of Project Camelot.
I don't know who the fuck the triad are.
I'm not sure.
Not sure.
This is a new wrinkle.
There's a triad.
She could have said Yakuza, but now there's a triad.
I think they're aliens.
Right?
I mean, it's got to be a trio of aliens.
It has to be, well, I hope it's at least a trio.
Otherwise, now we're in real trouble.
Yeah, this is confusing.
I don't like this sort of late reveal of-
How long has he been in Japan?
Look, every time I've ever seen him, he's been in the same study just inside.
He always is by Skype from places.
He's always in this very nice looking study.
Sure.
Wonderful wood shelves and tons of books.
Maybe he just got one of those backgrounds that's like a Shinto temple, and she's like,
oh, well, he obviously lives in Japan now.
Oh, maybe.
I don't know, because I've also listened to Robert David Steele's interview with Carrie.
I don't know.
I haven't listened to all of them because I've done a couple, but I don't remember the
triad coming up.
I don't remember Japan coming up.
I don't remember any of this.
I want to know who the triad is.
I want to know what they're doing with Robert David Steele.
I don't think you can just toss that in there.
No, apparently you can't.
Just toss in Robert David Steele works for the triad.
Works for the triad, man.
In order to stay alive.
Right.
Yes.
So the Illuminati, we know that they're pretty involved in politics.
Usually.
And they're pushing back about this election.
Okay.
Right now, there's a great deal of evidence of Illuminati pushback.
So I want to stop this really quick, because one of the things that Carrie gets really
upset about, not really super upset, like not freaking out or anything, but she seems
to be bummed out that people are not taking seriously the people who talk about these
allegations of widespread fraud.
Sure.
But I would like to say that what she does in this clip is one of the reasons that no
one takes these people seriously.
Okay.
I got a call this morning from someone, one of my sources, who said that, I think it's
Arizona, that the governor has come forward and said, oh, there's not enough votes to
really cause a recount.
And so that governor has obviously been threatened.
Obviously.
Has gone on the side of the Illuminati, even though I think I have it right.
Arizona is the right person.
I'm not sure.
Dr. Arizona.
What I'm saying is that some governor, and I heard it was a Republican governor, I thought
Arizona had a Democrat in the office, but I could be wrong.
Anyone in the chat can let me know which it is.
Do they have a governor?
Because then I might have the state wrong.
But this is what came out this morning via source.
And it's out in the news.
Yeah.
Not a lot of details there.
Not a lot of sort of familiarity with the topic.
I don't really know if it's a Republican or a Democrat or what they're talking about or
why, but I do know there's fraud.
Yeah.
Like, I guess if you're mad that no one's taking that seriously, I would suggest that
you're not taking that seriously.
And that's why I'm not going to respond seriously to it.
Yeah.
That would make sense.
Come on.
I think it's Arizona.
Maybe somebody said something.
Yeah.
What the fuck?
Also, fuck off.
You can't care about recounts.
There are aliens that are real fighting everywhere.
Yeah.
That is an issue for me, too.
Why do you care about electoral politics?
At all.
If Biden wins or if Trump wins, there's still fucking space raptors.
Yeah, exactly.
Who are always among us and who have treaties and they're breaking them and remaking them
all day every day.
What does Biden matter?
Yeah.
Doesn't matter at all.
Doesn't matter.
Now, that is true.
That is strange.
Yeah.
But these next two clips, I think, are really the balm that'll go on that burn you're feeling.
Okay.
And that is that like, okay, so this show is kind of nonsensical in the sense that it's
somehow concerned with a democratic politician.
Right.
There's a tremendous amount of information and evidence out there that Biden is not all
there.
Okay.
I guess everyone knows that that watches my shows.
But so that's just like all the other right wing media outlets.
Right.
That's just the same.
Yeah.
But here is why Project Camelot is special.
There's a tremendous amount of information and evidence out there that Biden is not all
there.
Okay.
I guess everyone knows that that watches my shows, but in case you don't, there is reason
to believe that he is a clone.
There we go.
I think that's the stuff.
He is a clone.
He's also a walk-in.
He's a walk-in.
He's a what?
He's a walk-in?
Yeah.
Grow up, man.
He's a walk-in clone?
You don't know about walk-ins?
No, I don't know about walk-ins.
Oh, look at this.
What, did he need a haircut and they just walked him into it?
They're like, ah, you're a clone now.
Look at this fucking kindergartener over here, not knowing about walk-ins.
I don't know what a walk-in is.
Come on, man.
Act like you've been there.
Is he a clone of Christopher Walk-in?
No, I did think that was a possibility.
That'd be great.
Uh, no, so yeah, I mean like, okay, yes, we have a situation where you're talking about
something very standard in right-wing media that Biden's not all there.
He's not all there, Dan.
Now your explanation for it is why I'm tickled, because he's a clone, and not only that, walk-in.
What is a walk-in?
Come on, man.
How are you?
You're really embarrassing yourself.
I'm willing to accept that.
He might be a walk-in.
I don't know what it is.
Well, I can tell you that one of the things that might lead you to believe that he's a
walk-in is if he uses language weirdly.
Sure.
There's one particular clip that's actually quite funny, but also very serious in a certain
sense where he's saying, I am going to be Joe Biden.
That's what he says.
And he says quite a few other things that indicate to me, uh, an alien who hasn't quite
learned the English language.
And so tends to put some words backwards or together that don't belong together.
Wait till I play a clip of you talking.
It could be an AI, but I, my, my instinct tends to say, this is kind of a man in black.
If you didn't know what men in black were supposed to be bodies, I know this is going
to sound, um, unbelievable to some bodies that have been dead and reanimated.
And then, uh, there's basically a walk-in and they get, uh, they behave as if they're
alive.
So that's what a walk-in is.
Apparently it's a dead body that an alien walks into.
I mean, I can't really argue with any of it.
Do aliens walk into a dead body?
Right.
Classic set up for a joke.
Of course.
That is not what the movie Men in Black was about by the way.
First one says, why the long face?
Second alien says, cause I ripped it in half.
Yeah.
So that's a good explanation for why Biden says things that sound weird sometimes.
Jack.
I just...
Come on, man.
I'm not an alien.
I'm not a walk-in.
I'm struggling.
I'm struggling with their evidence.
No, it makes total sense.
Has she ever hurt herself?
Like does she think that somebody could not possibly find a, whatever she plays with Biden.
Anytime she's misspoken, it's because someone was shooting 5G at her.
Oh, that's a good point.
Yeah.
So why doesn't Biden get the benefit of that doubt?
Maybe he's being shot at.
But see, you have introduced an interesting question and that is like, Trump misspeaks
a lot too.
Sure.
Now this is where it comes to, this is where the rubber meets the road and actually Kerry
explains it all.
I'm glad.
Now I know that people used to criticize Trump in this regard because Trump sort of uses
language in a certain way, but it's very unique to him and he's communicating.
So it's, you have to have discernment and be able to tell the difference actually.
I hate that word so much.
Well, you hate it because it's the truth.
I hate it because they don't know what it means and they continue saying it over and
over and over again.
So Biden misspeaks and it's proof that there's an alien up in him.
Exactly.
Walked in.
Of course.
Trump misspeaks and it's proof that he's communicating and he's individualistic.
Right.
And the only way to know the difference between the two is discernment, my friend.
All right.
Now let me posit you this theory real quick.
Alien wise, Biden makes mistakes in the way that we would consider normal.
For sort of an aging person.
In her estimation, based on the way that Trump is talking in a very unique and individualistic
way, then that suggests that Biden is making mistakes in a way that is very common.
Perhaps.
If that's your comparison.
Well, I mean common for an alien who doesn't know English.
Well, what I would suggest though is that it is more likely the alien is somebody who
is doing something different from what we would consider to be relatively a non unique
behavior.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
There's more than one alien, right?
That can walk in.
Naturally.
Why would you choose one who doesn't know English?
Like why would you ever choose the alien for that assignment who's weird with English?
I mean, every alien's got to cut its teeth on some assignment.
You know, nobody starts out the most experienced alien walk in.
We need you to possess the fucking president of the United States.
Now it's going to be difficult for you to rise to that rank because you're going to
have to debate.
You're going to have to make a lot of public speeches.
A lot of that.
And you don't know English, which is an issue.
Yeah.
Let's get the fucking alien who doesn't know much English.
Let's get the raptor being who is a little bit iffy on verbs.
Now I like that as a, I think I like that as a like relative place of earthlings in
the universe.
They're like, this is the guys that they haven't even, this is the guys starting out.
This is the new guy who's got to try and take over the president.
He's learning for a more important mission, Dan.
Not at all.
This indicates to me either these aliens are fucking incompetent.
That's fair.
Or they don't actually really want to, they're just fucking around.
They're sort of playful.
I imagine.
That's, that's fair.
Or, I mean, I do know that English is one of those languages that's like notoriously
difficult to learn later in life.
Especially if you're an alien.
Yeah.
Verb conjugation is very strange.
Yeah, yeah.
So it could just be something like that.
A lot of idioms that you, you know, you might not even be, even if you speak English, you
might not be able to understand people.
So that makes sense.
I still say that if I'm an alien, I'm not signing off on the walk-in who doesn't know
English.
I would say that communicating is probably job number one for someone who's running for
public office.
I would say, sorry, you're a great walk-in, bad, bad speaker.
You know, you do a lot of good stuff.
We're going to keep you on here.
You're going to go to class for another year.
It's not that big a deal, man.
I wonder when did he become a walk-in?
Has he been?
No, no, no.
Biden.
Has he been a walk-in this entire time or did he recently become a walk-in?
No idea.
All right.
Let's see.
I think maybe that might be good for us because his previous policies, not good.
Not good.
No.
He's an alien who's going to be a more progressive politician.
I like it.
Well, I'm rooting for alien on this one.
Well, all right.
But his soul is probably still in there.
Oh, shit.
That's a problem.
You've got to recognize that.
Okay.
There could still be Joe Biden, the soul, can still be in the body at the same time,
but they're pushed to the side and they are not really able to communicate for a variety
of reasons or they may actually be completely walled off and occupied elsewhere just trying
to hang on to the body, but not really being there.
And this can happen with a lot of illnesses with people, so it's not that unusual.
But what is unusual and what the Illuminati dark magicians must be laughing their asses
off about is the fact that the American people have actually voted for this guy.
So I know that this is a sort of a slap in the face behind the scenes at the Trump administration
who have plenty of magicians who are going to see through these ploys and know that that's
what they're doing.
It's a slap in the face.
Trump's magician.
Oh, God damn it.
My magicians lost.
His magician team is just so embarrassed that they lost to a walk-in.
Oh, no, no, no.
See, now I've got a whole new world that I would enjoy twice as much.
Imagine if Rudy Giuliani was exactly as incompetent and moronic, but could also fail at using
magic.
That'd be great.
Rudy Giuliani is a walk-in.
Yeah, he's a walk-in who can use evil magic.
I love it.
Much like the idea of Robert David Steele being in the employee of the triad, a walk-in
is a new term that I've not heard on other episodes of this.
This is really expanding.
Can you reach that soul using the power of love, Dan?
No.
Oh, shit, they're really good.
So recently, just after the election, we heard Steve Pachanik come on The War Room with Owen
Troyer and talk about how the election was actually an elaborate setup.
They used blockchain technology and barcodes in order to watermarks.
And they immediately pretended that didn't happen.
Yeah, they did not issue a retraction.
Steve went way too QAnon.
Turns out, carries into that.
Of course.
Obviously, a lot more votes went for Trump than went for Biden, in truth.
But it's very difficult at this time, at least at the moment, to know exactly how many of
those went for Trump.
So I think perhaps the blockchain is revealing some of this.
But I'm actually unsure, I'm curious how the blockchain was used.
If it was used, it was used.
And that's in, I guess, the sort of software.
Yeah, I'm curious, too.
But I also don't entertain any of these ideas because they're very stupid.
It's really unfortunate to continue to hear.
Well, obviously, this thing is true.
I'm curious as to how or why they did it, but obviously, there's massive amounts of
fraud.
I don't know where or why or how.
Yeah, it has been proven, but I don't understand it.
I'm going to leave that aside because I just wanted to play that clip just to illustrate
that like, oh, here's a connection with Steve Pachannik and all that bullshit nonsense.
But I don't want to dwell on it because I'm too excited about this next clip.
This next clip opens up all sorts of new vistas for us.
I had a whistleblower that was revealing what is, in essence, the fight in the Pacific with
our Navy and these Mer people back in, basically, associated with Mu underwater and the sailors.
So I had a whistleblower in this regard.
So I like that you were nodding aggressively through that, like, of course, of course.
Totally.
The sailors.
Who are associated with the kingdom of Mu.
The sailors associated with the kingdom of Mu are fighting the Mer people.
And then our Navy got mixed up in it at some point.
Great.
Love it.
Oh, man.
We're on this.
We're going to need a few more details on this.
Do our massive trillion dollar destroyers have issue with Mer people and tridents?
They certainly did back then.
Oh, well, that's fair.
Yeah.
Why did we invest so much money in it?
Exactly.
Why do you think the holes are so reinforced?
Tridents.
Too many tridents.
Yeah.
We've learned from the wooden holes.
I just feel like these are issues where we need to settle fundamental precepts.
We just need to, like, I'm not going to believe you when you tell me that there was a battle
with Mu and the Mer people at our Navy until you prove to me that Mer people are real.
I can't go the second step because I'm not granting you the first one.
No, no, no.
Mer people are taken as red, Dan.
No.
How many species continue to go undiscovered every day?
Raptors.
Millions.
Mercantile dogs.
All the time.
You go deep enough in the ocean, Mer people.
Big beetles in Vietnam.
It gets too dark down there to see.
Of course Mer people are down there.
Sure.
So, you know, Trump's a big problem for the Illuminati and all them.
And not anymore.
Well, you might have asked yourself, like, why didn't they just kill him?
That is a good question.
It turns out they've tried a bunch.
But also, if they do kill him, it's mutually assured destruction, so they wouldn't do it.
But they've also tried a whole bunch.
Why would they try it?
Okay, someone in the chat is saying he would have been killed, Trump would have been killed
by February if he won again.
Well, they've tried to kill him many times.
How many?
So it's important to realize that, again, it's kind of like a very interesting standoff.
And it's a lot like, you know, The Godfather, right?
So if you start killing people on one side, then the other side is going to start killing
people on your side.
And pretty soon there'll be nobody left.
So it's called mutually assured destruction.
And so this is not, and some people call it the nuclear option.
This is not really an option for the game being played today.
And it doesn't mean they won't try.
It doesn't mean that it couldn't happen.
I'm just saying that I know they've tried a number of times.
I believe that Trump and team do have ET protection.
Cool.
But I do think that it should mean that they wouldn't try.
I would assume that they wouldn't try, yes.
If it's mutually assured destruction and it's not the way the game is being played or whatever,
then it should not be a situation where they've tried and failed a bunch of times.
Because they would know that if they succeeded, they would destroy themselves in the process.
Sure, but I mean, you look at Cold War history and I could actually see people deciding like,
eh, let's give it a shot.
Well, here's my problem with that.
The Soviet Union existed.
That is a good point.
That is a very good point.
Yeah.
It's tough to get around that.
That's our problem.
So, if he's got ET protection...
Yes.
Probably from Pleiadians, by the way.
Sure.
Probably.
Because they're the good ones.
Ostensibly.
Well, hold on.
I don't know if you know this.
There are actually...
You know, almost every time we've ever heard Kerry talk about alien races, they're always
uniform.
They're always like, these ones are good, these ones are bad.
I think it's because like they are all like resonating with something or there's some
sort of like a, there's a magical element to it.
It's like, you cannot be bad if you are a raptor or whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
There's some level of evolution maybe that is unspoken of or yeah.
Perhaps.
Yeah, yeah.
It turns out that might not be the case.
Okay.
Because some Pleiadians are actually evil.
Oh no.
I believe that Trump and team do have ET protection of at least one race, and I'm pretty sure
it's the Pleiadians, but it's a certain division of the Pleiadians because there are some dark
groups in the Pleiadians.
And that was proven by my interviews with Eddie, Eddie, okay, guy's name, now I'm drawing
a blank on his last name.
Page.
It would be Eddie Page.
And I wouldn't say his name either.
I love the idea that the words, that was proven by my interviews with Eddie Page.
We can.
That's a really good point.
We can either decide from these interviews that Eddie Page is a raving crazy person and
a racist who likes to think that he's an alien, or we can believe that some Pleiadians must
be evil.
Well, there is that.
That's such an interesting decision-making tree.
I can't not believe that he's a Pleiadian.
So the fact that he's a Pleiadian must mean that there are evil Pleiadians.
Ooh, that's a good point.
Or you could just say, guy's talking shit.
He was talking shit, but only because he was an evil Pleiadian.
It doesn't have to be an either-or situation, Dan.
I gotta say it's liberating to not believe any of this.
Yeah, it is nice.
It is nice.
I feel less trapped in making up my own bullshit on a daily and constant basis.
Yeah, it's very simple to explain what's going on here.
Bunch of people talking shit.
Don't need to go further than that.
The end.
But Carrie can speak freely and talk all the shit she wants.
Why is that?
Because she doesn't work for CNN.
Oh, that's a good call.
One of the reasons I can speak so freely here is that I'm considered super fringe.
If I was mainstream, they probably would have fired me or killed me a long time ago.
So it's when we're out on the fringe that we're allowed to get away with talking like
this.
Although I am under attack and sometimes it's very obvious, like having two strikes on my
YouTube channel.
I wouldn't call that an attack, but yeah, I think that she does make a good point.
She can't speak freely because no one is her boss and no one can stop her from doing it.
If you had an employer, you would have been fired long ago because the work is bad.
It would be just bad.
Because you don't do good.
Yeah.
And to be fair, we would have been fired long ago too.
Not necessarily because terrible work, but because why would anyone pay us to do this?
It's ridiculous.
There is a freedom that comes with not being attached to some kind of a big entity or something.
It doesn't mean that there's anything inherently like integrity bearing about it.
It's just, you wouldn't have gotten killed if you worked for CNN, you would have been
fired.
Yeah.
You're talking about fucking merpeople battles.
Merpeople would be an interesting thing to hear on CNN.
Wolf Blitzer comes in, our Navy took out three merpeople and broke a treaty.
Oh, God damn it.
The mer-treaty's broken.
I like her version of the, because we always live in the, the enemy is both ultra powered
and incredibly impossible to, it can't win and you know, super weak simultaneously.
Hers feels more like a game though, because she's like, I'm allowed to do all this stuff
because I'm on the fringe.
They're still attacking me though.
So it's like, why would you do an attack unless you kind of mean it to fail over and
over and over again?
You want to inconvenience the people like her who are truth tellers, but you don't want
to make martyrs of them.
I'm combining her and Alex's beliefs about this, the way they rationalize like, Hey,
I've existed for a long time and no one seems to care.
That kind of like, yeah, if you went too hard against me, it would prove me right.
Or that kind of.
Right.
If you were to go against me at all, I would be too powerful.
I would succeed in the fringes.
All right.
So it's sabotage.
That's what they're more interested in.
I can see you have figured it out, Dan.
So she, you know, she carries on the same page as Steve in terms of the like watermarks
on balance, the blockchain, the whole thing.
And she seems to be on another sort of similar tip and that is really thinking Melania is
really important.
Thoughts about Melania and their son?
Well, I think Melania is OK.
Let me just say that Captain Mark Richards has said he believes Melania is in touch with
an E.T. race and that she is a conduit conduit for Trump to get the downloads and information
from that race.
And I think that's very possible.
Yeah.
And I guess it's Mark Richards also thinks that she's not fully human.
And that's that's also very possible.
I think that this is an interesting way that people like Kerry are trying to rationalize
the sense that Melania doesn't seem to be doing anything.
Or interested at all in this whatsoever.
Yeah.
And I think that like, you know, trying to have this like, all right, Trump is a superhuman
battling against the forces of darkness and all the demonic child abusers who live under
the Getty Museum or whatever the fuck.
Indeed.
You know, like you have this heroic figure and then his wife is somebody who just seems
to not give a shit about anything.
Yeah.
And in order to make that make sense, you have to create this elaborate backstory, which
I guess she doesn't talk that much in public and doesn't get involved in too much because
she's too busy being a conduit for the aliens to help Trump with his secret protection.
Sure.
And the aliens get like upgrade.
Okay.
The aliens upgrade Trump with a new wife.
And that's why he's had so many.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess that's one way you could get around.
One way you do it.
Yeah.
So Trump, you know, with the help of his conduit wife.
Sure.
He's true.
What he's doing is I can't stress this enough.
There's big Adronachrome out there.
Okay.
You know how there's big pharma, big oil.
There's also a big Adronachrome manufacturing industry publicly traded on the black market.
Oh, okay.
Secret market.
Okay, good.
Yes.
Shadow market.
And Trump is trying to dismantle that.
And this is so crucial.
And that's the same thing with Adronachrome and that whole manufacturing production line
that involves, you know, taking a baby, you know, from their parents or whatever, or even
in vitro creating test tube babies as product, and then getting a Adronachrome out at the
other end.
This is a very diabolical process.
There's nothing they have control over in those regards.
Now they may be attempting to get control and that has to involve a battle and you can't
ask nicely.
So that means a war.
That means the one with the biggest gun wins, you know, the best technology, however you
want to ride it, and so on.
So this is what we're dealing with and what he's dealing with.
That's what Trump's dealing with.
He's dealing with a manufacturing industry of trying to make test tube babies to scare
and then drink their blood.
I got to be honest, all too often, I don't really think about what he has to deal with.
Right.
You got to empathize a little bit more.
You really do.
Because if he's got to deal with this.
I have a quick question though.
Sure.
Alright.
Um, so we can clone people, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
So that means we can basically manufacture bodies, right?
Mm hmm.
Wouldn't that suggest we could also manufacture just the blood?
Yep.
And we can also synthesize Adronachrome.
Yeah.
So I don't understand.
So I guess it has to be some like dark ritual thing that they're talking about to gain the
intergalactic strength, I guess.
But in this cosmology, it seems like you could just really easily manufacture.
It's like in the underworld movies, if we're going to only ever talk about movies whenever
we're talking about Carrie Cassidy, you can make your own fucking blood and you move on.
Everybody gets a good job.
Yeah.
I think that, I think that, you know, it's interesting that they don't ever go down that
road of thought.
And it's to their detriment because it's a big gaping hole in their theory.
But what I think is interesting about the way that Carrie is expressing this and presenting
it is like, this is not going to end without a war, right?
So if a war doesn't happen internally, then that is evidence that this Adronachrome manufacturing
industry is still up and running.
There must be a giant conflagration or else there is no change in the status quo.
That's fucked up.
Why have we got Congress to regulate the industry?
What?
Why isn't Carrie, look, if she's interested in electoral politics now, why isn't she campaigning
for enough senators and congresspersons to write a law regulating the use of Adronachrome?
You broke my brain.
I don't know why she's not trying to go the civic route.
I'm just saying if we got a participatory republic, I think she should start there instead
of the secret war.
Fair enough.
That might be a good first step.
So at this point, Carrie's kind of running out of energy and like kind of, you know,
petering out a little, but she takes a couple of questions from the chat.
I don't think that she actually reads the questions themselves, but responds to them.
This first one is about the queen.
Okay.
So we'll find out if there's anything else people might want to ask.
So somebody thinks that the queen was beheaded and we don't have the regular, I'm sure they
think she's a clone or whatever.
Yeah.
How stupid is that?
A lot of this is conjecture in my opinion.
I mean, these people put out this stuff, but that doesn't mean they know.
Everyone knows the queen's a walk-in.
Oh man.
A lot of these dumb-dumbs think that the queen is a clone.
That's not true.
Joe Biden's a clone.
Duh, idiots.
So strange to try and figure out like what's the difference between conjecture A and conjecture
B. Completely different.
It was proven in the interviews with Eddie Page, Dan.
Some Pleiadians are evil.
Yeah.
That's all you need to know.
In this clip, she fields a call about whether or not Trump is Anunnaki.
Ooh, that's a good question.
He's not.
Okay.
Is Trump Anunnaki?
No, I think Trump-
He's an Anunnaki.
Is not Anunnaki.
Trump is a reincarnation of General Patton.
He is a villain of a civil mission and he is a person.
Pleiadian.
Yep.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, a hero of General Patton.
General Patton, The General Patton that we are speaking of.
Yes.
Okay.
Yep.
When did he die?
Actually, I did look this up.
Uh-huh.
He died just before Trump was born.
Really?
Ooh, maybe he is?
I think that's-
I assume that's why they say it.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
They looked it up, otherwise they would feel real stupid.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, it is- it's pretty close to like I think it's maybe like six, eight months off or something
like that.
Six, eight months off?
What is he- what's Trump doing?
six to eight months spiritually.
Got a lounge.
Got a lounge?
Take a load off.
Oh, that's fair.
Patton's life is tough.
Patton, it's exhausting.
Yeah, you know, you're right.
And then you gotta prepare for being a horrifying monster.
Yeah.
I gotcha.
At this point, Carrie discusses Israel and her feelings.
Oh, stop.
And...
She should not.
I'm gonna say I don't respect her enough
to even joke about how terrible and stupid her ideas
about Israel are, so we're just gonna skip past that.
Okay, good.
Good call.
And get into more interesting territory,
and that is Alex Jones believes that there is a virus.
COVID.
Yes.
COVID-19 is real, but it's also a hoax.
Even though he has David Icke on,
who says that it's not real at all.
Right.
That's another version of this.
David Icke believes there is no virus.
Correct.
But also seems to believe in medical science
to an extent. Somewhat, I guess.
Carrie doesn't believe viruses exist.
Okay.
My understanding of viruses,
and I credit Dr. Robert Young for teaching me about this,
is that actually they've never isolated a real virus.
That viruses are not what you think they are,
and that they're simply poisons expelled by our cells
when we're faced with poisons in the outer
and inner environment through food we eat
or somebody shooting us up with, say, a bioweapon.
Sure.
I think she might be right.
A lot of the times I worry that my humors and Icke's
are out of balance with each other, and that can happen,
and then you'll just start influencing.
A lot of people thought stuff like that,
about like humors and what have you,
and then at a certain point,
people thought about like germs.
Sure, yeah.
But they were wrong.
The viruses are part of what's called germ theory,
and germ theory is very old-fashioned,
going back to the past year,
and then that information was actually, as usual, wrong.
And I've done several interviews with Dr. Robert Young
about all of this, so you can go on my website,
search under his last name, and find those interviews,
and I highly recommend them.
If you want to find out about the history
and why germ theory is no longer believed
by the most intelligent, advanced doctors out there.
So that's important to know.
You gotta do a little better than Robert Young
as your reference for-
Number one.
No, we talked about him
on another Project Camelot episode.
He is the guy who like went to jail.
He talked someone into not getting treatment for cancer,
and getting his holistic approach,
and then they got stage four incurable progression,
and he got sued for millions of dollars because of that,
like malpractice, and didn't have a license for a period.
Anyway, if he is the most advanced, hippest, coolest doctor
who's telling you all about how germ theory is wrong,
I would say branch out, talk to a few more doctors,
because this is silly.
I like her calling germs there.
Oh, it's very old-fashioned, the germ theory.
Compared to obviously things create are inside yourselves,
and then they explode out whenever it's poisoned.
That's brand new research, Dan.
Nobody has ever thought- That's hip.
That maybe spontaneous generation of poisons
could explode through your body.
Yeah.
Ah, that's a new one.
So look, dude, the germs and germ theory,
it's all a plot by the aliens.
Maybe, who knows? Sure, eh, why not?
And you know, so you think that germs and viruses,
that you think everything's contagious, but it's not.
Oh.
But you know what are?
Bad viewings?
Memes. Oh.
What is contagious, however,
and can be taken in through osmosis, what's called osmosis,
and in essence, through memes,
is the mental infection that you get
because you are, you become,
you might mind control, basically.
Of course.
You are persuaded, influenced mentally
to take something on.
So that means that when you are in a household
and someone catches a cold,
you can easily catch it through what's called empathy.
Okay?
And so this is, it's all in the way you think about things.
And that is, that's first and foremost,
how we affect our bodies, is how you think.
Now, interestingly, this would be really easy,
or I mean, there would be a way to scientifically
try and get to the bottom of this.
You would have to construct something
where knowing that someone you care about deeply is sick
causes you to get sick.
Exactly.
And I don't think that studies have borne that out.
Nah, I'm pretty sure it's true.
Because if you're saying, oh yeah, yeah, yeah,
when you're in a house with someone
who has a contagious illness,
you get it because it's empathy.
Right.
That would be indistinguishable
from getting it because of germs or contagious illness.
So her theory would be tested very easily
if say you were long distance away from somebody.
Exactly.
That's what I'm saying.
Who cared very deeply about it.
And I don't know of any transmission of diseases
long distance.
There's no morphic transmission of diseases?
If Kerry can establish this
and point me to some literature on it, I'd be interested.
But I've got a doctor with your name on him.
Robert Young?
Oh yeah.
I don't, I'm not gonna listen to him.
Oh boy.
Anyway, Kerry's got one last thing to say here.
She's talking to a lot of people all around the world
and they're all interested in this election.
Of course.
And I'm talking to people all over the world,
you know, and in contact with them
since I travel so much in the past,
haven't been able to do much traveling lately.
And I can say that they are also very long.
Too much empathy?
Because they realize that in a certain sense,
this is all about who is gonna run planet earth,
at least on the human side.
Of course.
And so that's what this election really comes down to.
So, okay.
I think I am sort of done for now.
Yeah, me too.
I don't know.
I think that it's such a gross perspective
to be like, whoever wins this election
is who's gonna run the planet.
Yeah.
Just because, I mean, first of all,
it's so America centric.
Oh yeah.
It's so disrespectful to the other countries of the world.
Yep.
But second, like, I don't think,
like, of course I want everything to turn out
that Biden becomes president.
I don't want him running the world.
No.
But it's very strange that these people,
people like Kerry, people like Alex,
they do want Trump running the world.
Yes, 100%.
And the fear, like, it's just so weird.
Like, why would you want that even if you like this guy?
I don't know.
I liked Obama as president.
You know, obviously had some problems
in a lot of policies and decisions.
Sure.
But even as much as I supported him
as the president of the United States,
I never would want him to be the head of the world.
No, absolutely not.
Head of humans.
No, no.
It's very silly.
It's childish.
Yeah, I don't get how they can jive
those two things together without just openly saying,
like, I want the end of all participatory government.
Period.
Well, I mean, if you have-
Like, that's your-
You can't vote for aliens.
So, like, if you believe that that's the real world
that's going on behind the scenes,
what does it really matter if you give up
the pretense of democracy?
Yeah, exactly.
You know, like, sure.
Yeah, you can feel good about casting a vote,
but that person's working for a lizard.
Right.
You understand?
So it doesn't matter.
And I think the thing that really,
like, the thing that's interesting to me
about how they always go about this is that
at no point in time is it like,
let's get enough people together,
because they know that they can't actually
get people to do anything.
I mean, we saw the caravan.
We saw the caravan.
They're not gonna be like, let's get a movement together.
They're just like, it all has to be in secret,
because if I tried to get a bunch of people to know it,
they'd realize that I'm an idiot, you know?
There's that option, or the other option is,
let's wait until someone else builds something
and then co-opt it like a tea party.
Yeah, exactly, yeah.
Yep.
But look, I just think, like, you know,
I start to feel like Trump's been really bad
for these people.
Oh yeah.
It's like, this is sad.
Like, if you're somebody who's like,
I'm all about the ins and outs of secret programs,
and I'm all about the, like,
these aliens that have been visiting us forever,
and my friend who's definitely not a murderer
talks to raptors in prison,
and he tells me all about these great space adventures
and sentient spaceships,
you should not give a shit about a president.
Nope.
It's degrading for you two.
Okay, so.
Because Trump isn't fucking revealing
anything about the space.
Nope.
He's not gonna prove you right.
You know that.
I think one of the hugest things
that's been an issue for them,
with Trump being president,
and this is,
cause we've heard this joke so many times,
or at least I have this,
the joke so many times, like,
when Obama was president,
I didn't have to care about politics,
that's why I liked him,
cause I could walk, do my day,
and think that there's a reasonable person
who's trying, you know?
That kind of thing.
With Trump, everyone has been paying attention
all the time.
So all of that secret stuff,
all this stuff that's going on behind the scenes,
has to be so secret now,
that it's just either you believe it
to the point where you've completely lost
any sense of reality,
or you just have to go like,
no, this is too stupid,
this is just too dumb.
And that's where QAnon gets a foothold.
Exactly, yeah.
I just think that,
you know, when the history books are written,
no one will write about Project Camelot,
but if they do,
it's just,
it's just, you should,
everyone who made a decision
to sign up with this is like,
they made a bad move.
Strategically, they made a bad move for their grifts.
It seemed like it was gonna be really good
in the short term,
but it's just not gonna pay off.
There's going to be too much
that you're gonna have to answer for later
and explain away,
like, how are you gonna explain Melania
being a space conduit in five years?
Like, why isn't she still a space conduit?
Ah, they let her go.
Okay, sure, whatever.
They replaced her with a new space,
I don't know.
Okay, and then in a year,
like Biden, is he still a walk-in?
Yeah, that's a good question.
Like, what's going on?
Well, I think that's probably why it's so,
they're all so very desperate
for Trump to remain in office forever.
Because as long as he's in office forever,
you can make up all kinds of bullshit.
But after a while,
everybody starts looking at reality again,
like, oh man, shit, that's crazy.
Why did people believe that he was going to,
how many, Hunter Biden is just gone now.
We just don't even talk about that shit.
I'm sure some people still are.
Maybe.
I bet Kerry put out a video about him last week.
That's probably true.
Which again, I don't know
what the alien angle on that is.
That's a good question.
But yeah, it's interesting.
I feel like there was a part of me
that while I was listening to this episode,
I was like, what does this have to do with space?
And then it did come in,
and I was like, oh, that's what it has to do with space.
And some of it's pretty funny,
like the idea of merpeople battles.
Love merpeople battles.
I was learning about walk-ins
and how Robert David Steele's working for the triads.
But yeah, it's kind of,
I feel like she's in a rut too.
Yeah.
How?
It's tough.
I can't believe that they're this committed
to not admitting that they got conned.
Well, it's tough because, you know,
I mean, like the two people that we talk about,
maybe the most, Kerry and Alex, are both psychics.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's true.
So they can't get conned.
They have built themselves up so much
that to admit even the slightest bit of I got hoodwinked
is a real hit to their brand.
Yeah, they're both psychics,
which would be invalidated
if they were on the wrong path for four years
in the same way, you know.
But AJ apologized to Hamdi Ulukaya
and everybody just moved on.
But he tried to pretend that he didn't.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
Oh boy.
I don't know.
Anyway, this has been a nice little trip down a wackier road.
This has been a lovely wacky Monday.
Yeah.
Hopefully Alex will be back in studio
beginning of this week,
and we can check back in on the hashtag 79 days of hell.
See how that's going.
I'm sure it's going great.
But until then, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yeah, we're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledge underscore fight
and at go to bed Jordan.
Yeah, we're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook, it's outside.
If you could please find a local charity
or bail fund in your area
to help out people doing God's work right now.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo, I'm Leo, I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I am the truant time traveler.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
Love you.