N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys.
Knowledgefight.
Dan and Jordan, Knowledgefight.
Riddle her, riddle her, riddle her.
I need, I need money.
Andy and Kansas, Andy and Kansas.
Stop it.
It's time to pray.
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a first-time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
Knowledgefight.
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledgefight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're couple dudes that like to sit around, drink novelty beverages and talk a little
bit about Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are Dan.
Jordan.
Dan!
I have a quick question for you.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot might be a little bit disappointing, but it's again Assassin's Creed Valhalla.
I've been taking my time playing it casually.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
One of the things that I found really interesting about the game is without giving any spoilers
or anything, I find myself playing this game and having more moral choices than I have
in a lot of other games in the past.
That's fair.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And part of it is there are choices that you can make that I'm almost certain will not
affect the game at all.
Sure, sure.
But I feel bad about it.
They affect you.
Yes, absolutely.
I don't know if it's just that I have not been exposed to games that do that well in
the past, but I feel a lot more like these little things that you run into when you're
exploring around the world.
Sure, totally.
It's a little thing like you can rip somebody off if you want to and no one will ever know,
but you'll know.
You will know.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
I enjoy that.
It's one of those situations in the game where I realized like later on I had just finished
a quest and later on I was playing another one and I was like, I feel bad about what
I did to that guy.
I think it was the right thing to do, but you know what, it doesn't make me feel good.
You failed the test, bro.
So I enjoy that.
It makes the gameplay a little more fun.
And especially because I want to give a bright spot to Age of Calamity, the Hyrule Warriors,
but I just can't.
You just can't.
Disappointed?
I started dabbling in it a little bit because, you know, I can't not.
Sure.
Apparently I'm a gamer bro now.
That's what happened.
It happened so quick.
You can't go outside and all of a sudden we're gamer gators.
Yeah.
It took two seconds.
I didn't say gamer gators.
No, I'm pretty sure that's what you said.
I said I'm a gamer bro.
I know.
I'm just kidding.
I guess my feeling on it is it's fun.
The Age of Calamity is fun and if anybody enjoys it, I don't think you're wrong too.
I just kind of had expectations of more of a Dynasty Warriors-esque game and that itch
wasn't scratched.
Oh, that's unfortunate.
Or it hasn't been.
But it's still fun for what it is.
So I can't give it a bright spot.
Gotta keep it on the moral choices.
Stay the course with Valhalla.
How about you?
Maybe adjacent.
Dan, I went to a board game store.
Oh yeah.
Uh huh.
It was very exciting.
We had played together a board game called Mysterium, which I found very enjoyable.
So I was like, you know what?
I think I'm going to get into cooperative board games.
I'm going to find all those.
We're going to play them together.
It's going to be fantastic.
So I went to a board game store.
Guy who is very, very helpful knew everything about board games and card games and the assorted
like.
And I was like, hey, I need some help getting a board game.
I'm just starting to get into this.
And he was like, okay, this one is super accessible.
It's called Mansions of Badness.
Brought it home.
There's like 4,000 pieces.
You need a companion app for a god damn iPad.
There's damage rolls and shit.
There's a whole thing on it.
And I was like, this is very exciting.
I don't think we're ever going to play that.
And accessible is a different definition, but I'm very excited about it.
Well, now that you've brought it up, people are going to want us to play it on a, like
a live stream or something.
I don't know if we're going to be able to do that.
Probably not.
But that is fun.
If you're looking for a board game, they're a lot of fun.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
Yeah, for sure.
So, Jordan, today I've got something I'm looking forward to, and that is a nutty ass show from
Alex.
I like it.
Today we're going to be going over December 1st and 2nd, 2020.
I'm Dan, this is 2020.
Oh, hooray!
That is Tuesday and Wednesday this week.
And I was going to, look, here's the deal.
As I was getting this episode ready, we record on Thursdays, and on Thursday, Alex dropped
a big episode with him and Joe Rogan in the Info Wars studio.
Of course.
And of course, this rises the bat signal.
But it doesn't quite rise it in the same way as Alex being on Rogan's show, because it's
probably not going to be nearly as interesting.
No.
I don't care about Joe Rogan being interviewed by somebody.
What does he have to say that I'm going to be interested in from an interview perspective?
Alex is interesting- What's it like having a hundred million dollars?
Alex is interesting on Rogan because he's desperately trying to steal Rogan's audience,
and he's trying to impress upon them that he knows things, and that he is a guru they
should follow away from Joe.
Exactly.
Joe being on Info Wars is not that interesting.
Joe's probably just going to be like, ha ha, remember when we wore those masks, and ran
around Austin?
100.
We're such friends.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Whereas, whereas Alex being on Rogan requires an emergency episode, we got to get ahead
of that thing.
Yeah.
This, I don't fucking know.
I don't know if anyone will care.
I don't think, this is a tree falling in a forest and no one's there.
Yeah, I know.
I don't know if that makes a sound.
Did you hear about it beforehand?
No?
I am going to listen to it, and if it's worthwhile, it'll be our episode for Monday.
For sure.
And if it's not, then we'll just see what's going on now.
Find something else.
It's just a regular show.
I know that by the time this episode is out, people might be aware of the fact that Rogan
did a four fucking hour episode with Alex.
What an asshole.
So we'll see on that.
But before we get down to business on today's episode, which, like I said, a lot of fun.
Okay.
There's a lot of...
I'm excited.
Stupid, stupid shit.
We got to take a little moment first, though, to thank some folks who have signed up and
are supporting the show.
Oh, that's a good idea.
So first, Jeff A., thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Jeff.
Next, Dexter K., thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Dexter.
Thank you.
Next, Jordan looks exactly like I imagined but Dan doesn't.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Next, Joe P. Thank you so much.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, Joe.
Thank you.
Next, Joseph JP.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Joseph.
Thank you.
Next, Emily W. Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks Emily!
Thank you!
Next Thomas S!
Guess what?
What?
You're a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk!
Thanks Thomas!
And finally, I'd like to say thank you to a couple of people who donated on Elevated
Level.
We appreciate that very much.
So first, David M. Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
And your mother was a hamster and your father smelt of elderberries.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey mate, that's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
Alright, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this Watson, alright?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much Dave and thank you so much your mother was a hamster and your father
smelt of elderberries.
Yes, thank you very much to the both of you.
If you are out there and you're thinking, hey I enjoy the show, I'd like to support
these gents too, you can do that by going to our website, knowledgefight.com, clicking
the button that says support the show, or...
What you could do is you could gather two to five of your friends, ages three and up,
put together a nice little night every week to get together, read the rule book, find
out, yeah well absolutely socially distance responsibly, get the rule book, by which I
mean find some local charities or bail funds in your area to help out and then get all
your friends together and get it done.
Knocked it out of the park.
Thank you.
Nailed it.
So real quick before we get going with the actual episode, we gotta take a look at the
mail bags.
Yep.
And in here we got a nice little thing from Cassandra S. Jordan, you have a little box
in front of you.
Yes, I do.
Cassandra sent me a Alex Jones coloring book, which I will try to pretend does not exist,
because it's supposed to be, I mean coloring books are for kids, right?
Right, right, right, right.
This is terrifying.
There are adult coloring books now, that's a phenomenon that people enjoy.
I think I have a Cthulhu coloring book, and that's probably not for kids, but Alex seems
more horrifying.
It's not for boring kids.
Oh, this is intense.
Elliot's espresso nib peanut butter.
Nut butter's grown up.
This is intense.
Whoa.
This is, do you see the coloring and everything on this?
Yeah, yeah.
It looks like you got peanut butter, chocolate, and espresso?
And espresso, yeah.
That's a weird butter.
It looks like that's what's going on.
Oh yeah, it looks like you have to shake it up, oh man, oh man.
I feel like you have some reticence about sort of extravagant butter.
You know, I'm excited to taste this, here's the problem that I'm seeing with this, it's
not even distribution.
I think you just gotta stir it.
I think you're right, but it's looking like there's just weird black chunks at the bottom.
Yeah, those are like cocoa pieces, or espresso.
Cocoa nibs.
Cocoa, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm excited, I'm gonna try it.
It looks delicious.
I look forward to a full report.
Thank you so much, Cassandra.
Yes, thank you very much.
Alright, so here we go, we're jumping in.
December 1st, Alex opens the show with a video from the night before.
Okay.
He had some big breaking news, and he had to get down to it.
It's Monday night, we've been working on this story for two weeks, and now the whistleblower
has given us the authorization to go forward with the information you are about to see.
This is the first report, and several we're gonna be breaking with the documents if MSM
challenges this in any way.
This is such a perfect way for Alex to do business.
I love this so much because of how painfully transparent it is.
I don't even know, and I don't need to know what this is about, or what this alleged whistleblower
is claiming, because I know how this is set up.
This isn't how this kind of journalism works, you know, when it's being done sincerely.
If there actually was a whistleblower, and there actually were documents that proved
whatever it is they're claiming, it would be all released as a story.
The documents would be provided to help give credibility to the claims that the whistleblower
was making, because otherwise it's just a person making claims that you aren't really
able to fully assess.
Think about it.
In any conceivable world, can you imagine Glenn Greenwald meeting with Snowden, then
announcing that he has a whistleblower who's ready to make a bunch of claims, and if anybody
challenges them, that's when the documents come?
It's fucking absurd.
I think it's a great idea, you keep it in your plus two bag of holding until you need
it.
Nonsense.
It makes perfect sense.
They never would have acted like that because they had documents, and they had a story.
That did help them, yeah.
Without knowing anything about this whistleblower or the claims, I refuse to believe that anyone
would behave this way, unless this was an incredibly desperate bluff.
If we are challenged on it, if we are challenged on it, what does that even mean?
Quantify that.
If somebody says, hey, what are you talking about, they're like, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, that's not a challenge.
If you have a story, you'd never hold back the thing that proves your story, promising
to release it only if you have to.
That's schoolyard bully or entry level extortionist shit.
I will tell you guys about Deep Throat the moment someone asks, but until then, you just
gotta believe it.
Also, this goes entirely against Alex's entire career's guiding principle.
He's often told guests that if they have information, they have to get it all out or else they're
putting themselves at risk.
Alex constantly says that his guests don't tell him anything off air, they don't say
on air, because he doesn't want to have secret information that other people know he has,
since that's when things get dangerous.
Exactly.
Having secrets is okay and it's too late once you've already spilled a secret, but having
people know that you know a secret and that you haven't said anything puts a target on
your back.
Dangerous, dangerous.
This is the gate of gates all over again.
This is exactly what happened back in 2011 when Alex interviewed Bob Chapman.
Bob implied that he had secret intel on Ronald Reagan, which Alex insisted he needed to say
on air now because he said that he had these secrets and he was in danger if he didn't
get it out in the open.
Then Bob said that he'd seen a video of Reagan getting pegged and Alex got weirded out and
disappointed that it wasn't something more communist.
Getting on air and saying that he has proof he'll produce if pushed back on is anathema
to Alex's entire career's methodology.
It's not anathema to a really sadly broken idiot trying to bluff that he has a bombshell
story that's actually a dud, and I say that knowing nothing.
I could tell you that without knowing any other thing about where this clip goes.
Show me Reagan getting pegged and then I'll believe you.
The end.
So, um, I was like, alright, I don't give a shit.
Like you could have said, he could have said anything afterwards and I would have been
disappointed because it's like if you start by saying like we have all the proof and if
Brian Stelter tries to get Mauvey with me I'll release the proof.
I'll do it.
No.
Well then why not release it now?
Right.
Does he address that at all?
Why he's waiting for someone to challenge it?
I think he likes to be tricky.
Oh, okay.
He likes to set traps.
It's just a little fun.
Yeah.
Okay.
No, it's because he has nothing.
Oh, okay.
Anyway, this is about, uh, actually, let's see, do you think you can guess?
Do I think I can guess what the whistleblower whose documents might be coming out, and this
would have been Sunday night.
Uh, no, Monday night.
Monday night.
Um, uh, I want to say it's got something to do with Michigan.
Okay.
That's interesting.
That's what I'm going to go with.
Ladies and gentlemen, we have a major health executive over a 35 hospital network in Western
Pennsylvania that is exposing the fact that COVID-19 is a completely overblown power grab
scam.
Now we received this information directly from this whistleblower, checked out their
credentials and that was just the beginning of how insane this got.
Yeah.
I was surprised too.
I really thought this would be something election related.
Yeah.
Yep.
This is a little disappointing.
Yeah.
I didn't re I mean, I kind of, kind of forgot that Alex is spinning multiple plates.
Um, so yeah, I was, I was caught on my, uh, on my back heel as they say when it was like,
Oh, this is a COVID thing.
It's almost, uh, yeah, it's, it's almost kind of ridiculous that people are still denying
COVID.
Yep.
I mean, it's not almost kind of, it's insanely ridiculous.
It was ridiculous before.
But it also seems like this isn't what the season is on your show, Alex.
It seems like this is kind of what I was thinking.
It seems like you got bigger issues opening the show with this 79 days of hell and we're
doing okay.
Yeah.
So, uh, it gets to talking about this whistleblower here and, uh, this is kind of, I don't, I
don't think I believe this.
This individuals involved in the management of 35 hospital network in Western Pennsylvania.
The UPMC is the name of the company.
UPMC stands for the University of Pittsburgh Medical Center and the network actually includes
more than 35 hospitals.
Their website includes 36 hospital campuses, but they also have a satellite hospitals around
that they manage.
But, uh, you know, that are, they're included in the network.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
The other line about UPMC is that it is a giant entity.
Their board of directors and executive team are all publicly listed and I would definitely
try and track down who Alex is talking about, but I'm sure it's not someone on that level.
And I just, I started to listen to this.
I'm like, you got these documents you're never going to fucking produce.
You're going to forget this even happened in a week.
I'm not going to amplify the disappointment by trying to figure out which name on this
list you're trying to allude to.
I'm not going to read the chicken bones that I've thrown down on the ground.
Yeah, yeah, I think that's, uh, I think you should have to ignore that entirely.
He has, for you to engage with it, he must produce one document that you can research.
Otherwise, he's trying to get around you specifically.
I've gone, I've gone so far as to find a list of names of the people he's pretending this
is and that's good enough for me for now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's, that's too much work.
You're, you're giving him too much credit.
Well, let's actually hear what this, uh, almost certainly fake person has to say.
During the latest so-called surge of COVID-19 where they claim the hospitals are all overwhelmed,
we've got to have a lockdown again, they went from 96 beds to around 600.
That is only 10% of the capacity they have just for COVID-19 and their hospitals are
basically wide open.
And here's the most important point, no deaths of the 600 people.
Most patients stayed overnight for observation because they tested positive.
Media will say hospitalization patients have surged over 600%, but it's the test that's
been turned up 45 times and German courts have ruled that it is a fake test 96% of the
time.
So Alex is reading off a bit of an Info Wars article there, but he's also just making up
a lot of stuff and throwing it in.
Here are the parts of that clip that do not even appear in the Info Wars article about
this whistleblower.
And one can only presume Alex is just saying these things to try and imply or associate
them with the whistleblower, which is incredibly irresponsible.
This whistleblower article says nothing about anyone saying all the hospitals are overwhelmed.
The circumstances would obviously be different in different areas where there are varying
rates of infection that lead to hospitalization and varying levels of available medical resources.
This article does not say that this 600 beds represents 10% of the hospital's capacity.
According to the American Hospital Directory, the hospitals that are listed as part of UPMC,
they add up to having 7,371 beds.
But the number that's cited in the blurbs, some that I can find about the network are
8,000, which I think is probably reasonable.
Sure, sure, sure.
It would actually be less than 10% of that capacity, but it's kind of a meaningless
statistic to discuss this way, as we don't, you know, we have any information about the
distribution of the needed beds.
We don't know where the beds are at various hospitals, nor do we know how many of these
beds are ICU beds, or airborne isolation beds.
According to TribLive, as of November 20th, there were 17% availability on the latter
bed type, which is enough to worry people.
Yeah.
This is not something that can be easily captured by simple statistic, but that's what Alex
is trying to do, which is, you know, also in addition to the article, like it's not
in there.
The 10% of their beds.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know if he's making that up, or, I don't know, it doesn't appear to be coming
from his whistleblower.
A alleged whistleblower.
Let's see what happens.
Why not toss it in there?
As for the no deaths thing among 600 hospitalized individuals, I would be interested in seeing
proof of that.
Pittsburgh is an Allegheny County, and on Tuesday, the day this is coming out, 18 people
died with COVID-19 in that county.
But UPMC has hospitals in other counties, too, which also have registered deaths.
I just don't know anything about this claim, and I just would need to see whatever documents
Alex has withheld.
So I guess I challenge it.
Yeah, yeah, I suppose that's the only thing you can do?
Yeah, I'm not MSM, but...
Okay, we challenge you to produce the documents.
And a thumb war.
Is that what we say?
Is that all I have?
Yeah.
Ah.
The stuff about the test being turned up 45 times does not appear in the article about
this whistleblower, and it seems to be Alex is putting words in their mouth.
Similar things, I could say, about the nonsense about the German courts.
What Alex is doing here is he's taking a very boring supposed whistleblower claim and then
riffing on it to make it seem more bombshell.
If you read the actual article on this, all the person appears to be claiming is that
the hospitalization in the UPMC system went up from 96 to 600 beds that were occupied
during this last period that's being characterized as a surge.
No specific data is given about these patients, just that, quote, patients were kept in observation
overnight and no deaths resulted.
This is nonspecific to the point of being meaningless, but Pennsylvania has a database
where you can find all the information about county-level hospital bed availability, which
can give you a sense of the picture if you want.
In the last available report, in the entirety of the state, there are 4,290 adult ICU beds
total.
Of those, 695 are available, which is 16%.
This is not to say, I mean, there's other, you know, you could look at the other statistics
too that you want, but there's one.
There's 16% of ICU beds are available in the entire state of Pennsylvania.
I can't stress this enough.
This is not a whistleblower delivering meaningful information, and if you read on through the
Infowars article about this, you kind of see what's going on.
Quote, if you start with 5 patients to 25, the media will say there's a 500% increase
in cases.
Sounds terrifying, right?
This article is essentially Infowars trying to explain how numbers work to their audience
while also trying to make them distrustful and suspicious about percentage signs.
Sure, a 600% increase sounds scary, but it could just be like 20 more people, so who
cares?
It's no big deal.
But this line of argumentation is really not good, because a jump from 5 cases somewhere
to 25 would definitely be a bad sign.
I don't know if you remember what the numbers were like early on in the coronavirus days,
but if there had been a jump like that in February, people would rightly have been worried
about it.
And if you're in a small town, let's say, that has 5 cases right now, and tomorrow there's
25, that would be a big deal.
That's a real problem.
And it would definitely be an indication of deep community transmission.
What Alex is attempting to do here is make this reality of rising COVID cases and hospitalizations
not worry his audience by taking the numbers and shrinking them.
It's baffling, really, because even for Alex, this is a little insulting to his audience's
intelligence.
This is him banking on them not feeling really talked down to by bringing in a fake whistle
blower to explain how percentages work.
This is really elementary stuff, and it's kind of degrading.
I don't think highly of his audience either, but this is insulting.
Hey, if you only take the first few little bits of a logarithmic scale, it looks not
scary at all.
It's the last part of the parabola, if you just ignore the last part of the parabola
where it goes, real fast.
Sure.
Then you're going to be fine.
Yeah.
Ah, numbers.
You don't have to worry about them.
Well, I mean, a 500% increase could be one to five, or it could be a lot more.
Wow, you can't prove that, though.
I don't even know what kind of charade is being-
Okay, all right, let's start here.
If you multiply two by two, that's so much, but that's only four.
And then if you multiply that by two, that seems like a lot, but that's only eight.
And then if you multiply that by two, that's 16, and that is quite a bit more.
And then if you multiply that by two, it's 32.
And then it's 64, and then it's 128.
Holy shit, man!
Yeah.
So Alex keeps on going on.
This has nothing to do with the whistleblower, but he's just now, I guess, attacking the
idea of testing.
You've seen the big reports about the famous female CEO that had a test that could find
cancer in your blood, and it was incredible, and they made hundreds of billions of dollars,
and it turned out it was all a scam.
That's what this PCR scam is, and the inventor of it came out and said just that.
So a couple of things real quick.
Carey Mullis, the inventor of the PCR test, died on August 7th, 2019.
He did not come out and say anything about the PCR test for COVID-19 being a fraud, which
is what Alex is trying to imply.
So here is the clip that Alex immediately after plays of comments that Carey Mullis
has made.
If they could find this virus in you at all, and with PCR, if you do it well, you can find
almost anything in anybody.
It starts making you believe in the sort of Buddhist notion that everything is contained
and everything else, right?
I mean, because if you can amplify one single molecule up to something that you can really
measure, which PCR can do, then there's just very few molecules that you don't have at
least one single one of them in your body, okay?
So that could be thought of as a misuse of it just to claim that it's meaningful.
So that's the entire clip that Alex plays of Mullis.
This comment is out of context.
It's from a question and answer session that Mullis did about using PCR testing to detect
HIV back in 1993.
A lot of the stuff sounds applicable to the current pandemic, but it's really not.
The most damning you could make this quote out to be is to understand that maybe Mullis
was expressing that this form of test isn't good for determining the quantity of something
in somebody, rather it detects the presence or absence of it.
You could do that, I guess, but it's important to understand the context of these comments
that he was making, though, because it sounds like what he's saying is that if you look
at people, you can find any disease in them, but that's not the case.
He's talking about HIV patients and specifically about how if you have that virus, there's
a good chance you may have others and maybe many others.
He literally says that almost exactly after where Alex cuts the clip off.
You don't need to test for HIV.
You don't need to test for the other 10,000 retroviruses that are unnamed also in the
subject.
See, somebody that's got HIV generally is going to have almost anything that you can
test for because they have definitely been, HIV is a fairly rare virus.
At the beginning of Alex's clip, Mullis says if they find this virus in you at all with
PCR, if you do it well, you can find almost anything and anybody.
It's selectively edited to make it sound like Mullis is saying that using PCR, doctors can
find any virus in anyone.
In its proper context, which Alex deprives the audience of, it's clear that the virus
that he's referring to, so when he says if they can find this virus in you at all, he's
talking about HIV and his contention that if you can find HIV in a person, his contention
is that you can find most viruses, probably.
Also not to get too far off track here, but Carey Mullis, though the inventor of PCR testing,
is not someone who's remembered super well in the field of HIV and AIDS, as he was a
denialist of the conclusion that HIV causes AIDS.
Fair, fair.
The point that's relevant to our situation though today is that Alex's clip that he's
using of Mullis to attack the use of PCR for COVID-19 testing is completely out of context
and doesn't mean anything.
The complaint that Alex is making about PCR testing here isn't about COVID-19 specifically,
it's about the entirety of PCR as a testing method, and he's expecting the audience to
believe that the inventor of PCR testing, who won a Nobel Prize for the discovery, has
said that it doesn't actually do anything to find anything in anybody with it, ha ha!
It's a little bit rich.
I would assume he said that after he got the Nobel.
I don't think part of your campaign for the Nobel is, honestly, this thing doesn't do
shit at all.
I dunked on you fools!
What did you say at the end, sir, tricked ya, ha ha!
Surprise!
I'd like to thank the Nobel board for being so fucking dumb.
I think the thing that...
That's quite an acceptance speech.
Bunch of morons.
I just, I think the problem that I have is that he didn't tell me that the video was
from 93.
Sure.
Like, if you tell me anything about any testing, like, if this is from 93...
I mean, it's 27 years old.
If it happened before an iPhone, then I don't know if I can use it.
I don't care yet.
Yeah.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, yes and no.
No.
It's not perfect.
It's not like the way anybody should live their lives.
But if you're talking about PCR testing in 2020 versus something that Akai said before
the iPhone happened, I kind of think that I don't care.
Sure.
You know?
Yeah.
If you are using science from when grunge was king...
Yeah!
Yeah, if science hasn't advanced since then, we're in trouble.
Yeah.
If counting crows were cool when this science was around, I'm not interested.
It's a long November.
So Alex is playing this...
It is November.
Good stuff.
Thanks, bud.
This is my November.
This is my December.
Damn it.
That's a Linkin Park song.
Anyway, Alex is playing this special report of his, and he just cuts off in the middle
of it.
They're banning medical doctors and epidemiologists, virologists, and scientists who come out and
point all this out because they want to use this hysteria...
For what?
What do they want to use the hysteria for?
I was overwhelmed because this episode started with him talking about this giant whistleblower
who has the documents that they'll be revealed if anybody flexes, and then he just cuts off
in the middle.
I'm like, wait a second.
Maybe that wasn't important.
Yeah.
Maybe that was filler.
I guess that sounds a little bit like he didn't really care about that.
Maybe I got tricked into researching filler.
You got Nobel prized, my friend.
Yeah, I was like, oh, wait a second.
All right.
So anyway, Alex is just late for the show.
Okay, of course.
But apparently you're supposed to take that seriously.
Sure.
There is a whistleblower.
But it...
Okay.
And he got cut off in the middle because Alex finally showed up to the office.
Sure.
He was busy.
Oh, okay.
He's been waiting for this broadcast since 6 a.m. this morning.
And the news is so massive, so over the top, so dangerous.
But what about the whistleblower?
He wasn't able to go on until 12 minutes into the transmission.
That was five minutes ago.
Yeah.
So, okay, Alex had to take the first 12 minutes off because he was so busy working on this
news.
Since 6 a.m.
Yep.
He was so busy that he had to distract me with another gigantic bombshell story.
A huge bombshell story.
Unfortunately, we can't spend any time on it.
No, because this other story is the biggest news ever.
Way bigger.
We've talked about things that Project Veritas has broken.
We've talked about things that Breitbart's broken.
We've talked about things Tucker Carlson has broken.
All of which are the world.
When they do big things to say they've broken the biggest thing ever.
This isn't about credit, but I have to tell you, we are breaking information on this show
today that is the biggest thing ever broken concerning this fraudulent election and what
happened.
This is the number one biggest, go to bed, James O'Keefe.
But I really feel like the whole Germany's courts invalidating all testing as 96% fraud.
I think that's a way bigger story than any election.
There are people dying around the world, millions of them.
I mean, Alex would make that argument on another day, but he was late because he was working
on this gigantic scoop.
That's fair.
I messed up.
This thing is going really crazy on the 1st because there's, you know, Trump's attorney
Lin Wood is going batty talking about how Trump needs to declare martial law.
No, doing great.
Doing great.
Lawyers, that's what you want them saying.
Sidney Powell and Rudy are going buck wild.
They're fantastic.
No, I'm glad they're getting paid a lot of money.
Just a lot of nutty stuff is happening.
So I wasn't sure what this big news Alex had to break was literally any could be.
I thought this was it, but it's not.
But I found this clip incredibly charming, but let me just drop it on you right now.
Infowars.com live show feed headline must watch Tuesday live.
That's got a typo, but that's okay.
Top lawyers advise Trump to declare martial law, hold new election and that headline just
went out minutes ago, my typo, myself, let's get that fixed, please.
Some quaint about it, but I appreciate it.
Yeah, that's, that's, uh, he knows that he did that.
Yeah.
He knows that that was his typo.
You know what?
Can't get too mad about it.
You guys, somebody please fix that, please, uh, makeup.
If it was, if it was someone else's fault, I'd lose my shit and kill everybody here.
Well, he wouldn't be super furious, but he'd also be telling you how not mad he was.
There's something kind of quaint about just him being like, there's a typo there.
Yeah, that is a, that's one of those small refreshing human moments where you're like,
you know what?
At least you got that one.
I am about to get on air and talk about how it actually is really cool that Trump is being
told to declare martial law.
Sure.
Shit, I made a typo there.
It's like when a tweet goes viral and it's got a typo in it, I go, no, never take it
back.
I'll never take it back.
Now it's been screenshotted.
It's interesting because you're talking about this human moment there and I think that one
of the things that made this episode and the content we were going to get into particularly
like it like kind of, I don't know, elevated to me a little bit is there's a little bit
of pathos in here.
Okay.
There's a little bit like I don't, I don't want to make you or the audience or anybody
feel any kind of pity or sympathy or empathy for Alex of as a, you know, as an actor in
this world at all, but I think that there's a, there's a point in this December 1st episode
where you can't help but feel like, God damn, this is sad.
Hey, we all still appreciate Macbeth.
He wasn't a good guy, but we can feel the pathos of his choices.
Sure.
There is a tragedy to this episode.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah.
And it all begins in this next clip.
Then there's this story.
I hired a respected security firm that's done security research for the army and other groups
to dig in when I was asked by the White House to investigate it three weeks ago into Dominion
and it being owned by the Chai-Coms.
We got the proof.
We checked it with the SEC, confirmed it two days ago, and we now publish the findings
at infowars.com.
Firm that owns Dominion voting systems received 400 million from a Swiss bank account with
connection to Chinese government before election.
Oh, that's a, that's a scandal.
There's a lot going on in there and I really enjoyed it because this like for, it's been
a while, but it felt like this is really a conspiracy I could dig into.
Okay.
Okay, good.
So the company that owns Dominion, uh, they got a bunch of money from the Chinese government
or something.
Sure.
This is amazing.
In these kinds of cases, the first thing I like to do is I like to go to Infowars and
see what the, uh, the articles there actually say.
And actually this was an instance, literally unlike any that I think I've ever encountered.
And that's because this article includes links to five PDF documents that are apparently
used to prove their case.
Wait, five?
I've never seen proof.
Five?
Yes.
I've never seen-
Not one link to a zero hedge.
I've never seen embedded like documents.
Full on docs.
Crazy.
Okay.
Four of them are apparently SEC documents that have the following disclaimer on top
of them in big letters.
Wee wee wee wee wee wee wee wee wee wee wee wee wee wee wee wee wee wee wee wee wee wee
it's a good paper.
Quote, the Securities and Exchange Commission has not necessarily reviewed the information
in this filing and is not determined if it's accurate and complete.
The reader should not assume that the information is accurate and complete.
I don't hear any difference between what you read and what I said.
Yeah.
They're very similar.
This is not a good start.
So that's four of them.
And the fifth is a link that goes to a Reuters article.
This is not great in terms of documents, but there was another problem that immediately
jumped out at me.
The article begins with this sentence, quote, an investigation into SEC filings has revealed
that the firm which owns Dominion Voting Systems received $400 million from a Swiss bank with
close links to the Chinese government less than a month before the election.
In that clip we just heard, Alex said that the White House had asked him to look into
this three weeks ago, and then he hired a firm to do the research.
Where it all falls apart is there, there's an editor's note at the end of the article.
They've got to get rid of the thing.
Quote, a previous version of this article incorrectly credited a particular research
firm for performing this investigation.
That information was erroneous, and this article has been updated to correct that.
We apologize for the confusion.
Okay, so the research firm was not involved whatsoever.
Well, that's certainly getting confusing now, isn't it?
Yeah, it does seem to be that way.
This is amazing, and it definitely indicates a problem.
An archived copy of this article from Before the Correction credits the investigation to,
quote, Austin Security and Investigation Solutions.
This is a real company, but based on their website, they don't appear to be a research
firm.
They're more like the kind of people you get to do an unofficial stakeout, or help you
make court filings.
Okay.
Maybe, like when Alex had people following his wife around.
Right, right, right.
So it's the type of place that also sells nanny cams if you're in the store, they've
got some stuff for you, and they're like, oh, we'll do a little freelance investigation.
If you suspect someone's cheating, maybe you have them stake out their apartment or something.
What's their type of deal?
I don't know.
Yeah, they're hard-boiled detectives, Dan.
The only thing I can conclude is that either Alex is making up that some group did this
research to make it seem more official, or he needed this company's help to find SEC
filings, and then he tried to credit them for the conclusions he arrived at, and they
told him, keep our name off this shit.
That sounds right.
I'm not going to address the reality or falsity of any of the claims about this conspiracy
while I explain it to you.
Okay.
Just for the sake of simplicity.
According to Alex, Dominion is owned by a company called Staple Street Capital.
This group received $400 million from a company called UBS Securities.
UBS Securities is a Swiss investment bank that also owns a company called UBS Securities
Company Limited, which is an investment bank that caters to the Chinese market.
UBS owns approximately 25% of this Chinese investment bank, with the Chinese government
being the other owner through a number of other entities.
So the conspiracy here is that the parent company of Dominion got some money from a
Swiss investment bank which also owns a separate bank which the Chinese government is heavily
invested in.
Okay.
Even if every step of this is true and no one screwed up or fudged any of the details,
it still doesn't prove anything.
This is not a meaningful connection between Dominion and China.
Unfortunately, someone screwed up or fudged some details.
For one, this article on Infowars claims that Staple Street Capital, quote, acquired Dominion
Voting Systems in 2018.
This is kind of imprecise.
On July 16th, 2018, it was announced that Dominion Voting Systems, quote, has been acquired
by its management team and Staple Street Capital.
This was partially an acquisition, but not in the same way as them, like, outright buying
Dominion.
It was more of like a partnering and a deep investment.
Sure, sure, sure.
A little bit of a merger plus venture capital kind of mix up there.
It's in that territory.
Yeah.
Second, second, the article mentions that, quote, on October 8th, 2020, Staple Street
Capital filed SEC Form D offerings and sales amount of $400 million with the sales compensation
recipient identified as UBS Securities.
This is meant to imply that UBS Securities paid Staple Street $400 million to use Dominion
to steal the election, but the reality is that Form D with the SEC is used to report
on the sale of securities.
I hate to sound like I don't think $400 million is a lot of money, but when you're
in the investment market, it's not really that much to a company like Staple Street.
It's definitely not enough to pay them to rig a fucking election.
That's a comically low amount for that kind of work.
And also, I would assume they'd do the payoff more than a month before the election.
Seems, seems weird.
Timing?
I don't know about that.
Yeah, but you know, every time you see these people get bribed, I keep finding them taking
so little amounts of money for, like, the most- like, I could actually buy somebody
only getting $400 million to steal an election that's worth $20 trillion every day.
I can't.
You know?
Like, I see these people do, oh, we stole $50 million and I got paid $50 grand to my
re-election fund?
Like, that's what they do!
They're insane!
I think that what you're talking about is sort of the, like, boilerplate blase corruption.
Sure.
Not stealing elections.
Okay, that might be a bigger thing than I'm really throwing it out as.
Yeah.
Yeah, I do think that sometimes payoffs for, like, corrupt doing business kind of things
might not be the size that you'd imagine.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is a pretty big fucking heist.
It is a bit of a heist, yeah.
Far more likely, this was a payment from UBS Securities for purchasing some equity of investments
that are held by Staples Street.
This does seem to be the case, since in the form that Alex links to from the SEC, it says
that this is, quote, equity, and quote, pooled investment fund interests.
The third problem is probably the one that requires the least fact-checking, but also
is the biggest problem.
Alex wants to confuse his audience and readers about the entities UBS Securities and UBS
Securities Company Limited.
UBS Securities is the one that bought securities from Staples Street, and that's the Swiss
Investment Bank.
UBS Securities Company Limited is the Chinese investment bank co-owned by the Chinese government
and UBS Securities.
UBS Securities Company Limited did not buy securities from Staples Street, but because
the names are so similar, Alex wants the audience to come away with that impression, that the
entity that is part-owned by the Chinese government is the one that's giving the 400 million.
That's not the case at all.
This is why the conclusion to this article is just unearned.
Quote, the revelation that Dominion Voting Systems has financial ties to the Chinese
government via UBS Securities will bolster claims by Trump supporters that foreign actors
working on behalf of Communist China may have sought to meddle in the presidential election
and help Joe Biden.
None of that is demonstrated by the evidence provided.
This is all just paper-thin bullshit Alex is trying to pass off as a smoking gun.
Yeah.
Also, I hate to crash Alex's parade here, or rain on it and crash his party simultaneously.
But this story was not broken by Infowars.
They did a post about it, an article, on December 1st, and good for them.
Unfortunately, this exact conspiracy, using the exact same PDF files from the SEC that
Alex linked to, was going around on QAnon Twitter as early as November 29th.
There we go.
Alex is running around like he's late for the show because of breaking news, but it's
a fucking basil QAnon post.
God damn it.
Alex is just taking bullshit QAnon conspiracies one of his interns finds online, and then
he's pretending that it's the product of an investigation that he hired a firm to do because
the White House asked him to.
This is a pathetic level of insincerity and grift.
When you actually realize what Alex is doing, it becomes really disgusting to think about.
He, as a person, knows that the White House didn't ask him to do this investigation.
He knows that he didn't pay Austin Securities and Investigation Solutions to find these
documents.
That's the backstory that he needs to create to make himself look like a big, strong boy
for his audience, when he might as well just be reading your crazy uncle's Facebook page.
It's really gross to think about.
He knows what he's doing.
Being in that moment where you're so sad that you have to take QAnon posts and pretend that
the fucking White House paid you or insist they got you because you're the best, you're
the bravest around, you're the only person who can get this information out, so we need
you to do it.
So I dug deep in my pockets and I paid the best researchers to find these SEC filings
that you just found on fucking QAnon.
Get the fuck out of here.
It's so sad.
Being that hollow, that weak, in that moment, it's amazing.
He's a little bit like the America's Funniest Home Videos of the Q world now, where he takes
... He takes stuff that you could find on the internet in two seconds that went around
yesterday and packages it in for people who only watch TV.
He's like Tosh.0, but if Tosh was like, I got these from the fucking Chairman Mao himself.
You stumbled onto actually a really good metaphor, and it's why America's Funniest-
Stumbled onto?
Well, it's why America's Funniest Home Videos was a big ratings driver, and something like
Tosh.0 is fine, but whatever, it wasn't that great because the internet did exist.
You could find those videos then.
Back when America's Funniest Home Videos was on, that was the only game in town.
Just like Alex.
Exactly.
There was a time-
But then the internet existed.
There was a time when he was the only person who could provide you with nut shots.
And America's Funniest Home Videos still exists now in much the sad place that Alex Jones
exists.
Yeah.
Brutal.
Yeah, that means QAnon is-
Zagat?
Is Tosh.0?
Is QAnon Bob Zagat?
No.
Just Bob Zagat's later career?
Bob Zagat might actually be QAnon, though.
That might be true.
I'm not entirely sure.
I could buy it.
So Alex-
The Aristocrats.
So now that-
Yeah, The Aristocrats, just the family is telling the story of like, all right, so there's
a cabal.
What do they call the cabal?
The Aristocrats.
All right.
So, Alex is like, this story is not good.
It doesn't work.
The proof that he has doesn't back up the claims.
There isn't like, these documents don't show nefariousness to the level that he's implying.
And it's all just stuff he's cribbing from QAnon.
And he just won't give up this charade that he's on.
This is so huge.
But let me give you the big Infowars exclusive of two big Infowars exclusives that the system
is fighting and battling as hard as it can to make sure it does not get out to anybody.
Firm that owns Dominion Voting Systems received 400 million from Swiss Bank with connection
to Chinese government before election.
So yeah, man, they're trying to keep this under wraps.
Oh boy.
It's Infowars exclusives.
Now when Alex is going over the story, it's interesting because I guess he hasn't got
the memo.
The investigation conducted by Austin Security and Investigation Solutions centers on Staples
Street Capital.
Certainly hope you won't have to give an apology publicly to Austin Security Solutions.
I wonder if they have anything to say about you associating them with your bullshit that
you took from QAnon while you were on the air.
I wonder if they're thrilled about that.
I think we should see what they think.
I wonder.
Yeah.
I would have maybe checked in on it, but I don't like to stir the pot.
Ah, come on now.
Anyway, Alex, as he's going over the story too, the story sucks.
It doesn't work.
Sure.
But it sucks even more because he just makes up conclusions.
So the real headline is Chinese Communist government caught laundering 400 million through
Swiss Bank to Dominion month before election.
Whoa.
Well, you got me there.
That whoa, I can't hear it any other way than it being Alex, like kind of being impressed
with himself.
Yeah.
I can't believe I did that.
Whoa.
Look at this shit.
This sounds real.
We got five PDFs.
Admittedly, four of them say, don't believe anything in these, but we're still doing great.
One time I was riding my bike and I went down a hill and I lost control of the bike and
I was able to get a shoulder down on my way down and I ended up rolling and I got like,
it was one of the coolest things that no one else saw is I landed more or less like I had
meant to do it.
Sure.
Yeah.
You did a little bit of an acrobatic move.
It was all an accident.
It was all just landing exactly coincidentally how I needed to, to roll over and then sort
of be on my feet.
Sure.
All of a sudden you just woke up in the gymnast pose, like bowing to the judges that aren't
there.
And yeah.
Whoa.
Yeah.
That's kind of that.
It does.
It does have a little bit of that same feel.
I just fucking said that I proved that China paid dominion.
Whoa.
It is a little bit like the first time you throw a rolled up piece of paper into a garbage
can in the office from a ways away and everybody sees it and you're like, whoa, this always
happens when no one's looking.
Holy shit.
I got this one.
I mean, but for Alex, like everyone who's in the studio is like, no one's impressed.
Anyway, this is so sad to me.
Like I understand.
I, I, I can, I can see the audience, our audience, and everyone's laughing at Alex and I don't
begrudge you for it.
And I probably am only sad because I'm overly invested in, in this sort of like this story.
Right.
And it's so sad to me to see this guy who knows that he's lying about impressed with
himself, but, but, but, but lying about why you should be impressed with him like it's,
this is so gross.
Now I was put on the lead of this by a very high level individual in the white house and
I said, why me?
And they said, look, we already know it's there.
This has to be independent.
You need to go find it.
So I hired a security firm and I told him dig, and then this came in and it's all confirmed.
Like he has to create this, this whole spy novel where the white house is like, you're
there.
Oh, that you're independent.
This has got to come from the outside.
What the fuck?
This sounds like Pachannik wrote it for him.
I mean, even, even kind of a, so the white house came to me and told me to investigate
things and this is what showed up.
I can tell you that Steve didn't.
Okay.
Because Steve does show up later and Alex brings some of this up to him and Steve's
really not into it.
Not for it.
Okay.
Of course.
But, but some...
Steve's got a zag.
Some Steve-ish person, perhaps.
Yeah.
This is very Stevie.
I don't know what the deal is or like, you know, obviously this came from like QAnon
posts and online conspiracy swamp nonsense.
And Alex is the basis for Tom Clancy's Jack Ryan character.
But man, the, the patheticness of coming up with how important you are and, and needing
to project that to the audience is just like, God damn, I don't, I don't know how I, I don't
know how you could live like that.
It's just so false.
Totally.
Anyway, in this next clip, Alex is getting down to business on the Linwood situation.
The president's lawyer who has said that Trump needs to call for martial law and hey, why
not call for a new election?
Yeah.
Why not?
Do you think Alex is for or against this idea?
I'm going to go with for, but I would even almost argue against the new election part.
Just stick with martial law for a bit.
He's just for it all.
Okay.
And I'm going to go ahead and again, read you this headline right here.
Tony Linwood, president Trump should declare martial law and hold new election.
Then he goes through in this full page article, full page ad, can still pay to get your speech
out, I guess in America.
And I totally agree with his constitutional analysis.
Hey, totally agrees with Linwood that we need to just fucking have a new election because
he lost.
Why are you guys wasting my time even saying a new election?
Shut up.
Like if he wins that one, you guys are going to be like, well, I guess we were wrong this
time.
Yeah.
Like if Biden wins this time.
Get the fuck out of here.
Yeah.
Come on.
Like you are one, like you're going to let the election be whatever.
Yeah.
Shut the fuck up.
Just say you want Trump to be president for life and you'll destroy the Republic for it.
Hey, Jordan, shut up.
Yeah.
The only way there could be a fair election is if it didn't happen.
Is this a, is this a Zen Cohen?
Trump voting machines, Trump branded voting machines.
It's the only way to be sure.
It's the only way you can trust that it's impartial if they are made by Trump's company.
All right.
Let me pitch you this.
Everybody but Trump's own companies are against him.
Exactly.
Obviously.
All right.
He makes his own voting machines.
They look very similar to him.
They've got a computer screen where his chest is.
If you press for Biden, a little container opens up, a little gun comes out, boom.
Gotta vote for Trump.
Every time.
The gun swabs you.
The Trump Dalek.
Yes.
Yeah.
Anyway.
Um, Alex, uh, one of the reasons that there needs to be a new election is, uh, this story.
By the way, they now have a dominion engineer in the key County in Georgia, walking up illegally,
plugging a thumb drive in, walking out with it for a few hours, coming back and plugging
it back in totally illegal.
That's how you change votes.
I mean, we have them folks.
We have them.
Alex doesn't even know what County this video is from.
It's a key County.
Please.
He doesn't even care about this shit at all.
He's just literally repeating QAnon posts from social media.
He saw it.
This is just another one.
This was a QAnon witch hunt that started from a video of a dominion tech net technician
doing their job, which in the imagination of these idiots on social media became proof
of a person changing votes.
The proof that's given for this is that people watching the video assume that must be what
the guy's doing.
Therefore it's been proven.
It's almost comically dumb.
Yeah.
That is very stupid.
What's more profitable is the fact that the major players of the Q bullshit were amplifying
and leading a dachshund campaign against this dominion employee who is now almost certainly
afraid for his life.
This employee was not manipulating votes, but now because of people like Alex Jones
and Ron Watkins, a huge chunk of the public thinks that he's either definitely or probably
guilty of changing votes.
This is a real person who's been singled out and had a nefarious story written about him
for no reason, except to satisfy the corruption lust of a disenchanted group of conspiracy
lunatics.
And now he's got people tweeting nooses at him.
So fun.
Yeah, QAnon, the conservative media has essentially turned all of the internet into the Eye of
Sauron and if at any time points upon you, you'll be destroyed.
Yeah, and good job just amplifying that, Alex, and good job learning the lessons of your
career.
And good job, good job figuring out the things that have gotten you in trouble in the past
and then continuing to do those things.
Yeah, I mean, you know, he has in a way learned the lessons, which is that there are no negative
consequences except for people who aren't him and he doesn't care about them.
Well, at least he doesn't bring up the guy's name, so there's that.
Anyway, we need martial law.
And the reason we do is because there's already martial law or maybe something, I don't know.
Sure, whatever.
This is the UN global takeover.
So the response is martial law to stop their martial law and arrest them.
That makes sense.
Yeah, we need a coup to stop the counter coup.
Yeah, we got to coup the couers before they coup us and they'll be couped.
We need martial law in order to fight martial law.
And you know what?
Trump kind of has to do it.
He does.
Roger Stone calls on Trump to seize total power and assert martial law.
What he said was he has total power in the constitution.
If they have dominion software and fraudulent stuff, he has to move and seize those.
If the FBI and the courts won't act, he has to declare the civil emergency.
He's the executive protect the republic.
This is when you do it.
I'm an expert on martial law, ladies and gentlemen, wanted to have it through Obama or the Clintons
to take our guns.
This is them doing it to move the president out to do it.
This is their UN globalist medical martial law, as the archbishop and others have called
it's what it is to circumvent the government and hope the government just stands back and
watches it all happen.
I got to say after that clip, I really do think that he is an expert on martial law.
Um, and, uh, yeah.
Okay.
So if I understand this correctly, the UN is declaring martial law.
Yeah.
So Trump has to declare martial law in order to stop the UN's martial law.
Right.
Now I'm going to toss this out there for you as a possibility.
So Trump has declared martial law and martial law is declared.
What if the UN just removes Trump?
We're, we're still in martial law.
What do you mean?
I mean like once we're in martial law, it doesn't matter.
Somebody's going to be the martial law person forever.
Well, you know, in Alex's world, that's forever.
That's something that has always been a part of his ideas.
Right.
Now, let me, let me float this.
Look, their martial law is bad and it'll happen forever because you can't trust anybody.
Once they get in power, they'll never get out of power, except for Donald Trump because
he's really cool.
Right.
So you just got to let him have martial law temporarily, which I have told you on many
occasions is impossible and doesn't exist, but it will.
Trust me, he just wants to clean stuff up and then he'll get, he'll stop the martial
law.
Right.
But it seems like you're just getting rid of one of the steps that they would have to
take.
Because then they could just kill him and you're already under martial law.
And then they don't even have to bring in their people.
I don't know how Alex would respond to that.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, it's just dumb.
It's very stupid.
For Mr. Martial Law, Mr. Anti-Martial Law, whose whole career has largely been about
how tyrants never give up power once they achieve, you know, like some modicum of power.
Like for him to be like, no, we need a dictatorship for a short time in order to solve the problems
of my imaginary enemies.
That's great.
It's just kind of silly.
It's not, it's not funny.
It's sad.
Yeah.
It's very pathetic.
Listening to somebody talk like that and not be challenged with just like the simplest
of like, uh, that's dumb.
Yeah.
From anyone around them, from their longtime listeners, audience, from a voice within themselves.
Something.
Anything pushing back and being like, do you even, do you hear yourself?
Yeah.
Get the fuck out of here.
It's like, it's a wonderful life, but instead of the angel showing up, he just jumps.
Yeah.
At the beginning, he's just like, eh, fuck it.
Or like a Christmas Carol, but like all the ghosts are like, Scrooge, you're great.
You're the best.
You're just so great, man.
You are just doing so good.
When you die, you're going to get to hang with us.
We're going to have a great old time.
Hey, hey, Christmas morning, here's what you got to do.
Beat up Tiny Tim.
Take his crutch.
Take his fucking crutch, man.
Yeah.
Get him.
As in death, so is life.
Whoo.
The ghost of Christmas past just, get him.
Get him.
Uh, yeah.
That's good stuff.
It's just getting dictatory as hell up in here.
Therefore, we the people must demand.
Real quick.
He's reading Linwood's statement that he's made.
It's a long statement.
Alex reads most of it.
I don't care, but anyway, here, this is just a part of that and Alex's take on it.
Therefore, we, the people must demand a new and fair national vote, a vote that all Americans
can trust and live by regardless of the winner.
Without a fair vote, we fear, with good reason, the threat of a shooting civil war is imminent.
Gun sales are at all time high and 40% for the first time gun owners looking to defend
themselves, their property and their rights.
Therefore we must act now before there is no peaceful way left to preserve our nation.
Exactly why the Chai comms and the UN do this?
Because even if Trump removes the fraud, there'll be a civil war if he goes through the fraudulent
system.
It needs to be, it's Chai comm attack.
He has to arrest the heads of the media.
He has to arrest them.
They're all Chinese agents, all the proof, and we have to just go after them and have
Nuremberg trials.
I mean, this is an attempt to take over.
Wow.
Okay.
So I guess we've got to arrest them, the heads of the media.
So if I am sounding familiar, if I understand correctly, even if Trump uses the system to
root out the corruption, there's going to be a civil war.
Well, yeah.
Yeah.
However, if Trump instantly and extemporaneously arrests all the heads of the media, right.
Takes care of all of the generals that he doesn't like, removes everybody in government,
dissolves the Senate.
Yeah.
No civil war.
Well, dissolves the house at least.
Oh, well at least.
Yeah.
I mean the Senate for now is fine.
We'll keep that one in the Supreme Court.
Yeah.
It's strange.
So that one wouldn't start a civil war is what you're saying to me.
Here's, I mean, it's obviously a veiled threat.
Yes.
I'm pretty sure it's very much a, you give us Trump or we kill all of you as a threat.
Why are we even acting like he's calling for a new election?
He said, give us Trump or we kill you.
No, no, no.
There is a circumstance where in the new election would be acceptable.
Now a new election, just on these same voting machines owned by China.
Right.
No.
We can't have a new election because that'll just get stolen too.
Okay.
What about paper ballots?
Great.
They have to be counted by Trump family members.
I'm starting to feel like you guys want this to be in your favor.
Was gerrymandering not enough for you?
Apparently not.
Yeah, well.
It's really funny, Linwood and Sidney Powell have their press conference on the second
day of this, I believe on December 2nd.
And maybe it was on the first, I can't remember what day it was, but they are like, yeah,
and we're not going to participate in this Georgia election.
Don't vote.
Don't do it.
I guarantee it.
I think it's a terrible idea.
I love that.
And Trump, I wish you had balls to veto that defense bill.
Alex doesn't have any take on that stuff.
Although I thought that would be the most interesting, like Sidney Powell and Linwood
telling people not to vote in the Georgia runoff.
I'm all for it.
It's going to give a very significant advantage to the Democratic candidates.
Yes.
Please.
Why?
This is what I've been waiting for the whole time.
We can't be cooed and taken over by the dumbest people on the planet.
They need to dumb it up so much we don't even have to work for it, Dan.
I, I, yeah, I'm very interested in that.
And then also I was, I would be very interested in Alex's take on Trump's, uh, you know, threatening
to veto the NDAA.
The 230?
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Well, because that has to do with the 230.
Yeah, exactly.
Um, because Alex should hate the NDAA.
Right.
Because he does.
Yes.
So he should be in favor of Trump vetoing that.
Right.
But he also wants to get back on Twitter.
Well, it's such a complicated position.
He's finally forced into the most nuanced position of his career and he's reacting the
way we all knew he would pretending it's not happening.
Let me go ahead and gamble.
Uh, he forgets he doesn't like the NDA.
It's weird.
It's weird how he won't remember that very shortly.
Yeah.
But he does remember that he paid people a lot of money to dig up this story about China
and dominion.
Okay.
So he goes out, this is the total proof hiding in plain view and we have put it out for you
and hired the big investigative team to dig through all this and they tried to hide it,
but they failed.
They tried to hide it.
The subsidiary names and subgroups, but we tracked it all back and we have it now separately
going to break in just a few seconds, a promo code Patriot, you get an additional 10% off.
All right, man.
Yeah.
I think he's got a good point.
I think you can only own one business, the end.
No, none of this UBS, none of this, uh, this is steel and staples and UBS company limited
and UBS.
So it's 25% no one business per.
I don't think you have any idea how complicated it is.
One business per.
All right.
I mean, I do sometimes forget that you have a degree in small business administration.
One business per.
Not just that, not just very dumb.
Everyone gets one.
I understand that corporate structures are confusing and sometimes a bit complicated
to the untrained eye, simplify it by making it impossible to work.
Great.
Good.
Exactly.
That was my idea.
Yeah.
I mean, Alex continues to bring up this dominion employee who's been getting lots of threats
and I would say this is a bad idea, but at least, at least he's not saying his name or
anything.
And I'm going to come back and recap the top news and then show you footage of dominion
worker reportedly caught manipulating voter data.
What they did was illegal on tape.
We actually know who he is.
We're not going to release his name yet, but we've got the Intel and so do our people.
Uh, but this is incredible.
This will not stand global as you've been caught.
We do not accept your fraudulent leader, your chai comm agent, Joe Biden.
You're on notice.
Remarkable restraint on Alex's part.
Not saying this person's name because, you know, I mean that that's kind of a big part
of what's gotten him in trouble in the past, which is, you know, leading and amplifying
kind of campaigns that seek to harass, threaten, intimidate private citizens.
Uh, so I hope, you know, I hope, I hope he doesn't get into that.
Yeah.
I think it's, I think it's so weird how willing he is to go after individual people.
How weird.
Like I think that's the only way he can really assert power.
I suppose.
Cause I don't think anybody else is scared of him.
Like right.
Doesn't give a fuck.
That's fair.
James, the guy who owned comet ping pong was ready to take him to court.
Like he, Alex backed down hard when those people were like, no, fuck you.
Yeah.
Uh, people like a day of David Rothschild.
He showed up on Alex's show and talked to him for like half an hour.
Bill Ayers showed up and was like, what are you talking about?
Yeah.
Like these people aren't afraid of him.
You know who is?
Someone who could be hurt.
Random strangers.
Yeah.
But I, like I said, man, there's pathos, there's pathos because you can really tell that Alex
loves telling this story about how Trump's people told him to get to the bottom of this
dominion thing.
It's so sad when you know, what's up, and this is just a conspiracy from Cuban onboards.
God, this is so sad.
We are living in the most incredible time in world history on so many fronts, but I
got a call from the president's representative and they asked me three weeks ago when I was
in Arizona.
Uh, let's just say one of Trump's sons gave me a call and he put me in touch with a, a
executive, uh, with a major voting machine company.
I'm gonna leave it at that.
And they said, look, we know Soros, the Chinese are involved.
We want you to investigate it and we want you to separately bring it out.
And I said, well, if you know it, why, why do I have to find it?
And they said, look, I said, oh, cause it's, it's classified and I've got to find it myself.
They said, we're not saying that.
Well, I got a call two days ago from the security firm I hired, uh, that were former army internal
security, uh, researchers.
So they're good, good researchers.
And they ferreted out and found that 75 plus percent of a major Swiss UBS bank investment
firm is owned by the communist party, a central committee and by one of their major provinces
and that they put all of this money, 400 million into dominion.
I just can't get over how pathetic this is.
Yeah.
This is like a school kid bragging about like their dad being Superman.
You know, like the president will all just say, I'll leave it at one of his sons called
me and said, you got to get, Ooh, is it cause it's classified?
We're not saying that.
Cause it's not.
Yeah.
SEC filings.
It's a, it's a little bit like a, um, like a con man.
Uh, it's very much like, no, no.
Yeah.
I mean he is a con man, but I'm, I'm, this particular one reminds me of like the old
ones where it's somebody with a vaguely European accent who's talking to the New York stock
exchange people like, yes, I'm a representative of King Harold and uh, he's trying to keep
it all secret.
Very, very secret of course.
But if you loan me $1 million, I'll be able to, yeah.
And if you know that the King is, you're like, you're a fucking lunatic, man.
If you're not pulling it off, you look like an insane person.
Yeah.
And uh, you know, simultaneously I can see this and he is not pulling it off.
Right.
But there's probably enough people who are just dumb or just captured by him and think
that he means a goddamn word he says, and that's really sad.
It's really sad for them and it's really sad for Alex.
Yeah.
It really is.
Just on a human level that he's a 40 something year old man, 46, 47 year old man who's in
his studio bragging complete bullshit lies about the president's son telling him to do
this investigation that he just saw in a QAnon board.
Well when you put it in that context, it sounds bad.
It is.
Anyway, it's also like, this is just, it's painful to me.
Like I had a really tough time with the first half of this December 1st episode because
it is this.
It's, it's, it's, this dude is just a sad mope.
This is 1 trillion percent the smoking gun and then it just gets worse from there.
The communist Chinese wired through a secretive Swiss bank account, $400 million to Dominion
on October 7th.
I mean, wow.
I suggest you go get these documents.
I suggest you get them out and I don't normally say sources and things like that, but you
know, I want you to know how real this is.
Okay.
It's just, just a bummer.
Yeah.
Oh boy.
And the other thing that's really sad about this is like, if you really look at it from
a professional perspective, Alex is reduced to taking something from QAnon circles, pretending
it's not that, and then just trying to resell it.
Anybody who's like engaged in those QAnon communities would see this and be like, oh,
we already knew that.
We knew this days before your article came out.
This is old news to real conspiracy heads.
Like it's, it's, he's trailing behind the thing that he thinks is a rip off of himself.
Right.
And it's just, man, you should quit.
You should just quit.
Yeah.
If Shakespeare were alive today.
It's not good.
Me thinking she does protest too much would be like, Jesus fucking Christ, stop protesting.
It's too obvious.
Yeah.
Now I would say that Alex has been a little bit out of line with talking about this Dominion
employee, but I will say up till this point, he hasn't really been trying to like intimidate
the guy until now.
But here's video.
We know who the guy is.
We tracked him, Democrat operative.
We know where he worked.
McDonald's and GameStop before this, we've not released his photo or his name yet, Javier.
But we have the footage of him in the Key County illegally, whether he knew it or not,
going up with a thumb drive, taking it out.
That's pretty much, that's really fucked up.
That's really fucked up because you could also tell how much Alex kind of relished that
kind of that moment where he feels like he's threatening somebody.
Javier, I know you.
Anytime I can drop it on you.
But at least there's a lot of Javier's in the world.
So like at least he didn't say his name.
Palming the USB and waddling out.
And we've got his name, Javier Corey, as we told you.
I wasn't going to break it myself, let Gateway Punden do it.
Stay in attack formation.
Oops.
Well, I hope this does not come back to bite you in the ass and you don't get sued.
I hope it does and he should be sued immediately.
And even if nothing happens, the judge should look at his other lawsuits and be like, see,
this is what you're trying to do.
I know it.
I can see it in your eyes.
You're trying to do this.
This is a clear pattern of behavior.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is the same shit and we're going to stop you before you kill this guy.
Hooray.
Or this kind of behavior happening a couple days ago could be inserted as part of the
Sandy Hook trial.
As a piece of information.
Like he is not stopping from behaving in ways that are tailored to raising the possibility
of harm coming to private citizens.
I guess I do kind of understand.
He's an asshole.
I mean, it shouldn't work like, oh, okay, so you've just told me what the exact line
is, so what I'm going to do is tiptoe up to as close to the line as possible and then
wave my hands at you and be like, nah, nah, you can't catch me.
I didn't kill this guy this time.
Your honor, this is completely different because it's about a different thing.
Yeah.
Same behavior about a different thing.
Oh, whatever.
What a fucking asshole.
So now Jordan, I guess there's a lot of pathos at the beginning part and I was kind of bummed
out about it and there was a part of me that felt like, well, this is interesting because
it is pathetic and there's an interesting glimpse of Alex trying to put on his sort
of Superman jumper and try and play the role of what he thinks he is.
Daddy turned me into a detective, so I found everything.
And I was like, oh, that's interesting, but that's not great.
I need more from this episode.
And thankfully another someone who might be a daddy to Alex shows up and that is our boy,
Steve Pechenik.
Dr. Steve.
Let me remind you that a couple of weeks ago and several months ago, I told you that I
was told by my fellow countrymen in cyber command that I was to announce on your show
or when show your show that we had put a QFS watermarks on all the ballots.
We had monitored all the machines on Dominion and we had expected everything to come out
and it came out of cyber control.
Where's David Knight at?
I don't have the same factor that you have, but I do respect.
David, you in the building?
He's not happy about it.
I have to imagine.
Yeah, Steve's still on this still on it, huh?
And Alex is still having him on, which is weird because again, this is a direct contradiction
of literally every other talking point that Alex is spouting.
Now, Steve is not only contradicting Alex in terms of like, no, this was a sting operation
this entire election.
He also is not thrilled with the idea that Alex is like, Hey, maybe we should have martial
law.
Steve's like, no, we don't need martial law.
What we have in effect now is we have prepared the sting operation, which I announced here
on Alex Jones because I was given that permission.
He's given the permission.
It's cool.
So yeah, man, I mean, look, OK, I'm never going to be like, hey, I have common cause
with Steve Pachannik.
Right.
But I do find it comforting on some level that he's not saying we need martial law.
Yeah, but he's also said we should dissolve the government and Melania should be queen.
Yeah, that's why I don't want common cause.
I would like some clarity coming from Dr. Steve.
All right.
He's who I go to when I'm looking for sanity in this info world's world.
When you need a North Star.
Exactly.
That's what I'm all about.
Well, unfortunately, Alex decides that this is the time when he's going to be like, yeah,
I don't know.
Ooh.
Some people say you're making this up, you're full of it.
Let me just David Knight.
OK.
And I think you're a credible person.
I respect you.
You've been really accurate in the past.
So that goes a long way for me.
That clip is essentially Alex trying to play both sides of the fence.
Yeah.
Now, David says you're full of shit and I still want to talk to you.
So well, I think it's even less that and more just like if anybody in the audience were
to attack him from either side, he can cover his base with a clip like that.
That's fair.
He can say that some people say that you're full of it.
Yeah.
You're a hard hitting journalist and pushing back on you.
Then if someone is into Steve's theories, he'll be like, I said that he has a great
track record and that goes a long way with me.
Yeah.
He's just being mealy mouthed here.
Anyway, Steve's talking about the situation we find ourselves in.
The ballots are all accounted for and barcodes or whatever the fuck.
And also, some generals have sent troops all over the country and the Supreme Court needs
to be taken out.
OK.
I can tell you that Nakasone has been running a very effective monitoring system and that
we have deployed military elements all over the country.
I can tell you that in North Florida, the amount of planes that have come in with war
equipment, with a regular army, National Guard and others has increased markedly.
I can tell you that at the same time, John Roberts, the Supreme Court, may have a problem.
He is a sick man.
He's had a history of seizures.
We know that his interpretation of corruption is what we call the minimalist quid pro quo
corruption.
Yikes.
Sure.
That is what we call the minimalist quid pro quo corruption.
Yeah.
Cool.
You're talking about sort of, you know, the inefficiency, like A, he's unqualified, the
Chief Justice of the Supreme Court.
Meanwhile, we've got General Nakasone coming in and bringing an army into Florida.
Sure.
Wow.
Tomorrow we march on Florida.
What are you doing?
I never know which of their plans I would be interested in letting play out.
Not that one.
No.
But sometimes they'll have like a, like they, all of their plans are like they have a pwinko
board and then they just drop something down.
Caravan.
Caravan is a plan.
I'm glad they followed through.
That's true.
In this episode, I have another one that I fucking hope Alex follows through with.
It will be my next, like Caravanity project.
It will, if Alex does this, I might live stream for days straight of just like, we need updates
on what's going on with this.
It's one of the most exciting things.
You know what?
Fuck it.
Okay.
Unprecedented.
If Alex follows through with what he claims he's going to do later in this episode, I
might join him.
Okay.
All right.
For different reasons.
That's a tease because I don't know what he's going to talk about.
No, I won't because of fucking COVID.
Don't worry about it.
We'll figure it out.
All right.
Well, we'll talk about this later in the episode.
We'll get you in a bubble.
A literal bubble boy situation.
So earlier you said, by the way, I hate to be a tease.
This will all be revealed within this episode.
Earlier you were mentioning that like the way that Alex was talking about him being
told to do this dominion investigation sounds steveish.
And because steve is still on the, the election was a sting operation.
Why would then the government ask Alex to the left hand?
Can't know what the right hand's doing.
Dan.
This is a problem for Alex though, especially in terms of presentation.
He needs to ask Steve, help me out of this one guy.
Come on, buddy.
If Congress doesn't stand up, if the electors on December 15th, Dr. Steve, don't say no
to this fraud, then they will put Biden in and Trump says he'll go.
So if there is these watermarks and all this proof, and I believe you talked to those sources
who told you.
So I believe you're in good faith.
I think you're a good person.
When do we see the cards on the table?
What's about to happen?
Like why would the white house see to me, this doesn't mean I'm important.
It means the president's a quadriplegic politically cut off.
Why would they get me to go after a Soros and the chai comms and then we get the smoking
gun documents, but it takes us two and a half weeks to get it.
Why?
I mean, if they have this, why?
Because it doesn't make sense.
It's a great question.
Why would they do that?
Some would say it's an unanswerable question.
I would say that it's a very simple, they wouldn't.
Yep.
No, but Steve can't say that.
Oh no, that's a bad idea.
No, because in order for their illusions to continue, that the audience needs to buy into
to keep the cash flow going.
Of course.
Steve needs to not be a complete liar and Alex needs to not be shown to have not talked
to the white house about this QAnon post that he's passing off as a scoop.
Everybody's in a little bit of a dangerous position right now.
Right.
But there is a really smooth way to get out of this pickle and that is...
Leo Zagami.
No, Steve's just got to do exactly what he always does when things get tough.
I appreciate the fact that you're getting very excited, but the reality is the game
has already been played.
What's happening is that Trump anticipated most of this, Trump actually and the intelligence
community really picked you as the source for which I was to announce what they wanted
me to announce.
Because you're the best.
And I'm not just a certain person or stooge because I don't get paid.
I'm really not interested in promotion.
I really don't garner anything other than being a citizen warrior.
Crazy old man.
Chosen as the mainstream media, as opposed to the New York Times, The Post.
So although you're getting excited, what is happening all around you, Alex, is exactly
what we expected.
Yeah, so, you know, when you're encountered with this unanswerable question where the
only logical, rational, real world explanation is you're both crazy liars, you know, you
get out of that by being like, Alex, calm down.
You were chosen because you're so great.
You're the best.
You're the best there ever was, buddy.
Look at these compliments and don't look at me.
That's a very easy way to get out of the conversation.
And also, you know, then Steve can transition into other topics like Biden will never be
president.
Sure.
I will guarantee you Biden will not become president of the United States because right
now he's wearing possibly an ankle bracelet because he said he has a little bit of problem
on his ankle and he's you know, he's twisted his ankle.
I don't believe that.
So you might look at that problem.
So in effect, what you're seeing now, that sounds like cute stuff.
He's got an ankle bracelet.
I mean, I hope so.
I hope he gets a different type of bracelet.
Look, I can't get excited the way you can, Alex.
That's the reason why.
Come on.
I mean, this is not unusual for me.
We said it a long time ago.
Well, I want to believe you.
So in 50 days, I will tell you this, buddy, I am going to I'm just going to if you're
right in 50 days, you are going to be the king of the planet to me.
I already really like you.
You got me great info over the years.
You've been on the show for 19 years.
It's been really accurate info.
So I just I just hope you're right.
That is what it sounds like when someone doesn't believe someone.
Fuck you, Alex.
Fuck you.
That's not fair.
Get this dude off your show.
Not just that, but how dare you say that sounds like cute shit 20 minutes after you said cute
shit.
A bunch of it.
You fucking.
You're you're you're being very fast and loose with a private citizen's safety and you're
pitching a nonsensical, stupid voter fraud conspiracy based on QAnon.
Yeah.
Stuff.
So you're saying his QAnon bullshit is stupid.
Wow.
That's unfair.
That's just rude.
Well, you got to make it look good.
That's rude.
Yeah.
Anyway, Steve is a pro.
That's true.
When Alex says this sounds like QAnon stuff, he's like, hey, man, I can't get excited like
you get excited.
I don't know what that means.
But Steve's got to make it like, no, dude, you're so important.
You're so important.
Every time Alex is getting a little bit out of pocket, I think you might be full of shit.
You're a good looking dude.
I think you're great.
Yeah.
You know, I was wrong.
I should never have doubted you because of your show and that video that I did with you.
It was sent to China.
And believe it or not, I got a call from what I call my Chinese nanny, who's been my control
officer in China for the past 30 years.
That meant President Xi and the Public Bureau of Safety in China personally had to call
me up three weeks ago because of the show that I went on on your show, Alex, to explain
that they are not looking for any trouble to say that it was an excellent show, meaning
that they don't want to get into a problem situation.
Steve went on our info wars and President Xi called and was like, hey man, we don't
want trouble.
We don't want no trouble.
Steve.
I do not know what I'm listening to.
I do not know what's actually happening right now.
That's absurd.
Alex being like, oh, Trump personally sent me on a message to investigate shit that I
made up and I'm creating this whole fictional mythology around how I'm great.
And then Steve coming with that bullshit at me.
Are we talking?
What am I watching?
Well, look, I think Steve knows that we exist.
I think he knows that in order to be interesting, he wants to make it on our show.
Exactly.
He's got to come with it.
If you want to make the after show, your character needs to be interesting, especially if you're
only on for short bursts.
You don't want to be the character who doesn't get a rose, so to speak.
And Steve, I mean, he has, he gets a rose.
He is also somebody who unfortunately runs the risk of being pretty boring pretty easily
because he's made so many.
That's true.
Deep cuts.
His escalation has to be, yeah, it has to be president.
She called because he wanted to make sure no problems here guys just want to give you
a call.
So you got the go ahead and everything's okay.
She wants to parlay Hey guys, we just want you to say stay frosty
out there.
You keep going.
She wants me to work as an intermediary between Alex Jones and China.
And again, just inexplicable and pointless little bit of racism there.
Sure.
So Alex is having this interview with Steve and he's, he's also like, I gotta go.
I gotta leave early.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, I'm not going to be playing hooky in the next two hours
when Paul Joseph Watson has Candace Owens, an amazing guest on busy with breaking news
and documents and Intel that I have to go off air and tomorrow we'll have giant breaking
news here for you on air with the information I'm going to be getting.
But it's so huge.
I'm going to have to go off air in about 10 minutes.
It's not, um, there's nothing big going on at all.
I would probably make myself scarce if, um, the, the team up is going to be Paul Joseph
Watson and Candace Owens.
It's been my feeling that she's not thrilled with being associated with info wars actively.
Right.
Because I think that she thought that there was a bigger space for her, like with turning
point.
Sure.
Is never coming on info wars.
Right.
I don't know.
I haven't tracked her career as closely, but it seems like she's back in the place where
she would be on info wars.
Yeah.
She thought she could get out into a bigger pond and now she's back in the small pond.
We'll be with Paul as opposed to be with Alex.
If you're going to do it, go with Paul.
It's somehow seems safer for your reputation.
Um, so Alex is going to leave early cause he's got to pretend to work.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Steve has one going anywhere.
He has one more big swing to make.
Okay.
I love this one.
I was like, what the fuck?
So I'm telling you, Beijing called me directly because of the show that you're doing right
now.
And we wanted to use you as the main thoroughfare for that announcement.
The last part that you have to know is that ironically, one of my neighbors in Northern
Florida increased the fencing and the size of Gitmo by 200%.
In other words, I have a neighbor who's in charge of wire and fencing for prisons.
And he went to Gitmo a year ago and increased the size of Gitmo Guantanamo based by over
a hundred percent.
Shouldn't you be against that?
Is that, is he trying to say that's because Obama's taller than the other prisoners have
been in the past?
Is that what we're trying to say?
Yeah.
The globalists that you're going to incarcerate in Guantanamo and your fantasies, the issue
with them and the safety there is wall size.
Height.
Yeah, wall size.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, this is silly.
But what he's talking about is there were reports of Trump building new construction
at Guantanamo, whereas prior to this, the tendency and the trend had been towards closing
it.
So I think he's just trying to use some of those ideas, which are super popular in the
QAnon world.
Right, right, right.
I think Steve is really just like, at this point.
He's just a Q guy.
Yeah.
And so is Alex.
Yep.
Quite frankly.
Q and the mighty have fallen.
Yeah.
Ah, so like such champions of weirdness becoming followers.
It's sad.
I mean, it is something to be said about Q's ability as a mental disease to infect, I mean,
everybody, you know?
Yeah.
It just gets fucking in your head with these people.
You're not immune if you're a conspiracy leader.
Yeah.
You can fall.
Well, I mean.
These people who are leaders are smart enough to not say this is what they're into.
Well, yeah, exactly.
They know that they can take the ideas and the sort of trends in the conspiracy world
and then reorient them a little bit into being about like, my friend general has told me
the same thing.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Yeah, Q is saying that stuff, but that's just because it's parallel.
It's the same thing.
I'm just getting it from a real source, whereas, wait.
I imagine that it feels a little bit like stock speculating to be one of these conspiracy
people dealing with Q, trying to be like, okay, well, I think this is one of the theories
that's going to stick.
And if I get on this one, then I'll get more whenever it goes mainstream, whereas.
It may be stock speculating, but it's also, there's no consequences for being wronged.
Well, yeah, but that's fair.
People just forget.
Nobody just loses all their, yeah.
It would be like the stock market if whenever the stock went down, people forgot you bought
it.
Every day, every day, a clean slate.
So Alex says goodbye to Steve.
And this is not how you part ways with someone who you think is credible.
God bless you.
We'll talk to you soon.
StevePaschinek.com.
Have a great, have a great week coming up.
You too.
All right.
Man, I hope he's right.
You shouldn't have to hope he's right.
I have the best guests.
I have the best people and man, I hope that bullshit he just spun makes sense.
Yeah.
It sounds good.
Probably bullshit.
Nope.
Bullshit.
Yeah.
So we jump into the second and Alex starting the show, really just sort of ruminating about
himself as a child and talking about things that are absolutely not true.
When I was six years old, seven years old, I liked to watch PBS Frontline.
I like to watch the long Supreme Court debates, the few that they ever televised.
I really found how things actually work is incredibly interesting.
But then I learned that almost no one else actually wants to study how things work.
When Alex was six years old, he was so advanced, Jordan, you understand that he was watching
full, unedited C-SPAN Supreme Court hearings because he was so fascinated.
But as he got older, he realized no one was as serious as him.
Let me posit you an alternate theory.
When he found out how hard it was to actually do research, he decided that what he did was
actual research and what everybody else did was crazy.
Yeah.
At a certain point, he realized it's really tough to read a book, but to a third person
or to somebody else, to an external observer, there is no difference between you having
read the book and you saying you read the book.
That sounds true.
Yes.
That is quite a revelation to have at the age of six and I applaud Alex for it.
When I was six years old, I realized that if I put infinite jest on my bookshelf, people
will think I was smart.
I did that myself.
With the same book.
So Alex, god damn it, I was so excited at this point on the second.
I could have, I almost couldn't contain myself because I don't know if you remember this,
but I think it was a 2015 episode.
Alex got on air and he was like, I am going to, in this episode, jump the shark.
Yes, I do recall that.
I am going to, as a piece of art, performance art, call for the banning of Islam.
Yep.
And then he proceeded to talk himself into not doing it as a performance art.
It's a good idea to ban Islam.
But what he set out to do was like this thing that he was being overly clear about his intentions,
which kind of ruined the sort of satirical thrust of it.
But it was like, I love to see that you had an idea and you wanted to try.
Right.
I got that again.
Certainly, he made our satirical piece work by trying to do a satirical piece and then
winding up embodying the thing that he thought he was satirizing.
Yeah, it was interesting on that level.
And I guess it's the same this time.
Now, I thought about the best way to say this, but I'm just going to get it right out there.
I think it will be more effective to wake you up if I actually join the dark side.
Do it.
I am seriously considering completely shifting into the enemy mindset and presenting all
this and just telling people world government's good and that you should kill yourselves for
the earth.
I mean, like, I would love it if he did as a joke, just did like a Bill Gates is great
because it would be the most incompetent, nonsensical piece of satire or sort of character
based nonsense.
I would love it.
It would be, it would be a thrill.
One, it has to be a surprise.
Nobody can know you're about to do it.
Right.
Two, you have to commit to the bit.
You have to open by saying something like that.
You have to stay solid.
You can't break character and you have to go for a good long while.
Right.
So, but I was like, ah, maybe.
And he can't do any of those things.
But he's saying like, ah, I've just been thinking about this.
I got to go to the dark side and be like the globalists.
And then he started to get real fucking dark, like to a point where like you are being what
I would consider quite to the dark side.
The public cares, good people care, Christians care.
That's the main group that's resisting, but everyone else is running headlong into it
and wanting to be slaves, wanting to be slowly killed, wanting to be made unhappy, wanting
to be failures because they are not meant to go into the future.
They are meant to die.
Wait, what?
And that's God's plan.
Okay.
Wait.
So, okay.
So are you telling me that the evil enemy that you hate has come to the conclusion that
humans aren't worth living and has decided to kill all of us and you think that that's
evil.
However, you agree that humans aren't worth living and God is going to kill them all.
Correct?
Well, yeah.
And he, you know, he's sort of evidence for this that he's basing it on is that it seems
like only Christians are interested in fighting the Christian zealotry war that he's, the
crusade that he's imagining.
It seems odd that this Christian crusade is only backed by Christians.
Right.
And so that's strange to him.
And it's proof that everyone else is meant to die in God's plan.
I think that that's really fucked up.
Yeah.
I think he went from, I think I'm going to join the dark side to, I think I am the dark
side very quickly without seeming to realize that he was doing it.
No.
And that is not him being like performancey and on the dark side because his version of
performance of the dark side to be like, you should put this in your body.
It wouldn't be all non-Christians seem like they're destined for death and that's just
God's plan.
Yeah.
Isn't he the guy who says that Islam is violent?
Yes.
I cool.
I do think that at any point, maybe I was being hyperbolic when I said the GOP is ISIS,
but Dan Wolf, this is ISIS.
Yeah.
He's a ways down that road, at least in terms of ideology and thought and hopes.
And let's hope not deeds.
Now this was interesting to me because that's kind of it for this thing that he was intending
to do.
Sure, sure, sure.
He had this great idea of like performatively becoming the dark side and then he immediately
said something incredibly dark and did embody what I would think is coming to a dark side.
But now that he's done with that, Alex tells a story that I think does not make the point
that he wants it to make.
I think that he sounds like an asshole in this story.
They're in fantasy land, they're losers.
They're not the resistance, they're the establishment.
And they're I mean, I had this guy this weekend, Sunday, I went for a walk down at Zilker Park
and I'm walking along the creek there that dumps in the Colorado River.
And I see this guy, you know, about twenty five, kind of the academic type anti fun.
He's got his, you know, his beard, everything academic and he's wearing a black top black
pants.
But no, no anti stuff I could see.
But I could tell and see I was looking at my looks.
And then he starts walking towards me at an angle like he's going to hit me, he's going
to do something.
And so as he starts coming towards me menacing, I just couldn't help it.
I just instinctively started walking over and I was getting ready to just drive his
ass to the ground.
He was stupid.
I'm taking swing.
It was just instinctive that I started like a magnet coming to him and I was going to
knock his ass down on that ground hard.
And at the last minute, he kind of went like that and then looked scared.
It's like, yeah, dude, this isn't fantasy world.
This isn't LARPing.
You're about to get hurt bad.
It sounds like Alex just threatened a guy randomly that he imagined was, wished him
ill and was academic Antifa types.
This is, this is scary.
So let me see if I can get the details of this story correctly.
And I'm going to do this from the point of a neutral observer.
So I'm in a different angle.
Maybe you're a birdwatcher.
Just hanging out, not doing much.
I see Alex.
I see Alex Jones over there just shaking because he's Alex, uh, just visibly just vibrating.
And then I see a guy over there, uh, probably a little way fish wearing glasses.
He's got a black shirt on.
He's got black shorts on Antifa type.
And then he just starts walking away and then, uh, Alex Jones visibly shaking, starts walking
directly towards him and almost throws a fist at him.
And I'm supposed to think, oh, well, it's the Antifa guy's fault.
Well, at the last minute, the Antifa guy looked like he was about to get hit by somebody.
Yes.
And then all of a sudden he's so subservient, he's so scared of the clear threatening vibe
I was giving off.
I'm going to go with Alex Jones suddenly running towards me on a day where I was just reading
at the park.
He's going to make me go away.
In that story, I don't hear any clear indication that Alex's violence was in response to any
real violence or threatening-ness of this person who was just on the trail.
And Alex has decided because they're wearing black and have a beard, are academic Antifa.
Right.
Whatever the fuck that means.
Alex seems like he's a threat to people.
It does seem like what he just said was, if I feel a bad vibe, I will kill someone.
If you're wearing black, you're probably Antifa and I might fucking hit you.
I might just fucking haul off and beat the shit out of you.
Yeah.
And if you act like it's weird that I'm about to hit you or maybe you duck and cower, then
I'm going to be like, why are you emotionally manipulating me?
Yeah.
Why are you acting like someone's about to hit you?
You were about to hit me.
Okay.
Jeez.
Anyway, Alex has a lot of fantasies.
One is the academic Antifa is trying to get them on the trail.
Another is that in the near future, his books, I guess he's written a couple of books sort
of anyway, his show will be contraband and you can record this and you can save this
and in that dystopic future, you won't be able to find it on the cloud or online.
You'll have to have contraband old devices that your smart devices were fused, even allowed
to be plugged in.
You'll have to go through a lot of hoops to even have this saved.
So I would suggest you transcribe it.
And in the future, you'll have to hide it in the near future.
In the near future, I would love it for Alex to like go to Europe and see like a wall sockets
and be like, it's happened already.
Is this AC or DC nothing means anything anymore.
What a dumb dumb.
Anyway, in this next clip, the only thing I would say about that last thing is just
like, this is just such a desire to be forbidden or whatever.
He's just so into that idea.
I think it's probably from one too many bad sci-fi novels.
So we talk a lot about Alex's bizarre morality.
This idea of sort of galactic rules and stuff.
Mike down for this next clip, because he talks about it a little bit more.
And this is something I really need your help with, because this is another clue about how
this moral system works, but it doesn't make sense.
You're not injected with one microchip.
You're injected with hundreds of little tiny ones that all have the same amount of data
on them that a chip 10 years ago had.
And you're saying, well, why don't they just spray it out of helicopters or out of planes?
Then we ingest it and breathe it.
Metaphysically, they're not allowed to do that historically.
They have to get you under pressure to do it.
They've got to leave a way out for you on a skate patch.
But they need to force you to do it.
It's a push.
But then it becomes a shove once God removes the barrier hedge.
And then, yes, they will put it in your water, put it in your food, put it everywhere.
So God has a barrier hedge to this sort of free will thing.
The devil, once God says, eh, go ahead, then the devil can go ahead and just mess with
your free will.
And that's why there's chemtrails, I guess, because God is like, yeah, that hedge is gone.
Fuck it.
Who cares?
Yeah.
I think if I understand what he's saying
Because Alex does believe in chemtrails.
Yes, he does.
Yes.
But you can't spray things randomly.
No, no, no.
Targeted.
God removed that hedge already.
Right, right, right, right.
So I think, if I understand correctly, I think what he's saying is that the devil, the literal
Christian devil, which is real and is running Biden's campaign still somehow, it can't
And might have called Steve.
Yes, and might have called Steve.
China called, and so did the devil.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Both.
Steve got two phone calls.
Oh, the devil said he wasn't doing well.
So he can push you, right?
And God will stop him from going too far unless you've given a little bit of like a, hey,
maybe I'll go along with the devil, and then God will remove that final ring of protection,
and then you will be thrown into the abyss.
I don't think that's what he's saying.
I think thatI don't know ifI don'tI'm not certain, based on the things that I've
heard, that this hedge of protection that God has
Sure.
I'm not certain that that is, like, relies on your choice.
It has to, because you have to have the way out, and you have to be able toso you have
to choose the devil.
But how do chemtrails work, then?
Well, you chose to look up.
But it doesn't matter if I look up.
According to them, you're breathing in all these, like, these aluminums and whatever
the fuck in the air.
That is something that you can't escape.
You did not make any choice thatthat is something that is completely above your will.
You did not agree to that, therefore it's an infringement of your will.
Right, but it hasn't been primed yet.
It's just like a bomb without a timer, you know?
You've just got all the stuff in you, and then you have to believe something, and then
they'll activate it.
No.
I can't imagine that.
I'm struggling.
This makes less than zero sense.
Yeah, I don't understand this new wrinkle to it.
Yeah, I don't like it.
But there's another wrinkle, and that is
So soon?
Yes.
Oh, God.
And that is that you can't do things to kids.
But I think from the context of this, Alex is talking about vaccines.
Yes.
Now, the real ultimate sin here is, though, they target children before they are of age
to make the discernment.
And so that's why the Satanists are so cursed, is they cheat and they lie to themselves.
Why can they cheat then?
And they break the metaphysical rule that they are not allowed to hurt innocents.
They're only allowed to get adults to not support themselves and to make a bad decision
to receive the spiritual interdimensional transmission from Satan.
So it's real simple.
They're tuned into the security channel.
It's real simple!
They like it.
They like the Satan channel.
I want to be a ruler and I want somebody to slap his hands whenever he's like, they can
cheat.
Mm-hmm.
No.
You said they can't cheat.
But that's why they're cursed.
Yeah, but you said they can't cheat.
Well
I mean, if they're already cursed, then why wouldn't you just continue cheating?
There's no greater punishment after hell, right?
Right.
So if you've already cheated, why would you then be like, well, we still have to follow
the rules of chemtrail?
If you cheat, you're cursed, but you're not going to hell.
You're cursed.
What?
Oh.
Well, I guess I retract all of my arguments.
That makes you smile weird, and Alex can pick you out of a crowd.
That's fair.
Those are the problems with being cursed.
Alright, you can't be a daywalker anymore.
I gotcha.
Because I think what he's saying is that they're getting around the cosmic rules, because these
children are agreeing to get vaccinated, but they don't know any better.
So it's like
Who's making cosmic rules with loopholes that big?
I don't know.
There's only one person.
Also, I would suggest that if this is some kind of thing that really curses you, having
children make decisions that they're unable to understand, what about baptism?
What about child baptism?
Shouldn't that be a problem for them?
No, no, no.
Because the children can choose that, and that's good.
But, I mean, I understand that subjectively you would say that that is a good decision
as opposed to getting a vaccine, which you think is a bad decision, which you're being
tricked into.
Right.
But externally, from the view of the universe, these are both things that this child cannot
decide.
No, you can't trick a kid towards God.
That's the other cosmic rule.
You can only go towardsif you get baptized, you've meant to.
Right.
It just seems weird.
Yeah.
I just don't understand what it is exactly that makes those acts different outside of
wanting them to be different.
See, I just don't understand why you would want to be involved in any of that.
Like I don't want
This morality?
Yeah!
I don't want to beI don't want to be good in this morality.
This seems even morebeing good seems even more somehow evil in his morality.
And it's all incredibly confusing.
In coherence!
How can you live on a day-to-day
From day to day.
Yeah, right?
It's like, I don't know.
I might be the devil.
I don't know.
How do you make small moral choices like, hmm, should I tell my wife she looks pretty
today or do I have to be 100% honest?
Is me telling her she looks pretty going to take away her free will to dress herself as
she so chooses?
Exactly!
Am I the devil?
Oh, man.
Yeah.
Woof.
Yeah, there's almostit's paralyzing.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's terrifying.
But, look, anyway, the devil, he has weird rules.
The devil's followers
So does God.
are cursed.
Yeah.
But hey, man
So are God's.
But we've gotten to where we've gotten, right?
And the more youyou just gotta resist.
And the enemy's biggest leg up is that what they're doing is so focused, so diabolical,
so over-the-top that people just have real trouble grasping it, and they project their
own mindset onto the establishment.
And people don't want to face this.
People don't want to know the big truth.
They think that they can just deny it, and it's like a problem that's gonna go away.
It's a foul.
And so the more you resist, the quicker this is gonna be over with.
We're still gonna go through the fire.
But acquiescing to what's coming is going to destroy you.
So when I hear that, I hear something along the lines of like, you know, hey, let's all
burn.
Yeah.
The more you fight, the better it'll be.
So why not join an insurgency of some sort?
If I don't get what I want, everyone's going to die.
Yeah.
I mean, the fire.
I
It's a cleansing fire, as Alex has referred to it.
I want to throw a flag.
I want there to be a ten-yard penalty for him being like, people project onto the establishment
because things are too difficult for them to understand, and then they want to live
in denial.
I want to throw a flag on that.
You can't say it.
Yeah.
So Alex veers off from this path of like, fire.
We'll all live through the fire.
Fire will come.
He wants to hit on some of his sort of modern talking points, some of these villains.
All these articles about looking forward to the end of humanity, and Klaus Schwab is like,
it's going to be so good for you.
You are going to drink sewage.
These are actual quotes.
You are going to drink sewage and eat weeds, and there will not be any more people in it.
It's good for Earth, and again, you will be drinking this sewage.
He's saying this in German, by the way.
He only lives in German.
With a Russian accent, of course.
Most of his speeches are in other languages, but you can read the transcripts, it's in
the news today.
I'm not kidding.
So I think that's one of those things that's really easy to see through, like what he's
lying about.
These are direct quotes.
Well, I mean, it's like, yeah, okay.
I will feed you dog turds.
This is what you will do.
These are actual quotes, by the way.
Without-
I am telling you, I am in Germany, by the way.
I am a German man.
Without even doing any looking into any of this, it would be so easy for someone to be
like, oh yeah, he's talking about sewage treatment plants, turning that into potable water, and
the potential of weeds as being a cultivatable food source.
Think of turning things that we usually think of as not good into things that are good.
That's called progress.
Right, and weeds are things that grow without any human intervention.
If there were a way that you could turn that into food source, it would be amazing.
It would be something that would be really great.
Renewable water is something that will be increasingly important in the future.
Imagine if food was an invasive species, just food.
It's not like Klaus Schwab is coming in and being like, eat this dandelion and this cup
of piss.
I shall feed you all manner of poop.
Yeah, so silly.
Anyway, Alex is very serious.
Yes.
You're talking about foreign language speeches that Klaus Schwab gives, and his next subject
is just as serious.
I've already burned through this segment, I haven't got any of the clips I want to get
to.
We'll cover all the election fraud and that nightmare and where that's going next hour.
But everybody's flipping out about this video that's up on Infowars.com.
Flipping out.
From last night, we should probably repost the article.
But a COVID prediction from Project Runway in March of last year.
So a full 10, 11 months before it was even named that or on the radar.
But again, where do the globalists like to put stuff in fashion and in movies and in
culture?
I'm going to tell you, like some serial killers will do that.
This is so dumb.
You know what?
My instinct whenever somebody's like, uh, Project Runway predicts something in March
of last year is just to go, nah, get the fuck out of here.
But when it gets paid off with where do the globalists put things?
Fashion shows.
It's in Project Runway.
That's where they hide all of their secrets, Dan.
Yeah.
Bob comes up with an evil plan to make people eat sewage and then Tim Gunn says, make it
happen.
I think that's his catchphrase.
I can't remember.
Pretty sure.
Make it work.
That sounds right.
I think that's what it is.
I have not seen that show in a very long time.
But an ex of mine from years past loved that and I watched a fuck ton of that show.
Is that where you first heard about COVID?
What?
No, I didn't watch that season.
Oh, okay.
I looked into this though.
Of course you looked into it.
But there was a contestant whose name was COVID with a K, which is a Sanskrit word.
I'm already off the train.
And so there was a challenge called the head to toe challenge.
We had to make an outfit that involved the head to the feet.
An entire outfit.
All right.
So it's a guy named COVID creating a bodysuit.
Well, no, but the outfit involved a mask.
And so like COVID made a mask.
Yes.
Yeah.
I got it.
It's a fucking game show.
It is.
It's great.
We all have a great time.
It's a game show.
And if you wanted to take a really easy route, you could maybe make a hat, but the mask is
something that may be a little bit more adventurous, maybe a little more difficult to pull off
as an outfit.
And it just so happened that the person's name was COVID with a K, which is not the
same word.
Who cares?
Are you sure the globalist didn't plant a person named COVID to make a mask in order
to give us the cosmic realization that eventually a pandemic would be coming named COVID and
they will be using masks in order to turn us into their own models on project no fun
way.
Really, quite frankly, the laugh they're having is huge.
It's very large.
Yeah.
But you know what's also really interesting?
If it's anything like mine, it's very big.
You know what also is really interesting is they couldn't laugh unless Alex found out.
Like unless Alex reported on this, the globalists couldn't laugh about this.
It's a real bummer.
Yeah.
I don't think that's too subtle for anyone to get.
Oh, they need Alex.
Yeah.
They're in a terrible dance of death.
But Alex doesn't need them.
I really think he does.
They're demons.
They're vampires.
But he's a demon.
Well, but they're vampires.
Okay.
Well, that's true.
By the way, you know, there's paintings of Count Dracula, spitting image of Prince Charles.
So see, I could say a lot, I could do a lot here, but just you need to understand what
you're-
Blood drinking, child killing, pedophile murderers.
So you can either fight them or you can roll over and die to them.
Like Count Dracula.
But he wants to put his genetics into your blood.
He wants to defile you.
He wants to put his material into your cells and overwrite your cell, cell by cell.
It's not a flying saucer crashed out in Antarctica in the movie The Thing.
There are paintings of The Thing as well.
It's coming out of a Chinese laboratory.
No paintings.
It's not the movie The Hunger where they look under the microscope and they see the vampire
cell taking over the other cell.
I didn't see that one.
I'll have to check it out.
It's not a David Bowie movie.
Excellent film, by the way.
Which David Bowie movie?
It's the real world, boys and girls.
I want to hit two things here in a moment, but let me just do this.
I need money to fight this war.
Cool.
Love it.
I need money to fight these vampires.
Honestly, wooden stakes are expensive as hell.
And you should see the fucking garlic bills at Info War Studio.
You know, that's something that most vampire movies that have stuck with the old ways.
It's very cost effective.
You can find cheap stake material just about anywhere.
The later Blade movies where you have to have high tech stuff and the underworld movies
where you have to do all that stuff.
But even then, still, stays the same, basically.
Put a stake through its heart.
Sunlight, steak, garlic.
Garlic keeps them away.
Yeah.
I have a little garlic garlic.
You got a little garlic.
That's why we're...
Our studio's totally safe from vampires.
Totally vampire free.
Yeah.
I'm not scared of these things that Alex is really worried about, because I have some
garlic around.
I have garlic.
I've got wood.
We're good to go.
Yep.
And I have a not black cat.
That's true.
So...
Although Celine could be a vampire.
Yeah, probably.
She's drawn some blood.
She lost her eye to... could be a vampire fight.
Or she could have been fighting a lycanthrope.
Anyway, Alex, he ended that last clip with a plug, because of course he did.
And this leads to him doing a long plug, an ad, and also a convoluted story about why
he's not selling super blue anymore.
Eagle-eared listeners will remember that the reason is because he got a cease and desist
letter from the Attorney General of New York.
There's more to it than that.
Oh, there certainly is.
We have the charcoal toothpaste that's super high quality and concentrated.
That is amazing.
Turned your mouth black.
We had it in the pipeline for about a year and a half before we even started selling.
People said, well, will you stop selling your super blue and your whitening toothpaste?
Yeah, because the national media lied and said that I said it was a COVID cure and tried
to get me arrested.
And still trying, but after this and everything.
And the problem is if I sell it, they'll lie again and say, he's selling a cure.
And all these people flooded to buy it thinking it's a cure because they're saying it's cure.
Then they try to get affidavits from them thinking they bought a cure to indict me.
That's why we don't have that available for you.
Because of the criminal activity of the Democratic Party and Leticia James in New York.
I mean, these are savage mafia dons that murder old people in nursing homes on purpose.
I mean, I'm up against murderers.
I feel like if everybody's lying about how you're selling this stuff, that's not a reason
to stop.
They just don't do the things that they're saying.
Well, if you're not doing those things, then just keep selling the product.
If you have nothing to fear, then you have nothing to fear.
Like I don't give a shit.
There's no affidavit that someone could file that would say, I was under the impression
that this would stop me from getting COVID-19.
If you didn't do anything to make them think that, that affidavit would fail in court.
Then those affidavits directly quote you as having said something, and then they go and
they look and you said that stuff.
That's the reason to stop selling the stuff.
That's when you stop selling.
Yeah, yeah.
You wouldn't keep doing it if there was no problem.
Weird.
That's a problem, yeah.
So Alex doesn't mention this specifically on the episode, but Project Veritas has a
new little thing going on.
I didn't watch it because I don't care.
Don't care.
Fuck them.
Yeah.
Unfortunately, James O'Keefe may have gotten on a CNN morning editorial call and live streamed
it.
So he's like, yeah, Jeff Zucker coming for you.
We can get into the places where you think you're private and like...
And they're all like...
We have lawyers.
Could you not be here or we'll sue you?
I don't know what to tell you.
Get out!
I hope that doesn't blow up in James O'Keefe's face at all.
Really do.
Again, being facetious.
Get him.
Alex doesn't mention this stuff, but he does have a weird out of nowhere obsession with
Jeff Zucker.
Odd.
Which seems to be related.
Yeah.
Look at the photo of Jeff Zucker.
Looks just like Brian Stelter.
The little...
He's so in love with himself.
Just oh, he's so satisfied.
Oh, they drive him in a limo and oh, he makes millions of dollars and oh, he's Jeff Zucker.
He's a joke.
And by the way, he knows he's a joke.
A smug nobody.
And that's why he wants to bring you down.
He hates you when you have a good Christmas.
He hates...
He hates you when you pray to God.
He hates you because you've got a wonderful wife and children.
He will never be a good person because he is a filthy, degenerate sack of evil.
That's a little much.
Little much.
I can't say that that was intended to be antisemitic, but holy shit, is that trafficking and antisemitism.
That's dripping in classical.
He hates you when you have a good Christmas.
He loves it when you have a good birthday, but he hates it when you have a good Christmas.
So ridiculous.
Very neutral on Arbor Day.
I don't know.
I mean, I know that Jeff Zucker is somebody that Alex has brought up in the past.
He's not somebody who's a complete stranger to Alex's world, but he's definitely not someone
who's front and center for Alex.
No, he's right-wing du jour, if you will.
Yeah, but the focus is very glaring.
It's very apparent that like, oh, I'm going to try and catch some of the weak.
That's what I'm saying.
He's today's boogeyman.
But, I think that even Alex recognizes that James O'Keefe's stuff is best to stay away
from.
He didn't reference it this time.
Yeah, and he's not having James on, which he has all of these other times.
I think he's like, ugh.
This one might be too much.
I don't even know if it's like, consequences, it just might be like, I don't know, this
is a little soft.
That's fair.
Best to stay away, but let's kick Jeff Zucker.
Well, why not?
Yeah.
Alex thinks that the best way for Trump to remain president is to just do it.
I don't think Trump should even punt to the electors and the legislatures.
I think he should go with the American people, resolute desk, show all this evidence, and
say, stand with me, American people, say no to this.
I know I'm going to D.C. on the 12th.
I know I'm going to that event, and by the way, I'm taking that big march over.
We started it before.
These women hijacked it.
Now they're saying it again.
You can't even hear them on their microphone when 500,000 are there.
I'll be there.
We'll march to the White House.
It's going to be great.
I'll see you there.
There weren't 500,000 people there.
Also, you co-opted their event.
Yeah.
They had the permit.
They were there.
They organized the event.
They did all the work.
Yeah, you might have brought some people.
You drove there.
Good for you.
Attracting a crowd.
You still stole their event, and you're going to do that again and pretend that they're
stealing your event when they organized it and have the permits.
Holy shit.
So yeah, I think that Alex is on his way to another Tea Party, and I think it's interesting
that we know his trends.
We know his patterns of behavior.
We know what he did with the Tea Party, more or less, claiming that they were co-opting
his movement and what have you.
And I think you can see it happening a little bit again, on a smaller scale, at least at
this point, because the people who are having these rallies in DC are just sort of remnants
of Tea Party people.
They just don't dress up as fun anymore.
Yeah, now we're at a point where Alex is probably more hooked up with the fringe and the sizable
crowds.
True.
So he might actually be able to co-op them far more successfully than his attempts to
take over Glenn Beck's shit, when Glenn Beck was on TV and Alex was the voice in the woods.
But, I think one of the parts of what Alex, you know, his credibility now is he's best
friends with Roger Stone.
And just like we had Steve come in on December 1st, now we have Steve.
Now we have different Steve.
Other Steve.
Yes.
You'll understand why that slip of the tongue happened, because Roger's swinging.
Okay, good.
But, and for the fences, I don't mean like a Liberty.
No, no, no, no.
He's going for it.
Um, the first clip is the bad kind of a swing and that is, uh, Hey man, yeah, fucking martial
law.
Cool.
Great.
Uh, and I think the president has to have all options on the table as to how he proceeds.
The one thing he cannot do, Alex, is quit.
He has powerful forces arrayed against him.
Uh, it is, uh, it is extraordinary.
Let's call them the armies of the Pharaoh, the Pharaoh's armies.
Uh, but this is God's nation.
I believe he was selected for God for this job.
I pray to God every day that he will not, uh, not only not quit, but he will be strengthened
in his resolve.
Yeah.
Go tell Nixon about it.
Oh boy.
I just love the idea of like, Hey Roger, uh, like in, you know, like the seventies and
go back there and be like, this is going to be you.
This is going to be you.
God chose you for this.
Live your life.
Shit bag.
Yeah.
Enjoy the next 40 years of your life.
Knowing that this is what you end up.
Oh, that would be great.
This next clip.
Jordan.
Yes.
Maybe one of my favorite swings.
Mm hmm.
I can't like, Steve's had some big ones just about himself.
Like most of Steve's stuff is like really braggadocio.
It's really just, I am the most important person.
I've done everything important.
Yeah.
I overthrew a Ghana twice.
And then when Steve comes in, man, Roger comes in again.
You're doing it again.
Well, it's because of the swing.
Okay.
Let's hear it.
I just learned of, uh, absolute incontrovertible evidence of North Korean boats delivering,
uh, ballots through a Harbor in Maine.
Yes.
The state agreed.
Uh, if this checks out, if law enforcement looked, if this checks out to be true, it
would be proof of foreign involvement in the election.
This is North Korean.
This is the best North Korean boat.
Let me walk through this.
Our North Korean.
They arrived in Maine, Maine to deliver North.
Hold on.
Okay.
In the world.
They had to come by boat to deliver this fake ballot.
Man.
So the number of questions raises brings this claim into the territory of farce.
That is a swing.
That is a swing for the fences.
If this is a sprawling conspiracy involving tons of countries and us actors, why did North
Korea have the ballots?
Why couldn't they have been printed domestically?
Why would these conspirators need to print the ballots in North Korea?
Then have the country that's under the heaviest surveillance and under very strict embargoes
carry out a delivery by sea, which would obviously raise alarms no matter what the cargo was.
Also you were sort of, why would they arrive in Maine?
Does Roger not realize that in order for a North Korean boat to reach Maine, they would
need to either navigate South of Africa, then head North or transit through the Panama canal.
North Korea would have a much easier, but still almost ridiculously impossible time
getting a boat to the West coast, like some state on the West coast, since they're shorelines
on the sea of Japan, which leads to the Pacific ocean.
If we're just imagining that these North Korean boats can show up wherever they want, then
why wouldn't they go to Hawaii?
That's definitely their closest shot.
Literally, there could not be a more complicated coastal state for North Korea to get to than
Maine by boat.
How did he choose that one?
So if this is true, shouldn't this be intensely embarrassing for Trump?
Like that dude bent over backwards trying to impress and appease Kim Jong Un, and now
in Trump's hour of need, his dictator buddy sends a boat full of ballots halfway across
the world to screw him over.
That seems like an indication that Trump's deal making skills are what the cracked up
to be.
I mean this sincerely, Jordan.
This is the most amazingly stupid theory that I think I've ever heard someone suggest on
Infowars.
I've never heard anything like this in my entire life.
There have been dumber theories, I think, but this is something that Roger is suggesting
as being supported by, quote, absolute incontrovertible.
I am more likely to believe the earth is flat than that North Korea could successfully secretly
get boats to Maine, period.
Full of ballots.
No, I don't.
I mean, even like a dinghy, a dinghy with North Korea printed on the side of it couldn't
get to Maine from North Korea.
That is insane.
If North Koreans could get, like if the state of North Korea could get boats full of ballots
to Maine, why are we worried about their rocket program?
Like they could just bring a bomb.
North Koreans just fucking lift a bomb into Maine and then walk away and get on their
boats and click a button and like, haha, we've defeated you Americans.
I feel like Roger's acting like the surveillance on North Korea is just like a guy asleep.
It must be.
Just in front of a bunch of monitors.
No, no, no.
They put a picture of the room that they were supposed to be monitoring in the camera so
it looks like that the...
But it's not.
It's a picture on top of the camera.
I'm baffled by this, but I do think that this is the kind of thing you can get someone to
say whenever you get them out of prison.
Yep.
This is the kind of...
Yeah, sure.
You can do whatever the fuck you want, man.
Yeah, hey man, you were destined to be here by God and North Korean boats are the only
reason you lost the election.
They showed up in Maine and fucked you over.
Hey buddy, I got takeout last night instead of being in jail, so guess what?
North Korea did it to Maine.
Don't care.
Moving on.
It's awesome too because someone had to have made this up and that means that someone made
up a story with the stupidest stake.
There can't possibly be something else that this is based on.
I don't know.
Sell me on a thoroughly controvertible document.
I tried to look for some indication of what the fuck Roger was talking about and any story
that I could find had to do with Roger saying this.
So I don't know.
Okay.
I don't know.
Maybe it's some deep thing on Twitter I couldn't find.
That's a big swing.
I wouldn't be surprised if this was another QAnon thing, quite frankly, but just like
god damn.
Roger, buddy.
Say it out loud.
Buddy, Roger.
Put a globe in front of you and then just don't give me any documents.
Put a globe on your desk and just point to how they got there.
Show me how they both got there.
Just with your finger.
Did it go north?
I'm not asking for details.
Did it go above China and Russia?
Do your best.
Through the arctic?
Yeah, I don't care.
Did it go up there?
There are actual shipping lanes.
Just do your best.
Did it go down?
Maybe try to get through the Straits of Gibraltar?
Maybe try to get into the Mediterranean and then go through there?
Very serious question.
Did it go through the earth?
I think that the only state it would be more difficult to get a boat to is Kansas.
Because it's in the middle of the fucking country.
Because it would take a huge wave to get in there.
Really have to get up there.
It's a fucking black rock or some shit.
Fitzcarraldo is easier to say.
Yes, exactly.
It's a better reference than my lost reference.
So that's silly.
And Roger is dumb.
Very silly.
But this next clip of Roger is like, hey man, you've forgotten the script.
I have a very high regard for Sidney Powell.
I have an equally high regard for my old friend, Mayor Rudy Giuliani, who I've had a friendship
with since his first campaign for mayor of New York City.
Hey guy, didn't Rudy cover up 9-11?
No, no, no, no.
Forgiven, passing on, moving on.
Don't worry about it.
So Roger also thinks that Trump supporters need to get aggressive and they need to force
legislatures to just say, hey, Trump's cool, let him stay president.
And then we get a very familiar phenomenon.
And I think supporters of the president in the key states need to begin now contacting
your Republican state legislators.
Those are your Republican state senators or your state representatives.
Some states, they call them assemblies and urge them to support the president, to support
an objective and honest count of the election and the certification of electors that will
support Donald Trump at the electoral college.
The Stonewalling, there's no evidence, is ridiculous.
Yeah, it sure is.
How's that sandwich?
Stonewalling is strong.
So Alex-
Do more of the German guy again.
Alex bids farewell to Roger and he doesn't add, and he talks about how he has a promo
code.
You put Patriot on the website, you get 10% more off, and he's like, I never do promo
codes.
And I started to think about it like, I don't think I have heard him do a promo code.
Well, that's a good question.
Because I think I would have made fun of it.
I think so.
I think I would have made fun of whatever word he chose to be the promo code.
I think we would have gotten there sooner or later, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't feel like he does do promo codes very often.
I can't think of a time where we've made fun of him.
That's interesting.
I don't know what that means, but he then gets into talking about how you need-
It means you get an extra 10% off, buddy.
I'm not buying shit.
Oh, okay.
You need fish oil.
Yes, you do.
And so do your kids.
Sure, they do.
Wait, can they choose to take fish oil?
Promo code Patriot, emplorestore.com.
Just want to remind you, you're the reason we're on air.
Thank you.
These are great products you and your family need, especially for children, man.
This fish oil is so good for children.
So good for everybody.
But man, I tell you what it does for their brains.
It's what your brain literally runs on.
It's like the perfect thing compared to like sugar.
Sugar's horrible for your brain.
This is what it actually runs on, but I'm digressing.
Yeah.
I don't know if it's like fish oil or sugar.
I don't know if those are the-
It's fish oil or sugar.
It is not glucose.
It is not Omega-3s or whatever you would like.
It is either a big bowl of fish oil-
I can't imagine a conversation between parents.
One of them's Alex and he's like, yeah, you should give your kids fish oil.
And the other parent's like, no, we're going with sugar.
I give them sugar pills every morning, about twice a day.
Just concentrated stuff though.
So at this point in the episode, Alex realizes that Lynn Wood, the attorney, is doing the
press conference.
Yes.
Bat shit.
Quite.
Yeah.
Absolute wild bat shit.
And so Alex goes to it live and I was like, holy shit.
I love it.
1776, we'll commence again.
We're going to send that message.
We're going to send that message to George Soros.
Get out of our country George Soros.
He's not here.
Oh shit.
This is so scary.
I mean, we're laughing, but that's fucking terrifying.
No, no, no.
Yeah.
That's fucking, yeah, that is a Hitler rally.
That's not a non Hitler rally.
That is a Hitler rally where Hitler would Hitler, get out of our country.
Hitler rally.
Hitler.
Poor Hitler.
That is five Hitler mustaches, Dan.
On a scale of one to five.
On a scale of one to five mustaches.
I think it's four just because you got to leave some room.
That's true.
There's more Hitler to be done.
Yeah.
So Lynn Wood gets around to talking about, hey, hey, look, the media.
Bad.
Sure.
There's there are places that are good though.
Oh, well, that's good to know.
Yeah.
Especially because this is being broadcast live on info wars.
Yes.
Now everybody's been reading the media.
Stop.
It's a lie.
You can't trust them.
Stick with OAN and Newsmax.
They tell you the truth.
Read the Epoch Times.
We'll never say I'm bored.
This is a battle between good and evil.
They'll never say info wars were too powerful.
That is sad.
That is so sad.
Even fucking crazy people with nothing to lose are no better than to associate themselves
with that.
So sad.
The dude would have no problem saying info wars if he actually thought they were worth
a damn.
Yep.
Oh my God.
If they thought info wars was going to grow, they would say info wars immediately.
You know what's a better propagandist right now?
Coat rack.
Yeah.
Just a random person.
Yep.
A random face that is shaved and in a suit is better than Alex.
This coat rack has done a great job of being there, not talking, which is better than Alex
Jones.
Yeah.
A random person who doesn't have the intense baggage that Alex has.
Oh, let's see.
Someone who doesn't have to fucking pretend that the president's son told him to investigate
something.
Someone who's not an embarrassing sack.
Yeah.
Um, anyway, uh, Alex is like, yeah, we'll go back to it.
We'll go back to this.
We'll jump back and forth.
I got to take some calls.
I'll take some calls.
So this, uh, this caller, he decides that, uh, war is coming.
But like Dr. P says, Dr. Prochnik is the art of war and God has drawn out the enemy.
Now they are completely exposed, completely uncovered, and there's nothing that they can
do.
And Trump doesn't have to do another thing.
We, the people will do the rest, like Glenwood or like Glenwood just said.
And so I would say this, the declaration of war date is January 11th, 2021, according
to the executive order that was revived September 12th, 2020 Trump knows what's up, but do we
know what's up?
Are we ready?
Are we the people ready to take this country back from the globalist that have controlled
it since the 18.
So you're saying he's not up there commanding the forces that he wants it to be organic.
He's leaving it in our hands.
I hear you.
I think that's what he's doing.
Yeah.
Well, we better hit the streets and like Linwood's doing it, like we're doing, trying to find
meaning in your lack of leadership.
Yep.
He wants us to be a revolution.
Violent.
Wow.
So, uh, Rogan is everybody always want to fight a war.
It's 2020.
We can't outsmart these idiots.
What are we doing?
Fighting a war.
What are you doing?
Look, humans are not 50 years old.
Look, the issue is that Rogan's coming up tomorrow.
Sure.
Now it's promotes that.
And then the show takes the leftist of left turns, rightist of right turns as I'm not
positive.
It's just a crazy turn out of left field.
Joe Rogan is on the show tomorrow.
Yep.
Right here in studio.
So look for that.
And a lot of other surprises.
You know, I've known Steve Pacinik for, I'm sorry, what?
And I knew he was in the CFR and I knew that, uh, he did run the overthrow of multiple governments.
That's in the congressional record and a lot of other things.
And pretty much everything you ever told me turned out to be very accurate.
But I just, I believe he was told by high level folks in the CIA that Trump's done this
thing and they're all going to the global struggle.
I just wonder if they're feeding him a lot of bull because man, I mean, you saw what
Barr came out and did and everything else.
I just, I'm not up here saying we're out of the woods and I, and I'm not up here saying
that I'm not disagreeing with him.
I'm not saying I think he's a disingenuous person or a liar.
I just, you know, I have a bad feeling.
Yeah.
So Alex is, uh, is, uh, this is, this is weird because he did say that Steve was still working
for the CIA after the Las Vegas shooting when Steve tried to convince him that no one died
and it was all fake.
Um, so now, uh, he's trying to retain Steve's credibility, but just, he's been fooled by
high level CIA people.
He's trying to, he's trying to have his cake and eat it too here and it's just not good.
You gotta cut ties or you gotta lean in.
You can't half ass with, uh, Stevie P's.
But I do, I do kind of feel like, yeah, good call.
Good call.
Like knowing at least that you can't agree with him.
This one might be too, this one might be too much even for, even for us.
Well, because it's, again, David Knight just texted me mean language.
But it's also like what we talked about on the first time this came up.
It's too falsifiable when this never comes up, uh, up, it's like, Oh, what happened?
I thought the election was a fucking sting operation.
All the proof should be there.
Where is it?
Yeah.
It's, it's a disappointing game.
But look, Steve might be wrong because people might be lying to us.
True.
But there's one thing that's totally true.
What's that?
I mean, he wasn't joking, um, when he said China called him a pachinik has sent me video
and photos when he's in North Korea, hanging out with the North Koreans.
I mean, he gets around folks and so I'll just leave it at that.
He took a boat, uh, but, uh, from Florida to North Korea, he says Beijing, you know,
high level operatives called him and they're like, yeah, I know.
We know Trump's going to win.
You notice Putin won't congratulate Biden, man.
This is really sad.
Yeah.
Steve, Steve is like, Oh, well, man, you know, maybe, maybe he's wrong about all this, but
China did call him because I've been courted.
Shut up.
You can't even get it up for Steve pajana getting a call from China.
No, I've seen him.
He was in North Korea one time.
Hey, it's funny that you bring up, uh, getting it up.
I can't take super volatility.
I obviously don't need it.
Uh, but I mean, I don't want to get graphic as a family show, but I don't need to be walking
around with, you know, something going on downstairs.
Okay.
I mean, I, I mean, I take it, I mean, it's ridiculous.
It's like waking up at 4 0 AM or 5 0 AM, you know, you've, you've got a, an erection.
Is super male vitality actually just like straight up bull hormones?
What the fuck is it?
Every time we hear about it, it's like, Oh yeah, yeah.
His wife walks bow legged.
So buy this fucking boner.
I love it.
I've never heard, I've never heard that moment happen.
That moment of Alex being forced to say the word erection.
That is so awful.
It really was gross.
I have cursed all of you with that.
I was trying not to focus on it.
So Alex goes back to calls and uh, he's, he's sitting here and he's like, he's having a
good time with this caller because this caller is speculating that, Hey man, these globalists
they're so out of control, they'll probably let China grounded invade us.
Sure.
Right.
That's probably what they're going to do in boats.
And because Alex was so excited about this, he accidentally let this guy keep talking.
These go, there's a man who's so corrupt, they so dangerous that they don't, I think
they're going to let China invade.
I can just say, they want to break this.
They are foaming at the mouth to kill us because it's a spiritual thing.
I agree.
Tell me what your gut tells you.
Oh man, it's going to fall like Ukraine and go by to get in.
He's going to go against the American Patriots, the white people of the country that he hates.
They hate us.
That's why they robbed the whole, uh, belt, uh, with the votes.
All the white people right there voted Trump is we've seen it that night, but he's going
to cause war against the white Patriots soon as he get in office and then maybe I think
no, I agree to try to trick white people to attack black people.
No, it ain't about black and white because I'm saying they're trying to trick us to kill
each other though.
Yeah, but black people won't, they know what's going on.
But uh, these people that sent top, they don't like their own color, man.
They want to kill y'all.
Oh boy.
Alex, you should have pretended he hung up.
I am not comfortable in this conversation.
This caller who I've had a great time talking to has now revealed that he believes that
the Patriots are the white people.
It's very clear.
Uh, I um, it is fun where he's, he's like, no, no, I'm doing a good job.
I'm saying what you're saying.
All the Patriots are the white people.
And he's like, no, no, you're not supposed to actually say that.
And so Alex tries to save it by being like, yeah, they're trying to get the white people
to foolishly attack the black people.
No, no, no, no.
Black people are fine.
It's not about white people.
So Alex gets, uh, gets back from commercial break and I will say that, uh, you belong
to the city.
Did play once during this episode and Alex didn't get enthusiastic about it.
However, Gnarls Barkley, uh, the song crazy sure plays and Alex does get a little excited
for this.
It is not the destination.
It is the journey.
It's a test, my friends.
And it's real.
It's my only advice, Jeff sucker, look at you, you think you're in control?
Don't do it.
You might've noticed that the song skip there and that's good as Alex said, you guys are
in control of the bleep button at the wrong time.
So the shit went out over the air and a little cut, skip the part where he says, drop that.
Yep.
Yeah.
You got really into it.
I do like him that that's probably the most unhinged I've heard anyone sound in a good
long while.
That was, that was out there.
Yeah.
So Alex, uh, you know, he's into predictive programming and loves, uh, when it loves people
to say that movies are reality.
This is a new one for me.
Hey, Hey Alex, two things here.
Number one, if you remember a movie that came out in 2006, man of the year, Robin Williams,
they had an election, the voting machines switched the election and switched your results
to the candidate that was less desirable, just like what's happening right now.
That's right.
That's a good movie.
It's set in Latin America.
Correct.
Good conversation.
Hey, there's this movie that it's real.
These people just cannot believe for one second that the guy for the past four years, they
have heard nothing but horrible shit about from one huge section of the country.
They can't believe that that guy might not be beloved.
Well, no, because they haven't heard that.
It's all the mainstream media that's creating this false perception that no one likes Trump.
Okay.
That's fine.
Yeah, I mean, I guess that everybody in this world lives in their own bubble where they
don't have to deal with like reality at all, but I mean, you can't go out, you can't walk
down the street and not be like, Oh, a lot of people hate Trump.
Well, it's, it's kind of, you know, it's an interesting line that I struggle with sometimes
or at least I have in the past and that is that like, you can recognize that organizations
like the Koch brothers and stuff, they do fund things massively on the right, astroturf
stuff.
But knowing that you cannot say that people don't believe conservative principles or values
or have right leaning politics.
You can't say that all that's fake because there is this libertarian monied interest
that's floating in and trying to push things that way.
This same is sort of the trap that Alex and a lot of the Trump folk fall into, which is
like they think that the media is just telling everyone that Trump is bad.
And then they're sort of thinking that no one actually believes that the media is crumbling
and it's powerless and it's pathetic and everyone knows they're liars now.
Yeah.
But yeah, so that's kind of the trap that they're in.
I mean, I guess when you, I suppose if you dehumanize enough people or a large enough
group, then eventually people who know who are like, Oh no, I know plenty of people who
would normally fall into that group.
They must secretly be Trump supporters too or something because it's like, how can I,
I don't know.
These, this is nuts.
Yeah.
Wild.
So this caller believes that Biden, if he gets in, Kamala Harris will become president.
Biden will get out of there somehow.
Sure.
And then he'll trip and fall and wear an ankle bracelet.
And then Kamala Harris will make either AOC or Hillary, there we go, vice president.
And then Alex asks the most introspective question I could imagine.
All right.
If Biden stays in within six months, he's going to have a stroke or he's going to be
declared incompetent, which is going to move Kamala Harris into the president's spot.
And she's going to either put either AOC or Hillary Clinton in as her vice president.
Why?
That it would be the absolute worst scenario for this country if that would happen.
Why is there such a cult of Hillary?
Is this, is she such a devil worshiper like the demon that's able to inhabit her is like
they worship her.
Yeah.
Why is the left so obsessed with Hillary Clinton?
Yes.
Why are we the left obsessed, obsessed with him?
We just can't stop talking about Hillary, Dan.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's pretty, pretty cool.
Pretty cool.
I don't know if projection gets that loud.
No.
That's the most loud.
So this, Alex gets another caller and this dude says that they're going to take over
DC.
Sure.
Right?
There's going to be a protest.
Yeah.
Millions.
This is where I probably not going to do this, but now I do have the opportunity.
I don't know if I could do it safely, but if Alex did this, I would want to go make
a documentary about it.
Okay.
I really, really will.
I already have the website ready to go.
Take over DC.com.
Love it.
We're going to do with what you guys did.
However, everybody needs to be out there.
We need to set up supply lines.
We need to camp.
We need to take care of those.
Come out there.
No, I agree.
In fact, I've already decided.
I'm moving into DC.
Yes.
They let the homeless camp everywhere, but oh, watch, they'll say no.
I'm moving in to the Lincoln Memorial.
I'm moving in there.
I'm going to live in DC.
I would love to go and document Alex's time at the Lincoln Memorial squatting.
No, if you are listening to this and you have $5, I don't know where I was going to end
that.
We need a billion dollars to make that documentary is what I'm saying.
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't want anybody to give money to make a documentary.
No, I was going the way wrong way in my head.
I just don't think I can do it because just logistics of the world.
But I think that there's, there's such an amazing story to be told here if Alex were
to go.
And that is that he would realize that it's winter in DC and here we go home.
Here we go.
This is what I got for you.
We got to get Ken Burns in on this.
We got to get Ken Burns.
We got to get everybody.
Yeah, totally.
Bring back Ronson.
Uh, it gets, uh, Louis Thoreau.
Get Hertzog.
No, well, who better than Hertzog?
This is Grizzly Man 2, the grizzliest.
Alex eats Owen Shroyer.
It's too cold in DC.
It's too cold in DC!
Or Owen Shroyer skins Alex and wears him like a blanket.
Day two, Alex is trying to make a fire out of his femurs.
Owen's trying to light a fire with Owen's feet.
Now I heard that you can use whale fat, so maybe you can use Owen fat.
Owen was warned spiritually when I said that I would eat my neighbors.
So cosmically this is okay.
It's cool.
I think that there is such an amazing potential in my brain for, like, what this looks like
in the real world.
Alex isn't going to do this.
No, obviously not.
If he did this, he would stay at a hotel nearby and show up and yell in a bull horn every
now and again.
He would never stay.
It's not going to be over 40 degrees until March.
Nope, nope, nope.
Not gonna happen.
DC.
Average temperatures.
Low.
It's cold.
It's winter.
He's not going to go out there and camp out at the Lincoln Memorial?
He doesn't believe this shit.
Nope.
But I would love it.
I would love it.
I would...
I...
Man, I wish I was a millionaire.
If I was a millionaire, here's what I would do.
What would you do?
I would say, Alex, giant donation.
But you have to do this.
You have to yourself.
Not any of your staff.
You have to stay out there as long as this encampment lasts.
And much like maybe some MTV show from the early 2000s, you get paid more the longer
you stay out there.
I like it.
And all on camera.
Yeah.
Because I want to see your misery.
I want to see you camping out fucking pissed off at three in the morning so mad that only
2,000 people showed up to your encampment.
This needs to be fat bear.
There needs to be 24-7 live streams of everybody like making wagers and shit.
Like this should all be...
This should be on Bet365 daily.
This is what I'm talking about though.
Like I probably would not go for the sake of safety and just responsibility in the present
world we live in.
Under ideal circumstances, I would love to go and make a documentary about this.
The best I could do is if he actually does this and they actually have feeds, fuck, I
might be tempted to do nonstop coverage of it.
Like waiting for him to break.
But he wouldn't break.
It would be so disappointing.
It would end up being like two minutes of Alex yelling in a bullhorn and then Harrison
Smith in the studio or some shit.
And there'd be an excuse for why he has to leave right away so he wouldn't lose all face.
Family stuff.
Yeah, totally.
Totally.
Yep.
All of a sudden COVID will be real.
This is just another time, and it sucks because we've done this enough, that it's another
time that I see this amazing potential in what could come and it's not going to.
I'm preemptively disappointed in it.
I know it's not going to be great.
I remember it's the same thing I felt like the second time I heard there was a marathon.
The first time, I thought like, oh my god, 12 hours, he's gonna be gassed by hour three.
And then it's like, oh, hour three, David Knight's hosting.
Oh no.
And then the second time I'm like, it's not gonna be good.
Now I'm just like a caravan fucked me.
Everything just sucks.
Alex going to Georgia sucked.
I might have to write a song about Alex camping out in DC.
Now here's the problem.
When we make a show about an exhaustive failure who fails exhaustively all of the time, it's
hard for us to expect him to succeed.
But you kind of have to always...
Yeah, you always hope Charlie Brown's going to kick that fucking ball, man.
You have to come in with a little optimism or else, you know, it's a slog.
Otherwise, then you'll never try and kick the ball again.
So I beg you, Alex, please.
Do it.
You'll save America.
We will create a documentary for free.
You will save America single-handedly if you camp out at the Lincoln Memorial through the
winter.
And if you eat fish and try and get as fat as possible.
Yeah.
Come on.
That's so good.
Yeah.
So we have one last clip here and it's a caller who's threatening to shut down Biden
inauguration.
Okay.
He's going real deep right now.
I see him doing something major before.
I mean, he'll probably wait until their fake inauguration of Biden.
It ain't going to be in DC because we're going to shut that down.
They're probably going to do it in California or New York City.
It's going to be something.
Listen, I need everybody out there to understand me because I'm a major target.
I'm not trying to act fancy pants, but let me tell you, I put my ass on the line, my
skin of the game.
Okay.
I'm going to be there on the 12th.
I want people there.
And I'm going to be there on the 20th come hell or high water.
So you got my commitment and they told me, don't you show your ass back in DC.
Well, I'm coming.
And so you go ahead and do whatever you want.
Now that's what God wants.
He strike me down.
I'll become more powerful than you can possibly imagine.
The quote Obi Wan Kenobi.
You don't get to quote the Jedis.
No, no, no.
You're the bad guy.
Remember your favorite guy is literally the emperor.
Yeah.
You don't get to do that.
That's not fair.
Jerk.
See, now that would be, that would be acceptable on his, uh, I'm joining the dark side episode
where he quotes Obi Wan the whole time.
Yeah, that would make sense.
And he comes into the show with just swelling strings out.
That would be fitting.
Yeah.
That'd be great.
So I don't think Alex is going to follow through with this.
I think he's going to go do some publicity stunts in DC.
He said he's going to be there on the 12th, which is when that rally he's going to co-opt
is.
Yeah.
The 20th inauguration.
I could see him going to that as well and trying to cause a scene.
But when would the, when would the camping be?
Would it be on the 12th?
Would it start on the 12th and then go through the inauguration because that's what it should
be.
Set up a goddamn Zephyr.
No chance.
Get out there and broadcast from the Lincoln Memorial.
He eats more sandwiches in a day than he will spend hours on that mall.
This makes me sad.
I want it to happen and I'm not going to allow myself to believe that it's not going to happen
yet.
There's a chance.
Yes.
There's always the chance.
Hope springs eternal.
It's still Schrodinger's occupation at this point, so we will see.
Until we're allowed to observe it.
Yeah.
And another thing that's Schrodinger's, we have Schrodinger's Monday's episode.
Oh, that's true.
It could be a Rogan episode.
Could be.
Could not be.
At this point, it is both.
It is.
It is simultaneously an episode about Rogan and not and you'll have to tune in on Monday
to find out.
That sounds like something I would hear on the Joe Rogan show.
Head exploding.
It is both at the same time.
Yeah.
Also, how about, I can't remember what his sponsors were.
Damn it.
Wasn't there a toilet one, Schwifty?
No, that's Rick and Morty.
I don't remember.
Flushie.
No, Tushie.
Who knows.
Anyway, we'll be back, Jordan, but until then, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
You bet.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at Knowledge Dungeon Door Fight and at Go To Bed Jordan.
Yep.
We're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook.
If you could, please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work.
Yep.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZXClark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I'm a North Korean ballot tugboat captain.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.