N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Damn, Ed, Jordan, I am SWEATING
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledgefight
knowledgefight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Shang, we are the bad guys, knowledgefight
Dan and Jordan, knowledgefight
Rattle her, rattle her, rattle her
Need, I need money
Andy and Kansas, Andy and, Andy and
Stop it, Andy and Kansas, Andy and Kansas
Andy and, Andy and, it's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan
I love your work
knowledgefight
N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're a couple dudes, like to sit around, drink novelty
beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are Dan
Jordan
Dan, quick question for ya
Sure, hit me
What's your bright spot this week?
My bright spot today is, so I've not taken part in too much
of like ordering food from places
Sure, sure, sure
I've tried to keep that limited because it's expensive and stuff
and I like to keep things kind of special
Right
But I realized that I hadn't had Taco Bell in a long time
and so I decided to order some Taco Bell delivery
Which is a nice thing
Reliving those comic days
I couldn't imagine that being something you could do
Well I ordered Taco Bell
Oh totally, totally
It's like pizzas delivered, Chinese foods delivered, and that is it
Yep, yep
Um, so that was kind of fun
But I noticed something on the menu that I had never seen before
It was like an aged cheddar chalupa
Okay
And so it was like a chalupa kind of thing, but it had like cheese
Yeah
Like as if, you know, it's like an Asiago cheese crust
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I do always like it when the fast food all of a sudden is like
Ah, this is our artisan aged cheese
Very ambitious, very pretentious
Yeah
But I had to try it because, you know, you got to
And it was so good
It was also terrible
Yeah, of course, of course
I got it and was like, oh wow, this crunchiness of the cheese is really complimenting the
I'm like, what am I thinking?
What are you doing? What am I doing here?
It's fucking Taco Bell
Why am I fucking
Highfalutin' ass Taco Bell
Is this the Great British Baking Show? Come on now
Yeah, but I enjoyed it quite a bit and, you know, you got to find the light where it exists
Yeah, that's great, that's great
How about you?
Uh, I won't provide too many spoilers here, but Dan, as you might be aware
I'm a bit of a fan of Star Wars
Yes
Have you heard of Star Wars?
Yes I have
Okay, it's pretty good
That's the one with the Enterprise, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, the one with the Enterprise, the guys that have the uniforms, it's great
It's great
Ferengis
Yeah, yeah, yeah, got little things on his head
There's that guy Q who's now ruining our world
Oh no, is that where he came from?
I don't know
So yeah, Mandalorian, huge fan watching it
Baby Yoda
And yes, Baby Yoda
See, I can have conversations
He has a name now
Oh boy
Oh yeah, yeah, trouble
Should I try and guess it?
I think you should
Okay, Pete
No, really close though
Grogu
Very close to Pete
Grogu?
Grogu, I know, it's Baby Yoda forever
That's a Star Wars name
Everyone agrees that it's Baby Yoda forever
Right, yeah
Grogu
But, again, no spoilers
Except for the name of Baby Yoda, that's a spoiler
No, that's not a spoiler, you find out, that was last episode
So that was a while back
Okay, it's a spoiler in case you're a week behind
Also, is it a spoiler to know Grogu is his name?
You immediately forget Grogu and you're like, that's Baby Yoda
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, no one cares
Not my Grogu
Hashtag
No, so this episode, most recent one, a character came back who made me extremely,
extremely happy in a very lovely way
The second season has been basically, like, do you remember Fun Dip?
I don't want to be like a dick in case it's right
Uh-huh, but my instinct is to joke that it's Jar Jar Binks
Ooh, no!
Okay
No, no, no
Beloved is...
He's a great character
No, uh, shit, where was I?
You just broke my conversation
Oh, yeah, the second season has been Fun Dip
You know, it's the sugar stick that you're dipping in more sugar to eat
Like, everything has been junk food and it has been incredible
and I love it so much
That metaphor falls apart because Fun Dip sucks
Yeah, Fun Dip does suck
I mean, it's a sugar overload is my point
But it's all just sugar
Even as a kid, I didn't want any Fun Dip
Oh, I loved Fun Dip
Come on, man
That stick was disgusting
I chewed on that stick like it was my friend
Like it was a milk bone and you were a stray dog
Exactly
Well, I'm glad you're enjoying that
It's delicious
I feel like my plan is, uh, watch The Mandalorian once there's, like, five seasons of it
Yeah, yeah, yeah
And I can just watch it all
It's great
Yeah, I have this- I have that relationship with TV shows
Like, I want there to be multiple seasons of it that I can binge
Because if I like it, I don't want to stop watching it
Who was- I know Netflix was the first place to, like, just release the whole thing
Was it, like, Daredevil or something that was the first show where they're like
We're putting all 12 episodes out
And then I've never- I'm no longer able to watch episodic television
Yeah, I- it started earlier than that for me
Yeah
Or at least, like, the challenge of it
And I think it's because I- what I would do is I would come to shows late
Because I don't buy the hype and I don't want to get tricked by, like, people saying
This is the best thing ever
I like that's your relationship
Well, I don't want to get-
I don't want to get tricked by these liars who like stuff
A lot of television is reliant on cliffhanger-y nonsense
Sure, that's true
Especially hour-long dramas
Right, right, right
And so if you're watching it week to week
Like, the experience of that is so much more engrossing
And it can trick you into liking things that you don't actually like all that much
That's true
So I always try and give things a little bit of time
Give it a little space
Yeah, and so, like, Lost I started in, like, season four or something like that
And the experience of watching the prior three seasons, like, all in a row was pretty gratifying
Yeah, I think that happens to a lot of people with, like, The Wire
Where they're like, it takes three episodes to get into it
And I imagine if I started watching episodically
I'd watch the first episode and be like, eh, I'm good
Yeah
You know?
I don't know if you'd say I'm good, but it would be a different experience
Yeah, yeah, yeah
It would be harder
But yeah, anyway
Television, models have changed
Yes, this is us, commentary, cultural, it's amazing
So, Jordan, today we've got an episode to go over
We're going to be talking about December 3rd and 4th, 2020
I'm Dan, this is 2020
Hey! 2020 is great forever now
Yay!
I started listening to the episode with Rogan
Alex's interview, a four-hour long interview with Joe Rogan
Riveting stuff they talked about
They were stoned in the first minute
Just policy, real questions getting into the nitty-gritty of universal basic income
I made it, like, 15 minutes in and I was like, I'll do an episode about this eventually, probably
But, like, it's so annoying
It's so...
To give you some context, like, Alex's first real question he asks is, like,
at what point did you realize that you were, like, really famous,
but you can do whatever you want to do?
That's a great question
And Rogan's answer is something along the lines of, like,
you know what I like about smoking weed is it makes me think about more interesting things
That is a fair point
Almost a way of, like, yeah, that's a dumb question
That's a fair point
That is a fair point on him
So I just, I didn't have it in me to do that for this episode
So we're talking about Thursday and Friday on the Alex Jones program
Alrighty
We're going to see if he's going to continue his ideas about moving to DC and living outside
I think it's a good idea
Spoiler alert, no updates on that
No updates on that?
No
Did he even mention it?
Nope
I didn't think so
I'm thinking about it more than him
Yeah, that sounds right
So we'll get to business on this episode, but before we do we've got to take a little
moment to say thank you to some folks who've signed up and are supporting the show
That sounds like a great idea
Yeah, so first, great name, Dan from Colorado, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Dan
Thank you, Dan
Next, Kia I love you, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you, Kia, I love you
Wait, the cars?
Probably
Oh, okay
Next, Minnow the Cat and it's M-I-N-N-O-H, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, Minnow the Cat
There you go
Next, Lang, J-L-A-N-G last initial J, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, Lang
Thank you
Next, Patrick S, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a Policy Wonk!
Thank You Patrick!
There you go!
Next. EwingKing. Thank you so much.
You are now a Policy Wonk!
I'm a Policy Wonk!
Thank you very much EwingKing!
Like Patrick Ewingking
Yeah there's only one king, and that's Patrick Ewing
Patrick Ewing?
Yeah
Yep
Next. Kacmek and it's spelled K-H-A-S-M-E-K
Thank you so much!
You are now a Policy Wonk!
I'm a Policy Wonk!
Thank you very much!
Next. Biohazard. And finally... Biohazard.
Thank you so much! You are now a Policy Wonk!
I'm a Policy Wonk!
Thank you very much! Biohazard!
There you go! If you're out there listening you're thinkin'
you're thinking, hey, I enjoyed the show,
I'd like to support these gents.
You can do that by going to our website,
knowledgefight.com, clicking the button
that says support the show, or.
What you could do is you could take
that feeling of generosity, you can put it
into the rocket launcher that you have affixed
to your back, directly on top of your rocket pack,
of course. Sure.
You can bend down just a little bit
because a rocket launcher affixed to your back
is a terrible idea.
Pull your scope up and you fire that rocket launcher
into the imperial cruise ship of whatever charity
that you are looking for.
I think that one makes sense.
Was that a spoiler?
No, it was not.
Okay, good.
All right.
So Jordan, today, December 3rd, not a great episode.
December 4th, there's a little bit more going on,
but I did find a delightful out of context drop,
which I will share with you right now.
Jennifer Fleck, you're a constitutional lawyer, a patriot.
There's Admiral Atbar from Turn of the Jedi.
Hey, Star Wars.
See, it all makes sense now.
You love Star Wars.
It's all coming back.
It's a trap.
I love the idea that Alex is like,
you're a great constitutional lawyer.
Hey, there's Admiral Atbar.
Hey, there's Admiral Atbar over there.
It's like the Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade
has a constitutional lawyer float.
Weirdly, I think that perfectly sums up Alex's show.
It does kind of.
Talking to some nonsense person
he's calling a constitutional lawyer
getting distracted by Admiral Atbar.
Yeah.
Ah.
And how dare he maintain that he's not that into Star Wars.
You son of a bitch.
Yeah, so we start on the third here,
and I kind of maybe glanced this off
the first time I heard Alex discussing it
or bringing up this little factoid,
but I decided this time it would be best to look into it
and discuss what was going on.
Oh my gosh, now 2,777 people died yesterday.
They're saying from COVID or COVID related things,
which means you give them a test
that the German courts have now ruled are 96% false positive.
So we heard him say that on a previous episode,
but I think it was in the context of something
that there were bigger things going on.
Yeah, it was part of a list of bullshit.
But now the German courts must be brought into this.
All right, let's see what happens.
So this story is a little bit more complicated
than what Alex is saying.
That's a shock.
What's at the core of it is what a German court determined
was that four German citizens who
were in Portugal on holiday were held illegally
when they were quarantined after one tested positive for COVID-19.
I don't think Portugal cares.
Except it wasn't a German court, it was a Portuguese court.
See, now I think Portugal cares.
Yes.
One of these vacationers tested positive
and was in close contact with the other three,
so the Portuguese authorities quarantined them in a hotel.
They contested this decision, and ultimately judges
found that their quarantine was unlawful.
Part of the evidence that was used at their trial
was related to a study that claimed
that PCR tests were up to 97% unreliable
and caused that ratio of false positives.
However, as is always the case, that
is not what the study said.
This was a piece in the Clinical Infectious Diseases Journal,
which looked at what is known as the cycle threshold of testing
and how that could be a way to better understand
viral load and the possibility of infectiousness.
According to this article, the consensus
had previously been to understand someone is not
contagious after 10 days and a viral load that could not
be identified with a cycle threshold value of 30
or higher.
From 13,161 positive samples, 1,941
were chosen and tested using different cycle thresholds
to see how the early estimates held up
in those early assessments.
Yeah, quality control.
They found that with a cycle threshold of 25,
70% of samples were still positive.
At cycle threshold 30, that number dropped to 20,
and that when the cycle threshold was 35,
the number of positive results were less than 3%.
In the publication, they literally
say that this finding, using more data
than their original set, does not significantly
change the conclusions that had been reached previously.
The finding essentially boiled down to a feeling
that after 10 days, if your PCR test is
at a negative with an under 30 cycle threshold,
then you are almost certainly not going to be contagious.
This is not proof that the PCR tests are always
false positives, nor did a German court
decide that the test is a scam.
Alex has no idea what this story is about,
nor does he even know about the study that
underpins the story.
Even with this information, using the cycle threshold
value to infer whether or not a person is possibly infectious
is not a precise way to interpret these figures,
and some people definitely warn against it.
There are a number of other variables to consider,
but the talking point that's been taken from this
publication and disseminated on right wing media
is that the PCR test has been proven in German courts
to be a false positive rate of 97%, which is complete bullshit.
The court in Portugal ruled that the vacationers
had been illegally detained based on their inability
to find any indication of what the cycle threshold that
was used in their positive test result was,
and thus, in court, they could not defend
their positive diagnosis.
This was a case that was mishandled
by Portuguese authorities, not an indictment
of tests for COVID-19.
I also just, whenever he said that last time,
I was just like, this is a global pandemic
that affects a lot of countries.
I don't care if Germany is like,
Germany's court system can't be like,
eh, they're all full of shit, and I'll buy it.
I just don't, I just don't care.
There are other, there's other countries.
They're all like, I buy it, so I'm buying.
I found another story that I thought was
what Alex was talking about, and it turns out
there was a lab in Germany that processed,
I think in one month they processed 60 tests
and 58 were false positives, and the reason was
because there was a supply shortage,
and their normal reagent was unavailable to them,
so they used an incompatible reagent,
and the mistake was found, and like,
oh, okay, I'll redo all this.
But like, yeah, that was what I kinda thought
would make sense, but then I looked into this story
and was like, oh, this is clearly what's going on.
He just thinks it's German courts,
but it's Portuguese courts, it's German vacationers
in Portugal, and it's a misrepresentation
of what the court decided and the study
that was being introduced, so.
Why would I care what a court decides
about coronavirus anyways?
I don't trust most courts to be in any way impartial
or know what they're talking about.
I guess if a court decided that, I'd like to see it.
Yeah.
I'd like to read it.
Anyway.
I would be interested.
Alex has some heroes on the third,
and they're the people who are staying open
despite COVID.
Okay.
Danny Presetti, he's the owner of the popular restaurant
and bar there on Staten Island.
New York, New York told, hey, you're not essential, buddy.
You can have a little patio out here
and you can have maybe 5% of your patrons
for the whole winter and maybe next year,
you're going to go bankrupt.
They said, no, we're essential.
The police said, we're going to arrest you.
So he said, you know what?
I'm an autonomous zone like the commies,
but they sent in their undercover police.
So you're against it.
They were doing something secret and arrested him.
We'll go ahead and roll the footage of that.
Again, this is the Alex Jones show.
We're into hour number one here.
So Alex has this guy's name wrong.
It's not Danny Presetti.
It's Danny Presti.
And things took a little bit of a turn
between when he recorded this episode
and when we were recording ours.
Okay.
On the night of December 5th,
Danny Presti was arrested,
but it wasn't for keeping his bar open
as an autonomous zone or some shit.
According to NBC4 New York quote,
New York City Sheriff's office said,
deputies attempted to take Danny Presti, 34,
into custody at just after midnight Sunday
after observing patrons entering Mac's public house
via an empty commercial space next door.
Upon identifying themselves,
the Sheriff's office said Presti allegedly fled on foot,
got into his car, drove into one of the deputies,
and then continued driving
with the injured deputy clinging to the hood.
I think that Alex would like to paint this
as a situation where this guy is just like,
you know, I gotta put food on the table
and I'm gonna keep this going.
And nah, he's hitting cops with cars.
Yeah, that'll do it.
Anyway.
That's a little bit different from the heroic story
of fighting back against a government
that's out of control for closing your restaurant
in the midst of a pandemic, trying not to kill people.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a little bit different.
It's gonna be an interesting story to try and weave.
But Alex is really into these small business owners, man.
He's really, really worried about them.
Now let's show you a town in Michigan
where the business owner comes up
and takes over the local live feed
and says, listen, you're forcing me to fight back.
You're bankrupting me.
I tried to get the damn stimulus last time
and I was not eligible.
Listen, we went and tried just to see.
We tried to log on thousands of times
over a couple of months, thousands of times.
I'm talking 20 times a day.
I had like five employees trying
because we were losing a ton of money
and things were falling apart.
And I wanted to just see if we could get it.
Then I hired a law firm to check
and they said, no, you can't get it.
So what would you like?
Amazon got 33 billion.
That's bad.
Of the stimulus money.
This is a disgrace for a couple of reasons.
The first and most obvious is that the stimulus
that was given out and the management of it
was entirely up to his hero,
Donald Trump and his government.
If Trump and the GOP controlled Senate
had been willing to provide more support
for the people who were struggling,
then the stimulus probably would have been much larger.
If Trump's government was at all concerned
with governing and competent leadership,
then the website that Alex had trouble using
probably might've been better.
The people that Alex supports and deifies
are the exact people who could have averted the problem
that he's complaining about,
but Alex refuses to acknowledge that.
It's just so fucking Republican to destroy the country
and then be like, see, government can't work.
Yeah.
The second problem is that if Democrats had been in charge
and a robust stimulus package had been passed
that allowed these small business owners
to comfortably survive this health crisis.
Commies!
Exactly.
Alex would be super against that.
Yep.
He hates welfare and he hates the idea
of a social safety net.
If these business owners were being paid
to close temporarily to deal with the virus,
it would be proof that the nanny state
was trying to make all business owners
dependent on them to survive.
In a situation like the one we're in,
there is nothing that leaders can do
that will appease the shithead fake populists like Alex.
You got it.
If they pass massive spending bills
to take care of the public,
it's proof of a communist conspiracy
trying to pacify the population in order to make up serfs.
If they don't pass massive spending bills
to take care of people,
it's proof that they only care about Jeff Bezos,
which is proof that it's a grand conspiracy
to make you dependent on Bezos,
which will bring in communism or something.
Sure.
This is the part of Alex's politics that's a trap.
The joke is on you if you take him seriously
because he doesn't give a shit about any of this.
It's emotionally satisfying to yell
about the small business owners
who were hurt by the shutdown,
but his principles don't allow any other response
to a crisis like this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The only thing he can actually advocate
is acting like there is no virus,
which sounds better when you just present it
as yelling about these poor business owners.
I agree, though, that business owners have been fucked over
in this case, 100%.
But Bezos haven't.
Yeah, I don't think that there's problems
with some of the descriptive things
that Alex is talking about. Totally.
I'll just never respect him to speak on the subject
because he's not a sincere, genuine actor in this.
He's full of shit. No, it's the way
it always works.
Whenever things are going well, relatively speaking,
Republicans are like,
see, they could be going better
if we just got away with all this regulation and shit.
And then people are like,
yeah, that's a great idea.
And they elect Republicans
and Republicans destroy everything.
And then by the time we're here,
four years later, whenever we're not going to have one,
they switch their tune and they're like,
why hasn't government done anything for us?
And it's like, Alex is the only person
that forces me to constantly say like, how dare you?
There's so much drama written in how dare you?
And it's kind of overused and boring,
but Alex doing that makes me just go, how dare you, sir?
Yeah, I think he's the only person
because he's the only person we look at this much.
Yeah, that's true.
I bet if we covered Rush-
No, no, I'd do 300 other people a day.
But I mean, if we did a show about Rush Limbaugh,
I guarantee you he'd be saying,
how dare you, Mr. Limbaugh.
No, of course.
Or Hannity or any of them.
Of course, they're full of shit.
Yeah, so on this day, Alex is pretty excited
because he has that Rogan interview already recorded.
Sure.
And you know, I think it's been my contention
and I don't know, what's stronger than a contention?
Certainty?
Yeah, I would say certainty works.
I'm positive.
Concluding?
Yeah, Alex is using Joe Rogan to try and appeal
to a wider audience than he has access to.
And it's kind of nice that Alex just outright says so.
We're gonna air some of the highlights and excerpts
coming up at the bottom of the next hour.
And then at about one o'clock or so,
we're gonna post the full four plus hour interview.
And the reason this is important is,
everything Joe does gets millions of views.
And everything he does with me gets 20, 30, 40 million views
and with a lot of other people interviews are,
or he talks to her big as well.
But Joe doesn't do a lot of interviews.
And so this is a great way to reach out to new people
that, oh, I don't wanna look at Alex Jones,
but they'll look at something that Joe Rogan's doing.
And so this is a powerful interview.
This is an important thing to understand
and this is why Joe's kind of being used here,
is that Alex has a pretty keen awareness
that people look at this if it's Joe,
but they won't look at it if it's me because I'm a lunatic.
Now, the issue for me comes down to,
do you remember, I'm pretending Joe's listening now.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Do you remember when Alex was screaming
about your kids on air?
Sure.
Do you remember when he was calling you a sneaky snake
and saying he was going to destroy you?
Yeah.
Do you remember when he said that you were a globalist?
Right.
Do you remember all that stuff?
That was when you weren't making yourself available
to be used.
So wait, are you saying-
That was in response to when you got on your show
and said that you can't have Alex on
because of the Sandy Hook stuff.
Oh no, he's my friend.
No, you said he was not somebody who your platform
was available to, he talked about your fucking kids
on his show, said he was going to chop you up
like a sneaky snake.
That's just how he talks.
And then now, oh what do you know,
your platform's available to him.
You're gonna come, you live in Austin,
you're gonna come on his show,
he gets to use you for publicity.
Now all of a sudden you're not a sneaky snake,
you're one of the best.
I have a history of unhealthy relationships.
Is that what you wanted to hear?
Jesus, how fucking transparently obvious could this be?
Like- I was thinking it's,
look, we knew it, he knew it,
maybe Joe is the only person who doesn't know it,
but he probably knows it too.
If he doesn't, he has the most awesome mentality
and I'm jealous of him and the naivete.
Yeah, he lives a better life.
Yeah.
But at the same time, whenever he said it,
I was like, well, that's gauche.
That's a little, look, that's a little gauche.
Look, here's the deal.
I'm trying to use this dude to Trojan horse
my extremist views onto audiences
that know better than to listen to me.
Look, we all know that, but it's tacky to say it.
Right.
So I had a nightmare the other night.
I know that it's also not great to talk about dreams.
And it was that our show disappeared
because of like copyright issues.
Sure.
You know, I know this is fair use
through using Alex's stuff,
but it's still something that worries me is like,
hey, is there a possibility that, you know,
we could have all of our episodes taken down.
Don't give him ideas.
Well, it's too late because on his show,
he gave us permission to do this show.
Oh, that's good.
By the way, everything I do is free to air.
Everything I do is copyright free,
meaning that you can take it, you can share it,
you can edit it, you can cut it,
you can play it on your show.
We get so many emails and so many letters saying,
can I paint Infowars on my barn?
Or can I make copies of your DVD and get them out?
You better.
So apparently not only do we have his blessing,
we have his insistence that we do this show.
Dear Alex Jones at Infowars,
my barn is looking a little worn down.
Do you think I could paint Infowars upon the side of it, sir?
Alex, I wanted to paint Infowars on my barn,
but I was worried about getting sued.
Yeah.
Hey, Rob, Rob Dew,
I got word that someone in Nebraska
has got some paint cans.
Rob, Rob, you know how we will do-
Call Robert Barnes.
Rob, we will do anything and everything for free publicity,
but this one time, look, I fucking hate Barnes.
That's what it is.
I hate Robert Barnes and I hate Barnes.
The end.
Maybe that's what the person was asking for permission for
is to paint it on Robert Barnes.
Now-
That does require permission.
That probably does.
And Alex's permission too about Barnes.
This was back when Barnes was an employee.
So like I said, he's, you know,
Rogan is making himself available
and helping Alex get attention.
And so that means that he is brave.
He is a big, brave boy.
And it turns out that Tucker Carlson,
while his rhetoric is good,
he's not somebody that is going to have Alex on his show.
What a whiny-
So he's not as good as Rogan.
So you can sit back and say,
oh, well, Joe Rogan should do more.
No one else in his position is.
And look, I like Tucker Carlson.
I admire him.
He's a friend.
We talk.
I'll leave it at that.
But I'm banned from going on his show.
And he used to plug Info Wars on there.
And, you know, obviously you don't see that anymore.
Cause they, you know, it's, it's, it's,
nobody's been willing to go to bat for me
in a big position of power.
Oh no.
Other than Trump behind the scenes.
And, you know, Biden gets in.
I got told last week, hell, I got told two days ago.
You're fucked.
That I'm enemy number two.
He said, Jones, I got this call.
Even in your imagination, you're number two.
Works with the Clintons as a Republican.
He said, Jones, you had enough yet?
You ready to come in out of the cold?
And I said, just as soon as you stop running slave camps
in China, just as soon as you guys stop being involved
in pedophilia.
How about that?
How about that thoroughly fictitious person
that I didn't invent right now.
Here's some tough talk for you voice in my head.
Yeah, Alex is public enemy number two.
Once Biden gets in there, I don't even know.
I would be interested to find out
if Biden actually even knows who Alex Jones is.
I would imagine there's a possibility,
but there's also a possibility that he doesn't.
I think the people around Biden would know Jones.
I don't think Biden has ever actually been like,
I don't think they even need to broach the subject.
Like he might've gone like,
Hey, who's this Alex Jones character?
And they're like, listen, you don't need to worry about it.
Here's what I would say.
He is as aware of Alex Jones
as I am of the Property Brothers.
Sure.
That probably sounds right. I know that show exists.
It does.
And there are a couple of them.
I've seen them somewhere.
I don't know what their show is about.
Smiling.
I guess.
Yeah, mainly.
I would imagine that it's kind of like that.
He's aware of Alex's existence,
but probably has no idea.
That's my sense on it.
I would prefer if Alex Jones did
a Property Brothers type thing.
What if he just fixed houses on TV?
That'd be great.
Poorly?
Yeah, that'd be the best part.
He does the exact same amount of work.
I would be into it.
Yeah, I'd watch that.
So someone's called him and says that the DOJ under Biden
is gonna come at you.
They're gonna come after you.
I'd be fine with that.
But there's a possibility though,
that this is all just a ploy.
They're trying to get Alex onto the team.
I don't want to be given immunity by you
because you don't have it from God.
I've got my immunity.
Thank you very much.
All right.
Paul looks so inviting.
Oh, all the money, all the private jets,
all the best medicine, all the best sex,
all the best drugs, just Jones, we love you.
Just come with us.
Come.
You don't think I get hate from the enemy.
You know, it's like, oh, Jones,
we know you're gonna make the right decision.
We know you're gonna come over to us, Jones.
Come to us.
Come here.
Come.
Come to us.
No.
Meanwhile, all these corporate lawyers
and all these sellouts would do,
they'd kill their firstborn to be part of this.
It's disgusting.
And I won't be part of it.
And I'll stay in this fight
as long as you keep me in the fight.
Hey, man.
Two things that are back in stock.
Prosta guards have been sold out for quite a while.
Oof.
Oh, boy.
That's amazing.
Oh, God.
You could just, you could hear him looking at the clock.
Totally.
You could hear him
tiling it out to break.
Come, come, come.
15 seconds left.
Come, come.
20 seconds left.
How did I get the, yeah.
Prosta guards back in stock.
So stupid.
They try and steal me away from you guys
and the only thing keeping me from them is your money.
I'm gonna stay in this fight
as long as you're giving me money, too.
But let me tell you,
I have offers that others would kill their children for.
Listen, here's what I'm telling you.
The moment I don't have your money,
I'm on their team for money.
Sounds heroic.
Yeah.
Now, admittedly, I've gotten none of those offers
that I lied about.
No.
And the DOJ is not gonna come after you.
Doubtful.
So Alex goes to commercial after talking about Prosta Guard
and man, he loves that song, Bad to the Bone.
Yeah.
And I would say that it sucks.
I would say, and I'm sorry.
The part where he goes,
buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh.
Do you like that part?
I just, it's so droning.
Buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh.
Bad.
That's what I would say it is.
It's buh buh buh buh bad as a song.
Anyway, Alex is listening to this
and he's just loving it.
He just fucking loves it.
And then he has this weird fantasy.
I wanna be yours, pretty baby.
Yours and yours alone.
And I'm here to tell you
that I'm bad to the bone.
Buh buh buh bad.
Bad to the bone.
Buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh.
Some good music right here.
So like I'm cruising on the highway at night.
About 120.
Buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh.
It's a nice cruise to speak.
With the desert.
Buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh.
Till that jack rabbit runs out in front of you.
What just happened?
Buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh.
The car starts spinning.
The way out in the desert a hundred yards.
Lucky you're not dead.
Buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh.
The way out in the desert a hundred and fifty down the highway.
What?
I've got a message to present.
A message to all of you.
Okay.
All right.
It's fantasy.
Is that message learn the wrong lessons from things?
Yeah.
That's, oh yeah.
I mean, I guess that's a metaphor for his career.
Yeah.
He's like, you're driving irresponsibly.
You get knocked off the road by happenstance.
And then you go.
Twice as fast, baby.
Just as irresponsible.
Let's keep on going.
Yeah.
I would say that's a bad fantasy.
You know, like why not just keep on driving
down the desert road at 120.
Yeah.
It's a fantasy.
That jackrabbit does not have to be there.
I mean, I guess stories aren't interesting
without conflict of some sort.
You know, you have to have a,
I guess this is more of a man versus nature
kind of thematic story about.
The story as it is with context, not interesting.
Could be man versus self.
That could be a good starting point.
Alex is the jackrabbit.
Exactly.
So he wants to take some time here on this episode
to play clips of his Rogan interview.
Sure.
He wants to bring that into the show itself.
But there's a problem.
There's a problem.
It's copyrighted.
No.
People haven't edited those clips.
You know, I've got this big Trump clip
that I think is the best out of the 49 minutes speech.
We're going to air when we come back after that.
And then I guess we'll push other guests
back into the Joe Rogan stuff tomorrow, maybe.
Oh, because I'm not sure we can hear that.
But, you know, there's there's there's there's so much more.
To get to here today and so many angles to all of this bullshit.
But. I'm being sarcastic this morning.
I said, can I just have three clips,
just one clip from each person involved editing this?
And I'm just going to hear those at 1230.
It's going to be like 15 clips and I don't have them yet.
And I'm not mad.
It's just we just won't do it,
because that's the only power I've got at this point
is that every time we do this, just to give up,
because I got a lot of political news
and a lot of the sphere covered.
At least I can post the whole Joe Rogan interview.
We can get that done demand on video.
So that should be up by that should be up by next hour for you.
But again, the news websites are info wars dot com
and news wars dot com and so much more.
Separately. To fund this operation,
we need your support.
A lot of a lot of ad transitions.
I do appreciate the idea that he's saying, like, OK,
when these things happen, the only power I have is to give up,
which kind of means like I run this whole thing
and I'm going on strike against my subordinate.
How dare my subordinates do what?
What are we doing? What's the problem here?
Oh, wait, they gave me more options than I had requested.
Overachievers, a bunch of dicks, 15 clips here
instead of the three that I had requested.
I can't possibly be bothered to look through
and choose the ones I want to use.
No, I must on air throw a tantrum and threaten to go on strike.
I this is the type of stuff where you go, you know what?
A lot of people think this guy is a leader.
Yeah, the only the only thing I have left to me
is to give up in the face of adversity.
And the when there is a challenge, I say no.
And the adversity is like something you could sort out
during a commercial break easily.
Oh, just oh, hey, hey, guys, could you pick a couple of those clips
for me and then just send them over real quick?
Cool. If the devil is up against this guy,
if like this guy is the dude who's like going to stand up to the devil,
I'd be like, I guess I could just inconvenience him a little.
Maybe this is the devil doesn't even have to destroy Alex
or any kind of elaborate plan.
He could just make his life a little annoying.
And I was like, fuck it. I don't care.
Maybe this is God like flexing on Satan.
Like, see, this is how much better than you I am.
I'm going to pick Alex Jones as your mortal enemy.
It's like it's like Braun Strowman
winning the tag team championship with a 12 year old child.
All right, here's here's who we've got going up against Ivan Drago.
Mr. Magoo. Oh, quite a match.
Yeah, that'll do it.
So Alex does finally get some clips of Rogan.
Like, I am probably going to have to do this as an episode.
Oh, no. But like, they sound so fucked up just in this one clip that they play.
Oh, God.
And I understand that you'd be reluctant to ever accept or or multiply.
Awful ideas, but the best way to combat
that and it's been shown throughout history is better ideas.
The simplest way to combat that is to shut it down.
It's like if you have a kid and you're and you say you got to go to bed
and your kid goes, why do I have to go to bed?
And you go, shut the fuck up.
It's sort of the same thing.
Dad, is that you?
It's a crazy interview, four plus hours long, a lot of leaves, a lot of surprises.
Yeah, a lot of surprises.
I guess Joe's implying in that clip that you should debate your child about bedtimes.
Yeah. Yep.
OK, well, also in that context, you're framing yourself as the child.
And the parent does make the rules.
You got it.
So the bedtime is the bedtime.
That would make sense.
And so if the bedtime is sort of analogous to being kicked off social media,
you're going to abide by the bedtime.
Yeah.
Whether you fall asleep or not, it's on you.
But you're going to be in that bed because they're your fucking parents.
In many ways, one thing that you are learning how to be
is a member of society in so far as your actions affect others.
And in the same way, the people who are doing this bullshit
are children who need to be part of society, which means there are rules.
Yeah, yeah.
The metaphor may work not in the way he wants,
but it might work a lot better than he realizes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Anyway, I think one of the reasons that Joe sounds so fucked up in that clip
is I think they did something to the audio.
His voice doesn't sound right.
It's either sped up slightly or slow.
I don't know what it is, but it doesn't have the same tone
as Joe's voice normally does.
So I don't know what it is.
I think somebody messed that up.
Nah, he probably just has better sound people on his own show.
I don't think so because I listen to, like I said,
the first half hour or 20 minutes of it, and it doesn't sound like that.
No, there was something wrong with the replay of it.
Oh, boy.
But yeah, it's like...
Well, the only option we have here, Dan, is to give up.
Got to.
If this is the level of kind of amazing interview they had
where they're like, don't yell at your kid to go to bed,
I can't wait.
I can't wait for four hours of that.
See, what you got to do is be like, hey kid,
let me tell you about bed, all right?
What you got to do with bed is you get into the bedroom,
you lay in bed, you fall asleep.
If you don't do that, you're going to hell.
If Joe's point is that, like, a parent should explain to a child
who's curious about why there's a bedtime,
why it's healthy and they need to go to bed,
like, if that's the case and he wants to make that equivalent to, like,
social media platforms should be a little bit more transparent,
I'll go with you.
But I also don't think that, like,
I don't think the decisions that have been made are, like,
kicking Alex off, stuff like that.
I don't think that would be overturned by transparency.
Also, I would like to know Alex's take on whether or not
he explains bedtime very clearly.
He's curious.
So we jump to the fourth now, and here's how we open this egg up.
We are 48 days out from the inauguration of Donald John
Trump if we fight back.
The evidence is now red-handed in all five states
with the red-handed video of the illegal sequential ballots.
Devastating.
If Trump can get his hands on those, it's game over.
Game over.
Game over as he can get his hands on them.
But unfortunately, you know, he doesn't have the power of,
like, an entire government behind him.
Nope.
Can't do it.
Well, I mean, this is all just, like,
I get really bored of a lot of this,
because it's just Alex repeating and amplifying,
like, Rudy Giuliani nonsense.
I just kind of, like, it's exhausting.
It's exhausting.
Go home and bleed your hair dye there.
Alex has big news, though.
What's that?
Well, I have big news.
And that is Alex has been reading.
I would like proof.
I would bet that.
Let me give you the big news.
Let me give you the big news here.
I spent hours this morning and hours last night
at Infowars.com and at GatewayPundit.com
and at NationalFile.com and very little time on Breitbart,
because they are really starting to drop the ball
and turn against Trump.
Very disgusting.
But I guess that Mercer money must be good.
Very sad.
I like Breitbart.
Huh.
Think about that a little more, why don't you?
Think about that a little bit more, what you're saying, Alex.
What does it imply?
What does it imply about Breitbart?
What does it imply about?
I think what it implies about Breitbart
is that it only produces content based
upon what billionaires would like.
Huh.
Interesting.
Also, what does that imply about things like Parler,
your social media network that you really
seem to like that has a bunch of Mercer money going to it?
It seems like they would only allow things
that the Mercers would want.
I just think it's best not to use that
as an attack on Breitbart, because they're out of pocket
or whatever.
It's going to be too complicated for you
to thread that needle, Alex.
Don't do it.
I would leave it alone.
That's like following the money in an investigation.
If you follow the money, you're going to get corrupt
politicians.
It's going to happen, because they are.
So don't follow the money.
Well, you know what happens with corrupt politicians?
What's that?
They put ballots in black crates.
And then they count those ballots, corruptly.
Damn them.
One of these stories should turn the whole election over,
because it's so organized.
But there's hundreds with video in dozens
of cases of the fraud.
People looking over their shoulder, kicking everybody
out, saying a water pipe broke.
That's bad enough.
That should overturn it.
Then they pull out all the black crates from under the table
and look like Sylvester when he's caught
with Tweety Bird in his mouth and start
running the sons of bitches.
And then it turns out they're all Biden votes.
So this was a video that Rudy Giuliani had entered
into his evidence as proof of illegal votes
being counted in the Georgia State Farm arena.
It was alleged that these were secret illegal ballots that
were produced from black boxes when no one was looking.
Sure.
The surveillance video was reviewed
by election officials who said that there was literally
nothing abnormal about the video and that these
weren't illegal ballots.
If the material of the box is made of can't be harved,
why not make the ballots out of?
Gabriel Sterling, the voting systems manager in Georgia,
said, quote, the 90-second video of election workers
at State Farm arena purporting to show fraud
was watched in its entirety, hours of footage,
not just the 90 seconds, by Georgia Secretary of State
investigators, shows normal ballot processing.
Oh, damn them.
Once again, we have Trump's goons
trying to manufacture a voter fraud narrative out
of the appearance of something that they think looks
suspicious.
The fact that they keep doing this and each time it
turns out to be nothing should make his followers wary
the next time Rudy or Alex find some supposed irregularity.
But some people fall from multiple doomsday
predictions, so there's no telling.
Yeah.
The end of the earth is on December 21, 2012.
OK, December 21.
I got it wrong.
It's on December 21, 200, 2100.
So guys, come on, follow me for the next 100 years or so.
We'll be all right.
Yeah.
It's just, it's exhausting.
And I think that these are thin and I just, I don't know.
I lose my patience with covering the same topic
over and over again.
So I was very excited to hear this.
I don't know if it's true that La Cosa Nostra, the mafia,
had Jagger Hoover dressed up like a woman.
I don't know if he was gay.
I really don't care.
The point is, is that he did say that the mafia did not exist.
OK?
He gave testimony in the 40s and early 50s
that the mafia did not exist.
OK?
The reason that Jagger Hoover was
in denial about the existence of the mafia was that,
at the time, the FBI was basically
entirely focused on investigating
alleged communists and surveilling left wing
activists.
Yeah.
He didn't see going after mafia actors
as a good use of resources, since organized crime could
be difficult to prosecute.
And they were rich, so they could bribe people.
They gave people a lot of money, which is,
that was one of their.
Following the money.
No, that was a good idea.
You give people money if you want
them to investigate leftists.
Yeah.
If Alex had been around in 1955, he
would have been enthusiastically supporting the FBI,
leaving the mafia alone, saying they're just
good Americana businessmen.
What are you, hate Italians now?
Come on!
The FBI had bigger issues, like how literally everyone
I don't like is a communist.
That's what you've got to be spending your time on.
These good, God-fearing Catholics over here,
just trying to make a living in the new world,
and you're going to ignore them, and you're
going to go after the commies.
That's what you do.
That's more or less.
That's the way you do it.
So Alex is like, you know, he's sitting here,
he's talking about these globalists.
They're a menace.
They want to depopulate everybody.
They want to kill off the entire world.
So does he, though.
But the globalists, they seem to have like a gun to their head.
But it's an alien gun.
Ooh.
But Alex is talking about this, and he
realizes this sounds silly.
Is that more dangerous than a?
Yes.
Oh, OK.
Far more dangerous.
Absolutely.
But it's at your head.
Yeah, but it's, I mean, look.
You could survive a gunshot to your head
if it went just the, not an alien gun.
An alien will blow you up.
Oh, totally.
OK, OK.
So anyway, he realizes this sounds
a little silly in the middle.
This is like a kamikaze action.
It's like somebody's got a gun to these people's heads.
You will depopulate your planet, or we will destroy it all.
Hey, Marvin.
I mean, if I was a military tactician, I'd say,
this doesn't make sense.
It's like aliens have a gun to their heads to do this.
This is not going to be popular.
If I was a military tactician.
It doesn't help people.
And I'm not even saying it's aliens.
I'm saying the Bible says it's an alien.
OK.
Colonel, Colonel, I just, we can't figure out why.
I'm pretty sure that aliens have a gun to their head.
It's got to be an alien gun.
It's got to be alien guns.
I just grow so tired of trying to save face by being like,
I'm not saying aliens, but the Bible says it's an alien.
Yeah, the Bible says it.
You're saying it's an alien.
Cut it out.
You believe everything the Bible says,
so if the Bible says it's an alien,
you're saying it's an alien.
Right.
That's the next question I would like to ask him.
If you were to present this in my presence, I would say,
so you're saying it's an alien.
And he would say, no, I'm not saying I'm just saying
the Bible says it's an alien.
So you don't believe the Bible.
Exactly.
That would be the next question.
And he'd be like, oh, well, blah, blah, blah.
So it's an alien.
Wow, the Bible says it's an alien.
So you don't believe the Bible.
Look, I'm not saying it's an alien.
I'm just saying.
I'm starting to feel like we could do this for a while.
Yeah.
So yeah, Alex's enemies, they have an alien gun
to their head, but they're also the people
who James Bond villains are based on.
I don't know if you know that.
The aliens?
They all look like Dr. Evil.
Why does Dr. Evil look like that?
Because Hollywood knows these people look like.
Or?
Where's his mini me?
Well, that one is actually an interesting story.
Have you ever seen the island of Dr. Moreau?
You're going to take it.
You're going to drink sewage and eat weeds.
He said that last week.
Val Buehler.
The whole diet will be sewage, bugs, and weeds.
I'm not kidding.
He had the club.
See Marlon Brando.
This is in German.
They're going to do a diet to drink sewage and weeds.
The director actually went crazy.
It's a really interesting movie.
But don't worry, your tampons will be free.
He actually said that, too.
I mean, yes.
So that's Goldfinger.
He's more of a corrupt industrialist.
Pull up Adam Spector in From Russia With Love.
I'll never even show his face.
But just pull up James Bond.
Pull up Dr. Evil.
I got to digress here.
If you don't fund our operation, if you
don't do your Christmas shopping with us,
we're not funded by Paul Schwab.
Certainly, if you want more content like this,
please give us money.
All right, we have breaking news.
Hold on.
That guy looks a little bit like Blofeld.
Can we pull up some Blofeld?
Yeah, I know I'm Wolf Plisser.
Can we pull up Blofeld?
Sure, it's breaking news.
Pull up Blofeld!
My enemies look like James Bond villains.
Not that one.
The other one.
Let's get a picture of it.
What about Mini-Me?
No.
You will eat sewage.
They look like Dr. Evil.
You know what?
Just pull up Dr. Evil.
That makes sense.
I'm doing this great impression of sewage man.
Look, we need your money.
Well.
So that was bad.
I was like, oh, that's just a tragic ad pivot.
But then it gets even worse.
Because Alex is talking about this prostiguard
that's back in stock.
Sure.
I think he might be fucking around
and getting himself sued again.
Good.
And the Saw Palmetto is great for women, too.
It's just been found that the FDA has had to admit that, OK,
medical doctors should prescribe Saw Palmetto
as a regular daily regimen for your prostate.
Because it literally just basically 99% chance
it stops the cancer.
Depending on the study, you look like it's very high numbers.
Wait, what did you just say?
What did you just say?
Well, I'm not advertising it.
Hold up.
I'm advertising it as essential vitamin and minerals for you.
Sir, excuse me.
So what's great about that is that part at the end where
he's like, I'm not advertising it as that.
No.
No, no, no.
I am mentioning that in the middle of a sales pitch.
Well, there's that.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
99% chance you won't get prostate cancer
if you take Saw Palmetto.
Wow.
And is it a legal defense whenever they're like, OK,
well, you said this.
And he's like, no, no, no, no.
I put JK at the end.
See?
I don't know.
I think that's illegal.
Yeah.
Anyway, Alex starts talking about Biden, right?
Mm-hmm.
He doesn't have to worry about Biden.
OK, good.
Because what you really have to worry about is Kamala Harris.
OK.
Because she's actually going to be the president.
I thought it was because she's a woman
and they're far more threatened by women,
especially a woman of color than they are of white men.
I think that if you really got granular with it
and you got Alex into a psychiatrist's office,
psychologist's office, maybe this is something
that you could tease out eventually.
Right.
But no, on the surface, it's because Biden is just
going to let Kamala be president, basically.
Oh.
And he says so much in a clip that Alex plays.
Since I mentioned it, because it's too insane
to just say it and not play the clip, where
he talks about stepping down.
If he doesn't do what Kamala says, here it is.
All kidding aside.
The first lady to be told me she holds them for you.
Yes, she does.
But not because she and Kamala have become friends.
But all kidding aside, it's a matter of the thing
we are simpatico on our philosophy of government
and simpatico on how we want to attach, approach these issues
that we're facing.
And so I don't have any.
When we disagree, it'll be just like so far,
it's been just like Barack and I did.
It's in private.
She'll say, I think we should do A, B, C, or D.
And I'll say, I like A, I don't like B and C. And it's OK.
And like I told Barack, if I reach something
where there's a fundamental disagreement we
have based on a moral principle, I'll
develop some disease and say I have to resign.
We don't have that.
We haven't.
And we discussed at length our views
on foreign policy, on domestic policy, on intelligence.
And the great thing is she has a background.
Look at these two disingenuous, slimy frogs
that know they've stolen this.
OK.
All right.
I don't think that that clip says what Alex thinks it does.
OK, so what we're going to do.
I think he's saying that when he was Obama's vice president,
they had sort of private disagreements
over minor issues.
And if there was a really substantial thing,
that he would gracefully bow out in a way that
wouldn't cause psychological damage to the country.
That is not saying that if he disagrees with Kamala Harris
on substantial issues, he'll fake an injury
and then she'll become president.
When I was vice president and I didn't
have any actual say over what the final decision was,
I would give my input.
And if I found the final decision unacceptable,
I would not throw a tantrum.
I would be like, I can't do this.
I broke my foot.
I'm no longer vice president.
That's what he's saying.
Yeah, he's, I find that to be an incredibly mature position.
That like, yeah, I would assume that what
is being discussed there, if you want
to apply it to the president, it would be Harris will step down
if there is a fundamental disagreement between them.
That's pretty much what he's saying.
If we were, because he wasn't president before.
So his story isn't based on when he was president.
What a dick.
Yep.
Speaking of dicks, somebody who's a real pile of shit,
somebody who's, I can't stand, his voice is so annoying.
Oh god, Tom Papert, the National File is back.
And he's pitching this conspiracy
where this woman and her daughter in Georgia
were like, you know, they switched ballots and stuff.
And like, he's going to fuck around and get.
Like in a Freaky Friday situation,
it was like a magical evening and they
touched it in front of a fountain.
I don't care about what's going on.
They have not presented evidence that
rises to any level of suspicion.
There's that.
It is just like, I'm only going to play this clip
because these dudes are trying to get people killed.
Yeah.
You see the four or five people in the video
and everybody's wondering, well, who the heck are these people?
Well, now we know, thanks to the very good reporting
of the Gateway Pundit, it's the mother, a woman named
Ruby Freeman, and her daughter.
Her daughter, she says in a Facebook video,
is her supervisor while she works on the election.
She talks about people complaining
because her supervisor is giving out
instructions that don't make sense
and seem to be against the law.
She says, well, that's just how it is.
That's my supervisor.
She makes it very clear that her daughter is calling the shots.
Well, Alex, her daughter happens to have long blonde dreadlocks
that in a grainy security camera look a lot like braids.
Her daughter is the woman who at 8.22 in the morning
on election day brought in these suitcases full of ballots.
And then once everybody was gone because of the leaky toilets
on that night, she is the one who
started removing the suitcases from underneath the table
and counting them and ordering the other people to count them.
This is an elaborate conspiracy that he is directly
accusing people of.
And by name.
Yeah, and by name, I think that if these two people,
this mother and daughter, feel so inclined,
I think they should probably sue Tom Papert.
This is outrageous.
100%.
Because of the consequences.
I mean, granted, it'd probably take a lot of time.
It would be unnecessarily difficult and a pain
in the ass.
But the potential consequences of the actions
that people like Alex and Tom are doing right here
are so severe that they deserve some sort
of a consequence for it.
And I just can't believe they would do this kind of thing
to people.
I can.
Yeah, I guess I can.
I mean, they just have such a bloodlust.
They just really do.
Like a literal, like, not only are we
saying this person's name hoping they get death threats,
like, this is what we want.
And it's just so fucked.
Yeah, it's tough.
Oh, there's that stranger over there
who I'm going to exploit and maybe get killed.
The end.
So anyway, Tom is on with, he's much rosier than Alex
in a lot of ways.
He's basically convinced that Trump
is going to win these cases, and then he's
going to become president again.
So really what I should have said upfront when you came on,
the big news is not just all the smoking gun evidence now,
but also the legislatures are starting
to move in the right direction.
That's exactly right.
And these people, Alex, these are the modern revolutionaries.
These are the new founding fathers.
These legislatures, the state legislatures
are the new founding fathers of a new country that's
going to be under Trump.
Now, admittedly, many of these state legislatures
have also been in agreement with the whole lockdown and COVID
stuff.
And so after this one, we're going
to go back to tearing down their homes.
But for now, get into Trump, and then we'll fuck you up.
Yeah.
I mean, there is no loyalty.
There's no consistency.
And it's never more clearly embodied
than when they start talking about Attorney General William
Barr.
As we know, he was someone who was not
to be trusted at the beginning.
Ooh, bad.
Because he was associated with the Bushes.
H.W. Bush pardoned all those people.
Uh-huh.
And then he started to get real creepy and super accommodating
of some of Trump's BS.
Yeah, because he's a hero.
And then, yeah, he became a hero.
He's one of the good guys.
And then he got out of pocket a little bit,
did some stuff that Alex didn't like.
I always knew he was a monster.
Yeah.
And then he said some really, really fucked up stuff.
That's because he's a hero.
Right.
And so now he's a villain again.
Oh, he's a monster.
Barr coming out was a reserve army.
We know he's been a deep state double agent at least.
But the fact that he came out against Trump a few days ago
showed their total desperation.
That was their emergency get out of jail free card
and ain't working.
Well, that's exactly right.
I mean, you described Barr perfectly there.
I've never quite thought about it that way.
But that's correct.
I mean, Barr's father hired Jeffrey Epstein
to teach at a girls' school when nobody else would.
That's who Barr's family is.
So it makes perfect sense that he's
in the sleeper with a significant amount of Trump
supporters saying, oh, he plays the bagpipes.
I love him.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I mean, like the tone of his voice, I can't stand it.
No, it's terrible.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
It's morning radio-y.
It's just obnoxious.
It's terrible.
Yeah.
I almost said bingo because that is something that you literally
said that to me last week.
I wonder how long it's going to take for him to remember
the Epstein stuff.
Yeah.
Exactly this long.
The second I read the headline that Barr
said that there wasn't evidence of widespread voter fraud,
I texted you, well, looks like Alex
is about to remember that Barr's a villain again.
Yep, yep.
It's just so sad.
It's predictable as shit.
Yeah.
So in this next clip, Tom has broken the case
on what's going on with voting.
And I think he does.
Tom has broken the case.
I think he doesn't know how voting works.
I agree.
And I have a potential idea of how this may have
happened after examining Georgia.
So I talked to an election expert last night
who testified yesterday.
He said that what they found is they're
using homeless shelters in downtown Atlanta
and other Democrat strongholds to register thousands of people.
And mental institutions and nursing homes.
Which, by the way, seems to be a thing that experts have not
weighed in, meaning the lawyers.
But that seems to be a clear and obvious violation of the law.
You cannot have 2,000 people like Alex.
You can't just walk into a homeless shelter
and say, I'm here to register to vote.
I mean, it's absolutely ridiculous.
Yes, you can.
So I think these people have been older than we have.
I mean, we know that.
And it's a literal legal thing that you can do.
Does he think that people experiencing homelessness
can't vote?
They don't get to vote because they don't have homes.
Does he think that people without permanent addresses
can't vote?
They don't own property.
Only property holding white men are allowed to vote, Dan.
Didn't you know that?
Do you think that people in residential care can't vote?
Like Alex is saying they're registering
people in nursing homes.
Yeah.
You know those people have a right to vote.
Since when?
Always.
Oh.
Why you?
I mean, obviously.
I think it's a little transparent, but.
It's a little bit like.
It's remarkable the sort of the lack of grasp
on any kind of civics there.
Like just, oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, obviously, if you're experiencing homelessness,
you can't vote.
Oh, yeah, you saw.
Why would you let those people vote?
That's how they think.
That is exactly how they think.
Yep.
So Tom leaves, and Alex has a big piece
of news about social media, big tech.
Oh, is he getting back on?
No.
There's another really big story that I haven't gotten to,
and I really, really need to get to it.
And it deals with the next level that
is now here of censorship.
And it deals with YouTube saying they're
going to, quote, suppress the videos of white males
and not let them trend.
Wow.
Wow, indeed.
That is a huge wow.
I would imagine if they came out and said that,
there would be a large outcry.
So since he's saying that they did say that,
and I haven't heard about it, I suppose
they're suppressing the news of their suppression?
That might be.
That might be it, because Alex is dead serious.
OK.
They're going to discriminate because someone
has white skin and is male.
So now, just because you're white,
you're not going to be able to trend.
Quote Martin Luther King Jr. Do it.
I fucking dare you.
By the way, I'm not joking.
It actually says, we will suppress white males.
Ladies and gentlemen, what is that meant to do?
It's meant to create total racial division.
So I found the article about this on Infowars,
and it's just about YouTube responding to their creators,
who have noted that there seems to be
a bias in the algorithmic boosting of videos
and channels of white creators.
In response, they ask creators to voluntarily provide
information about their identity, which
could be used to help better track and see
if there is an actual underlying bias in their algorithm
that they can find a way to mitigate.
Sure.
As it stands now, there's really no way for them to test that,
because they have no data on the identities of the creators.
So this would be a way that they could
try to solve that problem that their users have
requested they look into.
Alex is just making up all the details of the story,
including that quote about not letting white males trend.
Yeah.
This is all just him trying to scare his audience,
because they're super into white identity fear.
Hey, YouTube.
A lot of white dudes.
Look into it.
OK.
So I just find this to be sad.
Yeah.
It's not.
White men really going hard now, but they're
so desperate with their bullshit, it's real pathetic.
Well, the problem that I have is that this
is so easy to understand what the actual story is
on YouTube's side of things.
And Alex seems like he should have bigger issues right now.
Like, there's this whole election fraud thing.
There's the vaccines and the COVID and all this.
Do you really need to try and stoke white fear out of the end?
And the answer is yes.
Yeah.
Because that's his bread and butter.
Sure.
That's something that's so important to keeping
the audience engaged, keeping them interested.
It is interesting that you can hammer one story.
You can hit, oh, voter fraud, voter fraud, voter fraud,
voter fraud, voter fraud.
But with white identity stuff, you've
always got to provide more and more new examples each time.
Otherwise, people are like, wow, that's the only reason
they're, or that's the only thing they're
oppressing white men about.
You have to make up some new bullshit all the time.
Yeah, and just misrepresent all sorts of shit.
Yep.
So Alex doesn't want to kill people,
although he has said that he's killed people
a bunch in the past.
And that he liked it.
Yeah.
And look, I don't want to start going around and killing
people, OK?
But I'm just telling everybody something.
We have a duty to not put up with this
and to get in these people's faces and say, look,
you may think there's too many people.
And in some areas, there probably are.
And there's some problems.
But man, come on.
Wait, what?
He's talking about the vaccine because he
thinks it's a depopulation thing.
Oh, I got you.
So he doesn't want to go around and kill people,
but they're going to have a vaccine, right?
So much like Joe Rogan explaining bedtime
to his child, you are meant to go to globalists
and say, hey, look, I know you think there are too many
people, but how about don't kill them?
I guess in this example, Alex is going to kill his kid
if he doesn't go to bed.
It does seem like he's going to walk around killing children
who don't do what he says.
Yeah, he'll become a legend of folklore, the guy who
kills you if you don't go to bed.
You'll be used to terrified children for generations.
Into your mirror three times.
Oh, boy.
So Alex, there's some talk from these ex-presidents
about how they're going to take that vaccine on TV.
Which I think is stupid.
Well, I think it's perfunctory.
I think it's what you have to do.
But Alex, of course, has a rebuttal all ready to go.
Bill Clinton says, I'm going to take a vaccine.
I'll do it on TV.
If you believe they're going to take an mRNA vaccine that
reprograms every cell in your body, I mean,
this is their move.
I mean, they're not just going to sterilize you.
You know that.
You're dead.
So I mean, obviously, it's going to be if they do get it,
it'll be that's not really the vaccine.
It's a fake.
It's like a placebo vaccine.
The moment they said that, I was like, what the fuck
are we doing?
It's not the real one.
Part of me even believes you get some sort of super rich guy
vaccine.
Don't think they're going to trust you guys.
I just think that not doing that is wrong.
Probably.
Because there is something about the communal experience
and seeing these people partake in something very basic
that we all are in.
There's something unifying to high profile people being like,
yeah, I'm getting a shot too.
In the same way that if you were a kid,
your parent might get a shot.
Totally.
It doesn't hurt.
It's fine.
Yeah.
We're bonding over this.
I think that there's something healthy
when our leaders do that.
And so I'm not opposed to it.
I'm not opposed to it for sure.
But pretending that it has any impact on people who are down
these roads is nonsense.
Yeah, the people who hate the three of you the most
are going to be like, well, if they're getting the vaccine
that I totally believe is the same vaccine that poor people
would get.
Yeah.
Jesus.
So Alex went to a protest the night
before this on the evening of the 3rd
against Governor Abbott or something, maybe the mayor.
I think it's actually the mayor.
But in this next clip, Alex admits to assaulting someone.
Hey.
Last night, I decided, because other people were down
there protesting the day before, to go down
to protest Mayor Adler, who is on a private jet, big parties,
not wearing masks, but saying our businesses should
be shut down.
The guy was yelling at me and threatening me, going, hey,
why don't you come down here?
So I just went down there and got his face a little.
And I probably shouldn't have pulled out his mask.
But I got a little emotional because he was taunting us.
But I probably shouldn't have assaulted him,
but he was taunting us.
Ugh, yeah.
I probably shouldn't have threatened his life
by removing his mask.
Hey, if you're the person who Alex pulled on his mask,
feel free to sue him.
Yep.
He has admitted on air that he assaulted you.
He did it.
No doubt.
He pulled your mask.
Yep.
The end.
He has confessed.
Open and shut case.
So in this next clip, Alex confesses to something else.
And that is that he is very stupid
and a big old Islamophobe.
UK police patrolling pubs, throwing out customers
for eating scotched eggs.
That's right, no drinking allowed.
And if we catch you, even with an egg that
has flavoring of whiskey, we're arresting you, yes.
But the Muslims can run sex rings
with your kidnapped daughters, it's fine.
Whoa.
So scotch eggs aren't whiskey flavored.
That escalated from local cuisine very quickly.
They're not whiskey eggs.
No, I was going to say, does he not know what a scotch egg is?
No, he clearly doesn't.
It's an egg wrapped in sausage and then covered in breadcrumbs.
There was a part of me that, like, I immediately went,
that's not a scotch egg.
And then I had to question myself, like,
did I not know there was, no, of course there is.
What's going on here is that in an area of the UK
where this restaurant in question was located,
the government had put in place rules
that bars can't serve alcohol unless it's part of them
operating as a restaurant.
Right, you have to go to bed.
That is to say that bars and pubs without food
are not allowed to be open.
There was a screenshot of a receipt from a London
restaurant called the Refinery New Street that
showed a bill for 63 Peronys, 12 glasses of Prosecco,
and one scotch egg.
This was being circulated to imply
that this is how they're going to get
around the COVID restrictions.
In reality, the receipt is cropped
to make it appear that the group only ordered one scotch egg,
but they'd also ordered a ton more food,
according to the restaurant.
This is just a social media meme.
It's such bullshit.
None of the stuff that Alex is reporting on here is real.
He's just misunderstanding a headline of a story
that he hasn't read, making up what he thinks scotch eggs are,
and using it to throw around completely
unnecessary Islamophobia.
This is what he does as a career.
He's an idiot who refuses to do any preparation
or any work and just spreads hate all over the place,
because it's all he can do.
He's useless.
Social media is the fucking devil.
We should just get rid of it.
We should only live in communities of 150 or less.
Everybody owns their own business.
I've remade the entire global economy.
I saw this.
I solved it.
I saw this picture of the receipt,
and I thought, like, ah, that's fun.
It's very obviously cropped, because it
doesn't have a total or anything.
Oh, well, that fucking dicks.
The receipt is cut off right under the.
How do you not get off?
Yeah, but it's like, ah, that's fun,
because that is a lot of booze.
That is a lot of booze.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
I would say Alex should try a little harder.
Yeah.
So in this next clip.
Social media internet.
Perhaps.
So in this next clip, Alex claims
that he's known what's going to happen, all this stuff that's
happening around us.
He's known it all for 10 years.
And he's been totally consistent on all of this.
Absolutely.
I told you lockdown's coming years ago.
Using a virus as the pretext to bring in martial law,
forced inoculation, and digital tracking systems on your phones.
People are like, how did Jones know it?
They said they'd do it in Operation Lockstep 10 years
ago.
Didn't exist 10 years ago.
That's what's so frustrating.
It doesn't exist now.
I'm just here like I'm going to play, and they go, oh,
the next page is there.
Romeo and Juliet commits suicide.
Oh, the next page is the.
And I'm just like, OK, now they're going to do this.
Now they're going to do that.
I mean, they're going to kill you.
Operation Lockstep isn't a real thing.
Alex didn't know about it.
Everything is such horseshit.
Right before the 2016 election, Alex
wasn't making his audience scared
about a virus that was going to bring in martial law
and tracking and all this.
He said that Obama was going to declare himself
the king of Muslim elimination.
He did.
There was that.
That was his.
There was none of this shit.
Stevie P said he was waiting for the government
to collapse so he could make everybody Dukes.
No, that was Larry Nichols.
Oh, that was Nichols.
That's right.
No, you don't get to play this card.
You don't get to pretend that.
It's ludicrous.
Dan, are we broadcasting from the rubble
of a nuclear explosion in Chicago?
I mean, according to Alex's predictions, yes.
See, that's kind of what I was thinking.
If he's been right about everything.
No.
This is the shell game that you get
to play when you're someone like Alex and your audience
has just decided to give up.
Much like you when you don't have the cliff you want to play.
Our only option is to give up and believe you're bold.
Once you've been browbeaten to the point of, like,
accepting Alex as a reasonable person,
you just think like, oh yeah, he has always
been saying that they'd use a virus to bring
in the world government.
No, he hasn't.
If I believe the shit he's saying about now,
why wouldn't I believe him when he says now
that he said it earlier?
Right.
And this actually gets to one of the reasons why, I mean, even
like, if I were Joe Rogan, I would just
be personally offended by the way Alex has treated me.
Yeah.
And I would, just as a matter of self-respect,
I wouldn't hang out with him.
But if you want to take it a step
farther and discuss what the real issues are,
when Alex was on Rogan's podcast last with Tim Dillon,
when they had that episode and Alex was one step away
from being exposed as having made up Operation Lockstep,
the way that they dropped the ball there.
And again, like I said, not their fault.
They didn't know what the deal was.
They never had a chance.
Right.
But because they didn't, that means Alex wins that point.
Yep.
Because of that, because Alex didn't get exposed in front
of millions of people as having made up this Rockefeller plan
that now he's claiming he's known about for 10 years,
he gets to play games like this.
And you have done, at least by virtue of your inability
to stand up to the claim, you've helped solidify it.
You've helped reinforce and make it look like.
And the fact that, like, here's what I'm more offended by.
What's that?
Rogan had every opportunity after that podcast to find out
if Alex was full of shit and lying to him.
And clearly, he didn't, because he did four hours
in an interview with him.
Yeah, it would suggest he didn't really follow up on stuff.
Yeah, yeah.
And that one's such a big, obvious one.
The lockstep thing is just so fucking obvious
if you know what he's talking about.
It's just disgraceful.
And so this, like I said, personal level,
the way Alex has treated Rogan as a person is disgraceful,
and no one should put up with that.
But societally, it does damage.
Just not being competent at pushing back
against Alex's narratives only serves
to sell your audience to them.
It does seem like with propaganda in those kind of outlets,
there's one chance to win or you lose forever.
Like, once you cede ground on that, it's gone.
It never comes back.
And if you win, you don't gain the ground.
You just don't lose any, and it's brutal.
Yeah, and if you put yourself in that situation,
you gotta understand that as the-
The stakes are high.
Yeah, exactly.
Especially if you've got millions of listeners every,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's why if you're somebody who has a platform
and you bring somebody on who's maybe a bad actor,
you have really high levels of responsibility.
Totally.
If you're somebody who has a show,
you can bring on someone like Richard Spencer
or Milo Yiannopoulos, but you have a great responsibility
to not allow them to frame everything.
Yep.
And that is your job.
And the challenge is such that you cannot half-ass it.
Right.
And Rogan, to his unfortunate naivete or whatever,
I don't believe that anymore,
but he thinks that he's just having a conversation
with friends or whatever.
At least that's what he wants to present.
And because of that, you're never gonna be in a position.
And that's why he can't have people
like Milo Yiannopoulos on anymore.
He can't have those guests on anymore
because it's too, you can't do that.
You can't do it.
Yeah, somehow Alex is still fine, but-
I don't know how.
I don't either.
That's what we're doing.
So anyway, we have one last clip here.
And Alex has a guest on named Jennifer Fleck.
And she claimed that she had footage or something
of voter fraud in Austin.
Sure.
Because of course, deep blue areas are only deep blue
because the Democrats are stealing all the votes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whatever.
That's the only thing that makes sense.
Right, so she's on and I found this really weird
because she was like, she was running for some office
lost in the GOP primary and then became a poll watcher.
Sure, that's good.
Got into some kind of a dust up
because she had like recording equipment
and you're not allowed to have that.
Great, great, great.
It's like, all right.
Okay.
I don't care.
I really don't care about any of this.
Like her voter fraud stories,
because they're thin and I don't see any evidence of this.
How do we let so many people in politics
who wouldn't be allowed in a bar?
There's a bit, bars have bouncers.
She wouldn't go to a bar because she's very into God
and going to church and all this.
I read that on her ballotpedia Q&A.
Great.
Anyway, I don't care about their interview at all.
Sure.
But I would just like to demonstrate
what sort of people the two of them are.
Okay.
As they get into some real ableist shithead joking.
Great, great.
I remember reading the governor's executive order
this summer and there were like 10 exceptions
to businesses closing or that he had like 10 exceptions.
And I remember one of them was that
he closed all the rafting businesses.
Like you couldn't, like your rafting businesses
couldn't stay open.
And I thought, how bizarre that he would attack
a small business in Texas and let all these other big-
Let's just say it, he's a miserable person.
I'm sorry he's a handicap.
He can't go rafting.
He doesn't want you to.
Right?
No, it's because float trips were spreading.
A lot of cases of COVID were happening at float trips.
Do you not remember the Trump float trip
that spread all the shit?
And float trips in rafts and stuff like that
are just like 20 year olds drunk as fuck in big groups,
barges going down the river.
Like it's obviously, yeah.
It seems if you've never been on a float trip before
probably might be like-
It's social distance, you're in a tube.
You're in a canoe and maybe someone else is in a canoe
a ways away from you.
That's not always the case.
No, no.
I can see, as someone who's been on a lot of float trips,
I can see why someone would close a rafting business.
And that's shitty.
That's fucking shitty.
The way they're acting and being like,
yeah, he's just mad that he can't go rafting.
Fuck you, Alex.
You loved Greg Abbott
until he didn't do what you wanted him to do.
Yeah, we're in a little bit of a bar situation here.
And now you dare attack him for his disability status.
Go fuck yourself.
What a piece of shit.
Yep, anytime you are talking about somebody
and then you use A
and then a descriptor that is not human,
then you, you know.
It's like whenever, you know,
when you're listening to Andy Daley and Paul M. Hopkins,
where he was as L. Ron Hubbard,
every time you heard him say like a Japanese,
you're like,
Ooh, that's fucked, gross.
Yeah, that sort of linguistic framing is terrible.
It's dehumanizing.
Yeah, and I resent it.
And I want to say everybody who Alex likes now,
look at how he's treating people
who have behaved in ways that are just slightly outside
of what he wants them to do.
Look at this, he loved Greg Abbott.
He was one of the best governors in the country.
Maybe the best.
Probably, real great governor, we love him.
Now he's being ableist against him.
He's attacking him,
not only for like him not being extreme enough,
but on these really shitty personal grounds
that are bigoted and horrible.
Rogan, when he's doing what he wants him to do,
Alex would be like, he's so brave,
he's braver than Tucker Carlson.
When he doesn't, he'll bring up your kids
and say he's gonna destroy you.
Cut you in half, bleed you like a pig.
Consider this, this is how Alex operates.
Yeah, I mean, so the thing is,
he exists in this form of unreality that has to be total.
You can't allow a single real thing
to come into the unreality bubble.
Otherwise, the whole thing bursts.
So just like if you're seeing your guy,
Barr is doing something different.
Well, now I can't allow that into the bubble.
Well, it's the nuance that you introduce
when you're like, why would Barr,
if he's the kind of shithead I want him to be,
why would he not do this thing that I think he should do?
You can't like...
Well, and not just that,
but you've painted the Democrats as total complete evil.
So any agreement with the Democrats means you're evil.
You must be.
You have to be.
Otherwise, that introduces the possibility
that not all Democrats are evil.
And then everything falls apart.
And then it's done.
Now, I will say that Alex also played a lot
of the Trump's speech, his 49-minute video that he put out.
Sure, great.
And I don't have a lot of clips of it
because Alex didn't editorialize on it all that much
because it sounds like Alex.
It sounds exactly like Alex.
Yes.
Yeah, it's word for word.
It's scary as shit.
And I want to make a point of this,
like as we close the episode,
that like, yep, that was on his show.
And it's scary as hell because Trump just sounds like Alex.
It's fucking terrifying, full stop.
I don't know what else to say about it.
I hope.
You know, it's so weird to talk to my family now
because it's like before, in the old times, you know,
they could be like, oh, we're just mainstream Republicans.
We don't talk about that Alex Jones stuff.
And it's like, now you voted for Trump.
This is what he's saying.
You're in my world and you're wrong.
That's it.
So if you want to, you can't argue with me, that's over.
The end.
You believe this shit.
Yeah.
Done.
And the thing that really bummed me out, I guess,
and it doesn't bum me out, but it felt really weird.
It's like, just because I listened to so much Alex,
when people would say like, Trump sounds like Alex Jones,
like, nah, not quite.
There's some slight differences.
Yeah.
Or it's like, that's not really what Alex's talking point is.
You'd think it is, but that's,
now I listen to the tapes of that
and I was like, holy shit.
No, Trump-
This is exactly the same as Alex's.
Trump might as well like play that 90 second clip
and be like, her name is this.
And it's, I wouldn't be surprised
if he starts doing that soon.
Yeah, it's-
It's crazy.
Well, I mean, I think you just,
you take the support you got
and when shit's looking real bad like it is,
what you got is Alex and Tom Papert.
Yeah.
Good luck.
I just keep, like the thing that I keep thinking
is just like, be wary, be wary.
Because when these lawsuits and stuff,
he's desperate now that when the lawsuits and stuff stop,
does anybody really believe he's going to be like, well,
guess I lost this one.
You know, when the lawsuits are done-
Yeah.
He's got to do something.
I think he might-
Desperate.
Well, no, I don't know.
Oh, you think he might just give up?
Yeah.
Well, I mean-
He made a bunch of money.
Well, that's true.
But he's never made, he doesn't make enough money.
None of these guys ever make,
I don't know.
Why does Bezos need another $30 billion
as everybody dies around him?
He doesn't need it.
Right, I don't know.
I don't know in like us war gaming,
what we imagine he's going to do,
like Trump is going to do.
Sure, no, I'm not war gaming.
I'm just saying be wary.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But trying to predict, I've found is a useless use
of my time.
Totally.
But being wary is always wise.
I think being wary, a lot of people are just thinking
it's going to go away, and I'm just saying, be wary.
Head on a swivel.
Yes.
Look around.
Always.
Yeah.
Keep an eye out.
This is not the 79 days of hell,
but it is the 79 days of hm?
Huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, where are you?
Easy.
79 days of careful.
Careful, watch out, it's a wild animal
and it's in a corner, just back slowly.
So we will see what happens.
But we'll be back.
And maybe we'll do that Rogan episode sooner than later.
Because it is a four hour like mystery box today.
I did only make it through the first bit of it.
It could be amazing once it gets rolling
or it could be continuing of that,
just walking through fucking knee deep mud.
Yeah, it has to be a disaster or something
to like sink your teeth into because that just,
see one thing I like about smoking weed,
yeah, Joe, we know.
Yeah, it's good.
Yeah, great, great guys, come on now.
So we will be back.
But until then, we have a website.
We do have a website, it's knowledgefight.com.
Yep, we're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter, it's at Knowledge Underscore Fight
and I go to bed Jordan.
We're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook, you tell us you're right.
And if you could please find a local charity
or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work right now.
Yeah, we will be back.
But until then, I'm Neo, I'm Leo, I'm DZX Clark,
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I didn't bring this up earlier,
but I think it's really funny that at the time
that we started recording this episode,
I don't know if Rudy Giuliani actually has COVID.
Neither do I.
Because the headline is just that Trump said he did.
Trump said, I know, so who the fuck knows.
I don't know if Trump actually is right about this or what.
He might have just made it up.
Anyway, that's pretty, pretty, I don't know,
it's not a good place to be as a society.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller,
I'm a huge fan, I love your work.
I love you.