N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am SWEATING
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledge fight
knowledge fight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
saying we are the bad guys
knowledge fight
Dan and Jordan, knowledge fight
Rattle her, rattle her, rattle her
I need, I need money
Andy and Kansas, Andy and, Andy and
Stop it, Andy and Kansas, Andy and Kansas
Andy and, Andy, it's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding
Hello Alex, I'm a 16th caller, I'm with your Japan
I love your room
knowledgefight
n-n-n-n-n-n-n-knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to knowledgefight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're a couple dudes, I'd like to sit around and drink novelty beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are, Dan
Jordan
Dan
Throw it in
I have a quick question for you
Sure
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today is a follow-up to our
Follow-up?
Yes, to our bonus episode that we put out on Wednesday
Indeed we did
People can find that over on patreon.com slash knowledgefight
You can just look at it
Sure, you don't have to be a subscriber or anything, it's free, it's public, but it's posted there
on that page and we had played a delightful game of Thomas Jefferson or not Thomas Jefferson quotes
Indeed
Um, and my bright spot is following up on some things from the Zeep mailbox
Okay
So Nick sent some chocolate and some of these little nanoblocks
Ah yes, yes, yeah
I have to say first of all that nanoblocks are the coolest, greatest thing
They are like little tiny Legos and I found building this pelican to be incredibly like a zen state
I just felt really good, I was relaxed building this because you do have to focus
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Put the piece in the right place
It was great, it was like a really, it really triggered a lot of those feelings that I had
that I loved about Legos and I appreciate that gift
And then also a follow-up on that chocolate
The fizzy jelly
Did you save any for me?
No
I did not think so and it was brutal because the moment you told me you liked it I was like
I would like to try it and I know I'm never going to get the chance
I will order a bar just so you can try it
Just so I can try it
It was so good
How was it good?
It was balanced
Was it gummy and chewy?
There were little bits of gummy but not like offensively so
Okay
Like it wasn't like there was a like gum in the middle of something
Okay, alright
And then there was like a fizziness, like pop rocks kind of thing
Really?
But it wasn't over the top fizzy
Okay
It was a nonsense game
Alright, okay
On paper it doesn't work but it was so good
This is one of those things where you're gonna have another one and you're gonna be like
You know what, I realize all I liked was the fact that these things don't happen to me before
and now that I've tried them again they're awful
There's a chance but as it stands now I ate the fucking shit out of that bar
I want to try it
I want to try it, you could have saved me a piece
Nope
So what's your bright spot?
Well my bright spot was going to be the piece of chocolate I was about to eat
Wow
Not gonna happen
No
You know who has it?
John Grand Prix has that chocolate
How's he doing?
Not good
My bright spot is a movie called Wild Mountain Time, I think is what it's called
And it is an inexplicable movie
I love it
You know those movies- The fizzy jelly candy of movies
A little bit, yeah
You know those movies where you're like this is not a good movie
This is not a bad movie
This movie just needed to exist where it didn't before
Like it's just a thing that you're like I'm glad that's there now
It wasn't
And it's my favorite type of story
I don't know exactly what you're talking about
It's my favorite type of story for two reasons
One, it opens up with Christopher Walken doing voiceover in a terrible Irish accent
That sounds like somebody doing an impression of Christopher Walken trying to do an Irish accent
Okay
It's fantastic
And you're like oh this is probably gonna stop
Nope
Keeps going
Oh yeah
This leads me to believe that it is a bad movie
No it's amazing
It's amazing
And it's also my favorite type of Irish story of which there are only two
There are two Irish stories in the world, Dan
There's Irish stories that go like this
Oh my god you're an outsider get the fuck away
And then over time they're like okay fine you can stay
But you know too much so you can never leave
Or the other kind where it's like ah get the fuck away from here
And then they leave
Like those are the only two types
If there's no story where the Irish people grow and change
Nuh-uh you're either in or out and that's it
Okay
And this is very much one of those stories
And then like the way it could be sold to you
The way that people are going to review it is there's like a twist at the end
There is not a twist
It's not a twist
It's just a reason and it's going to blow your fucking mind
Okay I'm not gonna watch this movie but
You gotta see it
Okay fine I'll watch it
Just because I want people to talk about it
I want more people to talk about it
I want to talk about this movie
You're gonna get some messages now from people who want to discuss
I can't wait
Rocky Mountain Fever whatever it's called
It's an insane movie I can't wait
All right
Jordan today we have an interesting episode to go over
My path was winding and rocky as I got to this episode
But I think we're gonna have some fun
And before we get into the episode itself let's take a little moment to say thank you
To some folks who've signed up and are supporting the show
I think that's a great idea
So first Galen O thank you so much
You are now Policy Wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks Galen
Thank you
Next Mylo F Thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you Mylo
Thank you
Next Devin Thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks Devin
Thank you
Next Most Nate thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Most Nate
Thank you
Next Brodie W
Thank you so much. You are now a policy wonk. I'm a policy wonk. Thank you very much Brody. Thank you. Next Richard H
Thank you so much. You're now a policy wonk. I'm a policy wonk. Thanks Richard. Thank you. And then finally Jimmy Van Gogh
Thank you so much. You are now a policy wonk. I'm a policy wonk. Thank you very much Jimmy Van Gogh. All one word no less.
That's like that's Jimmy Carter's brother in the way. It's Vincent Van Gogh's brother like that kind of yeah makes sense
Yeah, if you're out there listening and thinking hey
I enjoy the show. I'd like to support these gents too. You can do that by going to our website
knowledgefight.com clicking the button says support the show or what you could do is you could take that
Generosity and you could just funnel it into some sort of creative spirit and it doesn't matter what it's about
It doesn't matter what it's about or whether or not it's good what it's about is getting it out there
So even if you're confused by your generous spirit put it out there
Take it to a local bail funder charity and I'll be goddamn if it's not better said in Ireland. So there you go
There you go
Landed it. Yeah. Thank you. So Jordan this episode today. We're gonna start
Where where I'm sort of going down this road
Starting with a little bit from Wednesday December 9th. Okay on Alex's show
He's he's in a weird headspace can just bragging
There's about a half hour at the beginning about a half hour bragging about half hour of him
Just talking about how he's like so popular
Everybody loves all right. I mean look
We've been taking off almost every box system that plugs into the internet and quote gives you cable
But cloud TV is owned by Patriots. They put us on two years ago
We're number one on cloud TV
And if you combine all news channels together including OAN or bigger than all of them Newsmax OAN all of them together
And again, they're kind of shocked by that
They even moved us used to we were at the top is whatever was number one
They put at the top they kind of move us the bottom like well
He just he just dominates too much
We kind of that sounds like like a good reason channels will get some more viewers
And I'm not in competition with those folks. I love OAN. I really like Newsmax
It's just that they won't play just funny because we have more viewers than all of them combined on cloud TV
Obviously OAN is on a much more cable systems and satellite systems, and I love it
And I hope OAN or Newsmax become the number one stations. I don't care. We're too popular. We're just so popular
We're too popular
They used to put us up at the top because we were so popular
But now they put us at the bottom so other channels have a chance. That really doesn't sound right that doesn't sound like good business logic
This goes on for so fucking long. I was getting so annoyed and then Alex was like not only am I the most popular thing
I'm also like super alpha
See, I'm an alpha male so when I was a kid I
Had the alpha genes I guess and I'd see a super like like Jason Jinko jeans
513 where guys coming in with a knife, and you don't fight back and you run you fall down and you plead
I thought that was fake. I've grown up now actually the average man or woman does fall down and starts groveling and
But now actually if Jason pulled a knife out the average liberal would run up and grab it and go I love you
I love you. This is good for me isn't in horror movies isn't the thing that people trip isn't that?
Yeah, no white women in a scary situation in a horror movie are going to fall
But even dudes too like you trip over your feet
It's the trope that sure yeah, I don't think that the people
I don't know. Maybe there are some horror movies where people intentionally fall down and then beg off with Jason
But I think it's mostly like they're trying to get away and then something happens. Yeah. Yeah, I don't know
I think we're doing their best. They weren't like oh shit
Maybe this monster will have mercy. Oh what I should have tried was groveling. Yeah, I don't know anyway
I just got so damn tired of this. Yeah. I was just like I need why?
I just needed something anything to go on and there was one talking point that was going on on Wednesday's show
Like I was trying to find like this something to pull out. Yeah. Yeah, this is this is something that is worth discussing
We've got a lot more here to cover but
FDA six people died during Pfizer COVID vaccine trial so we're gonna be talking about something else as a whole on today's episode
But I did want to bring this up
I think it's a
Important for us to cover this and probably the sooner the better because that feels like it's gonna become a big talking point
Yeah on his show this week
Alex has been repeating this particular headline with outrageous repetition over at infowars
You can find the headline quote FDA six people died during Pfizer COVID vaccine trial
The actual article covers some of the details of this story
But these details you don't really hear them when Alex covers it on the show because he just reads headlines then rants about what he?
Wants the story to be about it sounds scary that six people died in these trials
But in cases like this, it's crucially important to consult the actual information to see what the data says
If you go to the FDA's website
You can find the vaccines and related biological products advisory committee briefing document on the new Pfizer
vaccine if you read this document
You'll find that six participants in the trial are dead, but that number has to be understood in context
The first thing to consider is that there were forty three thousand two hundred fifty two participants enrolled in the study
Six out of that is a very low number
But even so if the vaccine killed six out of forty three thousand people that still might be a cause for concern
Well, I mean if there's three hundred and three thirty million people getting the vaccine, right?
Yes scale up and that could be a huge number it would you know?
So that's why you kind of need to look a little bit further in the text
If you do you'll find that four out of the six deaths were people who were in the placebo group
Which is to say that they didn't even get the vaccine that's being tested
These deaths are absolutely unrelated to the vaccine because they didn't get the vaccine
So that leaves us with two people in the experimental group who died one of whom was retroactively John F
Kennedy so we know why he went down his corpse
It didn't get COVID so these two individuals were both in the older group
Which means that they were over 55 years of age one experienced quote cardiac arrests 60 days after dose two and died
Three days later. This was a person who was in the trial, but two months afterwards had a heart attack
This is sad for that person, but almost certainly unrelated to the vaccine
The other person experienced quote arteriosclerosis and died three days after dose one
Arteriosclerosis is a gradual condition
And it's kind of absurd to imagine that it developed in three days because of a vaccine in this case
It seems almost certain that there was an underlying condition unrelated to the vaccine that precipitated the death
I thought it might be possible that you can make a study out of whether or not the vaccine could have
Exacerbated an existing arteriosclerosis, but that doesn't seem like it was a major concern of the authors doesn't seem like it was likely
So there were two deaths in the experimental group, but both are unlikely connected to the vaccine itself
But that report is being misrepresented and reported by people like Alex to be that six people died in the trial and you're gonna die
too I just it it seems like a very obvious oversight for any news organization not to at least be like
Six people died in the trial only to receive the vaccine in the headline
I'm not I'm not positive how any other outlet reported it so I can't speak to that. I do agree with you
Yeah, that seems that you gotta do that. It's an important detail. Yeah, you can't not do that
Four in the placebo group is very important
Yeah, when you're looking at that number if two-thirds of the number you're talking about exactly is in the placebo group
But I only know what how it was reported on info wars and of course their standard is lying
Yeah, a little bit of a different situation
yeah, the paper itself from the FDA explicitly lays this out quote the incidents of severe adverse events and deaths were low in the
context of the number of participants enrolled and
And comparable for experimental and placebo. Yeah, so
This is a disgusting lie on Alex's part
Which he's able to pass off by neglecting to inform his audience of what the headline he's reading actually means
He gives the audience the illusion that he's informing them of important stuff when he reports that six people died in the vaccine trial
But what he's actually doing is misinforming the flashy clickbait style headline is not necessarily untrue itself
But the conclusion that's meant to lead you to is a lie and a misrepresentation effects
So I got this and I just was like I'm not feeling it. Yeah got one thing. That's like, okay, that's important
Yeah, and it'll probably be something you hear about moving forward as more countries roll out of that
But I was like, I don't want to I don't want to I don't care
I don't want to listen to half an hour of Alex
Rambling about how great he is and then I started to think about it this weekend
Alex is supposed to go down to DC. Yeah, I'm supposed to go move to DC
Sure, and that means I got to write a song about yeah, that is true. That is true. You've got some work to do
Uh-huh. So I felt like my follow-ups don't equal the original Monday
We've got to get into like Alex going to DC and all that stuff
Yeah, have a little better idea of what happened with that protest. We have a responsibility, right?
so I was thinking we have a responsibility to do other things and
Maybe now is the best time. Oh, we're not gonna do Rogan are we but you take DMT with Joe Biden
Shit so we're gonna cover the
Last week, I think maybe I just recently Joe Rogan showed up in Alex's studio in Austin
And they did a four-hour interview, which I regretfully I have I have just one
I just one thing to say about the vaccine shit, which is that I I
Mean just to take one quick step back
It is amazing to me that they can turn six dead in this trial into a terrifying thing
Whenever like it went we went from a brand new disease to a vaccine in a year and a half
That's a fucking miracle. It's a year and a half. Yeah, it's a
miracle to have done that like not since
Like what like they did it one time faster in like the 1950s like it's in a crazy miracle
Yeah, and they're just like Oh six dead like wait 100 years ago. They would be like, this is the demon like this is incredible
Yeah, and I didn't read that entire FDA document
I was looking over the section about the severe and non severe adverse events and a lot of it didn't see it like
You know, they have to report everything. Sure. So like there's like stats for number of people who had like
The a rash. Yeah, exactly or like pain in the site of vaccination. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's like, all right
Information is there. Yeah, you know, it's there
Um, anyway, I agree. I agree. Yeah, but we have issues. We have issues to deal with. Okay
I want to be a globalist. How do I get in?
So we're really doing this, huh? Yeah, we're really gonna listen Joe Rogan talk shit
I'm about people infinitely smarter than I'm gonna say this ahead of time. I
Tried to steer away from conversation about how fucked up they are
Yes, because I think that's kind of boring and it's not really all that like I would if I were in a studio with Joe
Rogan, I'd probably be fucked up too. Yeah, it's kind of low-hanging fruit a little bit and it would become tires
I think we just put a disclaimer up top. These guys are fucked up. Yeah
Yeah, and I think that other like other people living their lives. I don't think there's anything wrong with being fucked up
No, I do think that there's something probably wrong about Alex
Presenting himself the way he does and then being super fucked up with Rogan and talking nonsense. Yeah. Yeah, whatever
I don't really care that much. Yeah, I'm not a square whatever
anyway, I
Look, it's not as good as
When he Alex was on Rogan, of course not because Alex isn't really trying to impress
exactly as much as he is just trying to like solidify the bond between the two of them and yeah and
Try and get whatever he can out of it
But there is still a number of things that I think are important teachable moment. Sure
I mean Rogan in Alex's studio isn't fun because at the it's like they're on more of an equal footing
Like not in any cool footing but Alex doesn't have to supplicate himself quite as much because when you would
Know oh no
He really what do we start what a wine how dare you say you're an alpha
Why don't why don't we start and listen to this alpha?
Evil wars the most banned network in the world
Well, I gotta tell you I get bigger goosebumps with this guy on the air the one I've had Donald Trump on and this movie
Stars, no, seriously
I've known you for 22 years and you're a fun really smart amazing guy and you've put up a lot of my crap and
He's the number one not just podcaster but talk show host the world Joe Rogan my fellow Texan Alex Jones. Thanks for having me
Supplication. Oh boy, right out of the go boy. Did he learn that from Stevie P's that level of
Sequience. Yeah, it must have rubbed off. Yeah
Over the years you just learn how to compliment people if you get your balls rubbed by Stevie P's enough
So there's a there's a constant consistent thing throughout this
Interview where Alex seems to want to hit a couple of points pretty hard
Yeah, one of them is why did you move from LA? Sure. Why like how is Spotify?
Tell me tell me everybody in LA is evil. Tell me Spotify is a great company to work with and they might be willing to
Pay me
Hey, they let me on the your show on Spotify, maybe they'll let my show on Spotify
Yeah, and you know just a couple of other like pointed things run throughout
Yeah, and so the Alex starts off with hey, man
Why'd you leave LA?
Mm-hmm
I really love Texas for so long and I always was attached to LA because the comedy store because of business and just doing stand
Up there and podcast there
But once they locked everything down
This was the logical place for me to move and and it for me it felt like I had a nice
Excuse to move here and just like I thought about moving here for a long time
But it didn't seem feasible and then as soon as the lockdowns happen and then the riots the looting and I was like I gotta
Get the fuck out of LA. I don't believe that for a second. Uh-uh. It's almost certainly tax-related. Yep
Just got a hundred million dollars and LA charges me a lot of money
It turns out and I understand that, you know, Joe would perform in LA and and shit
But like I don't think he lived in the city
Mm-hmm. I don't think he lived anywhere where let's say
Protests were no. No, there are so many looters and writers outside of Joe Rogan's neighborhood
Recent hundred millionaire. I know Rogan's mill. I just don't buy it
I find this brings artificial and false
But it is probably about the best thing you could do as opposed to saying like I'm fucking loaded now. Yeah, I
Don't need them anymore used to be rich
I
Could be comically rich anywhere
I want and it just so happens that Texas is the state where I can stay the most comically
I mean it was either Texas or moved to Miami and I don't think he's going to Miami. Yeah, so Alex also
in with his sort of Steve pochenik esque buttering
He's constantly asking Joe like why?
What's it like to be the most famous person in the world?
You were so successful early on in your career all this stuff. What's it like having the biggest dick anyone's ever seen
What is it like more or less?
Someone's said once a friend of mine said that I'm the bridge between the meatheads and the potheads
I'd like to look at it that well, that was kind of my next angle of my next question
I mean you've been doing podcasting over ten years, right?
It's yeah. Yeah 2009. So it's almost 11 years. It'd be 11 years in December
Away, I mean, I mean you've been big right away. You probably been no no
No, it wasn't big at all in the beginning like literally no one was watching
It was a it's part of the comedy show. We were watching we were watching Joe. Oh my god. Oh my god
Little brother vibe. This isn't the fucking today's show
Oh
Yeah, I'll tell you you were successful early on despite your yeah, let me
Tell you about your experience I know it better
Yeah, I was here. So four minutes in to this interview four minutes
They've had some pleasantries and it's like all just kind of like oh, yeah, you're so great
It's so great to have you here awesome. They start smoking weed four minutes in on air. Let's go back to that
That was my first question. How did you develop your worth at ethic and drive because I have some great tobacco
Absolutely. I'll take a pop ball
So they're good
they're smoking weed and there was a meme that went around or like a video that someone put together from the
Last time Alex was on Rogan and they spliced together things to make it sound like Alex wanted to have sex with Joe
Oh and sort of it went around on Twitter and stuff. Oh, so Alex is constantly
uh
Leaning into that sure sure hoping that someone else makes a video. Right? Right, right
It's really desperate and very pathetic right? Yeah, it's it's obnoxious. He's he's just
Outrageously desperate to get a meme. Yes. Yeah
I think that's what he wants more than even having Joe on is like somebody in Joe's audience will make something
That'll go viral. Yeah, that's that's kind of the goal. I'm looking for 20,000 likes on something
Yeah, and if you got to make fun of me, you got to make fun of me
Hey, well, that's how people have really embraced me because I love being made fun of. Yes
I don't get folks that don't like it. I love it. No you you get a kick out of him
There's a show he would love that
I have a podcast to recommend to him called fucking knowledge fight. I kind of enjoy it
I don't think he's very serious. No, I kind of think that he has very thin skin
I think he has a hair trigger as well. I think he might react negatively when he receives any criticism whatsoever
Yeah, that could be mm-hmm. Well, I could be wrong though. Maybe he's an avid fan
No, he does not like being made fun of but he likes to say that he likes being made fun of well
It makes him look cool
He kind of likes being made fun of in ways that are profitable to him though
Like so if someone makes a meme that's poking fun at him
He gets a ton of people and a ton of attention and his name is all over the place then he'll take it
Yeah, I'll accept being made fun of for profit, right?
Right, I will I will accept payment to be in the dunk tank. Yes, but I will not do it for fun. Yeah
Yeah, he's a sad clown. Yes in many ways, but you know, it was not Joe Rogan Joe Rogan is the most famous
He's the most famous person in the world. He is the Walter Cronkite of our time. Oh god
No
when did you realize that you were in the site guys because you were already in the site guys to hit TV shows and UFC and
You know big movies and you know the national champion
I mean you've had success since day one you had to fight hard for it. But what did you realize? Oh my god
I'm like a real superstar not of some just empty movie or an empty actor that reads off a
Teleprompter a script you get to be your own self and be the biggest that's that's that's very rare
The tobacco is kicking in. I I don't know if I ever realized it. I'm not sure if I still realize it
Come on, you got it. Like like what cuz I mean, I'm pretty super famous, too
One of the reasons why I like pot is it makes me think about much more interesting things
So like wolf, but I kind of respect that answer because it's a it's a really embarrassing question
It is and for Joe as like a person like the graceful
dignified way to respond to that is I don't think about that too much because
To imagine that you do think about it is is gross. Yeah. Yeah
Joe I have a quick question how often and
Strenuously, do you sniff your own farts and believe them to be amazing? Could you just tell me real quick?
Your farts don't stink obviously, sir, obviously, when did you first notice?
Well, I mean like what other answer could he give that doesn't make him look like a shithead the fuck
Well, I think it was about July
2014 that I realized that I was the king of the world
Isn't the great pothead meathead summit of 2016? Yeah, whatever I brought them to together. Yeah
No one thought that I could reach day talk between the two but much like Steve pochenik solving all the world conflicts
I solved the meathead jock
pothead
Conflict it turns out everybody likes doing nothing sometimes
So Alex tried to destroy Joe when Joe said that he couldn't be on his show
So as this goes yeah a couple times back when Alex was on he lied to Joe's face about Sandy Hook
He did do that. Yes
Yeah
And apparently Joe found out about this and it was right around when a lot of attention was going on with the Sandy Hook suit
might have been around the time Alex threatened to murder the opposing council or
I'm sorry put out a million-dollar hit Wow
What's a what's a million dollars between friends? Sure
Yeah, so Joe said that Alex couldn't be on his show for the time being so that was resolved
I said that Joe is a sneaky snake you that threatened to destroy him talking about his children
Yeah, you didn't threaten to kill his well, but he was talking about them in a way that is very inappropriate
I'm not happy for public discussion. No
um
Now looks kind of wants to say sorry about all that
Well, I'm gonna mea copa some before you know the hardcore issues here with you tonight. We appreciate you being her Joe and
That's that I've kind of gotten whacked out under all the pressure all the attacks
Yeah, we've been over this so many times the opposite of Fame though
It's like being I get Ellen is is is you almost start becoming the villain, but I just want to say the way you help man
I wrote that was a big help. Well, we just
I wrote for a long time and I think that's it's just a
It's really a microcosm of what is happening online with people is that they're not talking to each other
No, it's not. It is not a microcosm of what's going on with social media. No, no not communicating with each other
It's very much a case of Alex trying to ride your coattails
this is one of those things where I
Remember this quote from Sinbad and I will till a day. I die the sailor or the comedian
the comedian, okay
Comics are funnier when they ride the bus
Mmm, just that like simple like you have no fucking clue what you're talking about. You hundred millionaire dumbass
Yeah, what are you talking about? What's going on online right now? Yeah, your experience is stupid. Yeah, sure and
like Joe
I I don't know what the fuck he thinks Alex does for a living
Like I don't I don't know does he not know what Alex's show is about. He's never watched imagine
He doesn't have the time. Does he imagine that Alex is talking about like real conspiracies still? Yeah
cuz I
He can't possibly know the horrible things Alex said about him for days
Yeah, it's quite a bit. It's not just they needed to talk. Alex was turning their fight into content
Yeah, but he was monetizing fighting between the two of them
Yeah, if you were Joe's friend, wouldn't you be like hey, I saw I know you probably don't have time to see him for us
But I saw this online and it's this whole long series of things that Joe said or that Alex said directly about you
You should watch this and remember it forever
Let's say that you're a friend of mine and we have a falling out and like maybe you're a high-profile person, too
Mm-hmm. I wouldn't
Have the instinct to threaten to destroy you for attention. Yeah on air
Yeah, that's kind of in that's a bad person
Yeah
If I started my own show like we have a falling out and I start my own show and then all of a sudden
You just start going on. I'm gonna kill Jordan rants one. Your show would become far more popular sneaky
Too I would be very offended Dan. Yeah, that would hurt my feelings nonsense. Oh, we just needed to talk. Yeah
Anyway, Alex carries on this charade that like he actually knows anything about what he's talking about
And in this clip we kind of get the first
Real meaty thing that I think happens and that is like a full demonstration of why Joe Rogan cannot do the things he's doing
When I get into issues when I'm being serious
I mean, I'm yeah, you can differ on my interpretation
But if I'm saying I've got a clip or I've got something I've got it
Well, that's why I wanted to clear podcast really clearly and I think we accomplished a great job, by the way
I felt terrible that night you pat on the back. You said this will be the best one. You just got proven, right?
I'm surprised almost everything you said was a car
I thought if you there's been mistake and and and you were damn right
My buddy Pat Raleigh was there and he said that was your best podcast with Joe ever. I went home depressed
This is why Joe is not equipped to do the job that he's assigned for himself
Joe didn't fact-check Alex
But he gave just enough of the appearance of doing so to rationalize continuing his association with him
Joe could have and should have completely destroyed Alex's career on that podcast
but he didn't have the ammo that he needed to take that shot and because he didn't now that
Podcast gets to be pointed to as a time when Alex's beliefs were really put to the test and he was found
To be correct. Yep
It's just a pathetic display from all parties and I find it difficult to imagine that Joe doesn't have some awareness of what he's doing
And here's what makes me the most convinced of that on that last podcast that they did
Alex presented Joe with information that he was previously unaware of
The Rockefeller Foundation had a public plan called operation lockstep that is identical to the current kovat 19 response
According to Alex everything that's happening now is planned 10 years ago by these evil globalists and the documents are easily accessible to prove it
I do not believe that a sincere person would not finish the podcast and then immediately or at their first opportunity
Check that claim
Alex can either be right or wrong if he's wrong
Your friend is a liar and he's using your platform to spread misinformation
That's gonna get people killed and you're complicit in it if he's right
There's a very easily provable
Conspiracy to kill off the population using the illusion of an outbreak and it seems like knowing that for certain would be pretty important
The only thing that really makes sense here is if Joe is treating Alex like Eddie Bravo
It's fun to talk to him about the crazy bullshit
He believes but there's literally no reason to take any of it seriously or think about it for a second outside of his presence
Joe's not gonna dig into whether the earth is flat after hanging out with Eddie and he's not gonna research the fake
Operation lockstep after hanging out with Alex because he takes them equally seriously
Joe probably thinks that what he's doing is fine and innocent enough
But he's doing a lot of damage and doing a bad job while pretending to fact-check Alex
Yeah, if you just want to shoot the shit with your friend fine. Once you step into the game of like
Validating his conspiracies and pretending that you're doing some kind of rigor or due diligence on this
You're giving Alex all the carte blanche to your audience that he needs. Mm-hmm. You're basically selling your audience to him
Yeah, you can't I'd like the first sentence
He said is just like we can differ on interpretation and it's like you on some things you can
But there are things that are or are not it's not everything is not
Differable on interpretation and then second you always have the documents. Why why would you say that?
Why would you say he always has the documents luck? Is it the joke?
Yeah, I hate it. Yeah. No, it's it's sad. That's pathetic
So Alex is a gift for Joe not only the gift of ass kisser II and nonsense
He also has physical gifts. Okay, you've given me a lot of great UFC tickets
But really nice to me for 20 plus years and I've never really gotten you anything
And I've seen people give you gifts on the show using some PR thing that they're selling. I don't know any stock in this
It's a it's a great rifle. I really enjoy it
And so this is something where you can go get four or five grizzly bears
That's so Texas grizzly bears at the same time. What are these rounds? I'm gonna guys bring the rifle in here
So this is your gift along with that box of cigars. You very much. So I got him cigars and rifle like
It's just like a parody of masculinity. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's really that's really bad. Mm-hmm
That would be a little bit too on-the-nose in a movie. I would be like, okay guys, we get it
They're supposedly men your bros. Yeah. All right. Yeah. This is a man cave. I gotcha. All right
Here's where it gets easy to pull it back. Here's where it gets even worse now remember it
They're smoking weed and drinking booze and booze and he is just gifted Joe a rifle right and then Alex says this
It's really wild when you go pick up the rifle and try it out a little bit
Don't you pick try it out? You know what I mean? Just check it out. Let's just put it away
I know what a rifle is. I got a bunch of all right. How Texas is this? That is the right response
Yeah, yeah, that's a good response. I was very I was very afraid because generally whatever info wars
Hey pick up that rifle is a of course. I'll pick up that rifle Alex Jones the pinnacle of gun safety
Just the guy who loves the Second Amendment
Responsible gun ownership. Hey, don't shoot it. Don't shoot it. Hey, what are you test out that rifle?
No, give it a go. Give it a go inside. Don't shoot it though. Just swing it around Wow pointed at your friends
so they get to talking about like
sort of meds and medication and
Joe knows some people who have mixed drugs with meds and it's had a bad response. Oh
Some side effects there's different people with different side effects, you know
And and some people are seeing it with things and cocaine, you know, there's a lot of people that say that mixing it with cocaine
Turns you psychotic and oral heart makes life say Xanax. It's not
Terrible for you and a lot of people do it. It's terrible for you
They say don't drink on this people are yeah, okay, and they drink on it, right? The problem isn't the meds though
Yeah, it's yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's the one it's that it's the inverse of what you think is
Yeah, I can't do my coke on these meds. No, you're sir, sir. Let me back you up one step
That is what it does kind of seem to me that well, I can't stop doing
Free basin for ten years now and just cuz you want me to take this med. Oh my cholesterol is high
Yeah, fuck you. Mixing booze and Xanax is really dangerous. So people who are on Xanax
Who actually use it as prescribed
It's a little bit like you say no, I'm on booze. I'm taking Xanax. Okay, that's that's my recreation. It's very strange
Also, very strange to hear that Joe's position on marijuana is evolving a little bit
And I think that's probably good because I I think for everything I could tell there is a little bit of a cartoonish
pro marijuana cartoonish carte blanche of
Like like permissiveness to yeah, it's all good. Nothing bad can ever come of we yeah, I think that was kind of a position
He may have presented earlier on it's not addictive and you blow the smoke in your four-year-olds face. It's good stuff move on
He's now evolved a little bit into a position where it seems like he is is aware that sometimes it can have negative outcomes
You know, I've been more and more open over the last few years
Especially to recognize that pots not always safe and I don't think it's a good idea to tell everybody it's always safe
Well, they made it so strong that it's definitely been connected to increases in schizophrenia. I have no I don't know if it's from the
Potency perspective. I think maybe it's always happened and we just didn't
two people
Personally who were normal and started smoking a lot of pot and went crazy. I do as well including edibles
I know people who have them worked here. One of them started thinking that everyone was reptiles. Wait, that's David. I
Was saying that I got bad news for you
If those people worked it in for us previously, they weren't normal
They weren't starting from like really grounded place and then they started smoking weed
They started listening to me. Yeah. Yeah
Sign that this person had lost it is that they thought everyone was reptiles. Yeah when in reality everyone is
interdimensional demons, duh
What are you? What are you high? That's the difference between mental health
Losing it is do you think people are reptiles or do you think they're interdimensional demons?
You know what? I don't I don't understand why people would listen to this
I don't understand why people would listen to two people have the same dumb thoughts. You could already have at home
Oh, you know no totally like like this is dumb as hell
Like I have thoughts that you can think of at home
But it's interesting because you have knowledge and research and shit. Well now we're both just being like, hey
I half remember the content of this thing that I might have read one of the reasons
I ultimately decided to do this episode was because I'm looking forward to Monday and we have the
The trip to DC sure for the episode on Monday. Sure
I don't know when we'll have time to get to the Rogan episode if not now, of course, and then the other more
Motivating factor was that it is something that people are curious about people are curious about like what a four-hour
Fucking episode unreal and no one should have to listen to no one. It's so long
It's mean there were long stretches where I was listening to this and I'm just like I don't care
I don't care. No, cuz cuz there are parts that are just like, okay. This is just a stupid conversation
It's not really relevant
Yeah, it's it's not that entertaining just talking about like a fun time you all had or something like Joe
Rogan does like 10 minutes about how great Joey Diaz is as a comedian. He is great
There's so much there's like skip and so I'll save people the time I'll listen to it for you
Thank you, and we can just listen to the parts that are interesting like finding out the two of Alex
Oh, there's gonna be a short into the grass. Of course, then they lost their minds, right?
also
Alex thinks that he's interviewing Joe kinda. Uh-huh, but the tables turn. Oh, I talk about interdimensional things
That's what the globalists believe in. Have you ever had an interdimensional experience? Here we go
Well, I'm interviewing Joe Rogan
Why are we interviewing each other man? No, no, no, we're not I just want to get all the cool stuff out
Let's just talk. Okay, I'll tell you
So he did not want to answer that question. He wanted to dodge that if you were an interdimensional experience explain to me how that
Question can blow you away if it's like
I talk about interdimensional stuff. Of course. That's what the globalists believe. Have you ever had one?
Because if I say yes, then I would have to admit that I also believe in that shit
And that's kind of probably gonna sound bad
It sounds silly for me to say that's what the globalists believe if I've experienced it and I know it's real
It kind of makes me look like an idiot that if I say no, then the globalists are just a bunch of
Yeah, those who have beliefs that aren't true. Yep. What kind of power is there in that? Not a lot
Yeah, kind of a trap. Okay, so Alex doesn't really answer but then he does he does say this
I don't want to make this about me, but I could actually shift into a psychic awareness a psychic awareness
Although the higher level how well do you think you'd do at rock-paper-scissors?
You know, we can joke about that probably pretty good
You better win every time exactly I'll give you a minute to shift into your psychic state and you better win
All right, that is full of shit that is huge
You I don't have to do any voices vibe out of this guy. Yes. Yeah, I
Can know I don't know about interdimensional experiences, but I can shift into a psychic state
Maybe I would hope so. Anyway, Alex has a good example of when he has done this in the past
No, but I know how to you know
I let's just say I I wouldn't call the exaggeration
It'll be accelerated to the next power where they claim
It's like actual projection or remote viewing right but but I can't control it had a lot of dreams to come exactly true later
And I've called a lot of things like two months for 9-11
I said they're gonna blow up the World Trade Center and blame it on been live what simple said
How did you know how to dream about it kept having a recurring dream? What? Yeah, did you talk about this Larry?
Yeah, there's videos over here. No. Yeah, so I can't really control it. Holy shit
So that's amazing. But that's only one data points. It's not amazing. No, it's not we've talked about we did
I think a whole episode about why it's not
But like that's that that's just one piece of data. What if he had a second dream that came?
Okay kept having this recurring dream of a guy in a pink and green striped sweater. Mm-hmm
When I walk around the side of a building attacking me with like a club Bill Gates and and and and as you wear
What is it Roger sweaters and we used to drive into town? It was like 15, but with older kids to get alcohol
He had to drive into downtown Dallas to get alcohol and weed
We got a like little crack houses, but we're buying weed on them
And then I was going around the side of all these buildings and it was a white crackhead and he tried to attack me
I'd have the exact dream a whole bunch of times and miss when he tried to club me in the head
So it was like it was like it was like my psychic understanding to get past that point
Happened like two months later. I kept having the dream of this guy
I'm all sudden walk around this house to buy some weed wasn't a big weed guy, but we're driving out again for girls
And this guy tries to club me in the head and crackhead and it's the same guy from the dream. Jesus Christ
Yeah those dreams so you've had two of those big ones. You've had a lot of other ones. Yeah a lot of them
Wow, these are the two examples that he uses though. Holy shit
So I guess maybe that was like he'd seen Nightmare on Elm Street
I guess like that's so that's so bullshit
Fuck don't I have one rule don't ever tell anybody about your dreams unless it's a sex dream with someone interesting
No one else. No one cares about anything else. Yeah, I'm positive that I could come up with some stories
Of dreams I had that I could make match things that happen. Yeah. Yeah
Anybody you can fudge the details cuz it's a dream, right? You don't perfectly remember any of this fuck off. Yeah
Yeah
So this is the Alex gets back to the 9-eleven prediction and he says something that I actually think is a real problem
Well, there was a two-hour thing. I did it in July 25th
2001 I went ahead and went on air and they're gonna blow the World Trade Center blend on the CIS have been live then launch all
These wars and and I said, oh I just got this from analysis and information, but I kept having the dream
The towers smoking all the rest of it
So what I what I want to point out and take issue with here is that Alex admits that he lied
About what the information source was. Yeah, he is saying I said that it was based on analysis
But really it was the product of a prophetic dream that I had right because he knew in
2000 that he could not say I had a dream about this
That would be very very silly and I would suggest that if this is all true and Alex is being he's reporting
this accurately then what happened was he was listening to a ton of Bill Cooper and
Patriot ass radio back then and at that point in time it seeped into his subconscious
Bill Cooper was saying very similar things and that's why he was dreaming about it
Yeah, that's and you combine that with the 1993 bombing of the World Trade Center
The feelings like bin Laden was somebody who was known at the time
Well, and he did say he was going to bomb the World Trade Center. There's that he was very explicit about it
Too like a long time in advance, right?
So like Alex's dreams about this or more likely the product of influences that he had sure and then he got on air and
Pretended that he was some kind of expert had some analysis and that's kind of a microcosm of his career
Yeah, yeah ending that he has information that he's just coming up with out of his fantasies
Yeah, I would say that what he's done is invalidate any time he's ever said that he predicted 9-eleven as being like a result of
Work. Yeah, so at best you had a dream you had a dream, right?
So then I will so then if you could your entire career is based on a lie
Unless you are selling yourself as a pure psychic who can predict things as opposed to analyze them
And it calls into question other times that he said he's analyzed things or he has information
Is he actually just lying about the dream? Yeah
How seriously should you take any information that he provides if he was willing to pass off a prediction about a terrorist attack as?
Analysis when it was actually a dream. Well, he did say Chicago was gonna be nuked. How are we doing? We're fine
Oh might have had a dream. Oh shit. We might still be fucked. But he had a dream. Yeah, that sounds about right
So look, this is an interview. Mm-hmm. They're gonna get down to the nitty-gritty
They're gonna get down and find out what the truth is unless Joe doesn't want to have an interview. Okay
So what are you in the comedy Oh
Alex this is so forced
What got me in the comedy it is not forced it is
Questions like we're doing an interview. No, I'm just because I actually but we're I can talk plenty. Look out. No, I know
Let's talk well you don't follow those if you were magically made ruler of the world
Oh, geez, what are three things you would do to change the world as it is?
Alex Jones never does this. I'm being different. I understand
I don't think the two of them want to are they're working on the exact same page here. I think no
Alex is kind of wanting to get something again. Joe just wants to have a conversation. It's still funny anymore
He's charismatic. Yeah, I mean I thought I would I would expect he would go for a joke every now and again
I think he comes off pretty well. Okay, at least all right, okay
I think he says a number of really stupid things sure, but at the same time like I you know watching this
I was thinking like I could probably
Hang out with Rogan Wow
I could probably get along with him as long as we didn't get into these sorts of topics. Sure
Sure, I think it might be fun. And as long as it wasn't like a show
I mean, I wouldn't want to do like I wouldn't want to be on his show. Yeah
Yeah, just hanging out socially having a conversation. I think he could probably probably be a lot of fun
Definitely hung out and had social conversations in green rooms with far worse people
He's able to like Alex you're forcing it why yeah asking a question
When did I get into comedy right like yeah that that is that's an indication at least on some level that he's willing to have
You know conversation that's not that's true boring. That's true. So but in terms of him being funny. I'm not I'm not a hundred percent sure
But Alex thinks he's funny. How about this kill fucker fight? Oh
Well, I don't want to kill him you're gonna fuck him and I don't want to fight him
I don't want to hurt him. It probably be the most gentle if I fuck him
All right, we don't like to keep him alive. No, that's rude that and then you're just making a mockery of it
Oh, you want a personal mama bill? Yes
I
You know, I'm trying to feed the memes right now. So desperate. Oh desperate. I get a meme going. That's really bad
Yeah, that's kind of heart-wrenching. Yeah, it's it's
Cringy, it's very cringy
Yeah, especially since he's he's trying to it seems like he's getting so much mileage out of just saying fuck
Just like kill fuck fight, you know, you want him to say that it's like it's like a family feud question
We're like you want grandma to say tits. We know it
Yeah, there's a little bit of a problem too in that like Joe doesn't seem to hate Bill Gates. Whereas Alex
It claims to know that he runs the world and wants to kill everyone sure
There is Alex doesn't challenge Joe on his non hatred of Bill Gates, which seems weird
I'm considering everything Alex says about Bill Gates all the time, but I would have said, you know, he's one of the 12
Maybe he's middle management
That's true when when Alex was on Joe's podcast last it was a disgraceful
Showing, you know, there were just tons and tons of things that were factually inaccurate
emotionally inaccurate
And manipulative at the very least. Yes, and you know, we did our episode about it and if anybody's interested they can find
cataloging of them there
But Joe seems to think that people were desperate to find something that Alex was wrong about
Let's go ahead and play it's Bill Gates himself saying that the vaccine made 80% of the people ill
Which is exactly what you said on the podcast and people were complaining and they were they were angry
They were trying to find something that you said that was wrong
It was so hard as we basically checked everything you said and all that proved to be accurate
so then we got to this part where you said 80% of the people that took the vaccine got sick and people are like he's
Spreading anti-vaccine conspiracy theories. So I said, okay. Listen, here's the video
We're not desperate to find things that Alex is wrong about it was not a struggle really. No
Oh, it's kind of a Google search honestly. Kind of exhausting. It's a bit of a Google search. It was an exhausting cataloging of things that he was wrong about that took for fucking ever
But Joe I don't understand how he can possibly not recognize that Alex was lying like that
Project lockstep operation lockstep thing is like so glaring that he should never talk to Alex ever again
But he seems to think that everybody was so desperate to find one the thing one place where Alex didn't dot his
Eye or cross his teeth see this this is a struggle because it does seem like he doesn't take Alex seriously
So, how can you also say that?
You know, that's the conflict that I have like he doesn't take this information seriously. Yeah, obviously
So, how can you say that it's proven and then not react to it really like it's a an issue
How can you go out of your way to rationalize Alex and sell him to your audience while at the same time?
Not taking a step and seeing if his fucking conspiracy about the plan to destroy everyone in the present
Yeah, using kovat 19 has any credence to it?
How could you be that not curious if you're willing to vouch for him? Oh
How how could you believe that that stuff has been proven and not use five of your hundred million dollars
To do something about it. Yeah yours. He's if you believe what Alex is saying then the elites are killing all of us
Murdering us all and you have a hundred million dollars. You should buy info. You could do something about it
How do you not make that just oh, I'm just a regular old guy just being trampled
Down to the machines. Yeah, fuck you. Well, I don't I don't know what his answer to that would be
And I don't understand how he can have this completely bizarre relationship with with Alex. Yeah, it's weird
It doesn't make any sense now
But I think one of the ways that he's able to play it publicly is to be like yeah
Everyone's just mad about things that you say because you're saying them. They're too attached to the messenger
Sure, people get trapped into the messenger. They get trapped into the messenger instead of listening to the information a
Fucking moron might have something important to say you never know when someone isn't. Thank you Joe
Not you, but if someone's an idiot at most things and they come to you with one fact someone could be a fucking liar
All the time, but then they come to you with one fact that they saw on TV, you know, get the fuck out of here
That's where crying wolf comes from right? Absolutely knows that a couple of did you learn the wrong lesson from the very story?
You just reference
Yeah
the lesson supposed to be like in that story is that when you cry wolf a bunch of times and there is no wolf people will
Not believe you
The lesson of that story isn't that the people who stop believing someone who constantly lied about there being a wolf or wrong to
Not believe him the last time that's a completely bizarre
Interpretation of that story the takeaway is supposed to be that if you're a liar and the lies you're telling affect other people
You can cause serious damage to people with your lies because the time you're telling the truth about a threat
They might not believe you. Uh-huh. Alex is kind of the boy who cried wolf except in his version
There still isn't a wolf at the end
He's just continuing to lie and the boy is getting rich selling anti wolf pills to a particularly gullible set of people in town
Yeah, there's an issue there. Also. This is a critically important point Joe is saying that people cannot hear the things
Alex says and evaluate them on their merits because they're caught up in the messenger
They hate Alex and so he must be wrong about everything
This is exactly the problem with how Joe engages with Alex just in the reverse
It's Joe who's completely caught up on the messenger and refuses to accept the possibility that Alex is a malignant narcissist
Who is not his friend. I hate Alex Jones more than most people and I can easily separate my feelings about how repulsive
He is from whether or not specific claims he makes are based in reality
It's not a difficult exercise because I care because I believe that there's a reason that this matters
For all Joe's talk about ideas and good ideas beating bad ideas. He doesn't think any of this shit
He's talking about matters
He's trapped by the illusion in his head that he's created where Alex is a good guy who means well
Which he only believes because the two of them have gotten fucked up together a couple times and said offensive things to each other
Which is bonding I guess and Alex gave him a rifle cigars, too
I challenge Joe to take his own of advice and separate the messenger from the message
Start with operation lockstep and go from there and consider the possibility that this person you insist is your friend is actually a dangerous liar
Yeah, I do. I mean it to your point. Yeah. Okay, Joe
Then do you watch like the other conservative news networks whenever they say all that bullshit?
Do you go? Well, obviously I must believe them because it's true
That's the only because they're not that no that's that's so fucked up
He's absolutely tied to the to just I will defend Alex no matter what. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's it's
sucks
Well, I mean it kind of sucks, but it also is really gaslighting to say people who yeah like disagree
But can't possibly have substance-based reasons for disagreeing. We just hate Alex all about it's all about your feelings
It's always it's he's creating this archetype of like all criticism is coming from
SJW snowflakes who are all mad because Alex Jones is too manly or something sure and then like it that's so
Boring, you're like trafficking in this like fetishization of ideas and that's the idea you have
Well, what it is we've done 500 something episodes of this podcast about substance. Yeah, that's wrong with Alex Jones
It's not I don't I'm not just mad at him. Yeah, we would have stopped a long time ago. I was just mad at him
Yeah, yeah, it's such bullshit Joe
It's it's just like with Alex's fears of and then being like on the other side and he wants those things to happen
It's what he's afraid of is the things that he desires in the same way
Joe is what he's really expressing is I react to things based on how I feel
So I assume that others react to things based on how they feel. I can't imagine them
Breaking free of the the mold that I exist in because obviously if I have a hundred million dollars the things I think are important
They're not just feelings that I have or fucking fake prophetic ass dreams that I have that must be where their
Criticism comes from as well. Yeah, and I mean Joe even gets into this kind of thing a little bit later here
I'll even go to this. I'll jump forward a little bit because it's really relevant
I'll go to this clip here because he's talking about like how people shape their ideas
And I think that this might be how he has right or it feels like projecting
This is the thing. It's like like you you're allowed to have other ideas
But the whole idea of who you are and what life is is
Mostly shaped by what you think is gonna give you the least resistance from the people that are around
But that's the Liberals always liked was the fact that they were open and free and believed in speech
And even though I disagree with them on some points they agree with my overall freedom. I'm so high
I don't even know what I just said. You said something really smart
I agree. I'm a bullshitter. So I know that Joe's discounting his own point because he's all high and shit, but the the
Presumption that you mold your identity by with that which
Ideas these ideas that will cause the least tension with the people around you. Mm-hmm. That's not how everyone lives
No, that's not very much personal experience. A lot of times your personality is formed by conflict
It's formed by tension
with groups that you don't fit in with having to find new people that you get along with better because
That's that's nonsensical. Yeah. Yeah, I I can't handle this. I get it
There's ideas and you can look at things from a different way
But we also have to exist in a world where some things are and some things are not
Mm-hmm. Everything is not open to interpretation. No, it just can't be otherwise we get places where it's like
We think there's voter fraud
So there was no things at there at a certain point something is or is not we can't live in a no
This is just how I interpret things like that's just not how we can share a universe. Yeah. Yeah, it's hard
Yeah, but I will say that they're modeling it for us
Here with Alex and Joe. That's why it's so shitty. They're two completely different people and they're getting along
They voted for different people. Did you know that Rogan didn't vote for Trump? What?
Listen, I voted for Joe Jorgensen. I voted for the libertarian because I think we should probably
You know, I'm voting out of California
So I'm like we should support third-party candidates because that's one of the solutions. I'd love to grill him on Jorgensen's position
God, I want to slap him so bad. I kind of how fucking dare you
I mean, I guess it doesn't really matter since it's California
Yeah, I I would love to see how much he knows about Joe George totally
That's just some fake ass
Like I'm so I look I don't agree with what Trump does and I don't like the way he does it
But listen, I can't support the Democrats cuz I'm an iconoclast. I'm Joe fucking Rogan. You don't know shit
I would have voted Democrat if they got Tulsi Gabbard. Yeah, right fuck off you fucking screw you
So again, I often feel like we're gonna get hit with the DMCA complaint and have like copyright
Claims put on our episodes big in cyberpunk 2077
All right, people are saying that you have to turn DMCA music off. Otherwise the twitch will kick you off
Oh, no, you'll get kicked off, but we're fine. Oh are we so again?
Thanks for watching and back to this exclusive in-depth Joe Rogan interview
Which is free to air all you can re-upload it. You can clip it out. You can make memes out of it
It's all copyright free the Alex show show and everything we do at info Wars calm
See, this is the double-edged sword of his desperation for memeing
It is a little bit is that he has to give blanket permission to people like us to be
Easy so I guess we're safe. All right, buddy. Yeah, so that was from a little
commercial that Alex inserted in of course
Of course he did. Why wouldn't he you gotta make money? Yeah, I don't actually even remember what this is about
This next clip. I doubt they do either. Oh, no now I remember
So they're talking about Joe's dog and how great this golden retriever is. Oh my god
Is Alex gonna kill his dog on air? I was worried about that. The rifle is right there. I know! He's swinging it around!
The dog isn't there
But they talk about how great Joe's dog is and the dog smiles and loves Joe and Alex gets mad because he starts thinking
about how like, you know some animal psychologists will say like what you think of as
happiness in an animal isn't always
Happiness. Right. A smile on a dog isn't necessarily happiness in the same way it is for humans. Alex gets kind of mad about this
That is a microcosm of his relationship to animals is his relationship to people. I don't understand why you don't think me! You're all
You're all nature. None of its nurture. Well, but but that's then but then they say they are up here though
They have souls. They have minds. They have decisions. Just you don't. He's talking about like the elites of psychiatry and what have you.
And it's an ultimate. They're in the lower class. We're in the lower class.
Elitism. What existed before the Germans and then in modern psychiatry and psychology
200 years ago, and so that's what I'm coming at here is it doesn't mean that the things they've created the list
They've made aren't real human traits
But it's really a cult a gill blocking us from the larger issue because your dog is magic. Your dog does have a soul
It does have an energy. It is smiling. You are interfacing. Dogs are psychic buffers way more psychic than we are
And so I'm saying is your dog is is the example of what humanity is to go towards instead of somebody like Bill Gates
Yeah, we should be less like Bill Gates and more like Rogan's dog. Jesus
Just it's meaningful. It's meaningful stuff. Just scream out. I don't want to learn that
That how dare they say something different than me? Well, like I'm not threatened by
Someone telling me that my cat smiling doesn't mean she's happy. Oh shit. What is it? What does it mean?
I'm not next question. I'm not threatened by the idea that her purring isn't always like showing love or happiness
How can I make it better right and I also don't question
The bond that we have like I'm not tied up in
Nope, if a psychiatrist said that that cat doesn't feel everything you think it's feeling all the time
That's because you don't have a soul. I'm not invested in projecting my feelings on to my pet friend
Yeah, I don't understand why people I don't know. I don't care. Yeah. Well, I mean, it's it's a thing
So Joe has been pretty shitty so far about the idea that people have valid criticism
Criticism right about Alex right right and in this next clip. I think this is like I really resent this
Listen, Alex, you got to think of what it's like to be a 23 year old kid
Who is friends with a bunch of other 23 year old kids that espouse a very rigid?
Ideology and when someone deviates from this ideology
Ideology and says maybe the guy's not a bad guy. Maybe he had like a psychotic moment. Maybe he had a bad time
Maybe maybe he believed it because he's seen so much
Bullshit, he's seen so many lies and maybe went crazy
Maybe you went crazy cuz he's on his own and because nobody wants to stand up and say hey
He's right about a lot of shit. So
He seemed like the the thing that he's saying is like psychotic is like a sandy hook stuff
Yeah, but like what Joe is presenting is this idea that like the only people who are really critiquing Alex or?
23 year olds who are socially uncomfortable with the fear that they have of saying hey
Maybe Alex is right about something. Yeah, that's
Ridiculous. Yeah. Yeah, that's very frustrating and and angering and
almost suggests a sort of distance from what people really live that could only really come about through a
hundred million dollars
And it's straw man straw man techniques in terms of like this is why people have a problem with you
It's because all their 23 year old friends are in a rigid
ideology it's it's crazy how I'm not even going to mention that maybe
People of color or women might have critiques of you. It's actually
23 year old men who are
Scared hurting their friends feeling. Yeah. Yeah by saying fuck you Alex has all those it's all those non
alpha men who aren't carrying a gun right now and smoking cigars and whining about how people don't respect
everything that we believe without questioning us like alphas do and the real problem is
That Alex got left out in the wilderness
That's the real problem even if you're wrong rather about some things
I meant well, you're a human being and your perspective is valuable
And one of the reasons why you were wrong about such things is because you were abandoned
There was so many people that didn't want to hitch their car up to your train because they were scared
They would get caught in the 9-11 conspiracy in the Bohemian Grove
Conspiracy and the fucking Bilderberg conspiracy. There was so many different things that led people down uncomfortable moments and uncomfortable
Conversations, they didn't want to be a part of it. So they just left you alone and
when people get
Abandoned by all of the other people around them that may
Possibly have an inkling that you are correct. You start going fucking crazy
Yeah, that look on your face was amazing. I'm so fucking mad
I'm so mad at that this okay. Okay, fine. I get it
We've all seen Good Will Hunting, you know, it's great to give the pep talk speech
But you know that was that was fucking Matt Damon as like a underappreciate
This is like giving that same pep talk speech to John Wayne Gacy and being like look a lot of people just don't
Understand why you're doing what you're doing man, but they're just not ready to challenge themselves. I I disagree here
Here's what I think. Mm-hmm. It would be like John Wayne Gacy
I haven't killed all those people. Yes, and then someone his friend being like look, you know
The problem was that you didn't have friends around you telling you not to dress up like a clown
You were abandoned
Didn't have people around you telling you not to report on Sandy Hook like that
Even though we have I don't know a deposition of Paul Joseph Watson saying I told him not to do this
There was that yeah, this is there was that this is this some bullshit
We were trying to make it not Alex's fault. They had done every bad thing. He's done in his career
These are the people who bitch about
participation trophies
This is the most like hey look just cuz you failed a million times
Upwards to the tune of millions of dollars now doesn't mean you're not still great. It's participation trophies and personal
responsibility and ideas like these people who think that's all they keep repeating and over and over and over again and
Here you have like Alex. It's not your fault. People just left you people just people left you on your own
And that's why you had to say that people were crisis actors who were grieving for their dead family members
yourself starting to think a lot of people's criticisms of
Entitled white men are right on. Yeah, but I'm probably just a 23 year old is worried
It could be that three-year-olds around me that it could be that you're right. Yeah, so when you are
Hearing something like Alex saying that he's not using Joe for exposure
How would you hear that?
Like a punch to the face and here's the deal
I'm not using you in this interview, but you're so big and the system
Likes wants to watch what you're doing so I can get messages through when you're on the show
so one of the things I wanted to say to the left is
I
Don't know about the left the average left person left us cool. I
Hear Alex say I'm not using you
But I know that more people will listen because you're here as him saying I'm using you now
I don't understand how you could be friends with Alex for this long without
Finding out his rhetorical trick of saying I'm not doing
But and then doing the thing yeah, because literally he does that every time Alex's son named his show
I'm not bragging as a joke
Exactly. I'm not doing this. I'm not using you. I'm doing this means. I'm using you
Yeah, every reason that I then explained. I don't hang out with him real life only on the context of this show
So occasionally yeah, uh and I picked up on that real fast, so I kept this clip in just because it's like
I think it's kind of indicative of
Some stretches of this episode where it's like what I was talking about earlier. It's like yeah, this is boring
Yeah, this is just them having a conversation that I don't care about but it goes on
You ever have a Kopi luat coffee
No, oh my god
That's
Not even a real razorback though Kopi luat coffee is coffee that comes from a civet
So the civet eats the coffee bar craps and shits them out
And then people collect them and clean them up and then sell them
And it makes the best fucking coffee ever when you said about tried it. I've heard of it. It's so good
It's really good
Like it's it's a cat like a civet is kind of a cat. It's like real close
By the way do you have a photograph of a civet by the way you have a ragdoll catch
Yeah
Hold on. Let's look at a civet
Now I was trying to stalk you but but but I watched the show a lot today, and I'm going hey
You've got ragdoll catch tell Joe you've got him so I didn't know you had right this week this week
I was smart well. They're really relaxed pretty blue eyes. Yeah, there's your civet
yeah, so that animal shits out coffee beans and
Then it's super expensive. It's called Kopi luat. I've heard of it. Yeah, so is it really good
It's really good Wow
Great I've been on road trip. I've been on road trips with comics before yeah, and there is one
I will remember forever because the two people in the back just started having such a boring
Conversation while I was driving. I drove so much faster
Just cuz their conversation was boring
That is the worst. I would I would literally stop being friends with people who had that conversation
Yeah, I was listening to that
And I just sort of whoa there was a couple points and that was one of them where I was just sort of like rubbing
My temples Wow don't know what's going on. I got guys this this is what this is on purpose
It's gonna stop the global
You can edit things
Well Joe has a big message that he wants to get across on this episode and that is that we need to get rid of
tribalism and when he says tribalism
He's talking about the idea of looking at everybody as teams like Democrats Republicans
We need to get over that and start looking at each other as people who have ideas
And look at the ideas that each other have and if I have a better idea than your idea
Then my idea will win and you will then have my idea all I hear is I would like people to stop
Criticizing rich white men maybe that could be it
We are dealing with the remnants of a savage past when people kill people with stone
Axe tools and now we do it with chemtrails and vaccines
Slow down my point is
Is
We're connected with this idea that we have to
absolutely have to
Be in opposition with each other. I don't think I'm sure bloods. That's dumb. It's nonsense
That's the weakness. The weakness is not like
flip-flopping or
Reconsidering your opinions. The real weakness is the really thinking that people that are just
Marginally different from you in terms of the way they look at things that those people your enemy
We have to stop seeing each other as the enemy, but that's what I want. Just
Talk, do you know who you're talking to?
Alex spends all of his time talking about how his imaginary enemies are like working for the literal devil
Yeah, like this is a fine point that he's making but it's farcical to be making it while sitting next to Alex fucking Jones
Like hey, you know what you should do after this. You should ask him what he thinks about Democrats
What does he think?
He thinks they're all demons. He thinks that they're literally possessed by demons
Yep. Wow. Yeah Wow. Oh my god. I mean sure it's a it's a it's a fine thought the
Alex does agree with him
he would like that to be the
Perfect world and it can only come about in an all-white nation
It seems like that's kind of the tribalism that I would like to Christian. Yeah
On those tribalism parts that he kind of focuses on maybe those tribalism parts are the worst ones
No, we start with we have to overcome it though as Joe is
Very repetitively pointing. Thanks. I think the thing that is
most
Difficult to overcome in our pursuit
For the understanding of the reality of the universe white male hedge money behavior. Oh
That there's a team that's in opposition to you and your beliefs which are righteous and true and good
But if I don't have tribalism somebody's gonna overtake me so I don't like tribalism as a necessary evil
Like I don't want a government that I need a strong enough government that has limited government to protect me from try radical governments, right? I understand
I think maybe the solution is an understanding of tribalism and then an agreement to never engage in it and
When people do engage in it, you should look at those people as being foolish
I agree, so we need a lot of good versus bad. Yeah positive versus sin
Look not the Christian cosmology of sin. What is a sin against humanity? I think lying I think being a chicken shit
I think me a coward. Yeah. Yeah, so what's evil Alex?
I find you guilty of your own sins against humanity
You know what? I love to listen to two dumber people have a
Conversation that was famous for happening
2,500 years ago
This is the exact... what are we doing?
This is the problem with so much like online based discourse and like the the whole the sort of
Debates that happen like among people who are self-taught
Yeah
Like she was good a lot of the times you don't realize that these ideas that you think are so
Revolutionary are things you might encounter in your first year in college
Yeah, like there is so much past these points that they're getting to where their minds are blown
But also I mean like I would take Rogan like as a good faith actor sure
Sure, and I would say that okay. Now. This is interesting. Okay now
There we go Joe you are on the right track buddy
Now what does it mean for you to say that we should disincentivize people to act tribally
And then if people do begin to act tribally we should look at them as fools. Yes
it means that how is society organized and what we need to do is
Give people a fine
For engaging in behavior with groups larger than a thousand wait wait
So now we have to have a fine for being foolish for being a fool
This is not enforceable in any way
And if you tried it would get so out of hand
It would be absolutely used to crack down on vulnerable populations trying to band together
But they don't think about that because they've never been the vulnerable population getting cracked down on but they do think that they are of course
They guess they're conservatives who are so fucking shadow banned
You know the reason I used to here's what I used to think that has just been blown away by this very conversation
the reason I thought people who have spent their entire lives studying this type of thing having a
Conversation and that becoming popular the reason I thought the the thing that blocked that for me
I thought was that it would be too dry. It would be too
Boring, you know, but this conversation is more boring than anything I can think of
Yeah, this is tragically boring and more people are gonna watch that then two people who've spent their entire life studying these questions
Yeah, I have I don't know it's tough for me to say because I guess I'm not a normal person
Necessarily and I am you know, 36
I'm on a different period of my life is maybe the target demographic of Joe Rogan. Sure
But like 23 year old meatheads, I suppose. Yeah
Who are afraid of yeah
I think a lot of people think of like college lectures and like academic conversation to be really boring
But this is fucking boring. This is incredibly boring. Yes, and the difference is if you engage with the academic stuff
You probably learn something. It's amazing. You're not gonna learn anything from this
No other than I think Joe's a little bit disappointed in Alex
Yeah
because when when Joe's talking about this need to overcome tribalism and Alex is like
I need my tribe to fight back against any other it try
Yeah, I think there's a sense of Joe being like you don't get it
You don't get the higher-level thing that I'm imagining. Yeah granted what he's imagining is a stupid
But he has no idea how to attain you just can't see my flying Pegasus world and it's disappointing to me
Yeah, no
But despite all that disappointment, I mean the two of them are friends and we can prove it
Well, yeah, like two years later. We shot a video. Yeah during the contested election
Making fun of the bushes. Well you and I dressed up I dressed up like
See, I just have a junior junior senior. Yeah, and I was in a wheelchair and we
Went running around
Was the capital the capital and we smoked a little weed allegedly every single time these two talk this story comes up
Wow, which leads me to suspect that maybe there aren't that many memories. Yeah, that kind of suggests maybe
Maybe
They got high and ran around the capital and masks
You know
I think that the basis like the stories for any friendship and that you that you share
Should not be I guess you had to be their stories, you know, because this story is one where I'm like, I
Maybe if I was there it would be funny, but this is no
I mean, I've seen it they videotaped it cool. I've watched it was still 20 years ago. Yeah. Yeah
Oh, I mean I you've had experiences like that with friends
You can extrapolate like how much fun that much sure sure and it was like, you know, 99 2000
It's just you're free, you know, like it's such a different time
Maybe a few years. Yeah, I
Just think it's kind of depressing. Yeah, I've heard this on other podcasts to like people who only have one story
Yeah, and every time this guest is on that story comes up. Yes. It's like, huh? Yeah get a new story guys live
Stop talking and live. Yeah, so in this next clip we get again another thing another instance of this
mentality that Alex has where he wants to be like
Rogan with this like yeah, we need to get rid of all this tribalism stuff, but I also need mine
Yeah, well, yeah, I don't have a hundred million dollars and and this is this is Alex expressing that like, you know
His nationalism is basically a cult
Yeah, but he needs that call well because he imagines that his enemies are also a cult
Well, and so he needs his call to fight their call. But yeah, I'm
Creating my own enemy in order to destroy myself
I don't understand what you don't understand and I'm creating my own enemy to justify really fucked up things
I want exactly we have to use our own nationalism which has failed and has problems and it's cultic
But our cults better than their cult humans organizing cults. It's our nature. I agree. We should transcend it
You're at that point Joe. I can see up on the mountain. I get where you're going
I'm just saying well, you're in a crisis though
It's like the lower brain
It is the nationalist called a free market money and family and God and runs and everything
It's gonna counter the chai comms where man you work 18 hours a day if you complain your ass is dead
yeah, because the global model is communist China and
All I'm saying is they're taking over. So what do we do about that?
Good response Joe first of all, whenever you're in a situation where you're coming at me
for global advice
We got real problems. I think there's a humility in Joe's response. I appreciate that, you know, like come on
Why the fuck are you asking me for a solution now? Unfortunately?
He does continue and give an idea. Well, I mean he can't not and he should have stopped it
You shouldn't ask me because this is dumb
But honestly, I do look at it like when you say like what do we do about it?
If you could wave a magic wand
You'd make them all do mushrooms all of them. Just all of them
Everybody anybody in a position of power anybody locked into an ideology
Anybody who believes nonsense anybody who believes things that they know aren't true clean
But they'll fight for them. Do you know people that know that the things they believe aren't true? How dare you?
They'll get angry you and how dare you there's a weird
How fucking dare you that if more people took hallucinogens they would but but then someone go crazy someone go crazy
Yeah, yeah, some kids break their legs. You see like an Islamic leader. You can tell they've never taken it. What? Wow
What? Wow, what? Yeah, no, no Muslims have ever tripped or something
This is I mean, this is embarrassing. That's spectacular. This is like Joe Rogan's like 50 no
No, no, he is late 40s. He did somebody's got to be true
He is something I never thought anyone could do which is he took the four ways to learn and really condensed it still further
Down one one way fungus mushrooms. Yeah. All right. All right. So here's how we solve Israel, Palestine
He's gonna be like great. That's gotta be like a joke. It's gotta be his brand. Yeah
I mean, yeah, you could really know. No, he's just doing like I imagine if your job is to essentially be high all the time
You know, yeah, you've got to lean into it, you know
Benson didn't stop doing weed jokes just cuz he got to 50 plus right, you know
I've done mushrooms and it is a fun experience, you know, and under the right circumstances
Sure. I also know a lot of shitheads who've done a lot of mushrooms. Yes
It doesn't it they are all for universal basic income. I don't know if they are it does not solve anything
It's not a miracle cure. No, it's not like oh if you're living in a contradiction you take mushrooms. It's
That's how it always works. Kind of hippie-dippie bullshit is every story that I've ever heard about
Hallucinogenics has been oh man. It's straightened out my political philosophy. Huh? That's what it did made sure all those
Inconsistencies I had in my head just went away resolved everything
Hey, what was the thing that I thought most on my trip was just like a progressive tax policy does work as intended
I expect this like in a bong circle with a guy coming out of the mouth of someone wearing like
blown glass necklace on a
Braid, you know, that's what I expect. I don't expect this out of a hundred million mayor
Yeah, yeah, who's almost 50 she's have some dignity
What he didn't get to be a hundred millionaire by having dignity or learning things
He got to a hundred million by being a guy who took shrooms
Especially the people who believe things that aren't true like the person I'm sitting right next to why do we always make the people most?
Deserving as of a slap to the face of the most famous and rich people available and good at martial arts
This next clip Alex reveals that he's probably taken some hallucinogens
He might have even done acid with Joey be a watch out or he got dosed by Joey Diaz and pissed his pants one
Where the other one was that you have you invited me to in Houston like eight nine years ago with Joey Diaz
Well, didn't you guys allegedly do acid allegedly?
Well
No, let's go back Joey Diaz
Joey Diaz hands me a cookie in Houston
Couldn't get out of the chair
I'm sitting I'm watching the whole day
That's where God did we go to dinner that night we did yeah, I was like crawling around the ground and you couldn't
Pillar of Christianity
Destroyer of globalists. Yep. I who got dosed by Joey Diaz and pissed his pants at a UFC fight
Alex Jones
See now that's where I would like to be
I want to see Joey Diaz roast Alex while he's tripping. That would be hilarious
I can't I can't provide that while he's tripping but there was a time like way back when Joey Diaz came to
Infowars Studios with Rogan. I did not know that. Yeah, we can cover that in a future episode
Like a good one. I like a good DS. It's really tough though because he's screaming at Alex. Well, that sounds right
It's something that I've always thought about like, yeah, maybe we'll do that for an episode
But I remember way back. I tried to prepare it and it was just like holy shit. This is incoherent
But maybe
My pants
I dosed Alex with way too much THC and he smells like piss
Anyway in this next clip Joe, this is this is another instance where I take him to task
I think that this is him revealing what his goals were with having Alex on his podcast
Mm-hmm, and I would say that this is not what he does
One of the goals that and this is real
one of the goals that what I wanted to achieve is
To have people consider that there's people that have wildly different ideas that you do that may be good guys
so there's maybe these people that have ideas of you and I wanted them to consider that maybe
That's a good guy. And if you and Alex were hanging out with me and Eddie Bravo
And we were all in a room together. We would be fucking laughing. We would be laughing hard
We'd be having a lot of fun. We'd be it would be fun. It'd be ridiculous
And if you're not in that room, it's easy to judge. Well, guess what guess who's not in that room
The millions of people who are watching. Yeah, you're you're saying like oh, yeah
I just wanted to show that it's a fun experience to hang out with Alex Jones. Mm-hmm. But meanwhile
The people who are watching aren't gonna have that fun experience
What they are going to see is me fumble and accidentally validate all of the lies that he's trying to disseminate
Yeah, and hey, man
Like I don't know I was Paul pot a fun guy to drink with could you have done a podcast with him?
Like I know that's probably an extreme example, but like yeah, okay
Yeah, you can get along with people who are like gerbils. Yeah fun. I don't know. I don't know
Let's let's hope we never find out don't I don't think so
I just don't think he was that kind of guy probably not but you know, what is a real Sudoku guy?
He wasn't really a hangout Joe is basically saying that his goal was to launder Alex
To his audience by virtue of seeing how how much fun we can hang out with
Furthermore. Hey, fuck you. How about fuck you you would have fun if you were in a room with me and Alex Jones and Eddie Bravo
What if you were a fucking Muslim woman not much not much fun
No to have the guy across from you who is saying shit like I want you to die
Yeah a trans person. What if you were not a white guy? Yeah, huh? Well Eddie's a
Person of color. Okay. Anyway, look, here's what I would say Eddie's Eddie
Here's what I would say
If this was your goal
Then you have a responsibility to not allow Alex to talk about anything conspiracy related anything political on your show
Yep, if your goal was just to talk about how fun Alex is you guys have an interview and a talk?
We get drunk and talk about college football and high school and like talk about that stuff
Yeah, you do not talk about the globalists
You don't talk about his bullshit because then that intersects with where his misinformation is and you especially don't turn it into a call back
No, you can always go back to and say hey look we had him on our show and he checked out
Mm-hmm. So if you if you think something's wrong, I'll tell you he checked out when I looked at you
It's a perfect case of wanting to play both games at the same time
yeah, it's like I wanted to show the world that you were fun by getting fucked up with you and
and tacitly supporting your conspiracies
like that's not that's not
You can't pretend that you're fact-checking him and showing that he's fun because you're doing neither
It's almost as though he grew up kind of choosing the path of least resistance
You know to just kind of get along with everybody around him and just kind of not make
Your identity that could be how you form your identity damn
So I will say that Joe is not comfortable with how much Alex wants to talk about how famous he is
What is it like to be?
You know the the main Oracle because you can say like, you know, Jimmy Carson was this guy
I mean older Cronkite was that guy you're kind of that fuse together on a first
You have the audience are bigger when every other media has been atomized
But in force is a close second or whatever, but this matters not about that
You're in the position of being the Oracle does that like an Oracle Adelphi right now?
Well, you're definitely not helping me with your weird description of what I do cuz it's not accurate nor is it respectful
It's ridiculous. He's a little bit more playful when he's saying it's it sounded like he was actually saying that's disrespect
But he is uncomfortable and he should be that's fucking weird
yeah, I would not be comfortable with that Joe interviews people and has
In formal conversations that go too long and yeah
You're the Oracle of Delphi. Yeah, you're basically Walter Cronkite and
Jimmy Carson Oh
Jimmy Carson. Oh, man. He had some of those great jokes
He used to wear a where a turban Joe Rogan actually was on Jimmy Carson. He got waved over to the love seat
Made his career overnight success
Oh, we got in at the store. Yeah
Oh
Jimmy Carson
So one of the things that I think was a big point that I made early on in our podcast
And I maybe make it less now because I don't like him nearly as much as I used to yeah
Not to say that I used to like Alex, but I certainly dislike him more. Yes. Yes
I actively dislike him a lot more. Yeah, but one thing that I still do believe but I think is probably less important
Is that the role that he used to fill is kind of a good role in society?
The kind of guy who will freak you out and maybe it's your brother's friend or something who tells you about the CIA
Or whatever sure. Sure. Sure. That is a voice that there is a place for in society
Mm-hmm a conspiracy theorist who you know doesn't behave the way that Alex does the guy who's not also
Who can't hurt anybody a complete racist bigot monster and semi throwing around demon shit all the time
You know somebody without malice. Yeah. Yeah, there is a place for that
Yeah, and I think Joe like he touches on like why?
Alex has anything and it's because there was a place that he fit in before
You've taught me a lot of things and this is very important. Like like I said earlier on the show about
people using
other
Departments or other
law enforcement or whatever to start smashing
Polite protests and turning them into violent protests like until you showed me all that stuff about agent provocateurs
I really had no idea that anybody would ever think like that. I had this naive perspective
I think a lot of people have that people that are in government and people that are in
Leadership they really just want the best for the citizens
So there is there is a role that can be filled of like
Discussing these kinds of topics. They often aren't
necessarily front and center sure there there's a value to that
Yeah, but unfortunately the double-edge of this clip is it so clearly demonstrates
Why what Alex is doing nowadays is useless. Yeah
Like yes in the 90s Alex woke you up to the idea of agent provocateurs, right?
That is his niche, right? That's what he should be right? He
Strayed too far and ended up being a guy who can shift into psychic spaces
And his lore is a little too complicated now his skill set is absurd
Yeah, he's a show that went on too long. He's ending the way Game of Thrones did
I think he's a victim of his own success. Yeah, right like he
Whatever the reason he got like millions of dollars and ended up in that flashy ass studio
Mm-hmm. It's the detriment of his career. Like he could probably have lived out a pretty
successful
Making a good living being a conspiracy theory talk-show host
But he got too big for his britches and now this is embarrassing. No comedians are funnier when they're on the bus
I never I've never dreamt of being like famous
I've always just wanted to be a comic who lived his life as like a comic like I want to live comic life
I don't want to make a comic show
I want to live comic life. I don't want millions. I don't I definitely don't want a hundred million enough. Yeah
Yeah, having too much might end up being
It might make you unable to do
Whatever it is
You need to do because once you start going down this road and you start worrying about like pill sales
And all this you start to think about like what are the things that I'm doing that gets the most attention?
For sure and then you know, it's no longer. Hey, here's a boring conversation about the reality of
Agent provocateurs and what you need to know about the history of this tactic, right?
It now becomes everybody is pretending that they have relatives who have died
Yeah, because it's exciting because it excites the internet and it gets a traffic
Yeah, because your incentive is no longer to educate or whatever if that was his attention at the beginning
I guess it's it's now a marketing base. Yeah, that's I mean, it's it's you know
the idea of not trying to be a millionaire and doing every single possible step you can take to get there is a
Radical socialist commie bullshit Dan and you're on my list fair enough. So whereas Alex
30 years ago turned Joe on to agent provocateurs
This is what he does now. I'm in Arizona three weeks ago. I got a call from the White House
High level high level. Well, I mean, you know a Trump son
Secret, I'll just say it's all about name dropping too late. Oh you need to look into
Dominion and communist China and Switzerland all the stuff
We'll call this guy. This guy calls me up from like this big company
He tells me all this stuff. And so I hire a company look at it. We get all the SEC documents
They're on him forwards all the news today
And but this is I asked him I said
Why are you telling me this and they all we've chosen you as the conduit?
I'm almost like is that to discredit it because they've said I'm just right
That's the thing like they can do that with someone so he that's full of shit that he just took that from
Q and on yeah Twitter accounts and stuff. That was just a
The conspiracy that he he laundered but it's interesting there at the end when he's talking about like are they doing this to discredit me?
Yeah, that moment of self-reflection was very strange. Why would Trump's son do that?
You forgot that you said that he was your source. Yeah
It does make sense if you think that they're trying to discredit
He's just lying and telling these intriguing stories to Joe to keep his attention. Yeah, and he just keeps lying
What are the what's the percentage of people that vote?
Usually it's about 60% in a national election about 49% in an off-year election up down to 40
But with the whole metric with Trump they had a overturn of about 90% Democrat how many percent Republican turn on?
Yeah, how many what they had 9% Democrat turn 90?
Never has been statistically fake. It's never happened. It's a 90% fraud proof though. They just used all Democrat voters, right?
But do you know that for a fact?
Yes, they had like 87% of Democrats audio
In the 2020 election there was a 66.7% voter turnout
Alex is just making shit up and saying it confidently which allows him to lie to Joe's face and not get called on it
Because Joe is attached to the messenger and Alex knows that he's exploiting it
Yeah, but the end goal is attention. The end goal is attention
He lies to Joe in order to disseminate this information and because Joe doesn't have the wherewithal to push back on it
Be like fuck yourself. There's no way there was a 90%
Democrat turnout what the fuck are you talking about?
Because he doesn't have that or maybe he doesn't want to cause conflict or whatever
Whatever reason these talking points end up being laundered to Joe's audience
Yep, if people look up to Joe and they respect him he's sitting there and he's allowing this point to stand tacit endorsement
Yeah, exactly. But again, the goal is attention and you can see that very clearly
in this clip
Imagine being like the hot chick back in like 1963 the cum dump
Well, let's look at it in a respectful way Alex the hot chick Christ back in 62
When there wasn't that many of them, you know, there wasn't no Instagram models Marilyn cum dump or uh, how dare you?
You keep saying that
The main goal there is let me on what's that? This is like the mean goal is beyond the mean gold, okay
Well, that's the cringiest shit
I've ever heard just he's so tickled by the idea that him saying cum dump is gonna be mean gold
Well, oh they're gonna be this so I can't think of it. I don't want you to play this on our show
It's really discussed. It's disgusting. Yeah. Oh
There's two different kinds of disgusting. There's the obvious disgusting. Oh, yeah, and then there's the disgusting of like
how
Transparently pathetic is this like how badly you want someone to make a meme?
Yeah out of you so much to make a meme of all the times. He's desperately begging to have memes made. Okay
Yeah, like cuz that's the reality of this
It's it's everything that he's saying that's like kind of gross and offensive is then tagged with I'm trying to get the memes going
Yeah, so sad
Also sad Alex makes a claim about something that Bill Gates said on Japanese TV
Mm-hmm, and because they're doing this and then putting it out later
Alex is able to drop in proof
Okay of his claim. All right, which they do about four or five times
None of it proves anything, but this is the most egregious example. Okay, this is
Outrageous and Joe if you're listening, which I know you're not I would I would say listen to this
Listen to the proof that Alex tagged on he had all the time in the world to find
Edit it later. This is it back in this is what he chose. This is your guy
No, he's Bill Gates said. Oh, don't worry. The Japanese TV goes this is gonna kill people
He goes it's for the he goes it's for other countries now, you know
The printer goes on why I don't know if exactly what you said is representative
Yeah, how many times have I told you a
lot
But when you go down crazy town was on Japanese, you know, I don't have a map
He said it more more defended. He goes. Yes, don't Japanese even they go, you know vaccine cause damage
Oh people are like you about he's this man. You claim you want to be popular he goes
Japan China the United States are not the target. We have special vaccines for other countries. He goes. Oh, yes
Oh, I mean it was like
He said the deal. Yeah, do I see that? Can you show me that on this? I gotta pee again
I don't think of this. I'll find it. We'll do it right now
I'd say it's an ironic if you take somebody who's doing their best to get the world ready and you know putting in my case
millions of dollars into these tools for infectious diseases and really trying to solve
Broadly infectious diseases including those that can cause pandemics, but that you know
We're in a crazy situation. So there's going to be crazy rumors. I hope whether it's individuals or
Countries then some ways that shows us how interdependent we are that to stop a a global pandemic
we need to find whoever's the best whatever the best vaccine construct are the best drugs and we need to make it
Without just focusing on one country. We need to make it for the entire world
Including for countries that don't have the resources to pay for vaccine research or vaccine factories
You know, they're actually
Many ways should be the priority for what we do. That's the whole clip that Alex plays
He played that clip to prove that Bill Gates went on Japanese TV and said Japan China US you guys get a different vaccine
I really feel like that proved the opposite of what he was saying. It certainly didn't prove anything. It didn't prove anything
No
it kind of proved that Bill didn't say that it kind of proves that Alex makes shit up or he has such a
Flimsy grasp on reality that he hears that clip and that's what he thinks Bill Gates is saying
He has to believe that that's like he's so smart
He's reading him between the lines. I would assume that that's the most generous thing that makes sense
Yes, because that literally says everyone should get the vaccine and we should focus on countries who can't make it for themselves
Yeah, they should be a priority. Yeah, because it is also a global issue as opposed to yeah
one country's problem to solve yeah, I don't like I
Like to say I don't get it. I don't understand but like there are there are a limited number of
Insertions. Yeah. Yeah. One is Alex is intentionally misleading. Mm-hmm
The second is he is a consumer of bullshit news sites. Yeah, and he thinks he's never watched the clip
He just has read a headline about it from National File or whatever
And he thinks that's what it said or he watched it and that's what he interpreted it as and it's completely
erroneous putting it in later, it's so it's so
Sad. Confusing? It's not confusing. Why would you do that? You know, I don't know
I mean
I think that there are
Some words that you can say that sound very similar sure and depending on what you think the word is is what you will hear
That could be I think that Alex would probably assume that he's implanted the idea that that's what Bill Gates was saying
Yeah, so if you hear that that's how if you think Alex knows shit
That's all you'll be primed for the correct interpretation of his so that's what I assume
he thinks it's almost like a
fucking gaslighting
Three-pointer, you know, it's like I'm going to tell you what you're about to hear doesn't say what you're about to hear
Yeah, or you just think people just like not really pay attention. Yeah, that's probably like oh, there's he played a clip of Bill Gates
It must have said Rogan's in the bathroom. I'll skip this part
Listen Rogan's fans are the meatheads and the potheads like, you know, you can trick him. That's fair. That is fair
That is fair. So once again Joe takes issue with people who critique his podcast
Interview with Alex strange and this one is also not a good point
Well, there was a lot of people that got tricked
They got tricked into thinking that the podcast was something other than what it was and they they read some
Someone else's description and more people did that then listen cuz well, you know, we did three hours plus right?
How many how many did you do 20 or something like that? I'm crazy. There's no way they listened
There's someone they don't like for three hours and 20 minutes. Like why would they do that? Yeah, why would we do that?
All right, Joe, that's a personal insult yeah that that one that is that hurts at all
personal
That is not abroad. These liberals are doing that's you specifically Dan
Why
What's most tragic about that is I don't have a good answer
Why would people listen to hours of someone they hate
Mmm, that's a good question
That's a good question. Also, you just described my job
Don't you dare say 20 hours like oh, look at how much work we did screw you
We put more time in talking about you dudes talk
Yeah, but I mean I I do understand that deflection of like it was really long people couldn't have possibly listened to it
I thought it was shit. Sure and like no, I mean, I'm more primed to listen to something that I think is shit
Yeah, that's something that is
Bad like this was way more painful than Joe's episode totally and granted him. This is four hours
I was three and a half or whatever
But like Alex was hot dogging on Joe's show
Which at least makes some kind of an entertainment value and Joe knows that this is his platform and he has to have some
Semblance of a shrine. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, and so like those dynamics played out on Joe's show, which made it a little bit more of
Interesting. Yeah than this which is long stretches of
Nothing. No, this is two dudes and Alex being like you're so famous
This is a two person make a mean is it a two-person smoke circle?
And that's the worst to possibly be in Alex's how it doesn't have the showmanship chops
To carry this as like a show so being on Alex's turf is a problem
Hmm Joe is not as good as like when he's a guest
yeah, as he is when he's on his own show because he'll just talk about how he ate or drank some coffee that a
Shit it out. Do you get it? Isn't that gross? But it's good. How can that be? Yeah
Yeah, I I just hmm. I feel like this must have been an apology like I something
I feel like this has to be a thing where
Rogan said you can't come on my yeah. Yeah
I'll go on your place. Yeah, but I won't be on your actual show. We'll just get drunk and record something
Yeah, I feel like it has to be something like that some kind of olive branch. Yeah, I don't know
It's a real bummer. There is no point for this to exist other than for them to try and get attention
Yeah, it's absurd unlike wild mountain time which exists only for itself to sure
So we have one last clip and it's Alex really summing things up well, and I think Joe nails it all right well
I've been on there 27 years and Joe Rogan. I want to thank you for everything
I want to say this is the best four hours. I ever spent. Thank you so much. That's what's outrageous outrageous about this world
That's what's outrageous. What is it this could be your best show?
This was nonsense. It is nonsense. Yeah, that's fair. Yeah. Yeah, I like ideas man
I do I like ideas. That's why I like listening to things that I don't agree with I like listening to Alex Jones because I like
Finding I first of all I mean he says stupid things like Alex with guns and shit great
There are certain things that just wouldn't normally come up in
Conversations of people I enjoy and I find interesting sure podcast that I would listen to for pleasure
Certainly a lot of those things wouldn't be overlapping with Alex, right? That's why I listen to stuff like project Camelot
Hmm, I like ideas yeah
Weirdest and weirdest ideas that you can possibly get let's fly in the face of danger and see if something might be true
What if you what if one thing is true Dan just like Joe was saying yeah?
Just because he's lied a million times doesn't mean you won't find that one grain of gold
I didn't know about that civic coffee. Yeah, there we go. We did it outside of that. I don't think there was any ideas
That were interesting that were presented on this show. I think it was a disaster. I think it was stupid
I
Just I I here's a thought that I have never been able to escape ever since I was like really really young
It's helped me so far if like whenever I was like 10 years old I remember hearing
All of my friends have this
Conversation and I remember being in the middle of it talking about it and I remember thinking there's no possible way that ten-year-olds in
1990 blue are
Having a new or interesting thought so if I am having a conversation
Think for a second did somebody have this conversation several thousand years ago, and then maybe just read
Maybe read instead of being like so here's what I think about the universe and what we should do is we should give everybody
But you know like we got
Tribalism and we got to do shrooms and like hey, maybe somebody's fucking thought about it before. Yeah
Yeah, that is that is a perspective that it's important to have. Yeah, I do agree with you on that
I think that exploring ideas
Conversationally is a fun pastime and I think that that's what what a lot of spring
Do in college sure
And I think that it's what people do socially. I think it's a fun thing to do with friends totally
I don't know if it's always
Productive. I certainly know from listening to this that it's not entertaining. Yes. That's a good one. I don't know. I
Come away with this. I tried to like really distill down like the points
Mm-hmm that run through this because there are trends and all I could come up with are
Left versus right tribalism sure nonsense. Yeah, that seems to be a thing that Joe really wants to talk about all about interpretation
There's no possible way that the somebody could be correct. You got to overcome tribalism Joe really wants to point that out
Alex wants to talk about how famous Joe is. Mm-hmm and how great it is that he's on Spotify
And then Alex just is too overt and too obvious about his wanting to be a nation. Yeah, it's just it's it's tragic
it's it's
Like I keep saying it's cringe-worthy, but that's the only thing that's the only way I can describe it. Yeah, it's
Exposing his is vulnerable underbelly of desperation. I mean, what's what's wild to me is
Ostensibly, these are two professional
broadcasters
How can you have this boring of a conversation when you've been doing this or some?
facsimile of this job this very job that you are doing for 20 or 30 years and you come up with
This and this is what you've got and one of the people is the Jimmy Carson of our time
Jimmy Carson of our times man, you're wasting it. The other one's a close second. Yeah, you are no Ed McMahon, sir
No, yeah, so there you go folks. You got it. Yeah, there it is
You got stuff like everybody should do shrooms. Yep
I think I might have also only decided to do this episode because I came up with the title for it long in advance
And I was fourth try not a charm nice
I
Stuck
But we'll be back on Monday with a discussion of whether or not Alex moved to DC and is living in a tenement camp
Let's hope he is
Who fingers crossed? Yeah, that'll be good news. We'll be back then but tell them Jordan we have a website
We do have a website. It's knowledgefight.com. You bet it is
We're also on Twitter. We are on Twitter
It's at knowledge underscore fight and then go to bed George dramatic time you were also on Facebook
We are Facebook in Dallas. I choose red and if you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help
Out those still doing God's work. Yeah, we'll be back until then. I'm neo and Leo. I'm DC ex-clerk. I'm Daryl run to say
Don't you try out that rifle?
Andy in Kansas you're on the air. Thanks for holding
Oh Alex, I'm a person color. I'm a huge fan. I love your work. I love you