N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight.
Damn, Ed, Jordan, I am sweating.
N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight dot com.
It's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledge fight.
Knowledge fight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys.
Dan and Jordan.
Knowledge fight.
Riddle her.
I need money.
Andy and Kansas.
Stop it.
It's time to pray.
Andy and Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding us.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your room.
Knowledge fight.
N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight dot com.
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight dot com.
I love you.
Hey, everybody.
Welcome back to Knowledge Fight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes.
We like to sit around, take novelty beverages, and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are, Dan.
Jordan.
Dan.
Quick question for you.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today is cereals.
Okay.
I have gone...
Like the old radio cereals?
Like the shadow?
Like the...
I wish that was what I was saying.
No, I'm talking about breakfasts.
Oh.
I mentioned to you that I have been exploring the world of ordering groceries for the sake
of safety.
COVID.
And one of the things that has led me to do is more browsing than maybe I'm used to at
a grocery store.
Sure.
I kind of get in and get out at a grocery store, generally.
Absolutely.
I kind of know what I'm looking for, and I don't eat that many different foods.
Wearing blinders at the grocery store.
Go to the frozen pizza section, kachunk, kachunk.
And go home.
Yes.
I'm browsing through.
I've noticed that there are a number of cereals now that really excite me, but also offend
me.
Okay.
All right.
These are the cereals where everybody is playing each other's game.
Okay.
Everyone is in each other's lanes, and I don't know what's going on.
Oh, do you mean like Kellogg's Rice Krispies will suddenly have like a peanut butter ball
version?
Yes.
And you're like, no, no, that's Reese's Puffs.
You stay the fuck out of here, Rice Krispies.
And you have like Fruit Loops with marshmallows.
Yeah, and you're wrong.
You're working Lucky Chimes side of the street.
What are you doing here?
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it's weird because when I was a kid, I probably would have loved this.
Oh, gone ape shit.
Yeah, but now as a 36-year-old man, I'm looking at this and I'm like, God, I gotta try it,
but I don't want to.
No, it's the worst.
Everybody's fighting on a corner war.
It's the drug war all over again.
One thing I was thinking about doing, but I'm not sure I'm going to be able to pull
it off because I don't know if I'll actually be able to get all of them.
And I don't know how many of these hybrids there are, but it seems like there's a bunch.
I was thinking about trying to get a bunch and seeing who steals other people's gimmicks
best.
Okay.
All right.
Does Frosted Flakes, is that improved with marshmallows?
I don't know how it would work.
I'll tell you, the Chocolate Frosted Flakes, I tried those, absolutely disgusting.
They're delicious for the first three bites and then you're like, I'm not four years
old anymore, so this much sugar is going to kill me.
Yeah.
I'm going to go with a no.
I think that there's probably a lot of that in what I would find.
I did get the Lucky Charms, but with the regular pieces that aren't marshmallows are like
honey.
Oh, were those good?
No.
Kind of just like, I like regular Lucky Charms.
They're good.
They're magically delicious.
I do like how many people are trying new stuff, whatever.
It's like, guys, I have been with Lucky Charms for four, it's like I've been smoking Newport
since I was nine years old and you guys are going to come up with some bullshit.
Like the camel crush, the first time the camel crush happened, I'm like, this is an affront
against God.
How dare you combine these two flavors?
It's wrong.
But then.
They're great.
Yeah.
So maybe you should try all these series.
Yeah, I know you should.
So what about you?
The next spot, Dan, is The Avalanche has released a new album.
The Avalanche has released two albums in one decade, Dan.
That's insane.
Below in your mind, isn't it?
Yeah, I was like, wow, 15 years between Since I Left You and whatever they came out with
second.
Yeah, Wildflower.
Yeah, yeah.
Wow.
And then just now, We Will Always Love You released Friday, absolutely fantastic.
That's cool.
I don't want to be a hater, but I didn't really like their second album as much as I liked
Since I Left You back when I used to smoke a lot of weed when I was younger.
I mean, Since I Left You was kind of genre busting in that they really took sampling
too far.
Yeah.
They were like, hey, what if...
No, no, no.
I know you like the Amen break and we'll strengthen it.
What if instead we took 48 milliseconds and combined it with 48 milliseconds of 10 million
other songs?
Yeah.
And like I was just the right age and like I said, smoking tons of weed and Frontier
Psychiatrist like blew my mind.
It blew everybody's mind.
How did you get that parent?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The music video of it was so bizarre.
Totally.
I don't know how any other album they made could not kind of be a letdown based on the
experience of that at that time.
Sure, sure.
But I'll try and have an open mind for this other one.
You know, in 2001 you thought they were mind-melting geniuses who were going to change music forever
and then their next album was a really good album if you were good producers, but it's
not, you know, genre-busting, era-defining stuff.
I think the problem is the decade in between.
Like if you put out a sophomore album that's just serviceable or just good the next year,
it's more understandable than like waiting for Chinese democracy and it just being, just
being eh.
You can't do that.
That is fair.
That's fair.
This one's really good though.
You can't live up to that hype.
It's tough.
This one's great.
They got a bunch of really good guests on it.
They do a lot of like classic trip-hop stuff.
It almost sounds a little Portishead-y.
They get tricky to do a verse.
Then they go full disco.
They got some disco and then they got some classic avalanches walking songs, which is
what the avalanches do best.
I'll check it out.
So, Jordan, today we've got an interesting episode to go over.
We're going to be talking about The Weeknd with the band.
The band?
Yes.
He's that guy.
Genre-busting!
He was!
Okay, back in 2007, whenever his first EP's dropped.
I don't know enough about The Weeknd.
I know quite a bit.
We're going to be talking about the day that was 12-12-2020.
The day out on DC's...
Alex didn't move to DC.
No, I didn't think so.
But he did go to DC.
I assumed he would go.
And so today we're going to be taking a look at some of the events on the nation's capital.
Oh boy.
But first, before we get to that, let's take a moment, Jordan, to say thank you to some
folks who have signed up and are supporting the show.
Oh, that's a great idea.
So first, Bamboozer, thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks Bamboozer!
Thank you.
Next, Jim F. thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks Jim!
Thank you!
Next, Ryon H. thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you RyRy!
That's what I'm calling old Ryons come on.
Next, it could be Jel J-E-L-L-E.
I think it's probably Jel.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk!
Thank you very much!
Could be a reference to Cats!
I'm gonna go with Jelle.
Could be a Jellicle.
This could be a Jellicle Wonk.
It could be a Jellicle Wonk.
I don't know if they had one of those in the original Cats, though.
Next, Kabir S. Thank you so much, you are now a Policy Wonk.
I'm a Policy Wonk!
Thanks Kabir!
Thank you!
Next, Will O. Thank you so much, you are now a Policy Wonk.
I'm a Policy Wonk!
Thanks Will!
Thank you!
Next, Rebecca O. Thank you so much.
No relation.
Okay.
Uh, thank you, you're a Policy Wonk.
I'm a Policy Wonk!
Thanks Rebecca!
Thank you!
Thank you to a couple of people who donated on Elevated Love and we appreciate that very
much.
So, Andy K. Thank you so much, you are now a Technocrat.
And it goes on.
Thank you so much, you are now a Technocrat.
I'm a Policy Wonk.
Crikey, mate, that's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
Alright, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, alright?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much, Andy.
And thank you so much, Andy.
Thank you so much, Andy, and thank you so much, and it goes on.
Yes, thank you very much to the both of you.
If you're out there listening and you're thinking, hey, I enjoy the show, I'd like to support
these gents too, you can do that by going to our website, knowledgefight.com, clicking
the button that says support the show, or...
Or what you could do is you could go to a record store, go back into the back part of
the record store, start searching through all your favorite bands, maybe some disco
bands, maybe some esoteric stuff that other people haven't seen, find some generosity
in there.
Get a little bits of the best generosity from each one of those little crates over there,
combine it together to make something amazingly generous, and take it to your local bail fund
or charity.
Bigging in the crates!
Yep.
Uh, great.
Yeah.
Thank you.
So, Jordan.
Yes, sir.
Today.
What about it?
We are going to be talking about the rallies that happened in DC over the weekend.
Yeah, they went great.
Now, one thing that's really difficult for me is I'm not going to be addressing, really,
the street violence.
Sure.
And I think that that is a failing of our show to an extent, and that is because I don't
have enough time to get into it.
Not on our show, I mean in terms of, like, cover it with the seriousness and the focus
that I think the topic deserves.
Sure, we're a silly show about Alex Jones.
Yes.
I don't want to give short shrift to that, but at the same time, it falls slightly outside
of what I have the time to cover.
As we've seen with Rogan, half-assing it is sometimes worse than doing anything at all.
Yes, but I did not want people to think that I turn a blind eye to that kind of thing,
or tacitly accept such, such.
So Jordan, on Saturday, there were multiple rallies that were happening in DC, surrounding
the idea that this election had been stolen.
Stop that steal.
You know what I'm saying?
Sure.
They were both about the same thing, had the same theme, and even featured some overlapping
speakers.
It was super confusing, but I think I know what was up.
One of the rallies was being held by the Women for America First, the group that formed out
of the Tea Party, which is trying to use these protests and some of this unrest to secure
more power for the Republican Party, while simultaneously trying to make the Republican
Party as weird as possible, like they did with the Tea Party.
Yes, correct.
The other rally was called the Jericho March, which made no secret about just being an overtly
Christian extremist rally with some really outrageous planned speakers.
Well, if I remember my story of Jericho well, I believe those people were the nice ones.
They decided to end the siege by negotiating, coming to a fair solution for both parties,
right?
Sure.
Yeah.
That Jericho March had Ali Alexander in the mix, a friend from Infowars.
They also had the Cowboys for Trump, and noted asshole slash Congress member Paul Gosar.
It's really hard for me to tell what exactly was going on, and I kind of don't think that
these two were opposing rallies per se.
Your instinct would be to think that the Jericho March was for the religious zealots, whereas
the Women for America First would be the more restrained one.
But honestly, the rallies were almost identical.
Yeah, they're both the same people.
I watched both of them.
Yeah, they're the same people.
Not all the same people, but it's the same vibe.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's what I mean.
Yeah.
Both featured Mike Flynn giving the same speech, both had appearances from and got funding
from the MyPillow guy, and both were overwhelmingly religious.
Watching these rallies, one thing that's abundantly clear to me, and that's something that I think
is very important for us to bring up, is we're not dealing with politics here at all.
This is not politics.
This is a cult with some interest in politics as a means to gaining and retaining power,
and I don't really know how to talk about that without, like, I don't know.
I don't know how to engage with the ideas of a cult.
Um, I mean, I think the best way to engage with the ideas of cult is on a grand scale,
and what we should do to stimulate the economy is train 50% of the country in cult deprogramming
to help them with the other 50%.
That's a new deal.
I think that's a good way to do it.
It's like the Works Progress Administration.
Sure.
Yeah.
It's just, it's really difficult because it comes off, or it can be, like, misconstrued
as attacking religion to attack this kind of thing that's going on, and I don't have
any interest in attacking religion or Christianity, I have a problem with what this is.
Yeah.
And that's tough.
Because when we hear a person say that Bill Gates said X, Y, or Z in an interview, it's
really easy to go find that interview and discuss what's going on.
When we hear that same person say that God has chosen Donald Trump to be president, it's
not too difficult to say that they're a bit of a fanatic, and they're probably unwell.
The difficulty comes when there are two multi-hour rallies attended by thousands of people where
the speakers repeatedly and incessantly insist that God has chosen Trump to be president,
and everyone cheers.
Mm-hmm.
That's tough.
Yeah.
That is really fucked up.
We know where Alex is at, we know where his head is, we know what he's up to, and so I
thought maybe a good use of our time today would be to look at these rallies themselves,
and try and assess where we're at with all this, and see if it's something that we can
learn to talk about a little bit better, and see if there's anybody who pops up who is
a particularly good crazy.
Oh, good.
Maybe there'll be somebody who's like... If this is-
I don't think Hamamoto's coming back.
No.
I don't think Hamamoto got his invite for this one.
Daryl is on the outs.
I think we can let that one go.
Yeah.
He's still yelling at Linda Katehi out at UC Davis.
Okay.
No, but I figure like, hey, you've got one... I think each rally was at least four hours
long.
Jesus.
You've got a lot of speakers.
Yeah.
Maybe somebody is going to be like, all right, you got something, or maybe you got a weirdness,
I'm going to be interested in looking into.
All right.
So maybe that's worth our time.
So we're going to start here, Jordan, with the Jericho March.
This was hosted by Eric Mataxas.
I'm kind of aware of who this guy is.
He's like a Christian writer and a radio host, but I really don't know a ton about him.
And based on his work emceeing this event, that will probably be the way it stays, because
this dude is straight up boring as hell.
Oh, come on, man.
A whole lot of awful stage patter type material, and then just calls to praise the Lord.
Oh, boy.
Okay.
Yeah.
So we're starting with the one that's more explicitly religious, and you get that right
from the job.
So we're going to get some Ace Freely band talk, and then we're going to smooth into
the...
First of all, it's Paul Stanley.
Whatever.
How dare you.
Yes.
Eric Mataxas does have some things he needs to get off his chest.
Okay, there we go.
He comes in, he's like, hey, what's up, DC?
I heard y'all like the taste of alcohol.
All right.
Let's overthrow democracy forever.
All right, let's move on.
Who out there is drinking screwdrivers?
It doesn't start with that, it starts very religious.
We are here because we love the God of the Bible.
We are here because we believe he is the God of history.
We're here because we know that he is the God who does real miracles.
When his remnant cries out to him in humility and love and says, Abba, Father.
We need you, Abba, Father.
We are here today to cry out to the God of heaven, to ask him to have mercy on the greatest
nation in the history of the world.
So it's pretty overtly religious.
Yeah, that one's a little bit on the nose.
That's like maybe 15 seconds into the rally.
I'm glad we got the tone set.
We were worshipping the God of history.
All right.
Yikes.
So this rally itself, this Jericho march, was the product apparently of two people who
had a vision.
And Eric Metaxas is going to discuss that here.
Oh boy.
Now the man and the woman who didn't know each other until a little while ago, Rob Weaver
and Irina Grossu, okay, each of them independently, in case you didn't know the story, each of
them had an insane vision from God.
How would we know the story?
Rob Weaver told me this story a few nights ago.
He says he doesn't normally get visions like this and the Lord woke him up.
It's a dramatic story and he had this insane open vision of people gathered blowing shofars.
There were nuns there when he described it to me exactly.
The bad news is it looked nothing like this and you guys need to leave right now.
I was kidding.
That was a joke.
He had a vision from God.
When God gives you a vision, you don't need to know anything else.
You just praise him that he cares enough to show you what he is doing.
I have vision questions too.
We'll learn more about this vision later.
But the thing that I think is interesting is that is a terrible joke.
I would have to go with yes, that is a terrible joke.
But at the same time, that's what he's doing.
And I think actually, if I were the promoter or the booker of this, he's a perfect host.
No, he's doing a great job for what he's doing.
He comes off slightly charismatic.
It's not offensive, but you can still tell it's an attempt at humor.
He's personable to the audience that's the target of this rally.
But it's also trash.
Yeah, but it's unmemorably a bad joke where you're like, joke registered.
You know what, I'm not going to hold it against you.
We're just going to move on.
It does feel like somebody who's there for a check.
Who's like, I'll get paid.
Gotta clock in.
Yeah, I've done those gigs before.
It's almost a cut and paste kind of host joke.
And I think you see a lot of that if you do enough stand up and you can kind of get that
vibe from him.
But at the same time, I kind of prefer that to someone who's maybe taken too big a swing.
Sometimes that goes really badly.
I would give a lot of money to see this guy try and do crowd work at one of these rallies.
That would be brutal.
So we got these two people, they had a vision.
One is Rob Weaver.
He is an evangelical Christian.
And then Aria Grosu, who is a Catholic.
And so the two of them both had a vision and the, uh, yeah, we'll, we'll meet them a little
bit later, but that's why this is happening.
All right.
So this is happening because the evangelical Christians and the Catholics have finally
both received the independent message from God that they were looking for in order to
combine and put aside their previous doctrinal differences in order to take back Trump's
presidency.
Right.
Your whole fucking religion boils down to Trump, you pathetic shitbags.
That's the part that I really have trouble with is like, I have nothing against religion.
I have nothing against Christianity.
I have a real problem with the way in which there be like Christianity and Trump are being
melded.
Yeah.
I mean, when we're talking about this religion, I'm not going to shit on Christianity as a
as like quote unquote concept or religion as a whole.
But I will say that it is eminently reasonable to shit on your religion.
If you think that your ultimate battle of good and evil involves Donald fucking Trump,
that is tough to wrestle with.
Yeah.
Your religion is so tiny and weak and meaningless.
If that's, if that's what it is, yeah.
If it relies on Donald Trump, uh, yeah.
And when you hear things like this and it's just like, what we are, what God is doing
in the United States today by his grace.
And today we're going to see heaven move.
Heaven is going to move.
Thank you, Jesus.
Before I introduce my friend Mike Lindell, who's going to tell you to use the discount
code Eric because I would never do that.
That would be self serving before I introduced Mike Lindell.
I'd like to lead you in the pledge of allegiance.
So like he's talking about how God is going to make heaven move and then immediately he's
going to introduce the MyPillow guy and he gives a promo code.
God does not give promo codes.
Mike Lindell does.
Yeah, I get that.
But if you're at a religious rally and somebody gives you a promo code, then leave.
One of the problems that I find with both of these rallies is they are very clearly
funded by MyPillow.
He's very clearly.
It's spawncon?
Is this spawncon?
Is that what we're doing?
I think it might be.
At your religious rally, there's sponsored content.
Okay.
Fuck off.
I'm a bit worried that that is the case.
And that means that he gets to speak.
He gets a walk on roll.
You get to buy your way in.
Yeah.
So MyPillow guy.
Nothing says Jesus more than buying five minutes of stage time.
So right before this event, there had been that Supreme Court had thrown out the case
in Pennsylvania.
Yeah, they screamed it was too legally good.
Yes.
And the MyPillow guy has some news about this that he received.
First of all, he says that Sidney Powell called him at two in the morning to give him some
news.
Good.
Why is she calling you at two in the morning?
He's the MyPillow guy, Dan.
He's the front coordinator.
I got problems with this story.
Hello, everyone.
I'm going to start off by bringing you some hope.
Last night, about two in the morning, I got a text from Sidney Powell's team, and the
Texas lawsuits had nothing to do with what she's been working hard on.
And she filed her lawsuits with the Supreme Court for Georgia, Wisconsin, Michigan, and
Arizona.
And everything that I've been telling you for three weeks now is true.
I have seen it.
The fraud is 100%, and Donald Trump will be our president for four more years.
By a pillow.
Wow.
Yeah.
So sorry, I said Pennsylvania.
I meant that Texas space.
Yeah.
All these sad attempts to overturn the election mixed up.
But yeah, I like the idea that Sidney Powell texted him and was like, hey, that had nothing
to do with me.
Don't worry about me.
I'm on crazy adventure number four over here.
This looks like a big setback, but that was not our deal.
Hold on.
I'm not even there.
Watch out.
I got to watch this guy rip a heart out of another dude.
I like that.
And it does set the tone, kind of, for the event, and that is everybody is joyous.
Turns out that there was this big setback where Texas and, you know, like all these
people had signed on, all these Republican members of the House had signed on with this
and then it didn't work.
It seemed like, hey, that was kind of almost like Ron Paul winning the Iowa caucus of this
cycle.
There's that moment of hope and then it's gone, but no, my pillow guy says Sidney Powell
texted him at two in the morning and said, hey, be cool.
So wild.
Yeah.
So I would buy this making sense if I knew that all of the rich Republicans and business
owners and all that stuff were all like buying a lot of property in a different country right
now and all of them slowly moving all of their stuff away.
So I get all this like edging with the lawsuits is them buying time to make good their escape
before they pull the trigger and everybody explodes, you know, but otherwise this doesn't
make any sense.
What are you doing?
My pillow, you're wasting a lot of money.
He must be making a lot too though.
He must be.
Yeah.
But they're not going to, they don't make any sense.
They're all magic.
Yeah.
I don't know.
But also when you consider, I mean, not, you know, this guy, the my pillow guy is out there,
man.
Yeah.
I can see that.
And basically you listen to him talk for like two minutes and you're like, Oh yeah, I get
why you'd make bad business decisions.
Yeah, that's fair.
Here he discusses in a rambling way, his story of having a prophetic dream about how he was
going to meet.
Why does everybody got dreams all of a sudden?
Everyone.
I'm sick of dreams.
So he has a dream about how he's going to meet Trump and then he, he, he does.
And look, I, and also I want to say really quick, he talks a bunch about how he's a recovering
crack addict and I'm not beaten up on that.
You're not making fun of that at all is just sort of background dressing to this story
that's important.
Good for you.
I got up to 2015 and I had a dream.
I get these dreams, these, these prophetic dreams.
And one of them was that I would meet Donald Trump in a room and I'm going, why would I,
why would I be meeting with Donald Trump in a room or whatever?
I was just some, some guy from Minnesota.
Right?
Well, and two things in the summer, buying appointments kept happened to me.
I was invited to the national prayer breakfast when, when Ben Carson was still running for
president randomly picked out of 12 people to pray with him in a room and I wasn't even
saved yet.
I'm going in.
I don't know how to pray.
I don't know.
You know, I was all nervous, but that was set up by God, you know, and, and then there
were these things kept happening to the summer of 2016 and I'm on a plane to, to California
and, and I'm, I'm sitting in the bulkhead and I opened this magazine that was about
Donald Trump.
And I said, you know, of course it was August or the late July of 2016.
And I said, God, I said, if I'm supposed to be Donald Trump and be part of this, whatever's
going on in our country, I need to know right now.
And at that moment in time, my phone dinged and it was an email, Mike, will you, this
is Donald Trump.
Will you meet me in New York city at Trump tower?
I go, God, you know, I don't believe that story.
I don't believe a word of that bullshit.
Not for one second.
Yeah.
Jesus Christ.
I'm, I'm, I'm not buying it.
No.
Uh, but it's fun.
And the crowd will like it.
Uh, yeah.
But I just, this story is, is, is I just was listening to this, I'm like, Hey man, is this
an event?
Jesse Ventura character.
It kind of feels fucking, this is Minnesota stuff, man.
That's, that's what I'm saying is these dudes sound like Minnesota.
It must be if they sound almost exactly the same.
So many vocal similarities.
Yeah.
That's fair.
I don't know.
I, we need to move the pressure now up back onto religious people.
You know, it used to be that when you were shitting on religion, that was like, that
was often a discriminatory or being mean.
Now we've got to push the responsibility back on there.
Religious people, if you don't want to be made fun of, don't listen to the, my pillow
guy.
That's on you now.
But the problem is he has so much money.
Yeah.
See, that's still on you.
All religion jokes are fine.
They are non-discriminatory until the majority of religious people are like, let's not do
my pillow guy.
I don't agree.
I don't agree with that.
Uh, axiom.
I don't believe I don't agree with that.
Uh, but that the issue comes down to like religion is fine, but this isn't about religion.
This is about wanting a Christian nation.
And my pillow guy is pretty clear about that.
This has been a spiritual battle in our country for decades.
This is a spiritual battle and we are in the, we're going to, this is the start of the greatest
revival in history for one nation under God.
And that God is Jesus.
Amen.
God bless you all.
Jesus wouldn't even say, and we're going to look back and we're going to say that all
had to happen in the name of Jesus.
God bless you.
Wow.
Hallelujah.
I love you, Mikey.
You know, you want to know miracle of God.
He went 60 seconds short.
Haha.
Good job.
Whoa boy.
Um, that guy is killing it.
Yeah.
I mean, almost everything that Mike is saying, uh, my pillow guy is saying is like, okay,
yeah.
I mean, if that was just at a, like a church revival or something like that, I don't think
I'd have any issue with it.
Like there's an awakening coming and you know, like God is, uh, you know, so important in
our life.
The problem is this is a political rally.
You know, I know it's of a religious character, but like the reason you're having this rally
is because Trump lost an election.
Yeah.
You're not having this because of like, no, no, he had a prophetic dream.
It's the combination of the two.
That's just fucking, uh, it's, uh, it's terrifying.
Yeah.
I think probably one of the reasons that I would have an easier time, like suggesting
that this was, I suppose non-religious is just cause I know too much about how Christianity
is supposed to work according to that book they say they like a lot.
I've read a little bit of it.
Yeah.
I know too much about it and all of this stuff is like, we're Christians and we want a Christian
nation.
And I'm like, have you motherfuckers even opened it?
And also here's a promo code from my pillow.
Exactly.
And the thing that makes me even more scared really when I think about it is that, you
know, there's this combination of this stuff, this Christian nationalism, and then it's
also intersecting with this deification, uh, admiration and, and, and, and just love of
not only Trump, but also general Flynn, who is somebody who's a hero, the QAnon folk and
has been, uh, uh, Q, QE himself.
And I hear Eric Metaxas, uh, teases, uh, Flynn's appearance in a little bit.
We have general Michael Flynn is coming.
Oh, Oh, then you've heard of him.
Oh, I'm so impressed.
Very good.
You guys, uh, that's awesome.
He is such a hero.
He has been such hell.
He's a Patriot.
He believes in the Lord of the Bible.
All right.
A lot of the people, the center of this administration love Jesus.
Don't you find that ironic?
I don't know what he's even saying.
I don't know what that's supposed to mean at all.
No, but that's the, you, you asked for like, why is he hero?
And then Metaxas told you because he believes in the God of the Bible.
I really don't feel like that's enough.
That's what, I mean, that's what they're saying.
I think another problem I have is that they are cheering for thoroughly fictitious people.
Flynn, the imaginary Flynn.
Yeah.
The imaginary Flynn is who they are cheering for.
Michael Flynn has no resemblance to that character whatsoever.
Yeah.
He's a shit bag from way before if they knew his history, they would, if I were him, I
would lean into the fan fiction way more than way more of the fan fiction.
Yeah.
Your actual track record is fucking evil.
So now Metaxas brings out, uh, Rob Weaver and Irina Grossu, who are the, uh, the, uh,
evangelical and the Catholic dreamers.
And, uh, Rob, I would say his description of this vision that he had is a little bit
lackluster.
Um, this event will be going on for the next few hours, lots of speakers, more music.
Um, but I want to tell you about how it started on November 5th, I was really, um, troubled
by the election and what I knew was wrong.
I think everybody in this country knows that something is wrong.
Can I get an amen anyone?
So I just call, I called out to God and I literally felt something pushing in my side
in the morning.
Quite frankly, I thought it was a remote, but it wasn't, you know, I, somebody, something
was pushing.
I heard a voice that said, it's not over.
So can I hear it's not over because God said it's not over and the, and the next part of
the vision, I sat down and I literally saw this and I saw marches going around the Capitol.
I saw marches going around all six of the swing States that are also going on today.
So hello.
If you guys can hear us there.
Um, so every one of them, let's, let's, let's give them a shout.
So this was birthed from a vision or a miracle.
That's not much of a vision.
Wow.
Yeah.
So does that mean that, uh, God was poking him?
Well, does that mean that for like, say the women's March was that inspired by God?
Must've been.
Or did, did, did the devil send that dream?
Devil probably.
Are God and the devil only sending competing dreams for rallies and shit now?
Devil's clearly a better organizer too because the turnouts have been much larger to the
point where, uh, these MAGA folk will just post pictures of left wing marches.
Their marches.
Yeah.
It does seem strange.
They should, they should get in contact with the devil.
He knows what's up.
Yeah.
He has a good street team.
The, the, uh, Robin arena are, are just there and you know, they had their vision.
Hooray.
Good for them.
I had a dream of people walking around DC, which could never have been given to me from
any other source other than God.
And he got poked.
Um, so that's true.
Then they have a prayer.
There's a lot of praying on this that I will, a lot of people through both of these rallies,
everybody wants to get up there and do the Lord's blood to do a good prayer.
You know, like how in the book it said, make sure that you pray loudly and performatively
for others and not for God.
It reminds me of like, okay, so like in early times, uh, in wrestling, you didn't want in
your first match someone to go through a table, let's say, because then if you want to do
that in the, the headline of the match, I feel like everybody is not respecting that
in terms of the Lord's prayer.
Like everyone's doing it, but everyone wants to, can you, I don't know.
It's just, it feels less, save your Lord's prayer for the end of the show.
Right.
Or Flynn.
I mean, he's clearly the headliner.
It's his to do or not do.
Right.
I don't know.
Anyway.
Uh, they pray and uh, we get a prayer that Steve Pechenik would be very proud of.
And then the stage gets interrupted.
Father, I pray a special blessing on Melania Trump, one of the best first ladies we've
ever had in history.
And I'm so tired of people coming against her father.
So go on.
Why?
I pray and her children and all the children in Jesus mighty name.
Thank you Lord.
Amen.
Thank you guys.
Oh, actually we want to introduce these Ollie Alexander from stop the seal.
So Ali had sort of walked out on stage prayer.
See the devil's a way better organizer.
So Ali walks out along with Ed Martin of the Phyllis Schlafly Eagle Forum and they are
apparently partnered with the, uh, the Jericho March.
And that's kind of interesting.
Um, because Ali starts talking about like, you know, Hey, we got, we got a lot of fun
things coming up.
We got general Flynn.
Then he says something that really struck my ears.
Today is going to be historic.
We have general Flynn.
We'll have the president of the sky or on the road and we got a couple of other characters
in a spirit of unification.
Thank y'all.
You got a couple of other characters in the spirit of unification.
That's very strange.
Also the presidents in the sky, they, uh, they have, uh, been promoting that Trump is
going to fly over in a Marine one.
Great.
Uh, and I think he does show up like during Flynn's speech, maybe.
I don't know.
Uh, there was a helicopter flying over at some point.
Straight up.
We're doing straight up fascist Nazi imagery.
I honestly don't know if Trump was even in it.
No, I doubt he was.
Why would you?
You wouldn't need to be.
Yeah.
They'll just see the helicopter and be like, eh, the president's in there.
Why would you actually go?
Symbol of president.
What is he going to wave out the helicopter window?
Get the fuck out of here.
So Ed Martin of the Eagle forum, the Schleifly Eagles.
Yes.
Yeah.
He wants, while he's up on stage, he's a magnanimous type.
Oh, of course.
And he wants to give it up to the good media.
Oh, Hey guys, we're gonna, we're gonna right now.
I'd ask you to join me in prayer if you don't mind before we do, I want to say thank you
to the Epic times for helping stream so much of this live Josh and, and RSBN bar, the brothers
at RSBN brothers and sisters.
Thank you for what you do to make it so people, yeah.
And victory, victory TV and one America news.
I mean, go down the list, right?
And I just want to say when we gathered at the Capitol the other day around the world
in Japan and China and Taiwan around the world, they're looking at America because we're a
beacon on the Hill and we can't let the light go out.
There cannot be the light going out for the world and for each other.
Let's pray.
One name conspicuous in its absence on that list, especially considering this dude standing
right next to Ali Alexander, who's constantly on info, all these great media outlets really
doing everything for it.
I just, I can't get to them all.
I'm going to name as many as I can.
Epic is great.
One American news.
Look, I'm running out of time.
I can't name anymore.
I just want to say, you know, yeah.
So look, they may not plug in for wars, but they are willing to let Alex give a little
speech.
Okay.
And so at this point, the mission impossible theme plays.
Oh no.
Here it comes.
Folks in the spirit of unity, I'd like to bring out my new friend, Alex Jones.
Is it, I think his name is Alex Jones.
Can't believe that many people cheer for him.
You know, see this makes sense though.
It does like as a wrestling, this is a wrestling show.
This is what you want.
You bring, you bring Alexander to be like, yeah, that's what you want.
And that's why people are cheering.
He is a star.
He's a show.
Yeah.
You want to hear Rob and Irena Grosu talk about their lackluster dream.
I had a dream that people would be here.
How excited are you going to get for the MyPillow guy telling a long story about his dream?
I think it was, I think it was December 20th, 19th, no, this was November 11th.
No, this was December 20th at 4.50 p.m.
Eric Matexis is a good host or whatever to keep the thing moving along, but he's not
going to get you riled up.
No.
Alex fucking Jones is.
That's what he's going to do.
Yeah.
That's what he's there for.
Yeah, exactly.
Now it's embarrassing.
Very.
Didn't even get your name.
Your rally is now the one that allowed Alex to speak at it.
So congratulations for that.
Yep.
But Alex does what Alex does.
And that is more or less just yell his ass off about nonsense.
Like what they want.
Applause line.
Exactly.
And Jesus Christ is King!
Not David Rockefeller, not Bill Gates, not Barack Obama, not Joe Biden, but Jesus Christ
is King!
And God gave us and rose up Donald Trump to stand against the enemy and draw out the enemy.
So as dark as some of these days are, understand, this is the beginning of the great revival
before the Antichrist comes!
Two quick points.
That's not how it works in the Bible!
I thought Obama was the Antichrist, Alex.
Don't worry about it.
And the second point, I believe on our last episode, he was calling Marilyn Monroe a cum
dump.
He was doing that.
Yeah, yeah.
Where are we?
There's a little bit going on.
What are we doing?
I like the idea of Jesus standing next to Alex Jones giving him that, hey, but I'm about
peace.
I was going to feed all these people.
Okay, well, let's just skip past that part then.
Let's just get to the Book of Revelations.
You realize there isn't a revival before-
Hey, Jesus.
No.
Do you understand?
I'm even going to blow your mind a little bit more with this.
Jesus.
No one's going to clap for that weak shit.
The Antichrist convinces almost all Christians to believe in him over-
We got a blowout sale.
It's actually almost like, so they would focus on a single person instead of the Lord and
really be like, this person is the true leader and we're going to give all of our allegiances
to him without thinking about it.
And then because of that-
You sound like a damn globalist.
You know what?
You're right.
I'm going to have to go.
So it turns out we're in Revelation, according to Alex.
And again, this is all just applause lines.
World government, implantable microchips, Satanism, it's out of the open, the Bible
is fulfilled, Revelation is fulfilled, Jesus Christ is fulfilled, God Almighty is in charge,
and we follow that mighty God.
Is this who?
You look at the miserable globalist, you look at people like Bill Gates, and you look at
people like Mark Zuckerberg and the rest of them, they are miserable slaves of Satan.
And we pray for them and hope that the Holy Spirit can still touch their soul.
Like this is embarrassing, but you get why people enjoy this.
Oh yeah, this is great.
It's incredibly dumb.
This is what you go for.
It's exciting.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is star quality.
Totally.
Whatever it is.
But you can also tell if you watch this that it really takes a lot out of him.
Like you can tell that he's pushing to get all this yelling going.
His voice is-
He's exhausted.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is difficult.
Yeah.
He's not a young man anymore.
No, but you got to do it.
We pray for President Donald John Trump in this incredibly serious moment.
And we pray for all the women in America who the system's trying to lie to to kill their
babies.
And we say, don't kill your babies.
The enemy has been forced out in the open.
World government is here.
And the system is publicly stealing this election from the biggest landslide and the biggest
political realignment since 1776.
I mean, just every single line.
He knows how to frame a sentence in a way that will end with like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not in like a necessarily bad way, but like, you know, you see comedians who like, you
know, structuring a line, you know, like, oh, what you're saying is funny, but the way
you've written that or the way you're saying that is not funny.
It doesn't lead people to the reaction that you're looking for.
Whereas Alex, every single sentence that he's saying is specifically meant to make people
yell at the end of it.
And that's, I mean, don't do this in the middle of your event.
I don't think it's a good idea.
Like you're going to make everyone else look like trash.
It's poor, it's poor quality.
Just don't let him on your show at all.
How is it that I could, I could run a better fucking rally just using the same principles
of booking a show, a comedy show.
I bet you, I bet you couldn't though, cause you'd have no idea who any of these people
are.
Oh, that's true.
I wouldn't have them at my rally.
You'd see a bunch of random names on a list like, what, I don't know what this person's
like.
I wonder if I could do that.
That would be an interesting challenge.
I'll take maybe 10 seconds of each of these people speaking and I'll see if I can't make
a lineup out of them that would make more sense.
That would be a great idea.
Wouldn't that be a fun game?
Yeah.
I might try and put that together.
That'd be fun.
All right.
So anyway, the big problem that I see with all of this, and I'm going to keep stressing
this, is the insistence on what you describe as like Christian nationalism and the idea
that your God is the only real God and you know, like just imagining being someone who
is not a, you know, a Christian of this stripe in the audience and think about how uncomfortable
you'd be.
Our God is the God of the universe.
Our God is the God of strength and honor and will and God is in control and God is on our
side.
Because it's not like, it's the Jericho march and you know, there is a religious character
to it, but it's also partnered with Ali Alexander in Stop the Steal and the Phyllis Schlafly
Eagle Forum.
You know, like it's not just, it's just, it's terrifying.
I mean, everything that they're saying though is screaming out a different form of we cannot
coexist.
We will not accept coexisting.
It's us or nothing.
That's it.
Yeah.
There is a, and to be fair, so far the main speakers that we've heard are the MyPillowGuy
and Alex.
Sure.
And it's not, you know, to be indicative of like everybody is unable to coexist.
These voices that are being welcomed here are fucked.
Yeah.
I mean, but even then, like the best you could say for so many of these people would be like,
Hey, hey, we can coexist so long as you stay under my boot, then we'll be fine.
Yeah.
So many people who have no idea about anything that has to do with the religion of Christianity
think that the crucifixion was a bad thing.
You know, like, Oh no, if only we could have stopped it.
No, that's not how it works.
No, no.
It was almost like crucial.
Yeah.
No one really thinks that, you know, it was necessary for the atonement and it was almost
preordained if you will.
Yeah.
So, but Alex also understands this.
Okay.
Good.
He's not, he's not one of these guys who would have like tackled the Romans or something.
So Judas is a good guy then.
I don't know.
Okay.
Christ's crucifixion was not our defeat.
It was our greatest victory.
When he rose again on the third day, he broke the chains of hell and death.
We have the deed to this planet.
We have the deed to eternal life and we praise Jesus Christ and the father.
Wow.
That's scary.
Yeah.
That's terrifying.
He has the deed to the planet.
Yeah.
I don't think that somebody could scream at me.
No.
So in this next clip, Alex gets into the first amendment and you know, stuff about like freedom
of religion.
But he's also gone too fast.
He's, he's, he's burned a lot of gas.
Yeah.
He's, he's out of it.
And so he has a little trouble.
Congress shall make no law, establishing the establishment of religion or prohibiting the
free exercise thereof, all Congress shall make no law, respecting the establishment
of religion or the free exercise thereof.
Our forebearers did not have separation of church and state as they spin it.
It means the state has no jurisdiction over any of us.
That's not true.
That's quite, quite an extension of the, uh, the, the state has no jurisdiction over any
of us.
I'm pretty sure they weren't, I'm pretty sure they weren't like Congress shall make no law
respect with respect to the free exercise of religion.
But what that actually means is Christians are free of laws.
We get to live however we want to.
Yeah.
If you can just create an excuse that's religiously based in heavy quotes, then the state can't
do anything like you can kill for your religion.
Yeah.
I don't, uh, I don't know.
I feel like that's what he's saying pretty much.
Yeah.
But also it's like these thoughts are not fleshed out.
It's just yelling.
Yeah.
And they're there for people to scream.
Hooray.
Yeah, you bet.
And here was Alex's lightning rod that he put out in order to get attention.
Okay.
So I don't know who's going to the white house in 38 days, but I sure know this Joe Biden
is a globalist and Joe Biden will be removed one way or another.
Nice.
Cause that was the clip that got the big amount of attention on the internet because people
fairly accurately interpret that as a veiled threat towards Joe Biden.
Oh, why is that?
I get that response, but it's also exactly why Alex said what he said.
It's almost certainly not legally actionable as a threat and if the secret service end
up talking to him about it, that's even better.
That's super cool for him.
Yeah.
Alex would love that.
I got a visit from the secret service, so you know that what I said was powerful.
Yup.
They're scared of me.
Honestly, when I heard that, I thought it was pretty tame for Alex.
And considering how up in arms people were like, there are articles written about it.
Like, yeah, I guess it takes on a slightly different character when he's yelling those
things in front of a crowd who then cheer.
But if you heard Alex say this and you think that's him crossing a line, all that means
is that you never listened to it.
Yeah.
I was, I was going to say, I saw his name in the news and I was like, well, can't check
on that, but if that's what it was for, Dan, I have surprising news for a lot of people.
Yeah.
And that line there is an attention trap.
That is a trap that people fall into.
And I understand why they do.
And I honestly don't know if the best thing to do is ignore it, but if you pay attention
to it, that gives him free press.
And that's why he implied on a stage that Biden would be removed one way or another.
Right.
I mean, I guess with Alex, the reality is he has nothing to back that thread up with
at all.
And all he gets from it is attention for making that threat.
And you know, I understand why you'd be like, Hey, what the fuck is going on here?
But at the same time, it's like, Alex is going, Alex makes money because he says stupid shit
like that.
And you go, Oh my God, no.
And then we do it all in two months.
Yeah.
I mean, that's kind of the theme of the show.
So Alex slows down a little bit and wants to talk about my man, G-dubs, George Washington.
Oh, our, our great first president, we literally are here on his farm.
That's where we're at.
George Washington didn't want to be king and every serve two terms that set that precedent.
He left.
He was a very quiet man.
I didn't talk about his beliefs when he was a Christian, but those that knew him privately
knew, he knew God controlled battlefields.
God controlled governments.
God controls the games and all his success was because of his love of God.
So this rally is being held on the national mall in Washington, DC, George Washington's
farm is now a national landmark called Mount Vernon, which is about 16 miles South and
in the state of Virginia.
Nah, come on now.
As for Washington's religious beliefs, that's actually a matter that even scholars in the
field of George Washington studies aren't fully settled on.
Yeah.
Mostly because of what Alex brings up.
He is correct, like Washington was really private about his beliefs.
The point is Alex can make that claim about Washington knowing that God runs everything
and all this and the seriousness of his beliefs, but Alex could never back that up.
He could never prove that.
Why would you?
Yeah, you just make that claim and it's good.
I mean, that's good for him because like, you know, even if he were talking to a Washington
scholar, they would be able to tease out more nuance to his beliefs.
They wouldn't be able to be like, you're lying.
Yeah.
I mean, looking at what they do with a guy who is alive and real and how they've created
a false story for him, we have no chance of them not trying to claim the founding father
said fucking whatever it is they want, you know?
True.
So Alex gets back to talking about how his God is the real God.
Sure.
So never forget, we worship the true God that created the universe and all of us.
And the satanic globalist trying to take control of us and trying to play God are fallen and
are failed.
And we need to just keep our eyes on Christ and never back down and never surrender.
Keep your eyes on Christ and away from politics.
Like he said, you remember how he said that.
Also get ready to overthrow the government.
Yeah, exactly.
I don't recall him being like, Hey, render unto Caesar what Caesar's cause we're going
to fuck him up later.
So you were making a joke about Jesus standing next to Alex on stage.
He's not there.
But somebody is.
And that's Owen Schroyer.
Okay.
Slight downgrade.
A little bit down.
Owen Schroyer is standing there on stage and Alex hands the mic off to him.
Oh no.
Now listen to this clip.
Oh no, Owen.
Listen to this clip of Alex saying, Oh, he's going to let Owen talk because it sounds like
he's going to do a fucking ad.
Okay.
He doesn't, but it sounds like he's about to do an ad.
I'm going to turn this over to my buddy for two minutes.
My great co-hosted in full wars.com, Owen Schroyer, and then the next great, the next
great guests are coming up here, but remember this, it really sounds like the next great
guest.
Yeah.
It sounds like he's about to remember this self-prostate guard.
We are having our Easter sale in December.
So Alex finishes up his stuff before he ends off the baton to Owen.
You know how 666 is the devil's number?
Sure.
Why not?
1776.
That's God's number.
Yeah.
It doesn't sound right.
God ordained this Republic to stand against the satanic empires, the Nazis and the communists
and others.
And so 1776 is God's number of victory over the satanic 1984.
God bless you all.
And I salute you.
Thank you, Jesus.
And that's, uh, that's Alex's speech.
So important numbers to God.
Yeah.
He's a real numbers guy.
Uh huh.
1776 is God's number because the United States was ordained by God to stand up to Nazis.
Yep.
I remember that.
There's a little complexity to that.
Uh huh.
I mean, so what happened then whenever we grabbed all their scientists and didn't, and
then weren't like, Hey, could you guys quit being Nazi?
And we're just like, eh, you guys are great.
Can you phrase that question in number form?
1944?
So Owen, he's not great after that.
Cause how could you be?
Sure.
I mean, Alex just yelled the applause line after applause line.
He's worn out the audience for like excitement.
So Owen, like this is so great.
God, what a sad man.
Boy, look at what we have here today.
What started with one man on public access television is now millions of Americans in
the streets of DC.
So many problems.
Started with one man on local access television.
He's pretending that Alex did all of this.
Like he created this entire event.
They're only all there for him.
And then he's also saying that there's millions of people there, which there are not.
Oh boy.
There are not.
There are too many.
Owen, Owen, Owen.
Yeah.
Oh boy.
So we got to do a little admin at this point.
Eric Metaxas comes out and he's got to maybe, you know, reset the room a little bit.
People got a little bit too excited.
It's like at the dance hall, the DJ can only play so many bangers in a row before you got
to have one where everybody gets to sit down and maybe slow dance, you know, that kind
of thing.
I think people got too excited and they're whipping their flags all around and it's a
problem.
I've got a little housekeeping.
They said to me that these flags in the front, when there, when there's a speaker, they're
blocking the video and this is being live streamed all over the place.
So if you could just drop the flags whenever the speaker is speaking or the prayer is praying,
dropping them means taking them down.
You probably don't realize the term drop means down with the flag.
Could you do that?
Flags is what is that?
A Korean flag.
Bring that down.
What is that?
A Kung Fu martial arts flag.
Bring that down.
Come on.
Seriously.
Cause we want everybody.
There's a lot of people who couldn't be here.
They're watching this on live stream.
Yeah.
Put these flags down.
That's a weird, that's a weird little bit of just tossed off.
I don't know what's going on.
Yeah.
I don't know what that flag he's referring to is.
And also there is a brown station wagon with its horns going off right now.
Could somebody please?
It's a brown station wagon license plate CE 9429.
Yeah.
So, uh, he gets, he gets these flags down right in time.
For the man, the myth, Ali Alexander to come out and give a little bit of a speech.
And he's, he's basically out here saying, Hey man, look, now is the time that moral
people, moral people are deciding whether or not this presidency and this government
itself is legit.
Great.
I think that we are making history.
I think that today, today is when moral Americans are deciding whether our government is legitimate
or illegitimate.
I think that this is a signal to the deep state that we're not going to tolerate a Joe
Biden presidency.
I'm going to tolerate it.
Yeah.
So he's saying essentially that all of us are going to determine whether or not this
is a legitimate government and the deciding thing will be whether or not Trump is installed
again.
And great.
Ali is a little threatening.
There's an interesting thing that I noticed through these two rallies.
The one with the women for Trump is largely not about destroying the GOP.
Sure.
Ali is threatening the GOP.
I like it.
I don't know if every speaker here is interested in destroying the Republican party, but Ali,
who's one of the organizers of this, is definitely open to that discussion.
I think it's a great discussion to have.
So not only will he destroy the GOP, he will also shut down all of the cities in this country.
All of them, Ali.
Our truckers will shut down the city.
Unionize!
Why isn't anybody clapping?
We will build and occupy DC full of patriots here, won't we?
We can do all things through Christ who strengthens us.
So to my Republican colleagues, put down those flags so that they can stream.
Please.
Dude.
Yes, you.
Thank you.
Really hung up on those flags.
How can you want to be led by such whiners like these people?
Very soft.
They're such whiners.
So Ali, he's gonna shut everything down and he's gonna do this with the help of cool media
outlets.
A few shout out to RSBN.
Whoa.
RSBN.
And One American News.
One American News.
And Newsmax.
Newsmax.
That was loud.
Epic Time.
NTDTV.
Never heard of it.
We don't need Fox News anymore, do we?
No.
No Infowars.
You just had Alex Jones up here.
You basically work there.
Why didn't you say Infowars?
Alex's whole premise is like, no one will say Infowars because we're too dangerous.
You have Ali Alexander.
You guys won't say Infowars because you're too toxic.
That is something that is very consistent.
That is so funny.
He is still on the outside, even with this completely wacky media landscape.
So Ali is really thrilled about this guy named Mo Brooks, who apparently has come out, he's
a member of Congress in the House, and he's said that, hey, look, even if the Electoral
College comes back and says, hey, Biden's the president, I'm gonna object.
You got it, man.
You took him down.
Ali is excited.
Thank God for Congressman Mo Brooks.
He has said that he will object to the House certification on January 6th.
And we need some of his colleagues to join him, don't we?
We expect them to join him, don't we?
Or we will throw them out of office.
Good luck.
Yeah.
But it doesn't stop there.
The threats against the Republicans who don't support Mo Brooks.
Threaten them.
Let me tell the Republican Party that if one of these senators do not join Mo Brooks, we
will burn the Republican Party down and we will make something new.
Oh, no.
Yeah, you're so threatening.
I mean, look, I would say that that response is a little bit not good that we have.
And that is because, like, well, in 2009, some of the similar rhetoric was flying around
at early Tea Party rallies, and it would have been very easy to be like, yes, destroy the
Republican Party.
But you see that when that effort happens, it's not like it cripples the party.
It ends up pushing extreme voices closer to the mainstream, or the mainstream goes towards
the crazy voices, as is more often the case, and we end up where we are now.
So I don't think that they're going to be capable of doing this, but encouraging this
sort of inner GOP fighting, I don't know if it's great.
Because it does also lead to the possibility of people like Ali or Nick Fuentes or Alex
Jones coming into a more relevant position than they would be otherwise.
I think you're right, presupposing that we do nothing, which is what happened with the
Tea Party.
We all sat by and laughed as they fought and we were like, ha ha ha, let them fight, instead
of using this as an opportunity to sabotage both wings and fuck them up together.
Like what we're doing is watching, like what they have done so successfully is constantly
push a wedge between the left and the center and the Democratic Party.
That's the best thing that the Republicans know how to do, is whenever there's the internecine
squabbles from the Democrats, the Republicans jump in and start throwing shit at the wall
too, to see if they can cause more conflagrations in between us.
And every time this happens on the right, the Democrats look back and they're like,
well, I bet the reasonable head shall prevail this time.
And it's insane.
Yeah, yeah, that does seem to be, I don't know, it's tough because I do want to laugh
also.
Yeah, me too, it's so funny.
I'd like to find a way to use this as a politically useful moment, but also laugh.
Well, I mean, I think the thing that, like I feel for these idiots kind of in a way,
not the leaders, I mean the people at the rally.
I feel for people's aunts and uncles and grandparents, like I feel for them.
Sure.
I don't feel for Ali.
No, no, absolutely not.
No, I mean the people in the rally, because they are being told, don't feel for Ali, feel
for the rally.
Yes.
No, I mean the thing that I want to scream at all of these people is, look, if you want
what they are telling you you want to get, then you have to start a shooting war.
Those are your options.
None of this shit that they're selling you is real.
They're wasting your time.
So if you really want to balls up, then start a shooting war or stop going to these dumb
ass rallies.
The people who are taking the rhetoric that you are digesting seriously are beating up
people on the streets.
Exactly.
And that is the unfortunate reality of the rhetoric and what you are acclimating yourself
to.
Exactly.
Yeah, that would be worthwhile for them to realize.
And the fruition of specifically what this type of rally is about, you get your goals,
you end up in a Christian theocracy.
And I don't think that anybody, I don't think most people really actually want that.
No.
There's all those people who love Christianity and they're super religious, but then they
get into those situations where they have to apply it and they're like, well, maybe
not this time.
You know what?
I'm still a morally good person, but this time I'm not going to act in this way.
You know, tonight I'm going to go out and get drunk and I'm going to have a really good
night.
And instead in a Christian theocracy, you're fucking killed for it.
You know, like it's that kind of shit.
Let's say you're a pastor and you marry, you know, you're already married and then you
end up banging around with the secretary at your church and then, you know, I mean, under
a Christian theocracy, you will not do as well as you do under a liberal republic.
A little bit different.
You know how rich Christians still seem to get all the abortions that they want to get?
It is weird.
So Ali Alexander, he thinks he's a mastermind.
And I got to say this next clip just sounds like he thinks he's a Bond villain and he's
coming out to this, this rally and like, here is our grand plan.
Oh boy.
So he's role playing it.
Yeah.
It's, it's a little cringy.
So the plan in January is to start organizing y'all.
We are going to go into the county parties, we are going to go into the district parties
and we are going to go to the state conventions of the Republican party and we're taking over
all 50 states.
We are going to work with the Jericho march.
We are going to work with Alex Jones.
We are going to work with anyone who will work with us, aren't we?
And let me just tell you how deep this goes cause I've been in this business for 14 years
and finally the movement has a strategist.
I sat across and I'm not going to say his name, a state party chair and I said, Hey
buddy, we've known each other for 12 years.
You're up for reelection in May.
I'm going to flood your state convention.
And then after we take over all of the positions, we're then going to call a quorum and then
we're going to impeach the rest of the officers, aren't we?
I'm a dangerous black man who knows Robert's rules of order.
Wow.
So the Republican party, I just want them to hear this message.
Look at this crowd.
We are the people that you must represent or we're going to replace you with Patriots.
That's called voting.
Yeah, I think he's basically, did he just discover voting?
I think he discovered community organizing.
I think so.
The thing that they have decried the left doing hate it so much cause it's cheating.
Focusing on local politics.
Yeah.
Oh, scary.
See, this is why it's hard to take Alex's threat seriously.
Like we're going to kill Joe Biden immediately following.
Like what we're going to do is we're going to go, we're going to call a quorum for everyone.
What are we talking about?
I know Robert's rules of order.
What?
God damn it.
I bet he doesn't.
I'm going to, I'm going to follow Patton into battle if he gives a speech like Robert's
rules of order are dangerous in the wrong hands.
Patton is actually on my mind quite a bit throughout this.
And I think it's probably because General Flynn, I watched him give the same speech
twice.
I just kept thinking like, this is not Patton.
This is bad.
That's what I keep hearing.
When you hear nationalist propaganda, you want it to be Patton, right?
Well, I mean, that's what Alex is trying to be and a lot of these people are just absolutely
whiffing.
Yeah, not good.
Granted, they're still bad and scary, but anyway, Ali ends his speech by talking a little
bit about how God is giving him science.
This is upsetting.
The last thing I'll say, and I'll probably be back up on stage later, is that we have
God's favor.
One day I'm going to tell you guys all the stories, but this, the sun coming out like
this, this is God.
He has gone ahead of us.
I have been to 10 different states and it's not rained once.
Get the fuck out.
To God be the glory.
No.
I've been to...
God damn it.
Have you ever been to 10 states and it didn't rain once?
Can you say that?
I guess I can't.
Ha.
Or maybe I can.
I don't know.
Does flying count?
I flew over 10 states and it didn't rain once.
Does that count?
Were you above the rain?
What counts?
God damn it.
This is how I feel every time somebody tells me about ghosts.
Every time somebody's like, oh, you don't believe in ghosts?
I've got a ghost story.
I'm like, tell me about how the sun shined for 10 states.
Fuck you.
It didn't rain.
God, it's a ghost.
Didn't rain.
Oh, ghosts are real.
Sure.
Didn't rain.
Yeah, okay.
I'm going to reverse Douglas Adams, rain god.
Get the fuck out of here.
So after Ali gets done, they have another speaker and this is a guy by the name of Leon
Benjamin.
Okay.
Who is a bishop, but I should also tell you that this year...
A bishop of what?
Uh, at a church.
Okay.
This year, he also lost the race for the fourth district of Virginia seat in the house.
Oh, that's a bummer.
House of Representatives.
That's a bummer.
He also probably would have lost in the primary, like all the ding-dongs that we talk about
on this show, but he ran unopposed until the general election, and then he lost by quite
a margin.
Quite a margin.
What are you saying?
38 to 61, I think.
38 to 61?
That's not as big a margin as I would hope.
No.
It never is, is it, Dan?
But it's still pretty big.
Yeah, it is still pretty big, but it's never big enough.
Yeah.
So Eric Metaxas brings Bishop Leon Benjamin up, and man, I gotta say, I thought that maybe
this was a racist event, but man, this cleared it up.
I heard, I keep hearing that we're all racists, and yet every now and again, I bump into a
black man at these events.
What is happening?
Every now and again, is it?
That's not supposed to be the narrative.
What are you talking about?
Aren't we supposed to be all about white nationalism?
I keep reading that, and you're screwing that up.
This is Bishop Leon Benjamin.
He's got a shofar at the end of what he says he's gonna play the flight of the bumblebee.
Don't miss it.
Another bad joke.
Wow.
Yeah.
Well, they're not racist.
That's cool.
Anyway, Leon-
Did he just make a minstrel joke while saying he wasn't being racist?
It might be on the cusp, I'm not entirely sure.
So Leon is really into Christian nationalism.
There are walls that must come down.
This is history.
This is December 12th, 12th, the number for government.
That means a fresh anointing is about to come on this nation-
That was the number for government?
An anointing that we have never felt before, an anointing we have never seen before.
Jesus is the lion of the tribe of Judah, and he will rule in America.
Man.
Yeah.
And the Nationalists just really miss out on a lot of great black preachers, you know?
So it's nice that they get this one, but-
Well, that's the advantage of Christian nationalism.
I guess.
Yeah, you still get a few good talkers here and there.
So Jordan, I know that we've heard a lot about wee-etches over the course of the time of
doing this show.
They're fucking everywhere.
It's true.
They've not really gotten any good advice about what to do about them, or like-
That's true.
How do you talk to a wee-etch?
How do you deal with wee-etches?
This is what I learned about witchcraft.
You gotta tell a witch, you gotta look them right in the eye and say, I'm coming after
you.
This is your last day.
This is your last time.
Every curse you cursed against our president and against our nation is gonna double fold
back on your head.
You have to be direct with witches, you understand?
That's the advice.
I just, I just, I'm just, all I'm thinking is Wizard of Oz, Dorothy wakes up, Glenda
the Good Witch shows up and she's just like, you get the fuck out of my face!
I will come and kill you!
You listen to me, I'm going back to Kansas.
That's how you deal with wee-etches.
That's how you deal with witches.
So Leon scares the hell out of me, quite frankly, because he says stuff like this.
But when you shout, just understand, you're shouting for not only this generation, but
you're shouting a legacy for the next generation.
Because the demons we kill now, our children will not have to fight these devils!
These are our devils, and we will kill them now!
They will not fight our children!
Just...
Man!
I understand that there's some, like, rhetorical license that you're not maybe intending to
talk about killing humans and your political enemies, but you're at a political rally,
and you're talking about these demons and these devils that we're up against, and the
conversation very easily, it could be understood as people who wear black and are, like, you
think they're an antifa?
Maybe someone at a Black Lives Matter rally?
Maybe these are the demons that you don't want your children to have to fight.
Everyone you get rid of is one your children doesn't have to fight.
Right, I don't think that, you know, you could make a legally reasonable case that this is
somebody threatening or inciting people to kill other people, but it's reckless.
It's recklessly expressed ideas, and I can't...
That's a great speech if it's 1977 and you're talking about climate change.
Every bit of greenhouse gas that we get rid of is one that our kids don't have to deal
with.
Exactly.
If you kind of put it that way...
Then it makes great sense.
It's a good thing to do, in fact.
Somewhat.
Yeah.
So Alex Jones gave his speech, and then a little video came out of him backstage as
he ran into General Flynn.
And this is really, really funny.
I had some words.
I recommend people go find this video, since we're an audio podcast, I'll play the audio
and then I'll explain what happened.
Crazy day, huh?
It isn't crazy.
Are you scared?
We're gonna win.
What?
You don't want me to get scared?
You guys are funny, man.
General Flynn did not want to talk to Alex at all.
I don't know why!
Alex comes up and he's like, crazy day, and General Flynn does not turn to him.
He kind of like turns his head, but not his body, and he's like, yeah, it is a crazy day.
He's like, ah, we're gonna win.
And then he's like, are you scared?
You scared?
And Flynn's like, what?
He's like, are you scared to shake my hand?
And then Alex kind of gets this like, someone else kind of walks up and Alex gets the sense
of like, I gotta leave.
Oh, wow.
And so he walks off.
And the camera pans over and Owen Troyer's standing a ways back.
So there's the reveal of Owen Troyer, just in the corner watching?
Yeah, like keeping his distance because he knows like, oh, this isn't gonna go well.
This isn't for me.
I'm not supposed to be there.
And then Alex tries to save face with like, ah, you guys are funny.
No, Flynn either knows who you are and doesn't want to be associated with you or has no idea
who you are.
Oh, man.
Either way, it does not work well for his brand.
Yeah, you should not meet your heroes that you created fictional versions of, assuming
that the fictional version will greet you warmly.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's an issue.
So Flynn, he gives a speech, gets up at this Jericho rally, and man, what a fucking beginning
to this speech.
Just awe-inspiring.
You know, I was gonna end with a prayer, but maybe we'll start with a prayer.
This sounds planned.
I told Mike Lindell as he was walking and we bumped into each other, I actually had
the first good sleep of my life last night.
So mypillow.com, I'll give him a commercial.
Mike fucking Flynn starts a speech with a plug for MyPillow.
Oh my God.
He must be throwing around cash at MyPillow guy.
On this, our safe Christmas day, I must remind you, we happy few.
How much fucking money is that guy making?
There is a 5% discount.
Did he find...
On straw beds when we return home heroes!
Did he find like a cache of Krugerands or something, like he find pirate gold?
How is he throwing around all this money at a pillow company?
I don't know, but Flynn's got that pillow cache.
God.
Anyway, so I know in Dune, I know people love Dune Talk, right?
People love Dune Talk.
They love it.
Fear is the mind killer.
Is that correct?
That is correct.
You tell me a little bit about this.
Fear is the mind killer.
It is the little death that, man, now that I'm on the...
No, the petite moor is an orgasm.
No, no, no.
Fear is the...
No, it's part of the litany against fear, Dan.
Oh.
It's something that the Bene Gesserit teach you to say whenever you're afraid.
Does this have anything to do with Muad'Dib?
Muad'Dib did learn the litany against fear and used it many a time in order to calm himself
and bring himself into a more stable state.
How does this relate to Duncan, Idaho?
Duncan, Idaho learned the litany against fear.
His mother was a Bene Gesserit, and so he was aware of all of that stuff.
However, he was never trained in the ways of the Bene Gesserit because men children
were not allowed.
Only the Kwisatz Haderach, Dan.
And were sandworms Bene Gesserits?
Yes.
Sandworms are not Bene Gesserits.
They were actually God himself, Shai-Hulud.
Fear is the mind killer.
Sandworm, body killer.
Sandworms kill everybody, but they are also God.
They are also the devil, Shaitan.
I wanted to discuss this a little bit because as Mike Flynn was talking, I was like, are
you going to get into fear?
He's talking about fear.
I was like, oh, is he going to say that fear is the mind killer?
He's very close.
This is very close.
I want him to do it.
In our minds, in our minds, that's where we find fear because fear is a mental thing.
It's something that you have in your minds and you fear things because your mind says,
I'm afraid of that or I'm afraid of this.
But it's in our hearts.
It's in our hearts where we truly know what is right.
Because in our hearts, that's where we differentiate between good and bad, right?
Where we differentiate between darkness and light.
And we know that.
We know that in our heart.
It's that gut feeling, but it's actually your heart.
It's your heart talking to you.
Not in your mind because your mind is going to say, I'm afraid.
So fear is the mind killer.
Trust your gut because your weird feelings are actually your heart, which is clearer
because your heart is free of fear.
The only thing we have to fear is fear because it comes from inside you, but it's also part
of your heart and you can't listen to it, but it's not part of your heart because it's
what you're afraid of and it's in your head.
And fear is what we fear the most itself.
Yeah.
And it's a pattern.
A lot of great speakers in history.
Not one of them.
No.
I realized as he was speaking that I don't think I've ever heard a full speech of his.
Me neither.
And I found it underwhelming.
I found that to be incredibly terrible.
So one thing I'm afraid of is helicopters.
That's not actually true, but it's a good segue.
Nice.
One thing I'm afraid of is Segues.
Well, we're both terrified.
While Flynn is on stage, that's when the flyover happens.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
And this is just depressing.
Imagine being able to just jump in a helicopter
and go for a joy ride around Washington, DC.
I love it.
I love the fact that he does that.
That's what he does, because he knows
that the people that he can trust
are people that he's never met.
And that's you.
I mean, he's never met.
Look at the millions and millions of people, right?
He trusts you.
He trusts you because he knows you know what's going on,
and you will not allow what's happening
to happen in our country.
None of us will.
It's just not going to happen.
I will tell you one more time, because I've been asked,
on a scale of 1 to 10, who will be the next president
of the United States, and I say Donald Trump, 10, a 10.
You know, that moment there where he's like, first of all,
the idea that Trump can trust you people who he doesn't know
is very sad.
So sad.
But when Flynn is like, he trusts you because you're
the ones who know what's going on,
you're not going to allow what's happening to happen,
makes me think of that Andy Daly character, who's
like the stand-up comic who says nothing.
Like, what else is in the news?
Can you believe this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Another?
I mean, come on.
What is going on with one of these?
What's with this?
Come on.
I mean, not when I was.
Not if I have anything to say about it.
When this goes down, oh boy.
Yeah.
Trump trusts you because you know what's going on
and you're not going to let what happens happen.
Wow.
Just fucking say that you wanted everyone
to incite an installing of an unelected president.
It just punctures so much of that.
Like, it is one of those things that you don't really,
it doesn't always hit you until it does.
Like, how much you've been fucked up
by movies and TV and culture and all that shit.
Because you just hear General and you
like see his military record and all of these war,
like all of this shit.
And he rose to this high rank and you're like,
that's the fucking guy?
Yeah, you kind of think of no-nonsense, stern sort
of men-a-few-words, stiff upper lip kind of, yeah.
And that's not the vibe Flynn gives.
Actually, he's the brown-nosing toady
who politicked his way up into the military, high ranks.
He's a fucking dick.
There's another guy who's like from Vets
for Trump who gives a speech that is fairly uneventful
and I don't have any clips of it.
But he was far more like what you're talking about,
what you would expect.
Like a guy who's like, oh, you're terrified.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're dark.
You're dark.
Yeah, you're a dark man.
You seem like an archetype of someone
who's seen some shit.
So this, I got to say, the Jericho rally drags at this point.
I believe it.
And I'm done with it.
We're not going to talk about any more of it
because it just ends up deteriorating into a thing
where like there's a guy from Bikers for Trump
and he ends up talking about how they formed this group, right?
They formed this group because they wanted to stop Antifa
from throwing dog poop at Trump supporters who are waiting
in line to get into events.
You said that in front of people.
Yeah, he said that in an interview on the TV.
Wow.
There's also some more religious weirdos.
And you know, I just, I lost it.
I couldn't.
I mean, there was also a couple other Infowars characters,
but they were like kind of really adjacent people.
Like Jason Jones, the guy who hosts The Fourth Hour
sometimes, like he was there and he gave an interview.
It was just kind of like, this is too much.
And again, I think the problem is that Alex was kind of early.
Yeah.
It really took so much steam out of him.
None of these other people could reach the heights of that.
Like, you know, I don't know of any actual comedian who
talks about laughs per minute, but I've heard the idea
discussed.
And applause lines per minute, Alex just wrecked shop.
Like no one is going to be able to recover from that.
He scorched earth it.
Yeah, yeah.
And so I.
Which I imagine he did on purpose, honestly.
Yeah.
Because I've been under, I've been
put where I wasn't supposed to go in the lineup before.
And I made it very clear I wasn't supposed to go there.
Yeah.
You know?
I'm going to bury whoever comes up next.
I'm going to bury your headliners so far
into the ground.
It's going to be brutal.
It's also notable that Alex and Mike Flynn
both come out to the Mission Impossible theme.
Like Alex might have stolen Mike Flynn's intro music.
Now that's some petty shit that I'm here for.
Yes.
I am here for that pettiness all day.
I think there might be something there.
So I watched a bunch more of this.
But I lost my patience for it.
Because I mean like how much, what else are we going to find?
More examples of people saying the exact same Christian
nationalist shit?
Who cares?
God, kill everybody.
We got it.
Moving on.
But there was another rally that day.
And this was the Women for America First rally.
This was being held pretty close nearby around the same time.
There's some particularly fun footage also
that's going around on Twitter, which
is of Alex trying to bum rush the stage at the Women
for Trump rally.
That sounds like a metaphor I'm able to understand clearly.
Very unsuccessful.
Maybe I just got a little enthusiastic, but we're going to do it, because Trump won't stop coming.
We're not allowed to be here, we're not allowed to be here.
Yes, yes, that is how you get escorted out.
This is a family show, Alex.
My first thought when I watched that was that Alex seems like he's on stimulants.
He seems amped the fuck up.
Red eyes.
Yeah, and like grinding his mouth and like ready to fight with a security guard who won't
let him through.
Yeah.
Feels like he clearly thinks he's entitled to get up there and get on stage at an event
where the security guard is like, you're not welcome here.
But I think about it and I'm like, well, honestly, he probably is coming over there right after
he yelled at the other crowd.
I would assume he was, he thought he was welcome.
He's probably jacked as fuck off the adrenaline of that.
Totally.
Maybe also some stimulants, who knows.
Yeah, why not?
He's an older man.
Yeah, so there, he got shut down from going to the Women for America First rally and you
can tell that that's that rally because you can hear the guy in the background talking
about the March for Trump, which was the bus tour that led to and culminated with this
Women for Trump America First rally.
I didn't hear him whining about flags either, so I assumed it was a...
Wait for it.
Oh no!
So this rally was a much, it's much less relevant to our focus since there's less direct Infowars
connections.
Alex wasn't allowed at this one, he was allowed at the other show and they even let Owen Schroyer
on stage.
Yeah, that's weird.
Alexander was one of the organizers of the Jericho rally and like I said, there were
a couple other Infowars people that you could find hanging around.
In contrast, this Women for America First rally felt like people who were a bit more
interested in being taken seriously.
The thing that I take issue with is that I can only find two real differences between
them.
One is that Alex was not allowed at the Women for America First one and they also seem to
mention political issues a little more than the Jericho one.
That was pretty solidly focused on demanding Christian nationalism, whereas this one is
hiding a little bit in conservative politics.
Big difference between the middle and far right wings of the Republican party.
And desperately trying to appear somewhat credible with their booking choices.
So they have like Katrina Pearson and Seb Gorka.
Yes, very credible.
Well, comparatively.
Yeah, well I mean I guess.
I guess they're bigger names maybe?
Like Sebastian Gorka has a show that's syndicated.
Okay that's fair.
Alex is on Genesis Communications.
Still amazing to me that Seb Gorka is just allowed to roam free.
It is.
And, shockingly, I texted you about this last night while I was.
I texted you that he seems like a character.
Like a sketch character.
Like I had not also heard much Sebastian Gorka.
Except for maybe like little clips or honestly a Domian doing an impression of him.
Yeah.
But you've played for me.
Way less.
I honestly felt like watching that, I was like Sebastian Gorka's leaning into the bit.
It felt like he was becoming the parodies of himself.
That sounds right.
Or maybe the parodies are just that good that like they really nail it because he seems
like a farce of a person.
Yeah.
Like whenever your front lines are run by a hair dye bleeding Rudy Giuliani in front
of a landscaping company.
Hey man.
Your parodies are gonna be just straight impressions.
Rudy's the guy who hits the barbed wire.
So Jordan, I originally intended that we would cover the entire rally of the Women for America
first.
Sure.
Just like the Jericho one.
Yeah.
But the more I thought about it, the less that seemed compatible with my goal of creating
a decent show that people can enjoy.
Yeah, we could have just done rallies that were terrible.
Mike Flynn and the My Pillow guy basically give the exact same speeches at both rallies
and the whole thing just drags on way too long much like the other one with people just
basically saying nothing.
Yeah.
Like it's really, it's really vapid.
Well it has to be.
Yeah.
They have no actual substance.
It's mostly getting people to chant about loving Trump and you know, whatever.
Yeah, it's fucking straight up Nazi shit.
I decided that possibly a better way to approach the Women for America First rally was to hand
out some awards, some superlatives.
Okay.
As if this lineup was a bunch of matriculating, graduating seniors in high school.
Love it.
So the first, the first title I'd like to bestow on someone is...
Most likely to secede?
No.
Hey.
Not bad.
All of them.
All right.
Most confusing breath of fresh air.
Okay.
What's up DC?
How was General Flynn you guys, was that amazing or what?
That man and his family have laid it on the line for our country over and over and over
again and we can't show them enough gratitude.
This guy is very clearly drunk.
Yeah.
He used to be in his late 30s, early 40s and is wearing what appears to be a red sequined
smoking jacket.
All right, now I like him.
Now I'm back on board.
He's got a beard.
He seems fucking day drunk at like noon or one.
There but for the grace of God go I, Dan.
He is absolutely out of place at this rally and as the kids say, I was here for it.
Also, I have no idea who he is.
He never says his name.
Yes.
No one says his name.
I don't know who he is.
I tried to find out.
I could not find out.
I looked at the comments of the YouTube video.
I Googled lineup of event.
I couldn't find it.
He was standing next to Alex when the security guard stopped him and he was like, I'm going
to go all through then.
But unfortunately, like all things we discuss on this show that are kind of fun, he ended
up revealing himself to be a piece of shit, but also in the same clip that he says something
that I was really tickled by.
There's three parts to my message.
I'm alarmed I lost all my guns, a tragic boating accident.
What?
What just happened?
You guys have been.
What did you just say to me?
Second part.
No, you stop about that.
I want to know the first part of the ability.
Something that we have to deal a lot with with the Kung flu.
Oh, come on.
Damn it, man.
Disappointing.
Oh, we were doing so good.
We even got tragic boating accident.
I wasn't expecting that.
I'm not sure if that is a joke.
Or if he actually had a boating accident and lost his guns.
Why would you say tragic boating accident?
That seems specific.
It's either pretty funny as a joke, like I don't have any guns, I lost them in a tragic
boating accident.
See, now that's something that I would toss off if I was emceeing somewhere.
I'd just be like, ah, I lost them in a tragic boating accident.
Everybody moves on.
Yeah, not a bad throwaway line.
Yeah, a little toss.
Also could be real, and I want to know the story.
It could be real.
Why was he specifically just telling me that he lost all of his guns in a tragic boating
accident?
Either way, I find him to be an engaging presence.
He's got this weird red sequence-smoking jacket and he's fucked up.
Why did you have to say that fucking racist flu stuff?
It's a little bit like a racist right-winger played by Kyle Kinane, you know?
I had no idea what is going on.
I don't know who he is.
He doesn't introduce himself.
No one says.
He's on the TV stream of it.
There's no name on the chyron.
No idea.
He might have just shown up.
He might have just wandered on there.
I have no idea.
But while he's on stage, he introduces a person who has the same name as a big celebrity,
but does not appear to be that celebrity.
You will never stand for it, and we're going to keep coming back until it's known, and
our president, the greatest president ever, is where he's supposed to be.
I fucking love this guy.
He's great.
I made sure this was an amazing woman.
I told her I'd keep it brief.
I don't want to get in trouble.
So Jennifer Lawrence, come up and talk to everybody.
It is not Jennifer Lawrence.
I don't know who this Jennifer Lawrence is either.
I thought maybe if I figured out who she is, it would help me find out who he is, and it
did not.
I still have no idea who anybody is.
Is this like when that couple crashed a White House party and everybody was like, holy shit,
how did they get in there?
If it is, I love it.
So Jennifer Lawrence is unfortunately a Christian nationalist.
Well, that sounds-
Those people on that hill over there need to remember that they work for us.
We the people, we don't work for them.
We answer to God, not government, and God is going to tell us who's going to be the
president, and God is going to tell us how this country is going to go, and we are going
to fight.
Okay.
Thank you, Jennifer Lawrence.
So then even if you get your president, you're still not going to do what the government
says?
I guess not.
Anyway, congratulations to clearly day drunk guy in a sequined smoking jacket.
You have won the very coveted title of most confusing breath of fresh air at that rally.
I was a little bit hoping that somebody out of... What if JB Smoove did five minutes?
That's what I was hoping the super surprising confusing breath of fresh air was.
No, it's day drunk guy in a sequined red coat.
Pretty close to JB Smoove.
Yeah.
So the next award that I'm going to give out, the next superlative, is the best integration
of promotional messaging into a stump speech.
My pillow, my pillow.
Nope.
Oh.
Well, my pillow might be involved.
Okay.
But this award goes to radio show host David J. Harris, and let me say, it's not even close.
All right.
He ran away with this thing.
Okay.
And a special thank you to the co-sponsor that really helped fund a lot of this, Mr.
My Pillow himself, Mike Lindell.
Amazing patriot, loves this country, loves us, loves the president, and the president
loves him.
And I got to tell you, I love his codes, right?
I love his pillows, I love his sheets, I love his mattress topper, and I love his codes
because you know what?
The Kraken has been released.
You are part of the Kraken.
So for the best deals to support this patriot, use the code Kraken at mypillow.com.
Amazing.
Just amazing.
I can't say enough how not smooth that was.
That is really, really bad.
But David doesn't just stop with my pillow codes.
He also throws out like, hey, I'm big on social media.
I've worked hard over the last few years to try to bring you real honest news at davidharrisjr.com.
I've got 2.3 million followers on Facebook, 1.1 on Instagram.
You can plug in his website, his social media, and that's great, but that is all just in
order to prepare you for another plug, which is the solution to Facebook.
Oh, okay.
I hear people talking about Parler.
Parler's amazing.
It's a great alternative to Twitter, but we need an alternative to Facebook.
Something that works and operates like Facebook, and I've found it, I'm going to be talking
about it loud.
I've got a lot of my friends are going to be talking about it loud.
It's called Spreely, stands for Speak Freely, and here's where you can download it, S-P-R-E-E-L-Y.
Spreely, you're going to hear a lot about that, and they're going to dominate Facebook.
I'm going to guess they're not, but all of these people, like a lot of them seem to be
pushing internet startups.
Like there was that Ian Rakelin guy who came to Alex's CPAC thing, and he was trying to
push a search engine.
I think that they're really trying to make a little bit of a fast cash on the conservative
agreement over social media market.
This is what I'm saying when I say I feel for these idiots in the crowd here.
You guys are being sold the idea that you can legally just get whatever you want, so
long as they'll fire lawsuits and then we'll get whatever we want, because we're right.
They're selling you all of this like, and when this happens, which we totally know it's
going to, it will keep us from having to do the one thing that we know is the only way
to get what we want to achieve and we're trying to avoid, and it's like you're just being
taken along by these guys who are selling you on Spreely.
No one's going to go on Spreely.
No!
Yeah.
He also has perfected this technique that David Harris has of protected prayer, he does
the Lord's Prayer, but he wants to really take every line of it and think about what
does it mean.
Oh no.
Yeah.
Are we going to get a commentary?
No, we're not going to listen to all of it.
We're not going to get an abridged version?
It's so long.
It's like six minutes.
Jesus!
Yeah.
But this is the end of it and how smoothly it transitions into a plug.
Oh wow.
Give us a greater understanding, Father, of your love for us as the individual son, as
an individual daughter.
Give us a greater revelation, Father, of your love for us and let us be that catalyst and
that change in our country.
In Jesus' name, amen?
Amen!
I truly believe we're going to win.
I truly believe the fraud is going to be exposed.
The Kraken has been released.
We the people will not be denied seeing another four years of the amazing presidency of Donald
J. Trump.
God bless you.
I think we're going to hear this and still 45.
We're going to hear that again.
So please visit davidharrisjr.com.
Help me fight these suckers that are just constantly on me.
Gotta fight these suckers that are on me.
Wow.
Quite a ride.
And Jesus overturned those money changers tables and said, follow me at at jesus underscore
magic.
Help me fight these suckers?
Yeah.
Yeah, I found his speech to be laden with a promotion to a point where it was distracting.
It was a little distracting.
Granted, I have no idea who this guy is.
So I can't judge his body of work.
I can only watch this and say it was a little much.
Yikes.
So Jordan, our next category is the most graceful exit from someone who clearly did not want
to be there.
This award goes to someone we know, actually.
He's a guy who promoted pizza gate quite heavily.
Oh no.
Jack.
Oh, God damn it.
They said that I could have longer time up here today, but I said, I want to give my
time up.
I want to give my time up to a whistleblower, a courageous whistleblower who saw something
and decided to say something and stand up.
So ladies and gentlemen, all the way from Michigan, Melissa Carone, who's going to come
up and tell you what she saw.
So that's the lady who appeared to be drunk with Rudy Giuliani in that video that everyone
loved so much.
Yeah, there it is.
Yeah, so Jack clearly, I got the vibe that he was, because that's like a minute into
his being married.
Yeah, that's great.
He's just like, I'm out of here.
That's great.
That is good stuff.
They would have given Melissa Carone a speaking spot if she'd asked.
Totally.
And I was like, yeah, I don't really want to do this.
I don't want to do it.
No.
But I do want my name there.
Yeah, just in case.
I would like my attention.
Yes.
But I do not want to do the work for it.
Thank you.
Yeah.
So congratulations, Jack.
You made a graceful exit.
That's well done.
Yeah, that's well done.
There's a, oh, there's a late entry.
What's that?
There's actually an escalation of this category.
Oh no.
Now we have to give out the award for the person who made the most graceful, I'm not
even showing up.
This award goes to Dinesh D'Souza.
Now it's my honor to introduce another young lady.
You know her father, Dinesh D'Souza.
You see him all over TV.
He couldn't join us today, but Danielle D'Souza's here.
She's a strong pro-life young woman, the author of the book, The Choice.
And I'm proud to introduce her to you today here in Washington, D.C., Danielle D'Souza.
Dinesh D'Souza was invited.
He said, fuck no, I'm sending my daughter.
I'll send my daughter.
Dinesh D'Souza.
Wow, wow, Jack, you didn't know you could half-ass it still further.
Yeah.
Lazy.
Yep, so.
Why did you not just say, why didn't you send in a video message announcing Melissa Carbone
or whatever?
Well, you know who did send in a video message?
Dinesh D'Souza?
No, Marjorie Greene, the QAnon person in Congress.
Oh, the crazy person, yeah, yeah, yeah, all right, good for her, good for her.
That was one of those, like, real curveballs in terms of, like, their booking.
Yeah.
I feel like you guys are trying to have an air of not out there too far.
So we got the craziest Congressperson we could find.
Well, and she only sent in a video.
Yeah, that's not good.
That's not good.
It could be better.
I think democracy is not always the most popular thing to do, and I've seen that.
It's true.
Yeah.
So the next category, Jordan, is the second most likely day drunk person after the guy
in a sequined shirt.
Ooh, he's 100%.
Yes, there's no competition.
Yeah, no, that one's all the way up to full.
Second place, however, second most likely, that honor goes to Boris Epstein, who I should
remind you, the guy from Sinclair Media, I should remind you, tested positive for COVID-19
on November 26th.
Anyway, he showed up and he seemed drunk.
Hello, America.
I was told I shouldn't take the mic off, but I'm going to do it anyway.
Right?
Right.
Who do we love?
We love Trump.
Why?
Get the flags higher.
We love Trump.
I love that Boris is like, apparently didn't hear everyone yelling to put the flags down.
Nope.
Get those flags up.
Get the flags in the air.
At two different events, people have been saying, put the flags down so we could stream
and Boris is like, ah, fuck that.
I don't know.
I don't know if he's actually drunk.
It's really tough to tell because it also, I realized as I was watching this, it's hard
to tell the difference between like maybe kind of day drunk buzzed and sort of just
jacked up off of being in front of a crowd this big and maybe doing those like standard
get the crowd pumped up kind of things.
Like those sound crazy if you do that.
You know?
Yeah.
And those are the kinds of things that you instinctually do and you're drunk.
Like getting a crowd to chant USA is really fun when you're drunk.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
USA.
I can't, that's, this is maybe the largest disconnect more than our politics even.
The idea, any politician, the idea of saying, if me chanting, we love blank politician,
fuck that.
It seems weird.
Period.
Yeah.
I think AOC is incredible.
I'm not going to chant, we love AOC.
Fuck that.
I would tell myself that I think I would be just as like put off by seeing large crowds
chanting we love Obama back in 2008.
Oh, creepy.
But maybe I wouldn't have been.
Maybe that's a bias on my part.
I don't know.
I like to think that I would be.
Sure.
But I'm not certain I would.
I mean we were much younger then and you know, Obama was coming out after the previous worst
president in American history.
I like to think that I would respond the same, it'd be like weird.
But I wonder if I would see that and I would give the like, sort of like, oh, they're not
in a cult of personality.
This is just expressing their political.
Sure, sure.
I wonder.
I like to think.
I mean, I wouldn't, I don't know Obama, Jordan.
That was significantly long ago.
I would say the most recent is obviously the Bernie Sanders campaign in the primary in
2016 whenever he had those massive rallies.
But even then, I don't remember people screaming like.
People are chanting like feel the Bern.
Something like that.
And then it's like, yeah, it's like a weird all in this together, not like, we love you.
You know, like that's creepy.
His slogan was not me, us.
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly.
Yeah.
We love us.
I would be fine with chanting that.
Yeah, I don't know.
It's tough.
I know that I don't like looking at it here.
Oh, no.
And I like to think that maybe even if I had turned a blind eye to it before, I would now
look upon people chanting like, let's say, I love AOC.
Yeah.
And I would look at that much differently.
Don't.
So maybe this has given me an illuminating moment.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So we have another superlative, another title.
Person who's putting the most direct.
I didn't prepare this title.
Oh, okay.
This one's a little bit off the dome-y.
Person who's putting the most effort into getting people killed.
Okay.
That goes to, I don't remember his name, but he's that gym owner in New Jersey who refuses
to stay closed.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you would have asked me back in February, if I thought that one person could make a
difference, I would have laughed and said, hell no.
But here I am today.
One man, a part of a team of two guys who stood up to a governor and told him, no, we
will not listen.
And it's starting a movement across the country.
They're trying that second wave that they've been predicting for so long and more and more
businesses are staying open.
And I'm here to advocate every single freedom loving American to go out and support these
small businesses.
And I'm going to give you a way how we created a directory, a nationwide directory of businesses
that are staying open, thinking of it as a Yelp for freedom loving Americans who won't
listen to COVID restrictions.
I have a flaw in that plan.
So go out there and support.
That is www.stayopenstayfree.com.
Check it out.
Go encourage businesses to sign up and go support them.
Because the more that do, the quicker this thing will fall apart, I promise you.
This works equally well as a registry of businesses to avoid.
Yeah.
Yep.
Wow.
Yeah.
I didn't think that one man could make a difference.
But now look at me, the horsemen of plague, spreading COVID to all who come near me.
Yeah.
Jesus Christ, King Midas.
That might not age well.
Yeah.
So I went and I looked at this guy's registry and I looked for Chicago and there's exactly
one business in the city of Chicago and it is an apartment building.
Which is just like, all right, I guess.
I guess if that's where you want to promote.
Yeah.
Seems silly.
Okay.
It's a Gold Coast apartment.
Well, that doesn't surprise me.
Yeah.
If it was going to be anywhere, Gold Coast is where...
I don't know if this is what that was for.
I think this is more about like, retail, right?
Yeah, I was thinking so.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Cool.
So next apartment of Jordan is actually a tie.
Yes, sir.
This is very shocking.
Okay.
Most insane preacher.
Ooh, there's two.
Two.
It's a tie.
This one goes to Reverend Locke out of Tennessee.
If you're glad to be on the winning side, let's make some noise, DC!
I read the back of the book and it doesn't end with, oh me, it ends with, amen, and this
thing is going to turn out all right.
We're not going to back up, we're not going to pack up, we're not going to slack up, and
we're not going to shut up till we've been taken up by the glory of God, and I am convinced
that Donald J. Trump is going to remain the President of the United States.
Do you believe that this afternoon, patriots?
Have you met my snakes?
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Dude.
We've got a revival preacher on our hands.
Come on, buddy.
We're getting a lot of different particular flavors of exciting preachers, and that's
why it has to be a tie, is because these guys have completely different styles.
Okay.
But Reverend Locke, or Pastor Locke, who knows.
Whatever.
He does not ask permission when he wants to tell the devil that the devil is on notice.
I think he should.
No, I didn't ask permission, for I said it and never do, but let me tell you something,
I serve notice on the devil.
This guy is an auctioneer.
I was actually thinking that exact same thing.
I was like, man, you have a gift for saying words fast and dumb.
Do not do this job.
He's very exciting, verbally.
Yeah.
And that's why, yeah.
I never asked the devil for a goddamn piece of permission, but I will tell you this right
now, everybody, we see five over there, and now it's ten over there, ten, I have twenty
over there, twenty, twenty over there, all right, and the Lord says so.
That's where it's functional, but unfortunately, he uses his gifts to yell about how everyone
will be forced to bow in front of Jesus.
That's not good.
That in the name of Jesus, every knee should bow of things in heaven and things in earth
and things under the earth, and that every, I said that, every Republican, every Democrat
shall bow and with their voice proclaim him Lord of Lords to the glory of God the Father.
So you have a choice, and the choice is clear.
We can declare Jesus Lord of our life right now because we want to, or we can declare
Jesus Christ Lord of our life in the day of judgment because we have to.
But make no mistake, Jesus Christ is Lord.
And I want you to chant, King of Kings, King of Kings.
Yeah, so that guy is scary in many ways, but the vocal patterns are fun, so I'll get him
mad.
King of Kings.
Yeah.
Oh boy.
So the next guy who's tied here for this most insane preacher is a guy named Brian Gibson,
and I actually found this kind of endearing.
Okay.
His wife brings him up, introduces him on stage, and you don't know that it's his wife
initially because she's just like, this next speaker is just my favorite person, he's my
husband.
Oh, that's cute.
It's adorable.
All right.
And then Brian Gibson, Pastor Brian Gibson, complains about how his Easter service didn't
work.
I hate my wife.
No, it didn't work.
His Easter service didn't work out.
He was going to try and give eggs to children.
Okay.
On Easter Sunday, I blew a fuse.
I put together an Easter egg giveaway.
We were going to give some kids an egg in the name of Jesus.
The health department called me, said if I gave those eggs away, that they would shut
down the church of the Lord Jesus Christ.
You keep those fucking eggs.
The health department is accused to not give up those eggs.
I swear to God, that's your bitching.
That's what you're complaining about.
You keep those eggs.
Wow.
And I'm going to tell you, no one has the authority to shut down the church of the Lord
Jesus Christ, except Jesus Christ himself, when he returns to church.
Come on, give God a hand clap, if you believe it out there.
Give God a hand clap.
Does God need applause?
Yes.
I organized a parking lot communion service.
I called all of the press.
I said, come out, tell the governor I'm distributing communion elements and they can come arrest
me because I'd love to go to jail for the preaching of the gospel.
That's not what you would be going to jail for, sir.
You were not actually preaching gospel.
Used to every time I got drunk and coked up, I got arrested.
What's up with that?
What is up with that?
Yeah.
Now I can't get arrested for preaching?
No.
Wow.
Oh boy.
Kind of a little bit telling there.
A little bit there.
Anyway, he would not make the cut if it weren't for his just extreme Christian nationalist
leanings.
Let me say this, America did not birth the church.
America did not birth the church, but the church birthed America.
Not true, sir.
Sir, sir.
Excuse me.
And the only thing that will save America is the same thing that birthed America, the
church of the Lord Jesus Christ.
So yeah, I mean this is just-
I was going to go with King George, but I guess I was wrong.
Nope.
I guess I was wrong.
I guess I was way off.
What about that whole no taxation without representation thing?
Wasn't that really important?
Or was it-
Church.
Is it just church?
All right.
Okay.
You realize that the Puritans were kicked out-
Church.
Because they hated them.
Because everybody hated them.
Again-
Because they're the worst.
These two preachers are at the one that is not the more religiously branded one.
Wow.
Jesus.
They're at the one that wasn't the product of a vision.
Yeah.
Yep.
I'm trying to tell you that all of this is-
You know, I want to say, I want to say, religious people, come get your guys or you get what
you get, man.
That's mockery?
That's mockery.
Oh.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't blame decent religious people for this.
I blame religion for this.
That's an interesting conversation I don't want to have right now.
Fair.
Fair point.
I do want to give out the next award.
Okay.
And this is the last award.
All right.
It's a bewildering transition between speakers.
Okay.
This begins with a woman whose name is either Anna Kate or Anna K. It's hard to tell from
the intro.
Okay.
The intro is a guy named Matt Couch.
Sure, sure.
Who's giving her the intro.
He's a guy-
From mycouch.com.
No, no.
There's a great promo code.
He's a dude who really did some damage to the Rich family, the Seth Rich conspiracy
shit.
Oh, he did.
I don't know what the fuck anyone's doing ever letting him speak in public again.
Wow.
Fuck me.
She's giving the intro to either Anna Kate or Anna K. No idea.
She's a very devout Trump worshiper who's apparently been in prayer for 40 days straight,
and I guess she's breaking that now to give the people of this rally an update.
How dare you fucking lie like that?
You lie piece of shit.
She says that prophecy has promised that Trump will be given two consecutive terms, so therefore
he must have won.
After saying this, she's got a message for the devil.
The second message is for the devil and his minions and all the wizards and witches that
are watching right now all over the world.
This is for you.
We're going to do a chant right now.
It's for me?
We're going to do a chant because it's awesome to exalt Trump.
Oh, no.
You're going to chant?
Trump is our anointed one.
He's your anointed one.
To bring justice back into this country.
Not justice.
I do worry that I'm one of the wizards.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure you're a wizard.
Yeah.
Yeah, without question.
I think that no matter what the reality is, I would be looked upon as a wizard.
Totally.
No, it doesn't matter.
Honestly, even if there was no religion, I'm still looking at you just going like, you
got a real Lord of the Ringsy vibe to you.
I've been forced into the role of a wizard.
I mean, you leaned into it though.
You're erudite, you're obsessive, you live on the third floor, you're in a tower, if
you will.
Come on, buddy.
You're John D reincarnated.
All right.
Fine.
I'm a wizard.
Anyway, this lady chants for Jesus.
She wants to chant Jesus' name.
Is the devil weak to chants?
Yes.
Oh, okay.
Shit.
I know that because I'm a wizard.
So they chant Jesus and then she repents for abortion, which is apparently a blood sacrifice
to Baal.
Sure.
Count of three, we're going to chant Jesus because this was a vision I had a few weeks
ago because it's shifting in the atmosphere now in Jesus' name.
Lord, we repent.
Before we chant his name, Lord, we repent for all the blood sacrifice that has been
poured out in this nation, Lord.
We repent for abortion, Lord God.
The sacrifice is to Baal.
We exult you, Lord.
So yeah, and then they start chanting Jesus.
Now, Jordan, here is the transition that is outrageous and made me laugh out loud while
hours into watching these stupid rallies.
This is your second rally?
Yes.
Oh boy.
And I loved this moment more than I can really put into words.
So mic down for this, enjoy this minute and 15 second ride.
Jesus.
Glory to God.
We're going to see a miracle.
Amen.
Amazing.
Right?
Hey guys, right here in the middle, if we could keep the flags down, we have some guys
at RSPN who have been with us the whole way.
They're amazing.
Let's block at the shot and we want to make sure people at home can enjoy it too.
Thank you guys.
Yeah.
Just right here in the center between us and the cameras, everybody else.
We love you guys as flags are amazing and we love RSPN because you guys need to be watching
them.
All right, next up, we're going to mix it up.
We're going to bring some amazing artists out here, Bryce and Graham, 4G out of Blow.
Y'all ready to turn up?
It's hard for me to move around with this mic though.
All right.
So what's happened here is that we started with the lady chanting Jesus who had a message
for the devil and the wizards, and then my drunk friend comes back out.
He tells people to keep those flags down, a little bit more admin, a little bit of business,
and then he introduces a rap act.
There's a rap concert.
It was easier to have religious epiphanies before technology, I imagine.
No point during the sermon on the Mount was Peter like, hey guys, guys, we are leaving
too much bread around.
There is a lot of bread going around on the floors, it is attracting too many birds, birds
are getting in the shot.
This is not hitchhock.
And now a rap concert on the Mount.
So yeah, this guy named Bryson Gray comes out to do a little rap set.
All right.
He has a couple albums that he's put out.
One's called Maga Season, spelled S-Z-N.
Oh, he's hot.
Another one, another album called Maga Christmas.
Another, another album called Maga Ain't Got No Color, and his other album, Can't Cancel
God.
So, was it his label who wanted the Christmas album or was it?
So I went and I listened to a little bit of his stuff and I got to say he's serviceable
as an actual rapper.
He's not good.
As a lyricist?
Yes.
And as someone who's delivering words over beats, he's not as bad as a lot of people
I've heard.
I will say that.
And I think he's just not, he's not anything interesting.
I don't find anything compelling about it.
It's largely just like rapping, you know, sort of conspiracy talking points and Trump
shit.
I don't really care.
But I went and I actually found a review of one of his albums.
It was shocking because like the review really agreed with me.
Like he's not terrible, but this is boring.
I like that because it was like, yeah, this review isn't insulting him.
It's not like saying he's a shitty rapper.
It's like, you're not doing anything interesting.
It's kind of uncompelling.
You have some skill or whatever.
Oh man.
No, you hate my politics.
Honestly, your politics, I do hate them, but we're talking about the music here, buddy.
If you could deliver your politics in an interesting artistic way, I might still appreciate what
you make, even if I disagree with what you're putting out, possibly.
I might be able to get there, but you're just boring as hell.
Look, everybody knows Cecil DeMille, okay?
We get it.
Yeah.
So he comes out with another rapper whose name I forget because I don't care, but they
have some tech issues at the beginning and so they have to vamp for a little bit.
Of course they have to vamp.
And then the music starts.
And this is the last clip because what ends up happening is just perfect.
It could not be more perfect.
I think that this sums up everything.
Who out here is disappointed in the Supreme court decision yesterday?
God, God told the Patriots.
They thought they was going to kill our spirit, but we still out here and we still live Trump
2020 on a gang.
Y'all got to say I'm working.
I heard the play.
Did you hear?
Oh, here we go.
I love the second amendment.
Y'all ready?
God gave it to me.
Not one politician.
God told him Bible reading, God believe in truth, speaking American, it's magazines and
Democrats.
They go away from the rap concert to do a MyPillow commercial.
Wow.
Uh, guys, guys, you were supposed to get the, uh, you were supposed to get the version without
the lyrics.
I just wanted to the instrumental guys, guys, the instrumental it's rapping with me.
Yeah.
It's rapping with me.
Mostly the track.
I'm supposed to, what is this riff raff?
I'm supposed to actually perform.
Yeah.
One of the things that I found really interesting too, is if you watch this video, there's a
guy who looks like Napoleon dynamite on stage.
Wow.
Gotta have him.
I don't know what this dude is doing.
I can't tell if he's with them and there as a visual joke that he's dancing along with
them or whatever, or if he's like from some other outlet cause he's carrying like a stick
mic.
Sure, sure.
Of course.
I don't, I have no idea what's going on.
It's bewildering.
It's modern Forrest Gump.
We're going to find a movie about that guy 20 years from now and he's going to be everywhere.
It's outrageous.
He will have inserted himself into the Vietnam war.
I can't tell you how like weird, like obviously we're recording this on Sunday and this was
all happening on Saturday.
And so in order to make this really work, it ended up like I had a really late night
last night.
And so I'm like, you know, late into the evening watching these banal speeches and then hearing
this lady being like, we must chant Jesus name and then a rap concert break it out.
I was so amused by it.
And then the fact that the broadcast goes straight to a MyPillow commercial in the middle
of maybe the most energetic thing they had on their stage the entire time.
It just was kind of disrespectful to this very serviceable rapper.
Jesus.
Jesus Christ.
Indeed.
That is, that has got to be the most surreal night I can think of.
Like to go that, so just to ride that all the way through to like three.
See now if you were just watching one rally, no big deal.
Sure.
No big deal, no big cuts, but you, you listen to Alex Jones.
Yeah.
I have a high tolerance.
But you're watching seven straight hours of rallies.
At least.
Seven straight hours of rallies on after a long day into the wee hours of the morning.
Yep.
And at a certain point, didn't you have to just have a complete break from reality?
I kind of did think at a certain point I was making up what was happening.
It feels like you, that must have been, that's how I would feel if you're telling me this
happened.
It was surreal.
I was doing it by myself.
Do you know what I mean?
Yeah.
There were, there were a couple points where I thought like, this is self parody.
There, there is no way Mike Flynn's speech started with a MyPillow ad.
It can't be.
Why is this guy giving out MyPillow codes?
This is nonsense.
This cannot be as a thing.
It's, it's so tough to like really put your hands on what this is.
Yeah.
It's, it's simultaneously a terrifying display of different levels of explicitness about
a desire to live in a Christian theocracy.
Yeah.
You know, it's not about, um, standing up for your right to be able to practice your
religion.
It's about enforcing your religious beliefs onto the government, making the government
adhere to your religious beliefs at the expense of everyone else who does not share your beliefs.
You got it.
It's horrifying.
Horrifying.
Because you have the, you know, the, the Jericho March, which is maybe, you know, obviously
more upfront about it.
It's called the Jericho.
But it shares overlap in funding and speakers with the same other March.
And quite honestly, I think that the people that I heard on the other March, the women
for Trump or women for America first, there was more Christian nationalism probably on
display there.
Yeah.
They, they did, they didn't have someone like Leon Benjamin saying, we got to kill the devil
so our kids don't have to.
There was that one.
There was a little bit more speak freely going on over there, but I, I think I'm more scared
of the women for America first rally, honestly, because they're smart enough to not allow
Alex there.
Right.
It's, it's fascism packaged by Coca-Cola.
Like it is, it is so much, and well, yeah, I mean, that's that like tying together of
just base base commerce, just fucking promo code level commerce with fucking your ostensible
belief system, which we all know is complete bullshit.
If you, if you think anything that those rallies had to do, those rallies had zero to do with
Christianity.
I agree.
Zero.
It's a mask that's being worn.
100%.
And one of the things that's really difficult is that like, I don't, I'm not saying that
of everybody who's in the crowd again.
Like I think that there's probably maybe some sincere and misled people who are there.
Sure.
I don't know.
I can't, I can't say.
Yeah.
But I don't think that, I can't imagine that the people who are putting this on are motivated
by a sincere spirituality.
Absolutely not.
It's very difficult for me to accept that and maybe it feels that way to them.
I'm not sure.
It's very difficult to judge.
I wrestle with this because it's something that's so intimate and personal within someone
like true religious feelings and whenever you sort of criticize somebody about their
sincerity or lack thereof, it kind of comes off as if, oh, you think you have sincere
beliefs.
No.
And I don't, I don't want to get into that kind of an argument, but this is gross.
Here's, here's what I would say about that.
If your beliefs are sincere and you're looking for Christ and all that stuff, go read the
Way of the Pilgrim and really, really like meditate on Thessalonians and the idea of
praying every day and every moment and what that actually means.
Or you could go to a rally and try and overthrow a nation and kill a bunch of people.
Yeah.
The novelty that I have is the combination of both of these rallies being so explicitly
like Christian nationalist in character, so overt about it and both of them being so crass.
Like the joke, like we're laughing our asses off at all the MyPillow stuff, but like that's
it both of these rallies.
It's happening at both of them.
So fucked.
And the parody level of the like praying and chanting Jesus into a drunk guy introducing
a rap act.
Just ridiculous.
Like it's bizarre.
It's surreal.
And I don't know what to do with it, but I do think that like Alex Jones got a lot of
headlines out of crashing that Jericho March one.
And so it does come into our view.
And I think that one of the things that's important, I guess, is to take what we know
about Alex and what we understand about that and glimpse the external world a little bit
when there is a chance to, and quite honestly, looking at these people, some of whom I'm
aware of, some of whom I'm not, who are chosen by these people who are organizing these rallies
to give these speeches, I don't see a lot of difference between what they're putting
out there and what Alex does.
Nope.
And that is not how I felt even like, even when we look back at like 2009, like even
when the Tea Party was going on, there were still substantive differences between the
Tea Party and Alex Jones.
Alex was more severe.
Yeah.
He may be more severe than some of these people and more extreme, but like these rallies,
I don't understand why, except for bad press, they would not let Alex speak at both of them.
I don't know.
I don't get it.
I don't get why they have to parade around even at the Jericho March with the code.
Pretending that he's not there.
And the code of like in the spirit of inclusion and you know, like all that, like go fuck
yourself.
He's right on board with exactly what you're, he's doing what you're doing better.
Yeah.
The idea that they are still allowed to, like that was Alex's role for Fox News and the
Rush Limbaugh's and the Glenn Beck's is for them to be like, hey, at least we're not like
Alex Jones.
Right.
They're all like that and they're still trying to act like by saying, hey, at least we're
not Alex Jones in Info Wars, we still get a, we still get that difference.
You're not, there's no difference.
There's no difference.
No.
Well, I mean, so how dare you act like you're too good for Alex.
If there is, I'm mad on it, I'm mad on his behalf.
Don't feel that way.
I don't.
But I think, I think that, you know, I can see where that thought comes from.
Yeah, of course.
It largely comes from the reality that if you watch that rally, you'll see a difference
in competence from Alex and the rest of the speakers.
Yep.
If the, if the goal is to rile up this crowd, God damn it does Alex do a better job than
any of the rest of them.
Even at that point when he's like getting not allowed on stage, he gets the crowd to
chant his name.
People are still chanting, we love Alex.
Yeah.
Yeah, totally.
Gets on the bullhorn and yells 1776 and people start chanting his name.
And that's how you fucking do it.
Right.
He can do all this better than all of you, but unfortunately his brand is so toxic that
no one, even Ali Alexander wants to admit that he basically works for Infowars.
Yeah, no kidding.
So, I mean, it's kind of like, I don't know.
I think that this kind of sums up what I think is one of the main problems.
Who's had it with these fact checkers?
Haven't you had it with these fact checkers?
That could almost be the big problem.
That's probably a better way of putting it.
Yeah.
I think, I think when you cheer for fuck fact checkers.
Who's up with all this reality?
Yeah.
Who's up here with, I'm sick of it, I'm sick of it.
Let's live in a dream world.
Who wants to live in a dream world?
Boo.
Hey, who likes to confirm things?
Read a book.
The mind is the fear killer.
Fear, fear, mind killer.
Boo.
Yeah.
So I thought this was an interesting exploration, a little bit sort of, not fully outside of
our realm but sort of to the side of it a tiny bit.
Sure, sure.
And it bummed me out more than usual just because it's like, oh, all these people chanting
and cheering and all these speakers sounding very similar to Alex.
It's a bummer and I think we have a very large problem in front of us that I do not know
how to deal with.
Yeah.
And I think that it's important to recognize that one of the major problems is the blurring
here.
This is not political.
This isn't about politics.
This is not about policies.
This is something else altogether.
And trying to approach it from the standpoint of arguing or politics, it's not gonna work.
It's absolutely not gonna work.
Here's my pitch, all right?
Now I think one of the speakers did point out that the nation was created and now he
said it was created by God and I would argue that it was created because of King George
and the like and his ilk.
Who's had it with these fact checkers?
All right.
But maybe we should learn something from King George, Dan, okay?
What did King George do?
I already dispute your premise because I hate fact checkers.
What did King George do or what did the king do when faced with Puritans?
They were causing a ruckus and then he was like, get the fuck out, and then they all
left.
Yeah, I know.
So we shoot him to the moon, Dan.
This seems too much like those mentalities that I find kind of noxious, which are the
like, you don't like it, get out.
I was being facetious about this.
I know, but even as a joke, I don't really like it because it sounds so much like the,
you know, you hear this rhetoric from Trump people.
You know, like Trump being the president, get out.
And I just don't think that's a good solution either.
Sure.
I don't know.
It's a, it's a tough time to be in the middle of this because I don't really know how the
ball breaks.
Well, steadfast tolerance of intolerance clearly isn't working.
No, I would agree with that.
Kicking people out.
That's not a great solution.
Didn't work last time.
No.
Violence doesn't work.
Violence doesn't do it.
Maybe we should try using like those.
So it's like 2020, right?
And that means that before 2020, there was like a bunch of years and humans and they've
probably dealt with some shit like this before.
We should probably try smarts.
Well, I wish that I had this clip because actually a really great general, Michael Flynn,
you might've heard of him.
I've heard of him.
Yeah.
In his speech, he discusses how this has never happened in human history before.
It's never happened.
So actually we can't learn anything from history.
It's a completely new and unique situation.
It's really convenient how we can't know anything about this because it's never happened before.
So unfortunately you're wrong.
All those book learning idiots, this has never happened before.
Don't listen to them.
Yeah, they're a bunch of dumb fact checkers.
Fuck them.
God damn it.
I don't know.
Anyway, we'll be back on our next episode talking more specifically about Alex Jones,
but I don't know.
These rallies sucked.
They sucked.
Anyway, we'll be back.
But until then, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yep.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at Knowledge Fight.
Now go to Ben Jordan.
We're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook.
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work.
Yes.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I am about to go buy a red sequin smoking jacket.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.