N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Damn and Jordan, I am sweating
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledgefight
knowledgefight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
saying we are the bad guys
knowledgefight
Damn and Jordan, knowledgefight
Riddle her, riddle her, riddle her
I need, I need money
Andy and Kansas, Andy and, Andy and
Stop it, Andy and, Andy and Kansas
Andy, Andy, it's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding me
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm with your Japan
I love your room
knowledgefight
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to knowledgefight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're couple dudes, I can sit around, drink knowledge
beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are Dan
Jordan
Dan
I have a quick question for you
Yes sir
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today is, you know, just the recognition
that, you know, decades from now, centuries from now
this will be looked upon as the week of too much of you and me
Quite a week of too much of us
Dan, I think that you are underestimating exactly how much more we're going to do in the weeks to come
This is an extensive week of programming between our episode on our Patreon
our little bonus episode and then also thank you to Robert and Sophie
Yes, huge thanks to Robert and Sophie
Behind the Bastards and I got to bring up something, I got to bring information to the table
that everyone is unaware of
Yes
About invention from Goldwater
Yes, I do recall that
Yeah
Yes
That's something we've talked about on this show but apparently was new to the proceedings
I would say that you were so excited to
Very excited
You were incredibly excited, you were shivering and shaking almost as though there was
like a bug in my pants
You know, it's just something I couldn't feel but it was there
So yeah, I guess that's my bright spot, too much of us
Yeah
How about you?
My bright spot is Dan Taylor Swift
Taylor Swift is my bright spot because you're so mad
I was worried about this
No, yeah, I decided to start listening to every Taylor Swift
I've never listened to Taylor Swift at all
You've never been to a Walgreens?
On purpose or in full, is that a better way of putting it?
So I've never done that before and then I was, I've really been struggling to come up
with a project since the book ended and I've just been like throwing shit at the wall and
it's not been going well
Well, here comes another piece of spaghetti
For some reason I was like, you know what, now I'm going to do it so I've decided to
listen to every one of Taylor Swift's albums in a row, chronological order and review each
one
We talked about this a little bit and I resent you for this because I think it's going to
have a really negative tone
Oh man, is it dark
Yeah
It is very fun to be incredibly mean to a seventeen year old who is going to go on to
be a billionaire
Yeah, but I also resent that at this point you're still at a point where I can't really
rebut anything you're saying
Of course
I don't know anything about Taylor Swift's first album
Sure, sure, sure
But if you start getting real shitty about some of those later albums we might have words
I think if you read it you will find that I am very complimentary towards things that
deserve complimenting
And I am hyperbolically incredibly cruel to things that are just meh
Okay
You know, that's kind of how I like to do it
I'll check it out, where can people find this?
People can find it on a friend of the show Matthias Drufki's website fancyboysclub.com
I'll be posting those probably once a week or until I get really pissed off at Taylor
Swift and decide never to do this again
And if I get bored enough I will write scheming rebuttals
I think that would be fun
But there will be only personally attacking you
Yes, I would love that
There's nothing to do with the music, just personally attacking you
What you should do is do the exact same thing but for each chapter of my book
Right
Every week we'll just hate each other
Has Jordan ever written a pop masterpiece?
No
Absolutely not
Alright, well Jordan today we've got an interesting episode to go over
We're going to be talking about December 16th and 17th, 2020
I'm Dan, this is 2020
Hooray!
Shit got interesting and weird this week so we're going to have a little bit of a, I don't
know, memento style
We're going to start with December 17th
And then we're going to go back
I've heard some news
Yeah
So before we get to the episode, let's take a little moment to say thank you to some folks
who have signed up and are supporting the show
So first, Batchain Masterson, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you
Batchain
Next, Olivia M, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Olivia
Next, James T, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Oh, thank you very much James
Next, Liz G, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Liz
Next, Zakaria K, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, Zakaria
Next, Jonathan T, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much JT
And...
Hmm?
What?
Triple T?
Are you talking about home improvement?
Couple JTTs?
No.
And finally, I'd like to say thank you to a couple of people who donated on an elevated
level.
We appreciate that very much.
So, Big Easy Blasphemy, thank you so much, you are now a technocrat.
And Cory S, thank you so much, you are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate, that's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much, Big Easy Blasphemy, and thank you so much, Cory.
Yes, thank you very much to the both of you.
If you're out there listening and you're thinking, hey, I enjoy this show, I'd like to support
what these gents do, you can do that by going to our website, knowledgefight.com, clicking
the button that says support the show, or...
What you could do is create some sort of tortured analogy towards trying to find writing something
about Taylor Swift into a generosity thing.
But I would just suggest that you guys go to your local charity or bail fund and support
people that way.
Go to the easy road on this show.
Man, it was just gonna be, I was thinking about it on the way here.
You were trying to get a little too meta with it right there.
I was trying to, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was tough.
It's a tough one.
Yeah, that's all right.
So, I wanted to play The Sound of Silence to start this episode, but that would be very
hacky, so I decided not to.
Oh, well, real quick, I have one piece of business, just real quick, right off the top.
Somebody reached out to me.
Nothing to do with The Sound of Silence.
Nothing to do with The Sound of Silence, completely unrelated.
Somebody reached out to me, and she asked me politely if we would wish her partner a
happy birthday.
His name is Joe, and I was told that the way to identify him was that he skips over our
theme song.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, which then made me be like, am I even gonna fucking do this now?
There we go.
We're gonna play it again.
That's what's gonna happen.
Take that.
Yes, yes.
Happy birthday, Joe.
I hope you have a good one.
It's been a tough year for everybody, you know, everybody who had a birthday this year,
wasn't their favorite birthday, I'm sure.
Totally.
Mine wasn't.
Nope.
And hey, here's the other thing.
What's up?
If you are dating a Joe, or married to a Joe, or whatever with a Joe who also skips over
the theme song, tell them it was you.
Tell them it was you.
We won't tell.
Totally.
I'm not saying anything.
I'm not gonna follow up on that shit.
We're not snitches.
I'm sorry to lie to your partner.
I built a strong relationship.
And now, back to The Sound of Silence.
Yes, indeed.
Hello Darkness, my old friend.
I couldn't help but like find, I was, look, okay.
Beginning of the week, we had the rallies in DC, and then I was kind of planning on
this episode to like cover the very predictable and obvious reactions Alex would have to it.
But then, today, Thursday, as it was getting game time to do this episode, we got hit with
some big news.
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
At Libertyterion on Twitter, the one person at Infowars who has managed to duck getting
banned because he's too boring for anyone to notice is there, David Knight announced
that he was fired, effective immediately, from Infowars.
Oh boy.
Stevie P's got to him in the end, huh?
I don't know if that's the case.
That is the obvious thing that you would think, because David Knight has been on a bit of
a public vendetta against Steve Pachanik, who has been trying to convince people at
Infowars that the election was a grand sting operation, and David Knight's not having any
of that bullshit.
David Knight fired for being inexplicably a half-truth teller.
To his credit, he responded appropriately to that.
Although to not his credit, he also, you know, the last time he had Steve on, he said, yes,
I believe Sandy Hook was a false flag, but I will not agree with you about Las Vegas.
So I don't know where his line is.
He's a half-truth teller.
Yeah, and this big, this big news, and I don't want to shit on somebody when they're down
or like make fun of it, but I mean, like, it's relevant to our interests.
David Knight has been there forever.
He's been there 10 years, probably?
Something like that.
Totally.
He has always been there through the thick and thin of so much horrible bullshit.
Went along with Alex as he got into Trump.
Maybe Alex just remembered that David Knight was there, and he was like, shit, I meant
to fire him five years ago, and then I just forgot.
He's just so boring.
I don't know.
I'm actually kind of conflicted.
I'm not entirely sure what I think the case is here, and I think we'll discuss this as
we go through the episode.
So we're going to start with the 17th, and we're going to start with Alex's conversation
about, because I think he knew he needed to get ahead of this.
And so he has fired David at this point.
We're past it.
Yes.
And so Thursday's show, he's going to deal with some housekeeping business for a little
bit.
First thing I want to say, the tank was a good idea.
It was a good idea.
Solid investment.
It was a good investment.
Anyways, we have lost some personnel.
The tank brings in more money than David Knight, sells more pills.
So we're going to look at that, and then we're going to flash back to the 16th, and we're
just going to discuss what kind of content was going on there, because I got just bored
as hell after Alex stopped talking about current events of his own issues.
So here's an out of context drop from today's show.
Now I don't want to liken myself to a US president, but this job is about as close as it gets.
Okay.
All right.
I mean, currently, maybe.
Maybe.
Look, I talk shit and vaguely read headlines.
I'm basically the president.
Pretty close.
Pretty close when you get down to it.
I get lied to by weirdos as a profession.
Yeah.
I too like Stephen Miller.
So I kind of had a sense that it was going to be something that Alex has to bring up,
because David Knight has made this public.
He's come out with it.
So Alex frames things this way when he gets going on the show on the 17th and he was late.
He was late for the show.
There was some special reports at the beginning, and I've got a really huge announcement coming
up at the bottom of the hour about the future of info Wars and about this organization and
a restructuring we're going to be doing that'll be announced today.
I've waited long enough and I've told folks about how we're under attack and what's going
on with info Wars, and I don't think people take that serious sometimes.
But info Wars is fighting for its life, just like the rest of the country and the rest
of the world is.
We don't get globalist money.
We didn't get the $10.6 million that black lives matter got from the new world order.
And the only money we get is from you.
And we can't fight if you don't support us.
We'll be right back.
Stay with us.
So there's restructuring going on in the info war.
Yes.
There's demotions.
Clearly.
Yeah.
There's nothing really specific yet at this point.
There's just kind of like the insinuation that we're going to talk about what the future
is going to look like around here.
Yeah.
And I podcasts.
They're the future.
I grow weary of this quite honestly, because we've been, we've been on this track before
we've, we've done some laps around this, uh, granted the move of firing David Knight.
That one wasn't really big.
That's a big one.
Yeah.
That one's tough to, to undersell.
That's, that's tough to look at as like, Oh, you're just blowing smoke.
Yeah.
There's something there.
Now, whether it's like a resources are tight.
I got a call from Melania and she said, get rid of David Knight.
Sure.
Is it the Steve situation or is it a money?
Yeah.
I don't know.
Could be.
I can't tell.
So, uh, I was like, what else is going on here?
Alex got anything to talk about other than your own dumb bullshit.
Trump tried to turn our economy back on, get us out of the global system.
He did really a splendid job on many fronts, made some big mistakes and still with 34 days
left.
If he levels with the American people in resolute desk speeches and asked for 10 million Americans
to March on Washington peacefully, but to March on all our other capitals, to demonstrate
that we know there's massive election fraud and that we repudiate the globalist corporate
media, the NWL has a very good chance of folding up and backing down.
Because then the justice department and others will have the courage to do the right thing
and prosecute.
So Alex is pretending that bunch of people could go March and then the new world order
would be like, Oh no.
Yeah.
What about plan B?
Nah, it's a show of force.
Yeah.
There's 10 million people in one spot.
You can't do plan B when they're all there.
That would be perfect.
That's when you gas them all.
There's too many.
That's when you hit the bio weapon.
That's what plan B is.
There's not enough bio weapon, it would be too diffuse and everybody would get a little
sick.
That's not how a bio weapon works.
This is a super bio weapon.
You forgot that plan B is a super bio weapon.
Yeah, a super bio weapon hits 5 million people in one place max.
That's twice as many.
I just, I just can't, I can't get it up for this kind of thing.
No, this is sad.
He doesn't even believe it.
No.
I can't, I can't handle the guy trying to tell me that like, Oh, we just need a bunch
of people to March and then maybe the cabal of people who've been planning this for thousands
of years will be like, Oh no, people, when Alex has already said that there's a plan
B, if all of, if they manage to like, even if they get Trump back in office, there's
a plan B that's just everyone dies, but it's a little less organized.
Yeah.
Like I don't, I don't, how, how, why, what does this matter?
I don't know.
But the idea of the devil who has been with humanity since there were two and now there
are several billion of us for him to be like, Whoa, 10 million is just too much for me to
look.
I got to tell the NWO to back off.
That's just mathematically a little bit problematic because you have to assume that the new world
order would be doing the devil's bidding.
They would have to.
Right.
The only reason that they're doing the things that they're doing is because the devil has
told them that they should.
Right.
And I mean, yeah, if the devil is like, who cares about 10 million people marching, it's
no big deal.
You'd assume they would just keep going with their plans.
Does the devil phone or does he appear?
I don't know.
He seems really interested in domestic politics.
He really does.
I feel like he should get a phone.
It's a whole big world out there for the devil.
Does the devil email?
Cause if he's appearing everywhere, this is, this is, this is stupid and it feels trivial
even within Alex's own conspiracies.
I just don't care.
No, this is dumb.
So how about you get back to your bullshit, Alex, I want to hear more about your, your
situation.
And info wars, I'm giving you the good news.
Info wars has three to five times the audience on a day-to-day basis that we've ever had
except for right around the last election.
And that's despite all the de-platforming.
What we do not have is the funding we had then.
And so I'm the type of guy that has kept everybody employed, kept the shows going, kept us in
the, in the field, kept funding everything, mortgaged my house a year ago to be able to
have emergency funding, to, to, to run this operation, to, to take care of shortfalls.
But I can look at the other things I have as, as an emergency backup, and it wouldn't
fund this place for a month if I had to liquidate everything I've got.
Cause this is a big operation, our own satellites, our own IT, our own feeds, our own everything,
all the DNC lawsuits against us, everything.
Wait, wait, wait, the DNC lawsuits?
DNC?
DNC lawsuits?
Uh, I don't know about that.
What are the DNC doing?
Uh, also I think that's called being overextended.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's, um...
You could, you could also put that thusly, um, we should have scaled back.
Mm-hmm.
Long time ago.
Yeah.
No reason to not have.
Mm-hmm.
That tank was a bad purchase.
No need for that tank.
Um, this studio looks great.
It looks amazing.
Completely pointless.
Maybe too big for just one person to sit there.
Yeah.
Could be too big.
Maybe a little ostentatious.
Ostentatious.
Oh, ooh.
The stumble upon a pun that Ralphie May made years ago with the name of one of his specials.
Yeah.
I don't like that.
I remember that.
Mm-hmm.
Anyway, uh, look, you need to buy his products cause Alex needs money.
Sure.
And you know what?
You need them too.
You need the products too.
I had one of the crew members over here, tore his leg, had some medical stuff, went to the
doctor.
They wanted to put him on stuff for his low, low T. He didn't do it.
Got tested again.
He came in on Monday or Tuesday, he said, look at this, I got tested, started taking
super male vitality and look at my numbers.
It was incredible.
I had to check with lawyers.
We can even show you this stuff.
There's the other system.
So you're not supposed to know what herbs can do, but that's the type of things that
are happening and that are going on.
And I'm just here to tell you, and you've come through over and over again.
I keep telling you, we can't keep operating.
We can't keep doing it at this level.
If you don't support us, if you don't pray for us, if you don't spread the word, we're
way more hardcore than Newsmax, OAN, everybody else.
And I love them.
I hope they get more hardcore than I am.
And I like OAN.
You know, we're on cloud TV.
Number one.
OAN and Newsmax are the worst thing that could happen for Alex.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The fact that those two outlets are doing slick shit, they have some sort of financing
from some mysterious source, I'm sure.
They have better than 19 year olds working in their rooms.
They have the ability to pretend that they're news.
They don't act like Alex screaming about the devil.
They say the same shit.
Absolutely.
They get to...
They have...
They're like all David Knights.
Yeah.
They have the editorial standards of Alex, but the appearance of a news thing.
It's the worst thing ever for Alex.
He has no place in the market anymore, unless he does something different.
He has to pivot, or else it will just be, I'm another one of them that no one will plug
because I suck, because I'm so toxic.
It's funny.
I kind of think Alex is confused by that, because I really do think that when he sees
his set and the way his show runs, he's like, this looks like a news organization.
Yeah.
You know?
He totally thinks that.
Yep.
So how can he look at OAN and Newsmax and be like, they're just like me.
You know?
Isn't that wild?
I don't think he watches anything other than...
Oh, that's fair.
I bet he doesn't have the time for it, nor the interest.
That's fair.
I think it's actually kind of interesting that because those things exist, things like
Newsmax or OAN, David Knight could easily get a job at either of them.
They've accidentally created employability for the people that work for Alex.
Right.
Who art Alex?
They've created a situation where he can't hold people hostage working at Infowars anymore.
If you have aspirations to be a right-wing shit journalist, there are other options now.
Yeah.
Alex.
Oh, God.
I think the good news is Schroyer's not going anywhere.
I don't think so.
Even after, you know?
Nobody's hiring...
Even Newsmax is going to see OAN Schroyer walk in and be like, and you may turn around
now?
I can't tell exactly from listening to this, but it does appear that OAN is the only other
person who survived the axe.
Oh, shit.
The axe.
Like straight up axe.
We'll get to it.
Oh, boy.
Now I'm excited.
I might have shown my cards too early.
You might have shown too many cards.
But we should know that Alex is being very clear that he's not quitting.
Okay.
And so, you know, I said on Joe Rogan's show five weeks ago, I said, I've thought about
retiring and the media thought that was just, you know, Jones trying to act like he's this
reluctant hero.
But that's not what it is.
Reluctant hero?
I only dream about this stuff 90% of the time, used to 5% of the time.
I have basically no life other than this.
That's all I do and I still feel like I'm not doing enough, but I'm not going to quit.
I can't imagine it being his life and him being so bad at this.
Yeah.
What are you putting time into?
I don't know.
What could he possibly be?
In regards to the show, okay, you've dedicated your life to this show.
You talk for three to four hours for being a very generous day.
Yeah.
Or someone cancels.
Right.
And you read and I think something happens while you are holding a thing.
He reads headlines.
There are words that he sees that then become brain thoughts, but I don't know what reading
would be for him.
The only thing I can imagine that would take a lot of time is maybe it requires like extensive
meditation or yoga in order to get into his like prophetic psychic trance or whatever
that he says he can kick himself into.
Okay.
So he reads headlines and then like gets into some kind of a weird trance state.
Sure.
And then he reports on what the trance showed him about this headline as opposed to reading
the article.
Yeah.
Because that would take too much time.
Do you know what his mantra is?
What's that?
Soros.
I can't.
I just can't imagine it.
Like because he doesn't need to practice talking shit.
He's really good at it.
No, he's ecstatic at it.
Yeah.
He doesn't take time is preparing and he clearly doesn't do that.
So I don't know.
Anyway, this is not the end.
It is a new chapter.
So it's been the greatest pleasure of my life, 27 years on air, knowing all of you and fighting
the new world order and doing all of this.
And I'm not going anywhere yet, but you need to know a new chapters here.
You know, when I tell you that the CIA follows us around and the FBI and the secret service
now, and they come and sit down next to us at the restaurants and tell us that they come
visit us at the hotel and turn our cell phones off so we can't videotape them.
And that, you know, the former director of the CIA comes out and says he wants me arrested
on Twitter.
That isn't me scared.
That's not me afraid.
It's me lying.
That's just InfoWars entering a new chapter of life.
Embellishing probably more than lying because Michael Hayden did tweet an agreement with
somebody who tweeted that Alex should be arrested for his statement about Biden at that rally
over the weekend.
Yeah.
Um, yeah, I, I don't know the new chapter, what is a new chapter?
What does that mean?
What does that entail?
And I, I, you can sum it up with a song title, no more, mr nice guy.
And so I'm here to tell you that I'm not going to back down and I'm going to do exactly what
I think is the most moral and best thing to do.
And that starts with not being a nice guy anymore, not, not, not being delusional about
where we stand and what we can do and the fact that I have this tendency to never even
shake up things in my own operations because I'm so loyal, even though to the point of
their operation, not being able to function.
So up to this point, you'd been an mr nice guy.
That speech.
I can only hear that, like imagining him just giving it directly to the mirror as he's putting
the joker makeup on, you know, like he's, he's just given this like, no more mr nice
guy.
All right.
Put a little bit more rouge.
The problem with me and the reason I've gotten to this point is I'm too loyal, too loyal.
I've never met Wolfgang never met anybody.
He's the crack.
And who's cracking.
We changed the crack.
But Donnie didn't work here.
I don't know that guy.
Never heard of him.
Never met him.
So look, a lot of people are gone.
And without mentioning David Knight by name, of course, there's some other people that
you might've gotten used to seeing it in for us that aren't around anymore.
And so I pledge to you that I'm going to work harder in the fight against the new world
order.
And I'm asking you to fight harder against the globalist, but I've already explained
to you, we had to let Caitlin Bennett go.
Cause we couldn't pay her anymore.
We had to let Millie Weaver go and, and God bless Caitlin.
She hasn't made up a bunch of stuff about us as we let her go.
You've seen what Milly's done.
God bless her.
It's okay.
She did a lot of great work in the past.
No, she did not.
No, no, no.
I like the idea that Alex is trying to pretend that he didn't fire her for shadow gate.
That's fun.
Yeah.
How could she make up all of this stuff?
When I literally said, I don't get into that stuff.
It's too scary.
This is the gate of yeah.
That weirdo guy from your film showed up at my studio and then was talking about Roger
Stone in ways that I don't appreciate.
You're fired.
Oh, it was finances.
Sure.
I hate that she's making up that stuff.
Yeah.
But like, because of things in finances and the difficulties that Alex is in, the situation,
he's had to cut back a whole bunch, you know, like there were people like Millie, there
were people like Caitlin Bennett that he was funding and now he can't, he can't do that
anymore.
But three, four years ago, when I still had plenty of money, I was funding dozens of organizations,
dozens of groups that were doing great work.
I was taking the money you sent us buying products and sending it out where I thought
it was key to fight the new world order.
I'm down to funding three or four organizations outside of our own operation now I've been
cut back to a hill I'm on and I'll die on this hill.
But everybody sits here and hears me say that you don't think I'm serious.
So we're going to have to reorganize and we're going to have to rethink what we're doing.
I'm going to stay on the air four hours a day.
So was on for three hours a day.
I've got a council, the nighttime election countdown show, just because there's not the
crew.
There's not the funds.
There's not the money.
And we're going to reorganize some of the other shows and then revamp them and relaunch
them because I never give up, but I can give out second old horse, you know, horses will
run and run and run until their heart blows up.
Yeah.
He's like a, he's like a horse, uh, with his, uh, with his heart, um, about to blow up.
Run, run faster.
Keep going.
So, um, from that clip, what I take away is the election countdown with Deanna Lorraine
and Robert Barnes over.
That's gone.
There's no staff for that.
Fuck it.
Sorry.
Barnes.
Alex is going to be on still and Owen.
Yeah.
Conspicuous in its absence from that list is the only other show and that's the David Knight
show.
Well, there's that one.
So you're going to retool and revamp these shows, but obviously the, you know, according
to David Knight's Twitter, he got fired.
So you're going to revamp it with somebody else, I guess.
Uh, yeah, probably.
Uh, he wants to bring in a younger crowd.
So, you know, 11 or 12 year old video game streamer is probably who he's going to hit
things with hammers.
Exactly.
Yeah.
He's electric.
Harrison Smith is probably the best they have there.
And that's bad.
Yeah.
That's not good.
Really bad.
No, no, no.
Uh, you can wear shades.
Uh, you don't need to actually.
So, um, like, uh, I, I think that this metaphor too is a little bit rough and I don't appreciate
it.
Alex talking about, you know, you can, you're a horse and you're just running until your
heart gives out.
David Knight had a heart attack last year and then he came back to work because he was
so passionate about this shit.
That's very funny.
Like, like I don't look, I don't want to be this guy.
Sure.
Like giving a shit when it's not my time to give a shit.
But like David Knight gave a lot to this.
He did.
And we are now a couple of weeks before Christmas.
Uh huh.
Alex is fucking firing him.
Yeah, absolutely.
That's so bad.
Ah, come on.
That's so shitty.
Come on.
Everybody was like, Oh, feel bad for Bob Cratchit.
What did, when did they think about how Scrooge was like a fucking horse who was going to
steal everybody's money until his heart gave out?
Nobody's thinking about Scrooge here.
Okay.
This is dirty man.
He's doing him dirty.
He couldn't wait until the new year.
What?
God, I just, I just want, I just hope that David Knight is overwhelmed by not like sadness
or regret or like anything other than just like, I am so stupid for coming back after
that fucking heart attack.
Well.
I should never have fucking done that.
I have a slightly different hope and that is that I hope it gets ugly.
Like yeah, I do too.
Not for his like, uh, like nothing negative for him or anything, but like, I hope he kept
some receipts.
Oh yeah.
For sure.
I hope there's some, uh, real fun.
Oh yeah.
Uh, but hey, look, uh, Alex is this horse and he's running and he needs a break.
Any good horse will run till its heart blows.
It won't stop.
You keep running a horse, it'll go till it dies.
And um, you know, I've met a physically, but also physically got to that point.
I can't stop working.
I've got to take a week off.
I've got to turn everything off.
I've got to do it.
And it doesn't matter where the middle of the shine battle because I know when smokes
coming out of the race car engine, you got to pull over and get it, get it, get it oil
put in there.
Yeah.
You got to put some oil in there.
Sure.
Yeah.
You got to take a week off Alex.
We got to put oil in the horse.
You just went to DC.
You just took a, took a trip to DC.
That was work.
That was work related.
Yeah.
I mean, he stayed in a nice hotel and ate really well, but he should have gone with
Owen on the caravan.
That would have been a fun road trip.
That would have been a nice time.
You guys could have bro-ed out.
Work-cation.
Bonded.
Yeah.
The whole thing.
Uh, take a, take a week off Alex, please.
Yeah.
Uh, so I was wondering like, what's the, this clip confused the hell out of me because Alex
describes what his last straw was.
Okay.
And it's something that doesn't make any sense.
And so I thank you all for your support and I love you and I appreciate you.
Uh, and I, and I, the last straw was this morning I got up and I saw this number, black
lives matter raised 10.6 billion since may.
When you go in a coffee shop like Starbucks or anywhere and they say, give it a black
lives matter.
That's just the communists and the globalists and Soros collecting money.
The DNC on record got 4 billion out of it.
Of the 10 billion last time I checked, look how much the DNC got of that.
That was a few months ago.
That was 4 billion that I'd read.
They'd gotten who knows what it is now.
Um, that's all just miss, uh, misinterpretations of the act blue stuff.
But um, yeah, I don't know why black lives matter getting a certain amount of money would
be the last straw for him in cause it doesn't materially affect what he's doing at all.
No, if I understand correctly, I wrote this down as I was tracking the thought.
All right.
So I wrote down first BLM raised 10 billion and then so I fired David Knight.
Is that the, is that the if then statement that I think we're going for here?
Cause I feel like that's what he's saying.
There's a weird feeling of it, but I think if you distill it down even more, it's like,
I saw that black lives matter made $10 billion and I'm not making close to that and it pisses
me off.
Yeah.
So I'm going to fire David Knight and uh, Deanna Lorraine and well, she might've been
like, I always got the sense that she was just kind of like a temp.
She's an independent contractor.
She was there on a little bit of a assignment or whatever.
She got a cup of coffee.
Yeah.
She wasn't there for any kind of long term thing.
I just, uh, yeah, I don't know.
I'm very conflicted because there's two sides of this that I think of.
One is like the, uh, David Knight had run afoul of Steve Pachannik in a very serious
way.
And that is something that is hard to have in house.
Right.
If you have somebody who is your intro show on your network right before you, who's saying
that one of your experts is a piece of shit liar, that's hard.
That's going to be tough to maintain the status quo.
Right.
And you're a media outlet that is built entirely around bombast.
So it seems fairly simple to be like, okay, well we've got the most boring man ever and
we've got the most bombastic liar ever.
I think we're going to go with the most bombastic liar.
Yeah.
I think we're going to really have a whole lot of stability in, um, uh, keeping th keeping
people in like unengaged, I guess, engaged, unengaged because you want people actively
consuming your material, but you don't want them engaging with it.
Right.
And having David Knight be like, uh, Steve Pachannik's a fucking liar.
Yeah.
Then you have to stop.
Why does, why does David Knight think that he's a liar?
Yeah.
And you can't, but why doesn't Alex not?
You know, it's too complicated and you run the risk of, uh, uh, kickstarting, like critical
thinking in your listeners.
And that's no good.
Yeah.
I can't have that.
Absolutely not.
Stick with Pachannik.
But it does seem like that was a little bit ago.
That was a couple of weeks ago.
Like I don't, I don't know if I could draw a causal link here.
And Alex is saying that it's because of money.
Sure.
Now the only things that are gone are the, uh, night show, which obviously sucked the
evening show that no one cared about.
They canceled when Alex went to DC because they didn't have the crew to run it anyway.
That was already like a secondary tertiary thought for them.
And then David Knight's show, it very easily could be monetary budget constraints, but
I can also see a possible world where Alex was like, fuck, I got to get rid of David
Knight.
It's just not working out.
This is an untenable situation.
How can we fundraise on that?
How can I drive sales with getting rid of David Knight?
I don't know.
I can't, I have no fucking idea.
None of it seems good.
Like none of it seems like this is a, no, I wouldn't look at any of these circumstances
and be like, I'm going to invest in this business.
This business's model looks good.
I'm going to wait until it hits rock bottom first, then I might invest in it.
But right now it's only going down.
Well that might be soon.
That's unclear because a last clip here from the 17th, Alex kind of implies that the Christmas
sale will determine the future of InfoWars.
Just do your Christmas shopping at infoawarsstore.com and we'll expand, but if you don't, we'll contract.
And so we're reassessing right now and InfoWars is contracting ahead of a big offensive.
Now I'm going to decide whether it's our big last offensive or just the next of many, but
I promise you this, we'll go out in a fiery inferno of liberty in a peaceful operation
of total victory.
Peaceful.
I did say offensive a couple of times there in a fiery blaze of, but it's peaceful.
It's all peaceful.
Don't worry.
I would like one last image of InfoWars to be Alex standing in the studio as everything
burns around him with his arms outstretched, his head facing and screaming into the sky.
I think that's how he's got to go out.
Sure.
Right?
That last image.
I don't want him to actually be burnt alive.
Like in a movie.
Yeah.
It would be a fitting arc.
Like Gary Oldman in The Professional whenever his eyes are all bloodshot and he's screaming
to this guy.
Yeah.
So actually I'm going to play this last clip here from the 17th.
I have one more, but it's just sort of like indicative of like me losing my patience with
Alex and why we're going to now jump back to the 16th to see what things were like 24
hours prior to Alex spending the beginning of his show talking about how dire shit is
and David Knight's fired.
So I like Andres Manuel Lopez Ormidor.
He's a socialist, but he is a real socialist.
And by that, I mean, he's a popular socialist and is actually trying to get higher wages
for people and trying to get corporations to actually not be tax exempt.
I don't agree with that model long term, but so Alex, what the fuck does that mean?
Alex has decided that he likes the president of Mexico because there were some comments
about COVID precautions that Alex enjoyed.
And so now I like him now.
He's a socialist, but he's a real socialist.
Whatever.
You should hate him more.
Fuck off.
That's the thing that you hate most.
You hate people who don't understand socialism, who think that, God, I hate it.
You hate people who you decide are socialists.
Exactly.
Yeah.
And so we jumped back to the 16th to see like, are there any signs?
Are there any indications that we can get from the 16th that like just a day later?
Hey, everybody, it's December 16th.
I gotta be honest.
We've never had more money than we have right now.
We're just so fucking flush.
Anyways, we'll see how it goes tomorrow.
So we start with Alex, the exciting and interesting source.
America and the rest of the world is under globalist, big tech siege, a corporate planetary
takeover to replace humans and to make us obsolete.
The Von Mies Institute is highly respected.
With some of the top academics, researchers, economists in the world, they've come out
with a big article that's on Infowars.com where they say this is a dystopic, big tech
bio slash digital technocracy.
The Mies Institute is not a super well respected.
They're like hardcore libertarian.
No, no, no.
We've talked about the Mies Institute in the past and if I recall, my feeling on them was
they're great.
One of the articles that I covered from their website was a defense of not feeding your
children because you don't have positive responsibilities towards people.
Exactly.
It's like, oh, great.
Yeah.
They're also libertarians.
They're also that kind of libertarian that's just a shit head.
Like if you're writing the in defense of not feeding your own kids, you're just a shit
head.
Get out of this Mies Institute bullshit.
You're also not going to not feed your child.
Of course not.
You're doing this as some kind of a weird mental intellectual masturbation.
Yeah.
It's a shit head thing to do.
Totally.
But Alex, not too long ago, was talking about how being a libertarian was the stupidest
thing he's ever done.
The dumbest thing you could do.
And now he's citing the Mies Institute.
Well, they're great, but they're real libertarians, Dan, and that's the smartest thing you can
be.
Anyway, Barnes.
His show is canceled now.
Good.
But, Alex-
24 hours earlier-
We have constitutional lawyer, Robert Barnes, who will shoot you straight on where Trump
really stands.
I can tell you he's in liaison with the White House, even though he doesn't want that known.
I can tell you that.
Why can you tell me that?
Because separately, I know the White House doesn't even care now.
The White House doesn't care.
That's why.
If he doesn't want that known-
Yeah.
Why would you tell me that?
Hey, look, this is private, but Barnes is working with the President.
He told me not to tell you.
He doesn't want me to tell you.
But the White House is- okay, so the White House is finally- but you know Barnes.
And he personally asked you.
And now there's no show.
The Evening Countdown show is canceled.
But there's no indication of that from Alex on the 16th.
There is no sense that, like, Barnes has been doing this show, it's gonna come to an end.
Sure.
It seems abrupt.
Yeah, it does seem pretty abrupt.
Speaking of which, this seemed abrupt.
But here's the big news we're gonna cover at the start of the next segment.
Mitch McConnell and his wife, like a lot of Republicans, have been on the Communist Chinese
payroll for a long time.
Oh no.
Sure.
Let's remember that Mitch McConnell's bad finally.
It's been so long since we've remembered how many people are bad, Dan.
Yep, Mitch McConnell has recognized that Biden won the election, and now-
So it turns out I remember all these things about him.
Or I'm just gonna make out that he's a Chinese agent.
Yeah, well.
Yeah.
Yeah, so that's great.
That's great stuff.
Now he's a villain.
I like it.
Absolutely, Alex.
McConnell is a villain.
Go after him!
So the knives are out, folks, and- Hell yeah!
There's no doubt that Mitch McConnell is a super bad dude.
A bad bad- Get him!
And we told you Amy Cohen, Barrett, and we told you Kavanaugh, and we told you all that
they were going to betray us.
What?
Because they come out of the swamp.
Yep.
You told them that the only reason to stick with Trump was so he could get those people
in.
Yeah.
Why didn't you bring up Gorsuch?
Also- Oh, Gorsuch is too long ago.
Alex was like crying- And that one's still stolen.
About Kavanaugh.
He was all about Kavanaugh.
This is the moment we've been waiting for.
Alex was so in favor of that, as if he was Squee himself.
This is the culmination of everything we've worked for.
It was a little more confusing, the Barrett nomination, because you did have Barnes coming
in and saying, this is a really bad idea, they shouldn't go this route, and Alex having
to dance around, but he did support her nomination.
Yeah.
He was in favor of it.
We like Catholics.
No, we don't like Catholics.
Oh, well, I guess we don't like Catholics.
Somebody else is like, I think she's great, and Alex is like, ah, I think she's great
too.
Moving on.
But they're all villains now, man.
Yeah.
Good.
We got a lot of new villains for Alex.
Love it.
Fight amongst yourselves, I want to make you hurt each other more.
So Roger Stone, not too long ago, came on and broke some gigantic news.
Yeah.
North Korea.
Boats.
Yep.
Maine.
Boats, from North Korea.
Arrived.
With ballots.
Sailed, with ballots, to Maine.
Arrived in Maine.
Maine?
United States, Maine.
Apparently there's a different situation.
Oh, did something else happen?
McConnell warns GOP of electoral college brawl in Congress.
Trump's got his electors.
They've seated theirs.
They lock the real electors out of the state houses.
We're just supposed to just go along with this and not let the president and the voters
of America press their attacks.
Yes, they've gotten screwed to legislatures.
Yes, they've been screwed so far by most of the governors because they're all a bunch
of cowards.
But when you get down to the brass tacks, you see mathematics that are impossible in
all those states where Trump's winning by two, three, four, five, six points.
And then as soon as they, quote, close the polls, all these trucks pull up, food delivery
vehicles, you name it.
Chinese men mainly run in with these big containers of ballots.
And then inside we have the footage of the workers and they're cramming it in as fast
as they can.
And then you have the Chinese government planes landing the day of.
Wait, what now?
You have the charter numbers.
I mean, private jets flying out of China, landing men running in with big boxes of ballots.
So now the Chinese government is sending their own planes with charter numbers and arriving
with ballots on election day.
So is this an addition to the North Korean boats?
Okay.
So is the North Korean boat like a backup?
Could be.
You know, like they're like, okay, we'll send the boats in like March of this year and China's
going to have the plan to airlift them in and everything.
But when, but hey, worst comes to worst, the boats will be in Maine in November.
Here's what I'm thinking.
I'm thinking that the Chinese planes brought in ballots, like boxes of ballots for Biden,
right?
Okay.
Now the North Korean boats were rogue.
They were crazy.
They were for Jorgensen.
Jorgensen.
Okay.
It's all Jorgensen?
They were going libertarian.
Straight libertarian, down ballot.
Are we sure these weren't ballots for the 2016 election and the North Koreans just got
to Maine?
That would make more sense.
Is it all for Ron Johnson?
Yeah.
That would make more sense.
So yeah, I just feel like this is silly and I'm going to need a lot more proof of this,
which Alex is not forthcoming with.
That's unsurprising.
But something that is also not surprising.
What's that?
Alex wants a do-over.
Second Senator leans towards objecting to Electoral College certification.
Yes.
Told you Rand Paul's a man of honor.
That's what we need for president in four years.
Get the fuck out of here.
Pence, Paul, Paul, Pence ticket will be good.
Okay.
All right.
Wow.
Yeah.
Paul Pence.
That would really inspire the masses.
Those two boring ass...
Those two dim shits.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
You want Rand Paul back.
Oh, how fun.
How interesting.
Pence can't be president because nobody wants to live in a world where we have to call his
wife the first mother.
That's just not happening.
It's just not happening.
And Rand Paul, like you had your chance, Alex.
You turned your back on him for Trump.
You know that.
Yep.
It's over.
We all watched that happen.
Oh yeah.
Rand isn't like Joe Rogan where you can turn your back on him and he'll accept you once
more.
No, I know because he refuses to debate me and that's the only thing that makes sense.
So Robert Barnes, a host for another couple hours of the election countdown is on and
he wants you to know that he also thinks that Mitch McConnell is a traitor.
So the fact is it leads an inference that well, all along, these were people who were
undermining the president and now it's like the Godfather line when the Marlon Brando's
character says he should have seen it was that one guy all along.
It was Mitch McConnell all along betraying and undermining and sabotaging the president.
It's not a coincidence.
It was his attorney general in Kentucky who was the only one to refuse to speak out or
join the Texas lawsuit.
So now the president knows that these were traitors in his own house all along.
Trump's called basically for the arrest of the governor of Georgia.
I mean these people are criminals.
We need to get...
Yeah, I want that too.
Let's talk about Trump.
What Trump should do, where Trump's really at, where we're at.
So Mitch McConnell was screwing it up the whole time.
He was the, uh, the, uh, the, the traitor behind the scenes.
Okay.
All right.
If you want to try and pull that now after this long, after this long, then either you
have to shut up forever because everything that you've told me, if Mitch McConnell's
the secret bad guy the whole time, he was there, right there, he's there, he's right
there.
There's no deep state.
He was, he's in your face.
Yeah.
You know?
And it's, um, I don't know.
It's trying too hard to make an interesting plot twist, I think, and I am not going to
go along for this, this ride and I pity, I pity anybody who does, but you see this, like
there are just like shoring up of ranks of like the people who are, uh, blindly willing
to just completely throw away any kind of semblance of dignity that they have for Trump.
Yeah.
They're good.
Everybody else.
Oh, they were secretly villains.
Evil.
And I have bad news for you.
What's that?
That Pence-Paul ticket might not be happening after all.
Oh no.
It's not that Pence is truly loyal to Trump during Access Hollywood, Pence was trying
to navigate Trump out so that he could be top of the ticket in 2016.
It was Pence who helped drive Flynn out.
It was Pence who helped negotiate with Ecuador to get Julian Assange arrested and extradited.
So Pence has not been a real Trump ally in a lot of the never Trumpers and problem people
have come from Pence's group of people and his staff in the white house.
Oh, it looks like Pence is an enemy too.
Good.
Yeah.
They're all enemies.
Arrest the governor of Georgia, veto the defense bill, tear this whole place down around your
ears.
No, let's not do that.
It's just a little much.
It's a little much.
It's a little cartoonish the way they're like defining good and bad people now.
I think it's, it's really just sad though, because it's, it's like you, you obviously
weren't actually fooled.
There's no possible way that you could be fooled by that shit.
You had to have known that they were lying the whole time and that they didn't really
like Trump because Trump's a fucking lunatic and they're all career politicians.
Right.
Right?
Yeah.
But this is the payoff of that.
If you don't know that, then, oh, that's just so sad, especially because I've been telling
you that for my entire life.
And it is, it's, it's, it's really interesting for me in particular to see like the, the
turning on people so bluntly and so stupidly, like Bill Barr was, he went back and forth
a number of times.
Oh yeah.
And now we have Barnes coming in here saying that everyone's an enemy.
Yeah, yeah.
Bill Barr was a, Bill Barr was a yo-yo for a while and now he's permanently walking the
dog.
Yeah, he's out.
Yup.
So on the 17th we learned that, that Barnes show is gone.
But does Barnes know now?
On the 16th, So on the 16th, he's promoting the show as
Barnes is back.
He's been too busy, but now he's back.
Very funny.
Next day, gone.
That's very funny.
Yeah.
I think, I think you're right.
I do kind of feel for David Knight a little bit.
He's losing his job right before Christmas.
I get it.
That's fucking tough.
I enjoy seeing bad things happen to Robert Barnes in a different way.
And I know that if he doesn't have his fucking moonlighting gig at Infowars, he's going to
be fine scamming other people with fake constitutional lawsuits.
I think he has, I just enjoy watching him get beat.
I think he has like a newsletter on Dave Rubin's Kickstarter or Patreon clone.
He's going to land five.
He's doing all right.
So Alex says farewell to Barnes, say we'll see you on the evening show that won't exist
in a day.
Yes.
And now I must get to another guest and it is a guest that I got the privilege of hanging
out with in DC when I was there yelling and all this shit.
Oh no.
Someone who had the best speech.
Well, there were a lot of powerful messages at the second million manga march.
This one was about a third as big as the gigantic one.
It was a month ago.
There were still hundreds of thousands of people total, five or six different events
going on.
And last time I had the most powerful message of, we're not going to back down to the globalist,
the new world order Biden's a chai comm agent, Nick Foyntas had the most powerful message
at these events.
The crowds were screaming for, he couldn't even hardly give a speech.
Yeah.
So Nick Foyntas had the best, I thought it was going to be for sure.
It's interesting because I watched hours of these rallies.
Nick Foyntas did not speak at either of the rallies that I watched.
He was clearly speaking in some impromptu fashion.
He was speaking in the beer hall punch?
Is that what's going on there?
He was speaking into a bullhorn on the street.
Something.
Yeah.
He was not at these events.
And there might've been like a third event that I would just don't even know about.
A Klan meeting?
I only have so much time in my life.
I can only watch so many of these rallies.
That is fair.
Um, so you know, McConnell, Barrett, uh, Kavanaugh, Pence, they're all the enemy now.
The GOP is the enemy.
Yeah, of course it is.
You know, I said Sunday when I had had a chance to see Saturday speeches by Foyntas on my
Sunday show.
I said, I think Foyntas is right.
The Republican party, the establishment are the enemies, but we have to make sure that
doesn't get Democrats elected.
We have to make sure we target, uh, neo cons and others to get them out and put populace
in America.
Ferchers in.
But now you see McConnell saying, Oh, we need to be nice to Democrats.
That's how we're going to win Georgia and let them engage in fraud.
He's definitely working for the other side than a shy comm operative.
That's not what McConnell's saying.
He said, he's saying that, uh, you know, insisting on denying reality is probably going to hurt
our electoral chances.
Hey, you guys, you know how you're screaming that all elections are frauds and that you
shouldn't vote.
That's going to hurt us in the elections where we need you to vote.
Yeah.
Um, no, you're a Chinese agent.
Oh, damn it.
Maybe I've gone too far.
I'm Mitch McConnell, so I will learn the error of my ways.
Nope.
No.
You will end up having the people that you have inspired and enabled and facilitated
now screaming at rallies about how we need to destroy you.
Excellent.
But first here's one of the eclipse of Nick Foyntez laying out the future and the future
battle plan at the second big March in DC.
And the first million MAGA March, we promised that if the GOP would not do everything in
their power to keep Trump in office, then we would destroy the GOP for a second million
MAGA March.
We're done making promises.
It has to happen now.
We are going to destroy the GOP.
There's 50 of us.
Destroy the GOP!
Is there anything you won't chant?
They love chants.
They fucking chant all the goddamn time.
It's fun.
Eh, that's fair.
Um, so Alex is like, I think he sees that video and he remembers like being in DC and
he remembers like kind of mad at those women for America first people.
I don't like how they organize these rallies and then don't let me speak at them because
I'm entitled to.
This is a parallel or an allegory or like a gauge on a submarine or a battleship or
an army tanker, a truck.
You have these women that are neo cons and I'm not going to attack them, but the point
is they get all the permits, they take control of the thing.
And then when you hear the speakers they've got, it is just people are falling asleep
and then I show up with a bullhorn and Nick shows up and you get, you know, out of the
a hundred thousand people, 20,000 that here you run over and they're all cheering.
And then it gets 5 million, 10 million views.
And then the poor Republicans with kind of a mainline rhino, a little Trump type deal,
they get 20,000 views.
It's not popular.
It's not constitutional.
It's not what made America, but everyone's always running away from what victory is.
So Alex, I don't think is wrong.
I mean, he's exaggerating stuff, but like, yeah, a lot of those other speakers were a
snooze and Alex yelling has some kind of star quality to him.
He gets people to chant.
But he's also sort of misunderstanding, like spectacle for substance.
Yeah.
Like I don't think that there's anything like him being able to draw a crowd of 10,000,
let's say, isn't an indication that he knows the constitution.
I don't think there's a difference for him between substance and spectacle.
You know, it's not that he understands or misunderstands it or it's just that it doesn't
exist to him.
Yeah.
You know, like 5 million views means 500 million people love this, right?
That's how it works.
Yeah.
That's the only thing that makes sense.
Also, I'd like to clarify one thing.
These people starting these rallies and organizing them and getting the permits does mean that
they can choose who speaks at it and who doesn't.
Well, I feel like I'm missing the part where he's going to say like, so next time we're
going to get the permit.
No.
He's not going to say that?
Well see, cause it feels like that's the real complaint here.
And he's just whining that he's not the winner.
He's too busy with all the work.
He is not.
Psychic trances take a while.
You know what?
I know somebody who just lost his job and is free.
I don't think he's going to fill those shoes.
So Nick Fuentes has an interesting idea for the way forward for these weirdo conservatives.
You know, it's interesting.
There were a lot of Democrats that were saying, destroy the GOP.
This is a message I could get behind.
But of course, that's only the first half of the message.
Destroy the GOP as it exists.
Destroy the GOP establishment.
And what we have to do now is replace it with a GOP that truly represents the American people.
We have to destroy the fake GOP establishment headed by Mitch McConnell that puts America
last.
We have to primary all those people, replace them in the House, in the Senate and the state
governments.
And we have to replace them with people that truly believe in America first, truly believe
in the kind of conservatism that President Trump pushed when he ran in 2016.
Look, Nick Fuentes is like 14 years old.
So I'm going to forgive him for not remembering that they did this already.
Yeah, it was called the Tea Party.
This is the crazier version that you guys wanted last time.
Yeah, this already happened.
We're in another cycle of this, like, oh, it's not the real whatever.
Who cares?
I'm going to forgive that.
What I'm not going to forgive is the fact that he doesn't remember they did that this
year.
Yes, they did do that this year as well.
Laura Loeber was running.
All these other people.
Enrique Tarrio was going to run.
Everybody lost their fucking primaries because the people that you end up attracting are
not not no, no, no.
It's just because it's just because the GOP people in the primary thought they were voting
for a GOP candidate because they've been in there for a while, but they were actually
voting for a traitor.
Right.
Okay.
Got to go.
There we go.
No, I think we should all be screaming.
I apologize.
I believe Loomer did win her primary.
That's true.
That is, she lost in the general, but a lot of those other folks lost in primaries.
Yeah.
No, I think we should all be...
And did the wars employ Deanna Lorraine?
Yes, she might have won.
She did.
I think we should all be screaming at establishment Republicans that the only way the GOP survives
is if they all band together and crush the extreme right wing, and I think we tell the
extreme right wing that the only way the GOP survives is if they band together and crush
the establishment Republicans.
I get the sense that at least half of that's going to happen on its own.
That's probably true.
That's why we got to make sure both happens, because if one half happens, we're going to
get to the Tea Party and then double it.
Yeah.
I don't know if that's avoidable, but interestingly, Nick Fuentes and Alex have slightly different
strategies about what they should do in Georgia.
I'm of the belief that the first blow that we have to strike against the Republican Party
is withholding our votes in Georgia, withholding our votes in the Senate runoff and preventing
them from reclaiming control of the Senate.
Now that's where I may disagree with you.
Do it.
Alex is not into that.
He's like, nah, I don't know about that.
He's primarily some Republican, you know, with a crazy person.
Yeah.
Great.
I'm all for that.
Yeah.
But torpedoing the election and letting a Democrat win, I don't know.
Whereas Nick Fuentes is, we need to punish the Republican Party, withhold our votes.
He's very much like accelerationist towards this thing, and Alex is more like, I don't
know.
These people disgust me.
Yes.
And I'm like, wait up, how fucking cruel are you to me to be like, we're gonna kill everybody
with Trump as the king of God and the good Lord and Jesus Christ.
And after losing the election, what we need to do is we need to focus on small elections
and we need to primary the Republican.
Fuck you.
Yeah.
The Lord chose Trump, but the Lord also needs primaries from time to time.
Fuck off.
But the, what the Satan made God forget was county seats.
Yeah.
What?
What are we doing?
Yeah.
So Nick has an interesting angle on QAnon.
What I like about the QAnon stuff is that it gets a lot of people to believe the right
things, although it gets them to believe the right things for the wrong reasons.
It gets them to start thinking about connections between global special interests.
It gets them to ask the right questions about pedophiles and satanic elites and things like
that, largely for the wrong reasons, but it does get them to some of the right places.
I do appreciate the hubris of all of these idiots who are like, you know what?
What we need to do is get the swirling masses to believe something similar to what I believe
and then I'll be able to control it.
It doesn't quite work that way usually.
No, it doesn't.
No.
Sorry Fuentes.
But I will say again, I'm going to give Nick a pass on this because he is a wee baby, but
he seems to be patting himself on the back a little bit for discovering the concept of
local politics.
Of course.
You know, Trump launched this hostile takeover of the top of the party, I mean literally
becoming the president, and now we have to wage a war for everything beneath the presidency.
We have to wage a war to primary, House Republicans, Senate Republicans.
We have to run in state races and local races.
We have to take over the RNC and the party apparatus.
So I'm actually more energized.
General Fuentes, I've not heard it better said.
That was perfectly said.
It's so trite.
I have in 2018, I have in 2016, I have in 2014, I have in 2012.
This is not revolutionary stuff.
This is very bland.
And that's kind of one of the things that I think is interesting and a little bit scary
about Nick is that beneath this there's also an obsession with the idea of fighting against
amnesty and identity and America, like all this stuff, but it is also like, okay, yeah,
you're talking about running for a local election.
You're running for the school president or whatever.
That's the banality, the minutia, the boringness of it with the evilness hidden behind it is
kind of scary.
Oh, Biden is stealing the election and he's killing all of us with the fucking globalists.
And that is why I'm going to vote no on the expansion of that road.
Route six stays the same length.
Yeah.
So Nick, Nick's out of there.
Uh, in and out, in and out.
Got to destroy the GOP.
Got it.
Um, now we're going to play a new game on this show.
Uh, I'm going to play, uh, an angry clip from Alex Jones without who it's targeted at.
Okay.
And you have to guess who is he yelling about?
I like this game.
Uh, this is called guess who Alex is telling to burn in hell, burn in hell, you little
Satanist on a power trip about how great you are and how amazing you are and how, how ascended
you are as you bring in global collapse and extermination burn in hell.
Who is Alex?
No, no, no, no, no.
It's little.
I thought the little, you can ask me, I can ask you two questions.
Two questions.
All right.
Rich or no?
Very.
Very rich.
Obscenely rich.
I don't know if I want to say obscenely, but quite rich.
Quite rich.
Yes.
All right.
I'm going to give you five questions.
I wish I had, I wish I had asked a more specific question because very rich is a, is a more
subjective question that I think I want.
Super rich.
Billion or higher?
Probably.
I don't know.
I, I have a really hard time.
So not one of our major, it's not Soros, it's not Spiros, it's not that, oh.
Out of five.
Um, have we mocked his or her appearance?
No.
What?
No, no, no.
Not us.
Oh.
I meant Alex.
I don't know why I'm saying we.
No.
Alex hasn't mocked their appearance?
I don't think so.
Well then it's definitely not Stelter.
I'm not sure I've heard Alex bring this person up before.
Well this is unfair.
Yup.
Little person who thinks there's a AOC.
I'm going to go with AOC.
He brings her up all the time.
Oh shit, that's right.
That's four.
What was I thinking?
God damn it.
You have all the pieces you need.
Ugh.
Um.
Bezos' wife.
No.
Oh, okay.
Tom Cruise.
Oh, because of the clip of him yelling about COVID, god damn it.
Oh, Dan, you threw, you played the player.
Well done.
That's why we play the game.
That's a good one to open with, yeah.
So, um, Nick Fuentes is gone, Barnes has come on, there's no indication of anything, trouble
in paradise as it were, and I get a little bit bored, honestly, listening to this episode
now, because like, listen to this, this is 30 seconds, this is what Alex thinks has substance
to it.
This is what he thinks his job is.
Pompeo tests negative for COVID-19, will quarantine, oh my gosh, oh it's so scary, even though
it has a death rate of like 0.00 or whatever, it's all just an excuse for Tom Cruise and
Nancy Pelosi to just act arrogant and scream at people and do whatever they want.
Over the counter home test for COVID-19, it's US Green Line, so we can have more hysteria,
more fear, Kansas mayor resigns over violent threats for backing mask mandate, I don't
feel safe anymore, we'll move to North Korea, you witch.
That's it?
Like this is the substance of his news breakdown.
Like it's kind of like a dishy insult after reading the headline, it's like what is this?
This is bad.
And also, Cruise didn't need that shit.
He gets to act like he owns everything and runs the place because he's the figurehead
of a religion.
I also find it strange that Alex isn't taking issue with the Scientology aspect.
No, no problem there.
No.
Well, that makes perfect sense though.
So Alex has been dealing with Hayden, General Hayden, saying on Twitter that he agreed with
someone else who tweeted that Alex should be arrested and Alex is pumped.
Of course he is.
Well, yesterday, I was getting more emails and more calls about CNN and all these publications
saying Alex Jones may be arrested.
On Saturday, there were a lot of publications that said, and I gave a speech in DC, did
Jones threaten to kill Biden?
And then by Sunday, calls for Jones to be arrested for threatening to kill Joe Biden.
And then by Monday, Alex Jones to be arrested for threatening to kill Joe Biden.
That's how the media works, how they're gaslighting and fraud works.
Alex is so excited about this.
Yeah, that's got to give him a huge boner, totally.
Michael Hayden is paying attention to him in a way that he probably would never...
I got months out of, yeah.
So now Alex is going to imply that maybe Michael Hayden's a pedophile.
I mean, this is a stolen valor monster.
He also is involved with some very mysterious international orphanages and transfer of children.
I can tell you that's being looked into already.
I got contacted by some folks, I'll just leave it at that.
And that's why I said he looks like a child molester.
I'm not saying he's a child molester, I'm just saying Brian Stelter looks about as creepy
as you'd get.
You're not going to want any babysitting kids.
But Hayden's own Twitter photo is the creepiest photo of him.
Please pull up Michael T. Hayden's Twitter photo, I just want to show people.
He's like in a Steelers cap on a mountain top.
It's not that creepy.
Sometimes I'm just not sure if things are real.
No.
It's very weird.
I was listening to that in my head, just part of this being like, is this real?
Am I dreaming?
What's happening?
What's going on?
It's pretty strange.
It's like, ah, this guy has tweeted something I dislike.
I am going to accuse him of stealing children from an orphanage.
Yeah.
Because he looks creepy to me.
It's very weird.
But Alex has a gotcha.
And he got this gotcha from, I don't know, I guess Harrison Smith probably, someone who
works at Infowars, scrolled through Hayden's Twitter timeline and found some things to
get upset about.
These guys are great researchers.
He put out a bunch of tweets saying pro-life about Trump, thank you Amy Covid Barrett for
groundbreaking decision.
So what this is, is he had tweeted a picture of like graves and it was from another account.
He had retweeted it with a quote tweet saying pro-life question mark.
Right.
So that's the first tweet.
Sure.
Sure, sure, sure.
And then they put out, it's a joke account, an image of a mass grave implying that Trump's
killing everybody because the Supreme Court ruled churches could be opened.
That's unconstitutional to close them.
But then literally days later, this is November 26th, go to his Twitter and show people this
guys.
He puts out a Pittsburgh Steelers.
That's November 26th.
On November 27th, he tweets, let's do some football, Pittsburgh proud, happy birthday,
no social distancing, NFL game.
Now folks, again, imagine the irony of this.
He's saying Trump is mass graving people.
Trump is murdering people because a Baptist or Catholic church or Buddhist temple or mosque
can be opened with 10 people, a thousand, whatever.
Walmart can be opened.
Target can be opened.
Disneyland can be opened, but your churches can't.
Liquor stores are open.
All this is going on, but he's a big Pittsburgh Steelers fan.
They actually work with Pittsburgh Steelers.
I'm, I'm, oh, I'm stalking you Hayden.
Open source, baby.
Wow.
So that gif that he tweeted was from last season in the football, back when there were
huge crowds for sporting events, it's just a gif of Steelers fans putting their towels
in the air.
Great.
Yeah.
It's not a gotcha.
It's not a, no, it's, it's a, it's an old picture.
Now, the only thing sadder than reading those tweets is scrolling through his timeline to
find those tweets.
Yeah.
And then Alex thinking that this is like an own.
I gotcha.
I gotcha Hayden.
Open source, baby.
Yeah.
That's, that's not good.
Log off the internet.
Get off the internet.
I mean, when you read, when you read too much about tweets, you know, you, you can read
everybody, reading one tweet is too many tweets, but when you read about tweets, now we're
in real, get off the internet.
That's what a whole lot of like national file articles are about.
They're just about someone's tweets.
So fucking crazy.
Yeah.
It seems trivial.
So I was getting a little bit like, I don't know.
I feel untethered.
I don't know what's going on here.
I, you know, I feel like it's really important that, uh, Alex is downsizing.
Well I've got bad news for you.
Effective immediately, Dan.
Oh no.
You are fired.
That's all right.
Sorry.
Uh, I doesn't feel like at all, like anything's going on here on the 16th.
It seems very much just business as usual.
Right.
And it kind of was boring me.
Yeah.
It's just Nick Fuentes has a great idea to destroy the GOP, but also I don't want to
do what Nick Fuentes has suggested in order to destroy the GOP.
Yeah.
I don't like that.
Um, and I just kind of like, I don't know.
And then Patrick, I can't remember his last name.
It'll come to me later.
Dempsey.
No, he's the guy who's the overstock CEO who was dating that Russian spy.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Marina Abramovich.
Bettina.
That's right.
Yeah.
He's back and he has an interesting story to tell.
He and the MyPillow guy should have a tag team wrestling team, like something.
I didn't bring this up.
This guy, Patrick, the overstock CEO introduced Michael Flynn at the rally.
Of course he did.
Yeah.
Why wouldn't I, why wouldn't I know that?
Why wouldn't I just agree with that?
I didn't bring that up on the show cause his speech was kind of like, I don't care.
Of course.
But he is back with Alex and man, he has got a big old story to tell.
I believe your story.
I know there were a lot of stings on Hillary.
She was very arrogant.
She was taking over what, $2 billion from different governments, individuals, anybody
that would give her money, she'd give them access.
That's what the email server shows out of the Southern district has been investigating
her.
I know they've been investigating Hunter.
When you came out and said this, and I saw the video yesterday, I said, that's the same
stuff I got told that there were successful stings on Hillary, but then when they thought
she was going to win, that all got scrubbed and that the justice department has all that
info has been protecting her.
So thanks for joining us.
We've got the floor here to give us the latest.
So Alex has played a clip of Patrick from another show and he's telling this story that
he got approached by the FBI to facilitate a sting operation on Hillary Clinton.
And then eventually they're like, yeah, we're not going to do anything.
We got her, you know, giving up, taking a bribe from a foreign country, but we're not
going to do anything about it.
And then Patrick didn't say anything about it until four years or whatever.
So he seems credible.
That sounds right.
Yeah.
I wondered as you were playing that, why have me on?
You just play.
I told the story in another show, but I'll give you some more detail.
This is true.
By the way, I'm in an incredibly precarious situation.
Well, I've already, no, I want you to want to know why you did it.
I have a good idea.
The country's in trouble.
It's time for us all to give our maximum.
Yeah.
I mean, the hell with it.
I I've, I've been getting myself an ulcer for two years wanting to come out, but being told
trust the process, trust the process, trust the process.
I, about a year ago, there was a conversation or communication between myself and the powers
that be that said, I'm not comfortable being part of a coverup.
And they said, you're, you wait until after the election, after the election, you can
say whatever the hell you want to say, tell the whole story.
So I waited to the election and I couldn't live with myself if I'm not coming out about
it now.
So he's got it.
He's got to tell his story now because the election's over.
He's free to, uh, to tell it all.
Throw tomatoes at this man.
So tomatoes at this man, he, in 2015, December, 2015, coming up on five years, right?
He was approached, approached by the FBI, of course.
And they said in December of 2015, we need you.
This is word for word.
I have something called an eidetic memory.
When I tell you something's word for word, it's word for word.
They came back and said, this part of the FBI is asking for your help again, the there.
There are two groups investigating the FBI in the FBI, investigating Hillary Clinton,
Patrick.
One is the email group.
And we know that's a whitewash, but there's a group in New York who really wants to put
her ass in stir.
They're going after financials, the Clinton financials.
Comey has been blocking them, uh, from acting saying there wasn't enough to justify them
going aggressive in their investigative techniques.
I don't know if, uh, it, it should be seen as like normal that an investigation starts
with wanting to incarcerate somebody.
Yeah.
That's probably not good.
It seems like that's a tainted investigation.
It's almost like one that wouldn't really hold up upon, uh, and it seems like if any
of this is true, which I don't think any of it is, uh, Comey might have been coming from
a position of there's no reason to engage in an investigation like this.
It could be a cover up or it could also be, you guys are telling me that you want to talk
to the CEO of overstock.com to try and sting Hillary Clinton.
Guess who doesn't get to do that?
You guys go away now.
Can I show all of my cards?
Sure.
I don't believe any of this.
I will, I will say this.
I believe the CEO is making this shit up.
Right off the bat.
The only thing idetic about this guy's memory is that he was able to able to remember the
word idetic.
He did memorize that.
That is bullshit.
So here's the deal.
Turkey has already bribed Hillary Clinton, uh, for $20 million.
Well, sure.
So now we just need to get Patrick to facilitate another bribe.
Okay.
So they were saying that Comey had been saying up to that point, there was not enough predicate
information to justify a sting.
However, Patrick, they told me information has come in and Hillary's accepted a bribe.
She took a $20 million bribe from Turkey and that information has come in and the group
in New York has now used that as leverage to force Comey to sign off on a sting and
he has approved a sting and the New York group is sending to you for you to help and you're
going to facilitate a bribe.
And there's another government that was known to want to bribe Hillary.
It's an idetic memory.
You're going to befriend that government.
You're going to befriend the bag man in that government and somewhere, and it's going to
happen in the next two months, Patrick, somewhere, there's going to be a room and Hillary Clinton
walks into that room.
There's going to be a room.
It's very formulaic.
Well, it was a very specific thing.
They told me that there's going to be a room she's going to come in for 10 minutes.
The bag man is going to be in for 10 minutes.
They're going to be there alone.
And that's it.
That's your assignment.
He's got to find, he's got to befriend this government, some unnamed other government
and insinuate himself in such a way that he can be a go-between between the bag man and
Hillary Clinton to get this, by the way.
I'm just going to throw this out there as like a huge question for this story.
I'm just going to go out and say, why did they come to him?
Does he have experience cozying up to governments or in any sort of like, he did date that Russian
spy.
I think that might be a bigger red flag here.
He started overstock.
Yeah.
Okay.
So yeah, I don't, I don't, I don't buy any of this.
It's so complicated and I can't, I just can't imagine any of this.
We know you're dating a compromised agent of a foreign government.
I don't know the timeline on that.
It might've been at a different point in his life.
That said, this is also a sting on that bag man because that other government isn't going,
they think that this is a real, no, no, no.
They're going along with the whole, no, the whole sting is planned.
The bag man is not in on it.
So now the foreign government is trying to entrap Hillary Clinton along with the help
of the FBI?
Probably.
I don't think so.
I think the only people that aren't interested is Turkey.
They want their money back.
I guess that's it.
Give me the overstock guy.
So look, I think that Patrick had a really reasonable response to this and it's that,
Hey man, if I do this, I'm going to commit crimes.
You better not arrest me for those crimes I commit in order to set this up.
I need immunity.
This sounds like somebody writing a much better movie where they didn't commit all the crimes
that they did.
Instead they were not crimes.
This is, this is the clip where it really turned for me too.
From a like, ah, story to a ooh.
They gave me that and it was up to me how to create that event.
So it's all up to me.
And I told them, look, to make that happen, there's going to be some bribing and stuff.
And I need a, I need something called an acts otherwise illegal letter, which is a letter
they can give you when they're asking you to do something like this, like get involved
in a federal election and bribe someone.
And they went back and I see the time I'll finish this in 45 seconds and then we'll continue
the story.
I'll finish this part.
And they, they said, we'll have to go back to the office and discuss it.
They came back in two days and said, word for word now, we've been told to tell you
we can't give you a letter, but if you'll come to DC, the director says you can be shown
a letter.
And I said, oh, this is coming from director Comey.
And two federal agents looked me in the eye and said, and, and I said, oh, this is coming
from director Comey and the president.
And two federal agents looked me in the eye and said, and I said, well, you can tell director
Comey and president Obama that from them is good enough for me.
Consider Hillary bride.
Come back.
You'll be right back.
Oh, so it's Obama's right.
If this one is just so big, we know the Obamas and the Clintons don't like each other.
Stay with us.
Holy shit.
Okay.
So this is, wow.
This is 2015.
Wow.
Obama is like, it's time to take Hill down.
It's time to take her down.
I had her as secretary of state for long enough and now we just got to get rid of her.
Well, it starts to make sense when they come back from break and they lay out more of what
the conspiracy is here.
But yes, it is a little bit hard to put your head around like, ah, yes, Obama is trying
to sting Hillary.
Also, also stop, stop me real quick.
If I, cause I could be wrong.
Is it regular practice for the FBI to clandestinely come to you and say, we need you to sting
the most famous woman in the world.
And let me tell you this, we've got no ideas.
Go for it, buddy.
However you think you can make this sting happen.
We're not even giving you help.
You're basically MacGyver and look, you know what to do.
Look, we, we here at the FBI don't like to micromanage.
Yes.
Comey said, Comey said, do your thing, Obama famously lacks secret super spy guy from Overstock.
Sell me on this story more, give me more.
I'm imagining this guy just like coming in from the ceiling on wires.
That's my only image of spy work.
Yeah, basically.
Yeah.
Um, so Patrick, they come back from break and he says something really interesting that
makes me think like, Oh, he might know more about Alex than he's letting on.
When all, when the dust settles, everyone's going to see the mainstream press.
There are the kooks that they are, they're trying to, they're part of this.
They're trying to keep people from understanding what they're seeing in front of them and good
for you.
So respect.
I'm trying to say in a graceful way, I don't know about your past beliefs, respect.
The only thing is I want to be clear, I have nothing to do with white, anything white identitarianism
is true, anything racist, I assume you're on the same, well, I mean, the media says
Trump's a Nazi.
I wouldn't support Trump if he was.
It's all pure crap.
Why, why, why did you need to bring that up?
Apropos of nothing.
I am just going to be here on Info Wars saying that I don't believe in any of this white
identitarian nonsense just in case anyone asks.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I, I, granted I have not taken as many media appearances as some, I've never found that
I needed to distance myself from white identitarianism in any appearances.
Seems like if you do that, that kind of is because you know that the person you're talking
to might have some leanings in that direction.
Or maybe you're just sitting there thinking like, oh, I'm being interviewed after Nick
Fuentes.
Oh shit.
Yeah.
I mean, this is a really complicated kind of situation.
Look, before we go any further, I just want to let you know that I do not support the
actions of the Thuggee cult from Temple of Doom.
I don't support that.
I don't know why I need to say that here.
Apropos of nothing.
Raises questions.
So the sting, it works.
Yeah.
They succeed.
They pull it off.
I forgot.
This ends with a success.
Yes.
Yeah.
And then the cover up.
Oh, it was so good.
Yeah.
Okay.
I got you.
Patrick pulled off probably the best sting since the sting.
That sounds right.
And then things fell apart.
Oh no.
So back to the, let me, I don't want to skip the punchline on all this.
So they told me I needed to forget it.
And I said, why?
And they said, look, it's been decided at the top.
We've realized there's no side Hillary.
Nothing's going to stop Hillary Clinton from being president now.
And the day she's president, she's going to send her men over the FBI, her people over
the FBI and ask who was part of investigating Hillary and everyone who was part of this.
Patrick, we're all going to be destroyed from the top to the bottom.
And this includes you, Patrick.
So it's been decided at the very top, this mission has been scrubbed and we mean it.
You have to wipe every moment of this from your memory.
Wow.
But it's eidetic.
He can't.
Yes, sir.
I understand.
I don't believe any of this, none of it, but I want to be clear about something.
If you make a claim like this, what we should do as a society is immediately put you in
front of like the most serious court that is imaginable produce evidence because the
stakes of this are way too high.
Crazy.
And telling the truth, the stakes and the importance for the public good is so important
that you cannot not prove it.
Yes, absolutely.
If you are lying, you need to go to prison because the stakes are so serious in that
side too.
You can't be allowed to make these sorts of claims that are about like international espionage
and like plots against society and just do it with impunity.
If you can't prove this, you can't make claims like this.
That's how I would like to see things shake up.
I imagine a system of pneumatic tubes where you make a claim like this and then all of
a sudden, and then you're in the court and you're like, whoa, whoa, what just happened?
But it should not be a situation where, you know, like you're punished.
It shouldn't be punitive unless you're clearly making this shit up.
Yeah.
It's just too serious.
And I think with swings this big, we're not dealing with quite as much nuance in the law.
You know?
This seems like it would be incredibly easy to prove.
Very simple.
If he's telling the truth, there'd be so much documentation.
I don't care about him saying like, oh, you have to wipe it from your memory.
Well, guess what?
Hillary didn't become president.
So all that fear of her like reprising against people didn't come to pass.
There'd probably be tons of people within the FBI who would corroborate your story.
Sure.
I'm going to guess that you remember the bag man's name.
You would think.
Maybe the country that bribed Hillary.
I don't know.
This is so offensive to me.
So if I understand correctly, the timeline of the story goes thus, all right?
Yes.
December 2015.
All right.
He kicks ass on the sting, gets all the way to somewhere in 2015 where everybody in the
2016, they decided that Hillary is going to win.
All right.
So they've just decided that it's over.
Right.
And then Hillary doesn't win.
And I believe that was the same year.
Correct?
Yeah.
And then there was the new president on 2017.
January.
Now, if, if I were somebody who had just successfully executed a sting operation on Hillary Clinton.
Right.
Who was not president.
Someone who is famous, not just not president, but someone who lost to the guy who screamed,
lock her up.
Oh yeah.
And like the whole, whole big crowds of people chanting.
I wouldn't wait until after he had lost his election to tell people I would go to him.
Yeah.
If you, if you were inclined to take the gigantic risks involved in that kind of espionage sting
operation.
Why again, Hillary Clinton.
Involving a foreign government.
Yes.
Yeah.
If you're willing to take those kinds of risks, I would assume, yeah, once Trump won, you'd
be like, I got to get in a room.
Now we get to do this whole thing.
Now we get to, now I get to arrest Hillary Clinton.
I did all the work.
It wasn't for nothing.
They probably will let me do it.
Like I'll put the handcuffs on her.
I think that that didn't happen because it didn't happen.
I'm going to go with that one.
Yeah.
That's reasonable.
So I was kind of confused about the idea that Obama was behind this, but Patrick does clear
that up here.
And after some hemming and hawing, eventually the following story was expressed to me.
And it runs like this, Patrick, what you need to understand, so this is late January, 2016.
You might need to check your notes.
What you need to understand is President Obama, and this is word for word, from there's really
four federal people of different types involved, and this is word for word, Patrick, you need
to understand that at this point, President Obama has his people across the federal bureaucracy,
but especially in the Department of Justice, Hillary Clinton is going to be president for
eight years and nothing is going to change that, but think of it this way.
Think of there as being a Bunsen burner within the Department of Justice, and on that Bunsen
burner, that information about the two bribes you were part of gathering, that'll be sitting
there.
But the hand on the Bunsen burner is going to be one of Barack Obama's people.
If Hillary Clinton is a good girl and defends Obamacare and such, that flame stays low.
If she's a bad girl and gets thinking for herself, that flame gets turned up.
And that way, Barack Obama's going to manage Hillary Clinton for eight years, she's president.
Well, that's exactly what the feds have tried to do.
No, no, no.
You don't want to step on the line.
You don't want to step on this line, Alex.
You want to hear-
Okay, so back to the Bunsen burner.
Two or three more sentences.
Hey, the story's too good, Alex, you're interrupting.
Do you know how many times people with an eidetic memory say, and this is word for word,
remind you.
They do say that a lot, I would imagine.
I don't know.
They say it-
But also-
They say it initially?
One time.
He-
And then you're like, oh shit, you're telling the truth.
They don't repeat it over and over and over again in the same story.
Yeah.
So Obama was going to manage Hillary.
Because he had this leverage on her with this bribe that the Overstock CEO managed to pull
off.
Right.
Yeah.
Here's what Alex stepped on.
Two or three more sentences.
That way, Barack Obama, for the whole time Hillary Clinton is president, Barack Obama's
going to be managing her, and she's going to step down, and Michelle's going to run,
and Patrick, that's the plan.
Still?
Wow.
Say that again, because I did mess up the bunch line.
The Bunsen burner can be turned up, it can be turned down.
It gets down, and that way, Barack Obama's going to manage Hillary Clinton for the eight
years she's president, then she's going to step down, and Michelle's going to run, and
Patrick, that's the plan.
Wow.
That makes perfect sense with Biden being an Obama-
Yes, it does.
Literal zombie.
Yeah.
It makes so much sense.
It makes perfect sense.
This ridiculous story that this dude is telling on your show, you just take without any kind
of critical-
So much sense.
That just makes so much sense.
No real follow-up questions as to, what the fuck are you talking about?
Nothing like that.
No.
He gets to the end of the story.
Obama set up so he could blackmail Hillary, and then eight years, he'd be the shadow president
behind Hillary, and then his wife would be president after that.
This is just absurd.
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
But kind of fun.
It is kind of fun.
A little fun.
I do like that he thinks that it's such a great punchline, that it's Michelle that's
going to run.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I do understand that we on Infowars have been screaming about Michelle Obama becoming president
since 2009, buddy.
We're fine.
They've been on that train for a while.
You are not going to blow my mind with a, Michelle is the secret at the end of this
conspiracy.
Right.
I also just don't think that there's a good use for this conspiracy, because it takes
some of the agency away from their biggest bad person, which is the Clintons.
No.
It's like McConnell, the secret one was Obama, it's double Obama.
No, Hillary is like the devil that you have to be afraid of.
It doesn't make sense for her to then be a patsy of Obama.
It's emotionally unsatisfying for the Infowars universe.
Also, just prove any of this, dick.
I think it's a fun shit-talking story, and if he wrote this down and he was like, I'm
going to try and sell this to people, one, he needs to get better at his delivery, because
I don't buy this shit at all.
This delivery doesn't matter how bad it is with Alex, he's going to believe him.
And three, Patrick says he has two more bombshells that are coming eventually, so we may have
even bigger swings coming in the future, but we're going to have to wait for those.
I would love for you to release your next bombshells next Monday, if you'd like, or
whenever you'd like, here on air.
We appreciate you, we appreciate your time, and thank you so much for coming on on short
notice.
Inshallah, Alex, and if I'm still alive, I'll come back on Monday and tell you a little
bit more.
All right, me too, I hear you.
You'll be fine.
This just reminds me of the Jerome Corsi might die over the weekend, he's got a dead man
switch.
Yeah, oh man.
No I can't come back on Monday, Alex, it's going to take me at least another week to
write the...
I mean, I can't remember, oh no, I have an eidetic memory, I mean, it's, oooh, vacation!
Smoke bomb.
Yeah, so that was an interesting kind of, I don't know, change of pace.
Little jaunt.
Yeah, jaunt is good.
Yeah, it was a nice little jaunt.
Yeah, I found that to be just...
I feel like I got took down the garden path for a nice little walk, and now we've come
back to the house and we shall return.
I also like the idea, too, that this Patrick guy is clearly someone who has some status,
at least in his own mind.
He'll tell Alex, you stepped on my punchline, I'm going to say these things.
Like he's not, he's...
I've made a lot of money.
He has a little bit of flex on him, which is kind of fun.
That is.
But I also was thinking, like, all right, this guy's clearly a little nutty.
Is he the new Larry?
Is he the new Larry Nichols?
He's got a Clinton conspiracy.
That would be good.
Yeah.
I wonder, here's what I wonder.
Wait, Stevie Pease wasn't on today, right?
No.
I'm wondering when exactly Stevie Pease is coming back.
Probably tomorrow, I don't know.
No, that's what I'm saying.
What if there's a larger thing going on between Stevie and David Knight?
There may be.
And now Steve's not even going to be coming back for a little while, so we got Overstock
guy to try and thread the needle of a Steve and a David Knight.
Oh my God.
He has so much of the Steve and so much of the Larry.
Exactly.
All in one.
Yep.
Put them in one.
Yeah, I don't know.
It's tough for me because, you know, we get blindsided by this news about the David Knight.
And then, you know, as I look into the episode itself, you know, you find that, oh, maybe
there's massive downsizing.
Or maybe this is yet again Alex overplaying some kind of desperation in order to move
product.
Who knows?
I don't know.
I have no idea what's going on there.
Things don't look good.
And it makes me even more suspicious when the day before, there's really no indication
of anything.
Yeah.
There's no trouble.
He's promoting the countdown, election countdown show that now apparently can't continue.
Yeah.
It's weird.
It's, it's a, it's a little bit out of nowhere.
Here's my, here's my pitch on, here's my conspiracy now.
This is what I've got for you on this whole thing.
All right.
Uh, Info Wars, not doing great right now.
Not going to go out of business, but they're not doing great right now.
Sure.
Okay.
And these months, uh, this, this little couple of weeks, you know what, everybody takes a
Christmas vacation.
And if you took a Christmas vacation, that wouldn't be that exciting.
We're in the middle of fighting the goddamn Info War, you know, you can't just go out
on vacation.
I see what you're doing.
So what we do is we say, we got to let you go.
I save money on overhead costs for a couple of weeks.
After the big Christmas sale, we get all, oh, for sure.
After the big Christmas sale, we get all the money in.
And then I'm like, guys, we're bringing David Knight back!
And we've retooled his show.
Exactly.
Huh?
Yeah.
That would be interesting.
That would be interesting either.
Yeah.
I am interested to see what ends up happening, uh, but not that interested.
Sure.
I'm torn.
I want them to do some work to make me interested in it.
Yes.
Yeah.
Make me care.
Fight.
Do something for my amusement.
The other thing too that I think is really key is that, like, Alex is about to enter
a very profitable space, which is returning to the attacking the GOP.
Right.
His purity in the GOP kind of thing is a really, really profitable sector for, like, right-wing
talk shows.
Oh yeah.
It's worked for millions of years.
Right.
But he also has never had to do it while there were large funded, uh, competitors.
Yeah.
And I don't know if he can, uh, beat OAM.
It's difficult whenever you also have, like, because before you had Fox News crashing the
Tea Party wing, just like, fuck yeah, let's ride or die on killing everybody.
But Alex even then still got to exist in that space of, like, everybody sucks and I hate
them all, but Obama's the devil and, you know, that whole thing.
But Fox News wasn't also hating Mitch McConnell at the time.
No, they did have Glenn Beck being a little nutty, a little conspiracy-ish, but, like-
But Glenn Beck didn't have two networks that they were competing, you know, you know what
I'm saying?
Right, right.
Yeah.
There was some competition in the form of Glenn Beck, but Alex was still, like, he would
say a lot of shit that Glenn Beck probably wouldn't.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And so, I don't know.
I don't know substantially what he can do to differentiate himself from the competitors
now, but- A good job I think is the only thing he could
do and I don't think he's capable of that.
Don't think it's possible.
No.
Based on this interview with the Overstock guy, I don't think it's possible.
I don't think we're seeing that kind of turnaround.
Certainly not.
It's a Christmas miracle!
No.
Uh, we'll be back, folks.
But until then, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledgefight.com.
Now go to Betjordan.
We're also on Facebook.
We are Facebook.
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out those doing
God's work right now.
Yeah, we'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZXClark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I'm more like out of stock.com.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.