N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledgefight, knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys, knowledgefight.
Dan and Jordan, knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding us.
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
Knowledgefight.com.
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledgefight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes, like to sit around, drink novelty beverages and talk a little
bit about Alex Jones.
Oh indeed we are Dan.
Yes.
Dan?
Quick question for you.
What's up Jordan?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today is that wonderful intersection of aspiration and limitations.
All right, are you talking about finishing an entire Waffle House meal?
No.
I got some sheet metal from the local hardware store the other day because it dawned on me
that I love breakfast sandwiches and I can make them myself if I could make eggs round.
And I was like, if I just get some sheet metal, I could make a round thing that I could put
in a pan.
You're making your own cutouts.
You're making cookie cutters.
Basically, yeah.
Out of sheet metal.
Yep.
You can just buy them.
Well, that's the limitations aspect.
So I spent a while cutting up some metal and I didn't cut myself or anything, so that's
a plus.
Well that's good.
That's a plus.
But yeah, I got through a couple trials of it and you know, like the egg kept seeping
out from under it because it's not perfectly, it's like, ah, what can I do?
How can I fix this?
And so I Googled it and I was like, oh, they cost eight bucks for four of them.
Oh yeah, yeah.
It costs nothing.
I was like, okay, I'll just order those.
I have no idea why you bought, why did you buy sheet metal?
What was your thought process on that?
I was taking a walk to get out of the house and I saw the hardware store and I like the
hardware guys and I was like, oh, I've been, I had that thought about round eggs.
Why don't I see if they have anything I could, uh, sheet metal in there?
And so I did and well, it felt fun.
Yeah.
The aspiration phase felt really fun.
Like I'm being crafty.
I'm trying to build something and I did succeed.
It just wasn't that good.
Sure.
I made something that worked.
I made egg patties.
Sure.
They just weren't great and they did leak a little bit.
But they were round.
You win some, you lose some.
Right.
I think that's great.
I consider it a partial victory that I then forfeited to buying a couple.
I agree.
I think that you even tried to construct your own as a victory in and of itself.
Yeah.
I feel better.
I feel better for trying, but also qualified success, qualified success.
I think you are though technically a weekend warrior now, Dan.
I have that urge.
Yeah.
That's what you do.
Yep.
I need a sink to fix.
I need a, I need these projects.
Yes.
To fail on.
I'm going to build a god damn chair.
I'm going to build a god damn chair today.
I'm going to try really hard and then I'm going to buy a chair.
That's my weekend.
Yeah.
It's a good thing you don't have any like trimming to do because you would have a series
of chainsaws and shit.
That would be a nightmare.
No, probably not.
I'd probably stop just short of that.
What's your bright spot?
My bright spot, Dan, is a, I don't know if you recall, do you remember a few weeks ago
when I talked to you about the Mandalorian?
Um, yeah.
Yeah.
And it was, what I said to you was that it was, it was essentially, it was like a, it's,
it's junk food.
You know, it's everything you want, you know?
And the season finale was such that it was just, I can't even, without spoilers, I can't
even begin to describe it because it was like I could feel myself in the writer's room.
Did they say that Baby Yoda's name isn't Grogu?
No, but if only they could.
I thought I would figure that would be a nice twist.
It would be nice if the twist ending, the person who arrived was like, nah, nah, nah,
nah, nah, nah, you're Baby Yoda.
Moving on.
Let's get out of here.
Grogu is dead.
Long live Baby Yoda.
Yeah, exactly.
But it was very much like a, I didn't, I knew it was possible, but I never thought they
would do it.
Okay.
Have you, I think I would liken it to, have you ever seen a wrestling pay-per-view, perhaps
when you were younger?
Yes.
Where all of a sudden you heard the music and you were like, oh shit, they did it!
You hear the glass break and Stone Cold comes out.
Exactly, and Stone Cold comes out and you're like, I didn't think it was going to be Stone
Cold and it was him!
It's like that, but if your childhood came back and kicked you in the dick.
Okay.
Well, it's fantastic.
I have no idea what you're talking about and I'm glad you enjoyed it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
I'm sorry I didn't make anything.
So technically I barely did.
Yeah, that's fair.
Today we've got an interesting episode to go over, Jordan.
We're talking about Friday of last week, which would be the 18th of December, 2020.
I'm Dan.
This is 2020.
Hey, that's good news!
This is an interesting thing.
It's a thing?
Yes.
All right.
And we'll get into exactly why it's an interesting thing.
I'm not saying an episode.
Is that David Knight's music being played in the background?
Glass breaks.
As David Knight comes to- Oh shit!
We're back!
Oh my God!
David Knight has parted the Red Sea!
And now it's time to bring back my show where I will talk for three hours or so.
No, that is, David Knight does not make an appearance, although we might learn a few
things.
I'm going to actually have a request for you taking notes throughout this episode that
we'll get to here in a few.
But before we do that, let's take a moment to say thank you to some folks who have signed
up and are supporting the show.
Oh, that's a great idea.
So first, Steven T. Thank you so much, you're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk!
Thanks, Stephen!
Thank you!
Next, David D. Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, David!
Thank you!
Next, Mo S. Thank you so much, you're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk Thanks, Mo!
Thank you!
Next, Owen H. Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk Thank you very much Owen
Next, Geena GM, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Gina!
Thank you!
Next, Adam, thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, Adam.
Thank you, Adam!
No last initial at all.
No last initial at all?
Mm-hmm.
It was the first Adam?
Yeah.
Holy shit!
Yep.
Next, Laura C., thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Laura!
Thank you!
And then finally, let's say thank you to a couple of people who donated on elevated
love and we appreciate that very much.
So first, Larry Klayman for Supreme Court, thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
And Mean Blackbird, thank you so much.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate.
That's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right.
We got to go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why are you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much, Larry Klayman for Supreme Court and thank you so much, Mean Blackbird.
Yes.
Thank you very much to the both of you.
If you're out there listening and thinking, hey, I enjoy the show.
I'd like support with these gents.
You can do that by going to our website, knowledgefight.com, clicking the button to support the show
or.
Oh, what you could do is take a look at your little spaceship.
You could hop in that little spaceship with the intent of solving many problems.
And when you arrive at your destination, you can tear apart everyone in your path trying
to keep you from expressing your generosity by going to a local bail fund or charity.
Give your generosity to Grogu.
Yes.
Give your Grogu to a local charity in your area.
I like the idea of you starting over watching The Mandalorian again, just staring at him,
just going Grogu.
You're fucking Grogu?
You're Grogu?
You can't experience it unless you don't know his name.
Yeah.
I don't pick I'll ever watch it.
Yeah, I know.
I'm interested in seeing Werner Herzog's delightful performance.
It's fantastic.
I'm excited about some of the screenshots I've seen of the child will be something incredible.
Yeah.
I would like to.
And now I can't.
Yeah.
Grogu.
Unfortunately, his name is Grogu.
Grogu has celebrated 50 birthdays, from what I understand.
Is that correct?
Yes, it is.
Someone who's celebrating a birthday today.
Nicely done.
We'd like to give a shout out to Wendy.
Happy birthday, Wendy.
Wendy informed us that her last name was Grogu?
No.
Birthday on Monday, and it's the shortest day of the year.
I know we had some dispute about day lengths a while back.
Oh, it is the winter solstice.
So happy solstice and happy birthday, Wendy.
Yes, indeed.
I hope you are a witch.
Oh, boy.
So Jordan, today, like I said, we got a thing to go over.
And that is going to be a lot of Alex.
Because Alex Jones did double duty on Friday.
Of course.
He hosted David Knight's show and then his own show.
Oh, God.
So here is an out of context drop from Alex.
You understand?
You've got to scare the living hell out of your kids.
Okay.
All right.
Good parenting advice from Alex.
No, that's good.
That's good.
Always got to appreciate that.
That was, I believe, scarecrow's policy.
Spare the scarecrow, spoil the child.
Scare the child, don't spoil.
I don't know how to do this.
So Alex hosted his own broadcast, the Alex Jones show, trademark, copyright free, anyone
can use it, whatever.
Who cares?
No problem.
Before that, because he had fired David Knight the day before, he needed to fill that time.
Sure.
Something had to go there.
And so what he decided to do was finally do that show that was mostly callers.
Okay.
So he's decided he's going to start a new show called The American Journal.
Get the fuck out of here.
The American Journal.
It's a parody.
I say it's a parody.
He would say it's an homage to The Washington Journal on C-SPAN.
And he says that about a hundred times throughout the three hour show.
I don't think his audience would get the reference otherwise.
He does really hammer it home.
It's like a Washington Journal, but it's America.
We've never seen C-SPAN.
So here is an out of context drop from one of the callers on The American Journal.
All these people that think that this COVID shot is going to cure them or even make them
into a cyborg human being.
They're wrong.
It is not.
It is going to kill them.
Oh.
Getting the pulse of America.
That is The American Journal.
I think that would be a fairly good chronicle of our times.
Yeah.
All these people out there who think the shot's going to turn them into a cyborg.
They're wrong.
Idiots.
They're so goddamn stupid, they think they're going to turn into a cyborg.
God, we're taking the time to hear these missives.
We've got to debunk all of these falsehoods that are going around, Dan.
So here's Alex starting off the Journal.
And the Journal starts earlier.
Alex is used to starting his show at 11.
This one starts at 8.
That's too early.
Yeah, so he's in there early.
You're listening to The American Journal with your host, Alex Jones.
Watch it live right now at band.video.
All right, folks, we are live on this Friday transmission.
Thank you so much for joining us on this December 17th broadcast.
So much going on.
There's so much happening.
I work seven days a week.
I'm not even sure what day it is anymore.
Makes my head spin.
It's the 18th.
Yeah.
It does.
That's not an auspicious beginning.
No, it does sound like he's already taking his time to run up the clock.
Already stalling.
Minute one of The American Journal.
Ladies and gentlemen, we begin our...
From a place.
Show.
In the middle of America.
We're going to take calls.
I'm going to say a million fucking times that this is like The Washington Journal, but I'm
doing it.
It's going to be a while.
I'm going to complain a whole bunch.
John Rappaport's going to host the last half hour because I got to take a break in between
this and my show.
Yeah.
Six hours straight is a lot.
The whole show's supposed to be about taking calls and the last half hour is John Rappaport
not taking calls.
Hey, come on.
He's John Rappaport.
He's not on his feet, man.
It's ridiculous.
No.
So anyway, Alex realizes that it's the 18th.
Now, I told the guys months ago, I had an idea, told the crew for something like a...
Let's buy another tank.
National Journal program based on The Washington Journal.
And that's what we're doing right now.
It is Friday, December 18th, 2020.
I was looking up there on the computer board and it said December 17th, 2020.
And I said, that's not right.
It's Friday, December 18th, but of course, that's why you can't always trust computers,
can you?
Sometimes computers lie to you.
You need to be aware of this.
Wait, is The Washington Journal the one where it's the guy who is steadfast in his not having
a facial expression?
Like somebody calls in and they're like, I think dogs are going to own this world.
And he's like, that was a good call.
The next caller.
And they have the Republican and Democrat independent lines.
Yes, yes.
That's the show.
All right.
Alex thinks he's capable of doing that and boy, I will tell you from round one, he is
not.
All right.
So flappable he is, un he is not.
I just, I mean like it would be like if The Washington Journal host constantly like forgot
why he was there.
That would, that's kind of the way you would make it meet.
All right.
I like it.
But the aspiration is there.
Much like me trying to make these egg rounds.
Sure.
Alex intends to take 90% calls.
So here we are and I told the crew months ago that I wanted to launch a show either
in the morning or at night and call it National Journal, kind of after The Washington Journal
to really habituate myself or whoever the host would be, I thought of it kind of as
a rotating group of hosts, to take a lot of phone calls and actually do it every day because
the show is based at least 90% on phone calls.
And so that is what we are doing here on this live Friday, December 18th, 2020 broadcast.
I will give Alex some credit and say that it's more calls than you'd expect based on
his history.
Sure.
It's still not 90%.
Well.
It's not, it's, and some of them are talking about how you're not going to turn into a
cyborg.
So then some of them you might as well not have.
That's fair.
And one of them is a guy named Mountain Patriot.
Okay.
Yeah.
Was that his birth name?
It's on his birth certificate.
All right.
Well, that's good.
On his new birth certificate that he got when he became a sovereign.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, that's fair.
So here's where I want to make a request of you taking notes.
Sure.
A large portion of this turns into Alex complaining about David Knight.
There is a large part of this episode is like Alex being kind of too aware that people are
going to tune in thinking it's David Knight's show.
What happened?
Yeah.
So we have to kind of address the issue.
Now on the 17th, the episode that we listened to on our last episode, we heard him give
the explanation that it's money.
It's money.
Right.
Right, right, right.
We got financial troubles around here.
Right.
We have to scale back and get leaner.
Yeah.
So write that down at the top of your notes.
So we're about to find out that it's actually about the number of emails David Knight sent?
No, that doesn't come into it.
Okay.
All right.
And maybe Steve Puchenik related.
Sure.
Because the two of them got into a bit of a beef.
They got a tiff.
Although also I'm a little reticent about that, or I had to been.
Right.
I want you to keep track of...
How many different possible reasons there?
Yes.
Okay.
I have to write down each new one.
I want you to listen carefully and see how many different stories about why David got
fired you could come up with.
He did an upper decker in the toilet and I just can't do it anymore.
I wish it was that interesting.
Yeah, that would be fun.
So here's the first one.
I'm going to give you this as a layout.
Okay.
Now, a lot of you are probably tuning in and you're saying, where's David Knight?
I love David Knight.
I really care about him.
He's a talented, smart guy.
He's been with us nine years and I personally am exhausted doing my own show every day.
And David, of course, took off quite a bit over a year ago with some medical issues and
came back.
And I just made the decision that David was not happy here.
I made the decision.
That it was not good for him to still be on air.
That's my own personal decision.
I was kind of watching him twist in the wind, very depressed with everything that's going
on, very, very upset.
And I agree with about 95% of what David has to say and what he does.
I did not let David go because I disagreed with what he was doing or because he didn't
agree with me on some things that had nothing to do with it.
So that had nothing to do with it.
It had everything to do with the fact that David Knight was unhappy by Alex's metric.
Alex determined that David was unhappy, but he couldn't save himself.
David Knight was too stubborn to leave the job when he was miserable.
And so Alex did it for him, gave him the ax.
Really, Alex is the good guy.
Yeah, that doesn't sound right, but okay.
Alex is your best friend that you think you don't need.
I just don't think we're going to find out that this is a consistent storyline.
I think I might have ruined that by setting up your note.
Could be, could be.
So one other possibility for why he might've gotten the ax is that Alex wanted to do this
call-in show and David did not.
I have wanted to launch, again, a program like Washington Journal, but National Journal.
David was not interested in a program like that.
We had, you know, first wanted to have a show that he would host that was, was calls and
yes and things, but he had total control over a show and it went another direction.
So here we are.
And when I host the show or when Owen hosted or when Harrison hosted or when other people
were looking at bringing in to host it, host it, if it's not a call-in show, then that
person won't be hosting it anymore.
So I've kind of gotten in a rut, not in a bad way, but it's a rut that I don't take
enough calls.
And I've gotten in a rut that I don't play enough clips and I've gotten in a rut that
I tend to get on one story and pontificate on it for an hour.
And that's somewhat informative for diehard listeners, but it's not for radio and TV stations
to really cover some quick news, get into it, take calls, have a quick guest and really
cycle through a lot of information.
And so that's what this show is going to be.
It's going to be your phone calls.
I agree with Alex on some level that his show is inaccessible to people who aren't already
indoctrinated.
I do agree with that.
Yes.
The format that he has is not good for someone like clicking around on the radio.
Right, right, right, right.
It might be able to grab your attention with a guy yelling, but he doesn't yell all the
time.
Yeah.
There's a lot of stretches of time that are completely boring, stupid shit.
Sure.
And you know, if you aren't already on the team, you're not going to give a shit about
that.
I mean, there's that.
And also the mythology has just moved on so much from reality.
Boy has it.
Like, what are you, like, you're, you're coming in on like episode 40 of the 38th season.
Yeah.
You're not going to catch up with all that's happened before.
I listen to this all the time and sometimes I lose track of the lore.
Exactly.
It's nonsense.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah.
I, yeah, it would be something that would be very, very difficult for you to get people
in the door.
Right.
And I understand that.
And I think our show probably is the same.
Yeah.
So I kind of empathize with Alex.
Totally.
And, um, you know, if he needs to switch up his format in order to maybe cater to an audience
that he can trick into buying pills, great, good for him.
I'm going to stick with what we got.
I would, I would also say that David is smart for not wanting to do a call-in show just
simply because you've also cultivated an audience that you don't want to hear what they have
to say.
It's true.
You would, like, if you're David Knight and you try and pretend like you take this all
very seriously and you're a, you're a, you're a thinker, you think Steve Pachenik's full
of shit.
So you clearly have some standards.
You're trying to enforce something.
You lose credibility by having to humor idiots.
And David Knight's probably too polite to tell people to shut up.
People who think they're going to be cyborgs are stupid.
They're going to die.
Um, oh, I, I mean, uh, uh, I am a cyborg.
What?
So, uh, you got a lot of calls coming up.
Okay.
And we're going to be taking a lot of your phone calls.
So I'll give you the number when we come back.
And part of taking phone calls is going to be, we are going to get to your call and move
the next person.
So I'm not going to do, thank you for calling and go, thank you so much, Alex.
Oh.
And then get into what you have to say.
We're just going to, Hey, you're calling in.
Here's the topic.
We'll, we'll talk about a topic, an hour, another topic, the next hour.
And that's how this is going to be something that I haven't really done personally in this
style over 20 years.
And so thank you for joining us for American journal.
We'll be right back.
Listen to this mellow ass music.
Yeah.
This is very strange.
This is real.
Eight in the morning.
Got out some coffee.
This is dissonant to hear Alex like, Oh, I haven't been awake before nine and 20 years.
It's surreal on a lot of levels.
Uh, just sitting there with like a calm show.
Yeah.
Just sitting there with a calm.
That's very funny.
So Alex starts off after he gets back from the commercial with introducing the first
topic and the way he wants to do this is he wants to have an hour block and then it's
so he has like, all right, we have our first topic.
We're taking calls on that topic next hour.
I'll introduce another topic.
We'll take calls on that topic.
Sure.
And I got a framework.
I'm not sure if it works out the way he wants it to, but here is the first topic.
And she passes out and falls to ground had to be taken out later on a stretcher.
So he's, he just, I forgot.
He had played a clip, uh, from Tennessee of a nurse who was giving a, uh, little bit of
a talk to reporters after getting the vaccine for COVID-19 coronavirus vaccine.
And she, uh, fainted after, uh, while she was talking to reporters.
Okay.
And so Alex played the audio of that, but it was really bad.
So I had to start this after, uh, the, uh, the auto is, it was just unlistenable.
And she passes out and falls to the ground had to be taken out later on a stretcher.
And they put out a press release on local ABC news saying, Oh, it's quite normal to
collapse like this when you take any vaccine.
So this video of the nurse in Tennessee was circulating on social media.
And man, it has all of the optics you wouldn't want.
If you're trying to reassure people about the safety of a COVID vaccine, but it's still
something that's being used dishonestly nurse, Tiffany Dover was answering questions from
reporters about getting the vaccine.
At which point she said she was feeling dizzy and momentarily fainted.
She later explained that she has a condition where she faints when she feels pain.
And it was unlikely something caused by the vaccine.
Alex is also just lying about the video and making up details about it.
Most glaringly that she had to be carried out on a stretcher.
According to the associated press quote, Dover was back on her feet shortly after passing
out.
As it turns out, this is just a reaction that some people have to any kind of shot.
And most doctors believe that it's related to pain or anxiety.
You could easily see someone with a history of fainting when experiencing pain, having
that amplified by the anxiety of being on news, getting one of the first vaccines for
a pandemic that should fucking up everyone's life for about a year.
But I do grant that the optics are not what you'd want here at all.
If you're just someone who doesn't care about details and go off emotional reactions to
surface level appearances, then this would be very powerful in terms of painting the
vaccine as dangerous, which I guess is the first topic for the American Journal.
Yeah, I'm not gonna, I'm not gonna say that it wouldn't be a smarter idea not to have
a Southern belle from the 1870s take the first vaccine.
Oh my God, this vaccine.
But I will say that when I got the hepatitis vaccine before I went to South Africa with
my partner, I passed out.
Like I was sitting on the chair and I had to go down on the ground and lay on the floor
because it was such a huge vaccine too.
So it was a, yeah, yeah.
I've not had that experience, but I've definitely seen it.
And I know that some people like when they give blood, they can have a chance of passing
out or, or even like when you see people giving blood or whatever the shock of, of that some,
some people get a lot of response to it and it has nothing to do with what's in the syringe
usually.
So anyway, but there's more to be worried about with this vaccine.
I guess this is also what Alex wants to talk about.
You know, it says on the inserts that it can kill you.
This is not a normal vaccine.
It's even worse.
It's an M RNA vaccine that actually goes in and reprograms every major cell group in your
body to produce quote proteins that block the virus.
Those same proteins happen to be in the placenta.
And so it also blocks having a baby and they had sure, sure toss that in children for a
couple of years.
When you take some of the M RNA vaccines actually have the medical reports from big pharma and
the trials here in my stack today.
Yes, this isn't a conspiracy theory.
This is a fact.
So what Alex is talking about there is complete nonsense.
He was recently yelling about the six deaths in the Pfizer trials, which we discussed on
a recent episode and four were in the placebo group and two were most likely not caused
by the vaccine.
Totally that breakdown that they released, which included that information is probably
one of the best resources for information about the effects that have been documented
in persons who have been given the vaccine.
And Alex says that he has this in his stack, he references this material.
In that very document, they say that quote at the time of the data cut off, which was
November 14th, 2020, a total of 23 participants had reported pregnancies in the safety database,
including nine participants who withdrew from the study due to pregnancies.
There's demographic information about the 43,000 people who were enrolled in the study.
And I considered trying to whittle it down to see if 23 was a notably high or low number
of pregnancies to see in that size group.
But honestly, it would have been impossible to tell from the given information.
You can make some general assumptions, but even if you're able to get a vague number
of the population in the study who are able to get pregnant and of a likely age where
they might, that still doesn't really help.
You still have no idea how many of these people are sexually active, how many were using birth
control, et cetera.
Without access to any of that data, it seems to me that 23 pregnancies is a fairly normal
number.
And it also contradicts all of Alex's bullshit.
Aren't you sick of all these fact checkers, Dan?
I hate them.
A more important piece of info we can take from that Pfizer report is from table 23 towards
the end of the report, which details serious adverse events experienced in the study.
There was one spontaneous abortion that occurred in that group of 43,000 participants, which
was the only pregnancy or perinatal complication or condition that was reported.
This was someone in the placebo group, so it was not caused by the vaccine.
Okay.
All right.
This is a meme that Alex has seen that suggests that the vaccine will cause infertility, but
it's a load of shit.
The basic idea is that the spike protein used in the vaccine is the same as the protein
that's used by the body to create a placenta, so the vaccine would train your body to attack
the very thing you'd need to develop in order to become pregnant.
The protein is called syncytin-1, but the problem boils down to an elementary misunderstanding
on the part of these viral meme makers.
The vaccine uses a spike protein of SARS-CoV-2, which does share a small sequence of amino
acid with syncytin-1, but it's not close enough at all in similarity to cause the kind of
reaction that Alex is suggesting.
Sure.
This is just flimsy meme-based nonsense that Alex is passing off as research, and it means
nothing.
Yeah.
Also, we have not yet to get to any calls.
Yeah, it's one of those, you know, it's one of those things where it's like, you guys
can't know about science for now.
You're just not ready to know a little bit about science.
You're going to hurt yourselves.
Yeah, a little bit is worse than none.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You guys just got to hold off on science.
We'll get to you.
You're going to learn it someday, I promise, but for now-
Yeah, just say it's like devil magic in the syringe.
Yes, please.
Please just, yeah, yeah.
This is no good.
Yeah.
So, he's going to open the phones next segment, but he has some questions.
These are leading questions.
Okay.
Well, I want to open the phones up next segment, and I want to ask all the listeners and all
of the viewers at 877-789-2539 and all the radio listeners at 877-789-2539 or 877-789-Alex,
I want to ask you, are you planning to take the vaccine?
If you're not, what are you going to do when they try to pressure you and push it on you
or try to say it's mandatory as we're doing in some foreign countries and now pushing
here?
And then what do you make of the vaccine makers having liability protection so that when and
if they hurt you, they don't get in any trouble?
I love the idea that his first question is, are you going to take the vaccine?
Obviously the answer from everybody is, fuck no.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Second question, what are you going to do when they force you to like, oh, let's swim
around in violence fantasies about justified violence.
And then the third question is something that none of them are equipped to have, a conversation
about why companies have liability protection and what it means.
That's something that no one who's calling into his show or Alex himself is prepared
to have.
I mean, I suppose one more question would be like, how would it feel to be immune to
a disease?
Does that sound exciting?
Does anybody feel excited about that?
Is that a Stan Lee superpower?
Watch this, you can't be hurt by this disease.
And it's cause real stuff, not cause your mind palace or whatever it is.
It's cause of magic.
Yeah.
Um, Alex does not go to calls yet because he realizes that like, ah, David Knight's
not here.
Right.
I'm doing his job.
He's still got more shit talk to do.
Yeah.
If you tuned in, you're wondering where the David Knight show is.
David's done a great job for nine years here.
And uh, David deserves a break.
We really appreciate David Knight.
And so I made the decision to go ahead and for now cancel that show.
He wants to do it on his own.
That's wonderful.
Maybe someday he'll do something here where it's once a week or something.
Uh, I just think that, uh, I'm burnout and don't want this job.
It's very exhausting, but I have a mission and, and David, um, let's just say David doesn't
give a fuck front lines.
If I think that it's a bad thing, I'm gonna leave it at that.
Uh, but to David, you know, has, as a trooper, he's to take care of himself.
Yeah.
So David Knight's not committed.
Apparently he doesn't have a mission like Alex does.
I'm not going to keep a guy on the front lines if he's not, uh, let's leave it at
that.
Okay.
Wait.
So now it's because he's not performance related to the cause.
I mean, it must be, whether it's like a will or ability, he's not somebody you have on
the front line.
He's not on the team.
That's not just a, you being a nice guy.
He's not happy here.
No, that's a, that's a whole nother explanation and it turns out Alex, there might've been
other influences.
Sure.
And that's it.
There's no controversy.
There's no, there's no secret reason.
It's not because he was bashing Trump every day.
I'm very frustrated with Trump that has nothing to do with it.
It has to do with, I just thinking about it, praying about it, having dreams about David,
really been worried about him.
And I was worried about him last time he had that big heart attack and almost died.
So I just, it's just, I just, I just said, Hey, that's that.
So we pray for David.
He's a great guy.
He's doing great, but, uh, that's it.
All right.
We'll be right back.
So you had a dream.
Uh, I had a fuck dream about David Knight.
So he's gone.
I thought the last straw was Alex learning that black lives matter made $10 billion.
No, it turns out this time, uh, it is, uh, because if you bash Trump every day and now
it's not about that, I'm mad at Trump too.
But if you bash Trump every day, you're not committed to the cause and you're fired.
That's an explanation that he didn't give.
That's an explanation.
You just put it under the pachannic section because it's like what you would think based
on what he's saying.
Yeah.
But there's another explanation buried in there and I'm trying to save his life.
He's going to die if he keeps this up.
All right guys.
I thought he wasn't committed.
I don't know.
I hope he does his show by his self.
You would sue him.
You know you would sue him.
There's a decent chance.
Yeah.
So, uh, Alex has something he's got to deal with, uh, before he gets to calls and that
is that, uh, Mike Pence got a shot.
Yeah.
Um, and Alex shouldn't.
Is he a cyborg or is he dead?
Well, I mean, he's an enemy according to, you know, recent Info Wars lore, but, uh,
still, still would be troubling if Mike Pence got this shot that Alex is saying is going
to kill everyone.
Okay.
This is footage of the vice president just 30 minutes ago or so right before he went
live on air, taking the supposed vaccine, and I got to tell you, they've caught world
leaders in Germany, Japan, other areas, claiming they're taking the shot and then not taking
it.
So he's just going to imply that it's a fake shot.
That works.
I mean, I honestly, I think it's reasonable to just go with.
They get the rich guy shot, right?
It's more you're looking for a theory and you can just make anything up, then why not
do that?
It's more reasonable to think that the wealthy are getting better and different care now
than it is to think they are taking the same shot.
I don't think that.
I think they're taking the same shot, but it's fucking reasonable to be like, Oh, they're
getting rich guy medicine while we get the medium kind.
And Alex has a tradition of talking about clean vaccine.
Yeah, exactly.
So why not?
Yeah.
I don't know.
And he's already said that the mRNA vaccine is better than the older type of vaccine.
No.
Or is it the inverse?
Alex has said, although he dropped this narrative really quick when he realized he didn't know
what he was talking about.
Yeah.
He said that Trump was putting out the Pfizer vaccine in order to cut Gates off at the pass.
Oh, that's right.
Because Alex didn't realize that the Pfizer vaccine was an mRNA vaccine.
Right, right, right, right.
And he was saying that Gates wanted to do this evil one.
So Trump was putting this out in order to put it in checkmate.
That's why I got it mixed up because they're both mRNA, but yeah, now I got it.
He's just dumb.
Yeah.
And that's why that narrative is no longer in play.
Alex realized, Oh, I should probably pretend I didn't say that.
Yes.
It would be smarter.
Yeah.
So Alex finally gets to calls.
It's probably about, I would say 20 minutes in given like a commercial breaks, maybe even
a little longer.
And man, it doesn't start great.
Washington journal, like Washington journal, but American journal, a lot of calls.
Lily in California, you're on the air on the COVID vaccine.
Where do you stand on this?
Oh, absolutely not.
It's the mark of the beast.
No way.
What a shock.
Sure.
Taking America's temperature.
Just all these calls are just going to sound like screech to me.
That's it.
A lot of them.
Yeah.
There's nothing, there's no substance.
There's also going to be a break in that screeching though, uh, for plugs.
Of course.
But there's a second thing I wanted to mention very quickly.
It's like, I want fellow listeners to know about the opportunity to support the info
wars, not only with products, but that there's a support us on tap.
It's hard to find it's that you make it very hard to do it.
Um, but like two weeks ago, I just spent $50 I've, I've purchased lots of, of your products.
Um, the water filter and, uh, and the various supplements.
But right now, especially given everything that you're doing, I just want to put the
money in your hand.
I don't know how much I would have to spend to get for you to have $50 of profit.
I, I, I'm blown away.
The first caller just plugging, giving him money.
Yep.
Not, not, uh, not screening calls.
Of course.
It's amazing.
That is Alex.
I want to take a little bit of time out on your show and plug the people could just give
you money without, without pills.
Can't believe that.
Uh, very shortly after announcing that you have to fire David Knight because of money
reasons, people are calling in saying, uh, you know, and they're definitely not planted
at all.
That would be crazy.
So she goes, Lily, Lily leaves and then we get the second caller.
This is mountain Patriot.
Sure.
Let's go ahead and talk to mountain Patriot in Colorado.
Thank you for holding.
Screech.
How you doing Alex?
Man, I'm just working as hard as I can.
We're in such a critical time.
Brother.
How are you?
I love you, man.
I'm going to miss David Knight, but totally understood.
Uh, we are at war.
I want to make a quick plug that DNA force, what are we doing?
It gets really annoying, really fast possible.
It almost feels like it can't be, you know, it is, it is not necessarily planted calls
or not.
I do.
I do believe that there is a possibility of just people hearing this happen over and
over again.
You get trained that like, Oh, the way a call goes with Alex is you plug a product and then
then you talk.
Right.
Okay.
This feels a little bit like, I'm sure you haven't seen it, but there's a movie called
Phantom thread, uh, starring what's his name.
Who's really good at acting.
I've heard the name of that movie before and uh, uh, spoilers, uh, essentially he's, he's
like part of their sex life is she regularly poisons him and takes care of him.
That's kind of a weird thing that they do.
So he just likes getting poisoned.
Sure.
So I feel like what I'm hearing from all of these people is like, I love getting poisoned
by your products.
That's just what I do.
I want to send you $50.
I like to trick myself into thinking that your pills do something for me.
Yeah, you're taking care of me, but because of munch houses, I guess I'm forcing myself
to get sick.
And this conversation that we're having is actually really interesting because it actually
kind of touches on something that really scared me about mountain Patriot.
Okay.
I want to talk about something called the placebo effect that I haven't heard anyone
mentioned in nine months since this all broke out.
We've been inside for these medicines.
They have to do a double blind study that is they have to do a double blind study in
order to eliminate the placebo effect, which is your own natural innate ability to heal.
So let's calm it, perfect metaphor, calm it, how they want to take our power away.
Don't do that.
Terrifying.
The placebo effect is how we're magic.
Yeah.
This caller legitimately thinks the placebo effect is a term that's used to describe your
body's natural ability to heal itself.
Doctors only use double blind studies because they have to get rid of the possibility that
you're just going to psychically heal yourself when you think you're getting medicine, right?
First of all, the caller is talking about a single blind study.
That's when a participant doesn't know whether they're getting a medicine or the placebo.
A double blind study is when the people administering the trial also don't know which participants
are getting the real thing or the placebo.
This is to remove any possible bias that could come from the researchers expecting certain
outcomes and treating participants differently depending on which group they're in.
Double blind studies are more relevant for eliminating what's known as observer bias.
Placebo effect generally both help with it, but secondly, the placebo effect does not
describe actual healing.
It's a phenomenon in the brain.
For instance, if you're told that you're being given a pill to treat anxiety, but it's actually
a placebo, the fact that you think that you're being given a pill that treats anxiety can
have the effect of decreasing your anxiety.
Totally.
This is a very interesting and complicated thing, but it doesn't work like magic.
If you have an infection and you're given a placebo, it will not treat that infection.
No, I'm pretty sure it will.
You may experience some pain relief or something like that, but you will still have that infection
because the placebo is not treating the condition at all.
No, no, no.
If you break your leg and they give you a fake pill that heals legs, your leg will heal
naturally if you believe in it.
Sure.
A good way to understand this difference is by looking at a 2011 study from Harvard Medical
School and DeCote College and the University of Hull.
Researchers there were looking to better understand the dynamics of placebo effect and symptom
relief, so they designed a study where persons with asthma were given real and placebo inhalers
as well as no treatment and also sham acupuncture.
Gotcha.
The study found that patients with placebo inhalers and even the fake acupuncturism...
Wait, was it specifically sham acupuncture?
Yeah, yeah.
They didn't give...
Real acupuncture might work?
Just in case.
It's just to eliminate another possible...
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
No, no, no.
I gotcha.
I'm sorry for interrupting it.
Yeah.
It seemed really...
It is weird.
Yeah.
So the people with the placebo inhalers and even the fake acupuncture groups subjectively
reported feeling better, and they felt like their symptoms were improving.
However, both of these groups that got the false treatments showed no improvement in
terms of actual lung function.
The actual asthma was not affected at all by the fake treatments, but some of the symptoms
of asthma could be alleviated.
Sure.
This was not true of the group that got the medicine, in this case albuterol.
Those people actually did have greater lung function.
It's great that through the experience of getting treatment, people can experience a
beneficial result, but it should not be mistaken for actual treatment.
If the people who got fake inhalers were then forced to perform a task that required lung
exertion, they would be at a higher risk than the people who got the albuterol.
This is the placebo effect that blind studies hope to minimize so they can test how effective
an actual medication is, and what kind of side effects it could have independent of
a person's expectations.
There's another kind of placebo effect, which is basically Alex's business model.
This is where you convince people they have a fake ailment, then you give them a placebo
to cure it.
His pills won't really do anything, but if he convinces you that your brain just won't
work without his iodine, then you take his iodine and your brain works fine, you'll attribute
that to his iodine.
Iodine efficiency is a real condition, but pretty much everyone listening to Alex's show
doesn't have it.
But making you think that you might, eh, it's a super profitable thing when you sell iodine
and you can manipulate that placebo effect.
Yeah, I think the only thing that we can confirm his products to, or at least points heavily
to his products to, is boners.
And that might even be psychosomatic.
Yeah, totally, but every time somebody talks about it, there's never like, I have more
energy, or like, I feel more assertive.
It's always like, my wife hates me now.
You know, like it's never...
Yeah, but if you're taking that, maybe you have some kind of a mental block that's inhibiting
your ability to come around.
Or it's just basically bull testosterone that you shove in your face.
It's possible too, I don't know.
But anyway, the fact that this caller who's plugging Alex's product doesn't understand
the placebo effect, that is like, art.
You can't have science.
It's perfect.
You can't get it.
It's perfect though.
It's so...
Trax.
Yeah.
It's just, they're just not ready for it.
They're just not, just like how like Galileo, admittedly he was a dick, but the people around
him just weren't ready for science yet, and he kept trying to give it to him, and then
he got trapped.
I mean, again, that was mainly because he was a dick.
But it happens, you know?
Those people weren't ready for science.
They weren't ready for science.
These people aren't ready for science.
You know what Alex isn't ready to do?
Take calls?
Stop talking about David Knight.
Okay.
I've had the idea for this show for many, many years, never done it.
I decided to do this at about two o'clock yesterday.
I made the decision to go ahead and just launch this show immediately.
Bad idea.
Really regretting that.
We're all stressed out.
There's so much going on.
There's so much happening.
We could have just taken the day off.
I would watch David Knight, who's just a great guy, get ready for four hours in the morning
before he went on at 8 a.m., and then I would sometimes get off my show at like two o'clock,
and he would be in the studio researching, looking like he was in living hell, and I
was like, dude, you've got to not work 16 hours a day.
I mean, stacks of notes, computers out, just insane.
Isn't that what you say you do, Alex?
Unreal.
So now he said he's firing David because he works too hard.
He works too hard.
The man is too committed to the info war.
That's why I had to fire him.
I've never seen him in flip flops.
He's too serious.
So we have both, he's not committed, and he doesn't care enough, and that's why he can't
be on the front lines, and also, he works too hard.
He researches all the time.
He's just too committed.
He's here at four in the morning, grinding.
He's not committed to the info war, Dan.
He's treating this as if it's some kind of job.
None of this makes sense.
It's a little bit internally inconsistent, but it is fun to just hear him go all over
the place.
But look, whatever the actual reason behind it, David needed a break, and Alex knows that
because he needs a break.
Alex needs a break.
But I just wanted to have a clean break.
It hit me yesterday morning, watched him on the show and worried about him.
And so that's what this is.
And it's also a financial issue.
David doesn't get paid that much, whatever, does a great job.
It's just that we don't have enough crew to run all these shows, and they're burnt out.
And with COVID, a few people's wives or whatever were in a place that had it, so they had to
leave and take care of them.
And it's just been like we're a NASCAR that has been in two or three races, but hasn't
even had the engine looked at.
And now there's fire coming out of the engine.
So I'm taking off all next week, and I never take off a full week.
I always work wherever I'm at.
I'm going to literally hide my phone and turn the computers off.
And I told my wife last night, I said, we're going to put your phone up, and we're going
to spend time with the family, and I'm going to disconnect and come back five years younger.
I believe he probably is going to take the week off, but it's also Christmas.
Wow.
I mean, he deserves a break, so he's going to do something out of this world and take
the week of Christmas off.
Some people would never dream of doing that.
I'm going to take him at his word.
They're called everybody who doesn't care.
I'm going to take him at his word and believe that he is actually going to take the week
off, and we'll see if he does or not.
That'd be nice.
He's talking about what's going to happen on the shows, and he's like, Owen Schreier
is going to host this morning's show and my show.
And they're like, wait, his show's on right after your show.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Put Owen Schreier to it.
Put him through the gauntlet.
Hell yeah.
Harrison Smith's going to host the war room.
No, I want Owen to go through the crucible.
We have to be on air from eight to four, eight to five every day.
How else are you going to get your chaps, man?
I used to go out and do four or five sets in a night.
You got to get your chaps going, so you might as well work 12 hour days.
Anchoring a absurd call-in show, then sensational thing, then conspiracy bro down.
Yeah, yeah.
Three different vibes.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's not going to work.
Yeah, no, it's not going to work.
So Alex gets to another caller who has an interesting question.
Everything that you said about needing your essential vitamins and minerals, that should
be enough.
Nobody needs these vaccines on top of everything else that's wrong with them.
But my daughter is a mortician in Arizona and she's busy.
She won't listen.
She used to be open-minded and I don't know how to get through to her.
And I just want to know if you have any suggestions.
Well, I mean, I'm sure you've seen the band segment, a band out video with all the nurses
and doctors, hundreds of videos saying it's an overblown fraud.
We've got all these top scientists saying the John Hopkins report that came out said
there's been as many deaths this year as there was this time last year of other things show
if the overall death rate's not up, that means they're moving other deaths of flu and pneumonia
and other things into the COVID column, which we know they're doing.
Can't imagine why this lady's mortician daughter isn't listening to her.
I don't know why my daughter is working also 12 hour days and she just doesn't believe
me.
Well, she looks sadder than David Knight.
She looks real sad.
Something's really weighing on her, you know.
Johns' narrative here is a load of shit, and if he did one tenth of the research he pretends
to, he would know that.
So here's what happened with that Johns Hopkins thing that he's talking about.
On November 13th, an economics lecturer at Johns Hopkins used faulty data to assert that
there was no evidence of excess deaths in the United States this year.
The numbers and analysis this lecturer were using were elementary and didn't take into
account a bunch of relevant variables, whereas peer reviewed studies that follow higher standards
have regularly shown an approximately 20% increase in mortality this year over long
term averages.
This wasn't a study or a report, it was a misrepresentation of data that was delivered
in a lecture.
This claim was then covered in the Johns Hopkins student newspaper, the Johns Hopkins newsletter.
Naturally, as soon as people noticed, the paper retracted the story and issued a correction.
In the meantime, however, the Gateway Pundit had found the article and began reporting
on the erroneous claim made by the econ lecturer.
The right-wing conspiracy narrative is that the lecturer is correct and that the retraction
is a cover-up of this obviously accurate information, but that's a bunch of nonsense.
Even the Gateway Pundit's framing of the story is intentionally misleading.
Their headline was, quote, Johns Hopkins study mysteriously disappears after it revealed
in spite of COVID no more deaths in 2020 than in prior years.
There was no study to disappear, it was just a fabricated and sensationalized headline.
You can follow the thread from right-wing bullshit website reporting on blog posts from
another right-wing bullshit website all the way back to the student newspaper article
that has been retracted.
Even in that article, they say that the lecturer, quote, also mentioned that more research and
data are needed to truly decipher the effect of COVID-19 on deaths in the United States.
So basically you have an economics lecturer who gave a talk where she inaccurately interpreted
some data, which was then covered by a student newspaper, which was then inaccurately reported
on by dumb right-wing blogs.
The student article was retracted, which the right-wing blogs then made part of the conspiracy.
Of course.
This is then reported on by Alex as Johns Hopkins proving in a study that there's no
excess deaths in 2020 and that COVID deaths are all a hoax or just other deaths shuffled
over, which is what this caller should then tell her mortician daughter to help open her
mind about vaccine denialism.
Oh boy.
American Journal.
I do not want to denigrate student newspapers at all.
During the protests in Chicago, student newspapers did a million times better job than any other
local media, and especially better than the national media in Chicago.
There's a double-edged sword to student.
But at the same time, it's still a student newspaper.
We can't be, the right-wing can't be like, ah, student newspaper did something, so yeah.
It's sort of a, it's hard to make like a full statement on, because it's like, okay, yeah,
some student journalists are amazingly capable and can do good work.
Totally.
You know, some mistakes that wouldn't happen in professional newsrooms can happen at student
newspapers because they're student newspapers.
Exactly.
It's, you know, the knife cuts both ways.
Totally.
It's tough.
So we got another caller.
Yeah.
Let's take a few calls here before we go to break, and I'll come back and take nothing
but calls, but I wanted to hit those stories.
Holding the longest would be Kurt in Oklahoma, Kurt, welcome.
There is nothing better, nothing more comfy than waking up, saying a prayer, brewing a
cup of Wake Up America Patriot Blend, and calling in to the American Journal.
That's right, sir.
Well, we're honored to be here, and we're glad to be taking your calls.
What is your view on this situation with the vaccines?
So this guy's plugging Alex's coffee.
Yeah.
It's just, it's getting annoying at this point.
It's very frustrating.
Oh, there's nothing more relaxing than drinking your coffee and calling in to the first episode.
Yeah.
Of your show.
Is that some sort of, like, among Info Wars, like, diehard listeners, is that some sort
of meme, like a way they communicate with each other?
That's interesting.
Okay, if you plug, you know, like, we're all so used to Alex plugging.
Yeah.
Like, is that part of, like, a memetic language that they have with each other?
It's possible, and I also think that a lot of times Alex's ads end up using callers in
them.
Right.
Because there is that, like, frack, I need your help, frack.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That you would play.
So maybe they're hoping...
Yeah, that could be.
They're hoping that they'll become a commercial that Alex uses.
Right, right, right.
I don't know, that's possible.
That would be interesting.
I mean, I know that when I was, like, 13, 14, I would call and request a song on the
radio, like, call the DJs.
I was hoping that they would record it and use it to introduce the song.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
Maybe that's the same thing, but they're adults.
Yeah.
They're trying to help Alex sell pills.
Yeah, that's a little bit less, it's lower on the totem pole than Rick asking for a song.
Yeah.
Exactly.
That caller, just in case you were worried about this.
Not into the vaccine.
In case you're curious.
Something that Alex isn't into is stop talking about David Knight.
And I intend to host this some, I intend to get other hosts that are going to rotate through
maybe David Knight if you want, sometimes.
I'll come in and do it.
I'm going to show a TV viewer something that was just regularly a David Knight slot for
the last four years, and I just abruptly decided yesterday to end that show because it was
just my gut level thing to do, the right thing to do for David, for him, for us, for the
country, for the world, because the country that he's been worn out and exhausted by this,
just like I am.
And my gut, my spirit told me to do it.
Here's an example.
Here's a promo.
We started putting out last week, send out to all these TV stations and around the country
saying if you haven't picked up the David Knight show top thing here, please pick up
the David Knight show.
Then Alex Jones, then the war room, this has been sent out starting last week to every
one explaining that we're on galaxy 16 video satellite, AMC 18 radio satellite.
I love David.
He's been here nine years, really smart guy, but the election and some of our political
disagreements were making him super upset.
Not me.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
So now he's pissed off.
Not okay.
First.
So now David is uncomfortable about political disagreements with Alex, but Alex, totally
cool.
Above it.
Totally cool.
He's chill.
He's chill as hell.
And also the whole thing about the promotional materials being sent out last week.
It sounds like nobody picked up David Knight's show.
So they canned him.
That's possible.
But Alex is trying to use that as evidence that like, I don't know.
We've got more support behind David Knight's show.
Yeah.
All that proves is like maybe it was a snap decision.
That's all.
Yeah.
Nobody picked up his show.
I think if you've been racking your brain and so worried about how much work he puts
in, the fact that you had promotional materials that came out last week doesn't help your
case.
I feel like everybody's so attuned to the vagaries of the TV show business now that
there's a part of the...
Why not just say that we didn't pick up his show again?
Right.
Like it's not hard.
It could be so easy and everybody'd be like, oh, there's a reason, but they just didn't
pick up the show.
Hey, Alex.
Shut up.
Heroes didn't get a third season and everybody's like, well, yeah, they didn't pick up the
show.
It's...
Or did it get a third season?
I know they had a comeback.
Ooh, that's not good.
It was bad.
It wasn't good.
That's not good.
Look, dude, there are a hundred ways you could do this and none of it requires any of this
shit.
None of this shit!
No.
We've got 16 reasons, some of which are I'm a hero and the others are David Knight's disagreeing
with me and the others are insane.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, boy.
But we do have one explanation for his termination that we get crossed off the list here.
Why?
One thing that definitely had nothing to do with it.
He does have both feet.
And during the break, they're like, yeah, people think you got rid of David because
of Steve Pacinek.
Steve Pacinek didn't even enter my mind and those two fighting with each other.
So it was him.
Zero, zero, zero to do with it.
It had to do with David was very ashen, very white, looked really sick to him.
Wow.
And I thought about telling him quit at that point because he looked so depressed.
Okay.
And I almost did it then.
And he had a massive heart attack and almost died and he's been looking the same.
And that's it.
And it's not a personal issue.
It's none of that.
I care about David.
He needs a break.
He just needs a break.
Oh, man.
Listen, it's not Steve.
Now there's nothing that makes me know it's Steve more than him being like, I never thought
about it.
Zero possibility, zero possibility of that.
It makes me more suspicious of that for sure.
And this is one of those instances where it's not just you and I have been saying that.
Sometimes Alex will say like, oh, people will say I kill dogs a lot.
We say that.
That's us.
Yeah.
This is something that a lot of people on Twitter have been pointing out because David
was tweeting on about how Steve sucks.
So it is a little bit more of a public thing, but look, dude, he just worked too hard.
That's all it is.
He was ashen.
I care about David.
He needs a break.
I mean, again, four hours before the show getting ready.
Three hours of a show, three, four hours after studying, looking like he's in hell.
And so I fired him.
God told me to do it.
It was like 10 a.m. over there.
God told me.
Okay.
I've got to go let David go.
It's just got to do it clean and be done.
And then later at the show, they go, what are you going to do?
And I said, I guess we'll cancel the show.
And they go, a lot of stations picked that up.
I said, I'm too exhausted.
I'm taking off next week.
I might quit.
This is a real conversation.
They said, you can't quit.
They said, I know I just can't focus on the evil anymore.
I know how David feels.
And then you feel like you're not doing enough.
And then I and then your brain runs out of dopamine.
And then I'm super exhausted.
And I don't even have time with my children.
They said, just take off next week and think about what you're going to do.
But I had to make that decision because I didn't make the decision when my gut told
me to do it the last time he almost died.
Okay.
So I told God this.
I've told you this.
I'm going my gut now, period, because it's never been wrong.
And I haven't been following my whole life.
And the more I follow my gut, the more I never make mistakes.
So I'm not going to put into all the reasons of why it happened.
It has zero to do with Steve Puccini.
Okay.
So it was Steve Puccini.
That pissed me off during the break when they were like, uh, yeah, they think it's so I'm
not involved in this Twitter beef.
Yeah, man.
This, this playground nonsense on Twitter.
So Steve Puccini, I will, I will put that down.
The lady doth protest too much.
No kidding.
Come on, man.
I'm pissed off that people saw through the bullshit.
We did pick up his show.
That's all you have to say.
Or it could just be like, it's personal.
Yeah.
You know how many people have left Info Wars in the past?
How few of them anyone care has gone now.
Yeah.
I couldn't, I can't imagine.
I mean, I guess there's some like old timers who probably like, Hey, where's Jakari?
Where's Leanne McAdoo?
But like, no one cares now.
Joe Biggs is gone.
No one gives a shit.
David and I had a creative disagreements and so I let him go.
I honestly think that the financial thing is probably your best play.
If he could have just stuck to that.
We're broke.
Yeah.
Because that elicits support from the audience who want to see your thing not disappear.
It doesn't require you to get into the mud with David about how he works too hard, which
is confusing.
Wild.
Cause he's also not committed at all to the Info War.
Right.
And his workload seems to be less than you pretend you have for yourself.
Exactly.
It's all just too complicated.
Just say like we had a really good salary for him and we couldn't carry it into the
next quarter or whatever.
There's like, that would be adult, right?
But because it is definitely personal, he just can't stick to the story.
It almost certainly has to be.
It is personal.
And so we can't stick to the fucking story.
There's a mystery here.
And I think what I might need to do on Alex's week off, this is going to be painful as hell.
I might have to go through the last shows that David Knight did and see if there's some
kind of a clue.
No.
I don't know.
Maybe there will be.
That would be a terrible Christmas episode for us to put out.
I just hope that Alex Jones fires me for the next thing I'm about to say.
I am working too hard.
So Alex gets off this topic for a moment.
Anybody notice my ashen face lately?
So leaving aside Alex's anger and confusion about what exactly happened, he has some optimism.
Now I've told you, Trump has a real shot at staying in office and defeating this election
fraud.
If he gets bold and if he comes out against the globalist and points out that Biden's
a communist Chinese agent, and if he puts all his people in from the Pentagon at key
positions and sells the American people on a limited form of martial law that General
Flynn and others have rightfully called for.
When do you call martial law?
When there is a foreign power that has occupied you.
That is what the definition says.
That's the reasons for martial law under US military history.
Wow.
So declared 60 something times in US history, it's usually for insurrections or things like
that.
This is a ChaiCom takeover.
We are infiltrated.
Joe Biden does work for China.
Sure.
India did lie and say he was the president.
They did steal these key areas.
We have all the evidence.
We bare minimum need a new election.
Wow.
The 64 thing or 60 something odd times martial law has been declared is it's something Alex
is just repeating from an interview you heard with Mike Flynn.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I want to tell you a little trivia.
Sure.
How many times do you think martial law has been declared since World War II?
Since World War II, uh, twice.
Nine.
Nine times.
Okay.
And you know what?
Five of them.
I found this in an article from 1989.
Sure.
In the Law and Order Journal.
Oh, since World War II.
Five of them, I would almost guarantee are during the civil rights era.
Yes, there we go.
Yeah.
Quote, in five instances, it was designed to counter resistance to federal desegregation
decrees in the south.
There we go.
Over half the times any kind of martial law has been used, it's because of people like
Alex who think that desegregation is a communist plot.
Yeah.
Yes.
It's, it's, it's you.
Yeah.
Uh.
I was, you know what?
I, I, I, uh, if Trump overthrows the government, does he still get to keep the POTUS Twitter
account?
You know, cause they're going to transfer it over to Biden.
Jack.
When Biden becomes president.
Do we have, do we have DOTUS dictator, somebody grab up all the dictators, get all the dictator
related Twitter accounts.
Um, Kim Jong Trump.
That would be a good one.
At Kim Jong Trump.
I don't know, man.
I think that Jack would have a really tough decision to make at that point.
Yeah.
Whether he wants to die or give Trump the Twitter handle.
I don't know.
We'll see.
Billionaires generally are willing to die for causes.
So Alex is at bare minimum new election.
Right.
Bare minimum.
Yeah.
Which everybody in the United States will accept.
That'll be something that we are all like, you know what, we got to get to the bottom
of it this time.
Yeah.
Bare minimum new election.
Now back to calls.
Sure.
Yeah.
Let's talk to Baldy.
Let's talk to Baldy in Florida.
Baldy.
You were down there at the bottom and I missed you.
Sorry.
Go ahead.
Sure.
Just as a reminder, I'm the one that all through March was calling, begging and pleading with
everyone to realize that this was the April fool's virus.
Real quick.
I do not remember Baldy from that period.
I'm not worried about it.
Now before I give my Baldy briefing on the pending inoculations, is that a regular segment?
For generations to come, I wanted to spread the truth that it's President Trump that won
the election.
Hey, brother, do me a favor.
You got me on speakerphone?
No, sir.
No, I missed you asking.
Somebody missed his email.
Speakerphone.
Is this better?
Say it again?
Uh-huh.
Is this better?
Just hang up.
Just talk quietly.
I got to put him in my home.
I can't handle it.
Oh, boy.
Don't do a call at the show, man.
You knew this was going to happen.
God, everyone knew this was going to happen.
I'm shocked it doesn't happen more frequently during this episode.
Oh, man.
There are some tech issues, but this is the worst of it probably.
But Alex gets pretty pissed off.
I do not appreciate.
If he does not have some sort of performative show or something, if he's just saying this
is a baldy briefing to people in regular life.
Get the fuck out of here.
No, no, I love it.
No friends.
Zero friends.
I want to hang out with Baldy.
No.
No, thank you.
I want to be briefed.
Here's a baldy briefing for you.
Goodbye, sir.
Thank you.
I got a baldy briefing for you.
It's your turn to buy a round.
If that's what he calls sex, I'm out.
So we get another caller, and this was interesting.
He wants to know about Steve's election sting stuff, because there is an interesting thing
that like now, Alex, you need to make a statement on this, because it's obviously not true.
So you need to put a flag down somewhere of, is Steve lying to you or is he wrong?
That kind of thing.
And of course this leads into more shitting on David's eyes.
Yes, of course.
And Steve Fuchenich, he did say with certainty that he had that whole sting operation with
the blockchain and all that.
None of that's been verified.
I mean, what's your comment on that?
From everyone's point of view, it kind of looks like he was a BS-er.
Well, we're sure going to find out.
I mean, I'm not wedded to Steve Fuchenich.
He's been a guest on the show probably 50, 60, 70 times over the years, maybe more, maybe
a hundred times.
He went on Owen's show.
I had no idea that was going to happen.
I had him on about some other issues, and that's one of the things that pushed David
over the edge.
I mean, I'll just tell people, he started saying he's going to quit to everybody here.
He said, I'm quitting.
Alex is having Steve Fuchenich on.
He went in and told, you know, Rob Duke, and he said, shouldn't have him on.
Like Alex doesn't tell you to have one.
So I don't tell David who to have on.
He shouldn't tell me who to have on, but that had nothing to do with the fact that David
was saying he wanted to quit.
He was miserable and he wouldn't quit.
So I just said, fly my friend.
The door is open.
So now, apparently, David wanted out, so I kicked him out the door.
Yeah.
David didn't want me to have Steve Fuchenich on anymore, which had nothing to do with anything.
And he was going to quit.
So I just said, get to walking.
Get to walking.
Now also I am pointing out that he told me not to have Steve on my show, which I said
is a courtesy to a friend.
Yeah.
Talk to that guy.
He's a menace.
He's ruined your life.
All right.
Okay.
So now we're getting closer to the real answer.
Now Alex starts to get a little bit mad about David Knight giving him editorial advice.
Sure.
There we go.
Yeah.
The Steve Fuchenich thing pushed him over the edge.
He basically told the whole crew he was going to quit.
Well, he didn't do it.
And he said he was going to quit years ago.
So I finally said, look, dude, you don't want to be here.
You're free.
And I like David, but I'm not going to sit there and he's not doing this.
He's a standup guy.
You can leave a million dollars with that guy in 10 years, come back and every dollar
would be there.
He's a great, true, good guy.
So I fired him.
Engineer.
Yeah.
But like a lot of those guys, like a lot of those guys, it's his way or the highway.
So okay.
It's never me telling David what to have on.
It's the other way around.
And he didn't do it a lot, but you know, years ago, he's like, Hey, you shouldn't cuss on
the show.
And you know what?
He's right.
But sometimes I can't help it.
And we delay it out.
But it's sad.
I get it.
He's older than me.
I respect my elders, but I'm the boss.
Does that make sense?
Yeah.
He told me how to do my show and I'm pissed off about it.
That's why I had to fire him for his health.
It has nothing to do with him and Steve pachanic fighting, even though I brought it up multiple
times.
It has nothing to do with him and me fighting, even though I am clearly very angry about
it.
And I resent that he told me not to swear on my radio show.
And I'm still hanging on to it.
Telling me not to swear on my radio show that I will get fined if I swear on top station.
Someone politely offering me just a little bit of advice as a friend, obviously is him
telling me.
David Knight does sound like a stand-up guy.
Yeah, he does.
Telling Alex not to have Steve on is a blessing.
That's what I would expect of somebody who worked for me.
That's a friend.
Yeah.
Someone telling him, hey, come on, stop swearing.
You're letting your passions get the best of you.
Your job is contingent on you not swearing on anyone.
It just seems like a guy who's got your back.
Oh, man.
Wow.
Oh, boy.
That wasn't because of Steve, though.
You need to know that.
Oh, sure.
I respect my elders, but I'm the boss.
Does that make sense?
And then the last thing I want to do a touch on, because I know we're kind of...
Stop asking me about David, or I'm going to keep saying more.
I'm asking listeners to drop it, to drop it.
I swear to God on my children.
Hold on a minute.
I'm not going to let you go.
I swear to God on my children, Steve Pacinek had nothing to do with this.
And David marched up and down the halls here saying he was going to quit for months.
He's gone.
Because of Steve Pacinek.
Come back up.
So he was marching up and down the hall saying he was going to quit.
Because of Steve Pacinek.
But Steve had nothing to do with this.
Nothing to do with this.
And Alex seems a little mad.
Maybe.
A little mad.
Maybe people keep bringing up the real answer and it's making it hard for me to continue
lying about it.
But this caller didn't say that.
No.
This caller's question was, do you have a comment on that specific piece of bullshit
that was on your show?
Not just Owen's show.
You've talked about the election sting on Infowars on Alex's show as well.
Oh yeah.
That is a very fair question for someone to ask a commentator.
Right.
Hey, you put this out.
It is inaccurate.
Do you have a statement on what you think?
Would you like to clear that up?
Instead, Alex starts yelling about David Knight.
Great.
Which makes you think that thinking about Steve makes him think about David.
It makes you think that maybe.
I swear on my kids lives who are strangely enough, uh, Oh my God, I just heard they died
after I swear it on their lives.
Shit.
I will.
I think that might be my fault.
I will eat David Knight to save my kids.
What?
Wait, what's going on?
I don't understand.
Anyway, look dude, had nothing to do with Steve.
So I'm the bad guy.
Just like Tony Montana says, point at me and say good night to the bad man.
Okay.
Alex Jones is a bad man.
This is not a Howard Stern show where we have fighting on the show and fighting with the
crew.
I'm not mad at the caller.
I just can't handle it.
Everybody's always got to have some drama.
Steve Pechenik has nothing to do with my decision.
David Knight saying to everyone that would listen, he was going to quit is the reason
most places you say you're going to quit a couple of times.
They go, go ahead and quit.
How about 200 times?
And I'm not mad at David.
So I have respect for David.
He got what he wanted.
Oh, let's go ahead and talk to Jefferson in Virginia.
Jefferson.
You're on the air.
Welcome.
Wow.
I feel welcome.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Oh boy.
So a very respectful tribute to David Knight's time.
90% calls on this show, I would say it's not accurate.
I realize now that the thing that I don't want people to ask me about is going to be
the only thing we talk about on a call in show.
I love, I love the idea that this is the American journal.
We're really getting the pulse of the country and the country is conflicted about why Alex
fired David, except no one appears to be except Alex.
Alex is the only person who's given contradictory reports on this.
Oh God.
Oh boy, buddy.
I would just totally have accepted a number of explanations if they seemed consistent.
Yeah.
If you just kept saying the same one.
It's so overtly and insanely defensive over the one that you are telling me it's not.
For no reason.
While you're filling in on his show.
Here's what you could do.
Hey, do you think it's because of Steve Pacenik?
No, no, no.
It had nothing to do with it.
He's just wasn't feeling well.
Hey, guess what?
Alex is also a liar.
Oh yeah, there's that.
He could just say he had another heart attack.
Ooh, that would be easy.
Yeah.
And then David would get on his Twitter and say, I didn't have a heart attack.
And then who cares?
Nobody would go forward.
You're a liar by trade.
No one cares.
Yeah.
Anyway, I was interested after listening to this American Journal to see how Alex holds
up on his own show.
Of course.
So a little bit after this, he takes this call from Jefferson and then he hangs out
for a little bit.
It's boring as hell.
And then John Rappaport takes over for the last half hour and Alex jumps in and he realizes
as soon as he gets on his own show that there were some calls that he didn't take on the
American Journal.
And so he calls them back.
He has the producers call them back.
Oh, boy.
I was called by a listener and he was on air and reminded me that there's actually a federal
law saying we can all be experimented on en masse, H.R. 4373.
So we're all about documentation.
The slugs over George Soros run media matters that literally are mercenaries against your
very life are hoping you don't research this.
I'm guessing that Alex means H.R. 4373 from the most recent session of Congress.
H.R. 4373 from the 2015-2016 session was the End Drunk Driving Act of 2016.
So I'm guessing that's not what he's talking about.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
He still doesn't know they start over every Congress.
H.R. 4373 in the most recent Congress is a bill called the Engineering Biology Research
and Development Act of 2019.
In December of last year it passed the House and was sent to the Senate.
There it was sent to the Committee on Commerce, Science, and Transportation, where no action
has been taken on it since.
It's essentially a dead bill.
Even if this bill had passed, it wasn't something that would allow large-scale evil testing
on people.
It was basically a declaration that more grants should be given out to engineering biology
fields to expand the pool of researchers working on those topics.
In case you were curious, though, the End Drunk Driving Act of 2016 didn't even make
it out of the House.
That's not surprising.
Everybody loves drunk driving.
Yeah, so Alex, you know, Media Matters is afraid of you looking into these things and
finding out these bills that are stalled in committee exist that don't say what I'm gonna
pretend they...
Get the fuck out of here.
You didn't look into this.
It would terrify you.
Yeah.
If only you worked half as hard as David Knight pretends to, you'd be able to look into that
bill and find out whatever.
Anyway, Alex is sort of continuing a lot of the themes from the American Journal, like
the whole, like, your placenta will be attacked by the vaccine.
Sure.
Yeah, you're never having a baby again when you take this.
And the thing is, they're gonna commit this mass crime and have the nurses and the doctors
all signed on to it, so when it turns out millions have been sterilized and millions
die, slowly, everyone will enjoy it on the cover-up, and the Nazis call that the cement
of blood.
They'll now be corrupted and follow any order.
Okay.
All right.
That sounds...
Okay.
Sounds scary.
Can you sue for defamation on...
On the behalf of, like, a field?
Yeah.
No, no, no.
Not on behalf of them, but, like, could, like, Pfizer just be like, hey, I'm going to sue
you.
Well, like, Fox News had to say all those things that they said were lies.
Sidney Powell's Dominion stuff.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They had to be like, hey, I'm sorry, we didn't, we lied about that.
Now, obviously, they're gonna continue lying about it, but can you do that to Alex?
I mean, nobody cares enough, I guess.
I think it would be hard.
But I mean, it seems like you can't just say that a company's vaccine will force you to
never have a baby again?
Yeah, it seems like it would be something that should be actionable in some way, but
I don't know what the mechanism for it would be.
Well, I mean, obviously, the vaccine itself cannot sue for defamation.
It's true.
Yeah.
And all the people who, like, really do have some standing don't have the time and are
public figures.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, like, Bill Gates would have a really tough time suing Alex for defamation.
Even though, like, I mean, there is actual malice, Alex knows the things he's saying
are not true.
Yeah, could the people who actually created the vaccine sue?
Conceivably.
I don't know.
I would be interested.
Yeah.
I don't know enough.
That would be interesting.
Yeah.
Let's do it.
So, Alex gets another caller from earlier who's still waiting to talk to him.
He has an interesting question.
PB in Rhode Island, you're on the air, go ahead.
Princess Bubblegum?
Peanut Butter.
Thank you for taking my call and thank you for everything you do.
Thank you, brother.
I just got a question for you.
As far as the communist Chinese leaks of over 2 million communist Chinese agents pretty
much released around the world, there was a list of 20 United States governors on that
list.
That just seems like a lot.
What do you think of that and how come it hasn't really gained as much traction in the
media?
Because the mainstream media is sold out to the Chai-Coms.
I mean, that's what I've been telling everybody forever and now it's come out.
Oh, oh, maybe, maybe because it's not, that's not accurate.
Yeah.
Maybe?
20 seems too high to ignore.
Almost half.
Yeah, 20 seems just too high to-
Almost half of the governors in this country are Chinese secret agents.
If you said like two governors had successfully become secret agents or whatever, that's more
believable than almost half the entire country is run by communist secret agents?
Yeah.
Although that caller would have fit in on the American Journal.
That's true.
Alex is still optimistic at this point on the 18th that Trump is going to seize power
and he reveals accidentally that Roger is still lying to him.
Okay.
I don't ever want to be over positive, but now I see Trump going after the globalist
and I see all these arrests happening and I see them canceling Biden's military briefings
and it tells me Trump's getting ready to drop the hammer.
And I was told something about Trump, I'm not going to say whether I heard it from Trump
or Roger Stone, but they told me when he was president elect four plus years ago that Trump
expected this to come down to this.
And so, look, I'm just telling the new world order, if you're looking for trouble, you
came to the right place.
Yeah.
I heard this from either Trump or Roger Stone.
Okay.
Yeah, it was Roger Stone.
Great.
In 2016, Roger Stone was saying that Trump planned on declaring martial law and seizing
power.
Yeah, there we go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, cool.
Glad you signed onto that.
When he was president elect, Roger Stone told me that Trump would overthrow this democratic
government and create a dictatorship.
So I'm looking forward to that.
Yeah.
I felt like that was the most constitutional thing I could support.
I mean, it's obvious.
Like Trump is either, when he leaves office, he's either going to lose all of his money
or he's going to wind up going to jail.
I don't see him de-escalating.
I mean, we say that, but like, why wouldn't he just be on the next season of The Masked
Singer?
Yeah, that's true.
Why wouldn't he just reinvent himself as a pop star or something?
I don't know.
Probably because he's directly responsible for the deaths of what's going to wind up
being 400 to 500,000 people.
So, I mean, like obviously I'm on your side, but speaking from the other end, who cares?
There's a giant portion of the population that doesn't care and will give him money.
That's true.
So like, so in America, that means there's another chapter, as long as, as long as he
doesn't end up going to prison, even if he lost a ton of money, like rags to riches to
rags to riches or whatever the fuck.
It's not like he hasn't lost a ton of money before.
Exactly.
Yeah, that's true.
So at this point, Alex has gone to break and he comes back and it's very jarring because
he comes in with some rap music and then gets really weird.
And I'm not going to cover this news in the next hour because there's more coming in.
I want to really tell you what I think and the back of my brain, I'm still percolating
what's happening, but Trump's going to make a run at them.
I mean, that's the bottom line.
And I've talked to really serious people, a lot of them at the Pentagon, and they're
all very excited and are going to make a run at them.
And they're getting the hearings ready to give them the political backing for what they
need to do.
They're already raiding facilities.
It really is happening.
And right here in Austin, the raids did happen in Germany.
And let's just say this country is fighting for its life right now.
And with 33 days left, we should see some big action the next week.
Well, and I'm going to be taking off.
Yes.
Yeah.
So this is classic Alex, just him coming in and being like, I'm not going to cover this
story because my gut doesn't.
I'm going to cover it.
Trump's going to make a run at him.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
How funny.
So Alex has just heard this Pentagon story, which he covers a little bit.
Yeah.
This is out of Axios, Bloomberg, all of it, acting Pentagon chief halts Biden transition
briefings, signaling that Trump is not going to concede and going to use the military.
So this is kind of what tipped him over the edge into, like, Trump is going to make a
run at him.
Sure.
It's kind of bullshit.
The Pentagon has said that the reason for the halt in transition activities is because
many of the staff felt overwhelmed by the demands of the transition, but are, quote,
still committed to a productive transition of power.
We didn't used to have to do our jobs.
That quote cut off at transition.
I just said of power.
Yeah.
So maybe I don't want to mislead by adding to the quote.
Right.
You know, the people said that they decided to, quote, take a knee until after the holidays
because, quote, the D.O.D. staff working the meetings were overwhelmed by the number of
meetings, and, quote, these same senior leaders needed to do their day jobs and were being
consumed by transition activities.
I'm fairly cynical, but the way I see this, it's pretty clear that Trump's entire team
is full of incompetence in the field of actually governing.
Yeah.
So it's not a surprise that the people he would choose would be the type of folks would
be overwhelmed by work.
This is still upsetting and horrible and everything, but I'm not sure it's proof that Trump is
set to use the military to stay in power.
No.
When incompetence among officials that Trump has directly appointed is an option, it's
almost always the right one.
We can't get this shit done, and there's too many meetings.
Oh, no.
I could see that.
Yeah.
I could also see it being a, like, just almost sabotage, petulance kind of thing.
Totally.
I don't know if I think that it's an indication that Trump's going to use the military.
I don't think so, but I mean, it does make so much sense for the transition team to be
like, here's the intelligence that we expect you to give us.
And they're like, ooh, we were told not to learn that kind of stuff, so we don't have
it.
Yeah, running out the clock to show that, ooh, we were drinking these last four years.
We did nothing.
We were allowed to act with impunity.
Yeah.
That's a possible explanation.
Totally.
And I don't know.
I guess we'll have to see how it plays out.
But that's really what is behind Alex's ha ha ha.
Breaking news the entire Biden family is under house arrest.
Oh, no.
That's not good.
So Alex has found this news story about the Supreme Court and someone yelling, Justice
Roberts yelling about how we can't do this.
We can't let Trump's cases come to court.
But it looks bad waiting this long for McConnell to roll over, be a Chiacom agent, the Supreme
Court roll over, be Chiacom agents, have Roberts screaming and yelling, saying the Democrats
will burn America.
So we're all scared of Trump's martial law to counter their martial law.
But we got the justice that the opposing chief justice saying we can't do this.
Because if we do, screaming at the other justices who all crapped their pants and got in line,
the other eight, that's in the news now.
Credible sources, congressman sources, the aides, talk to their aides that he pistol
wept him.
He he he screamed at him for hours that they'll be riots, they'll be because that's what Black
Lives Matter and ten point six million dollars of B.S. was.
So this story isn't true.
Critics just saw a viral online post about it where a man named Matt Patrick argued at
a December 14th meeting of the Texas electors that the Supreme Court was too cowardly to
deal with the issues in front of them.
He claimed to have heard a story from a Supreme Court staffer that Justice Roberts yelled
at fellow judges that they needed to dismiss the Texas attorney general's case, saying
that he didn't care about Bush versus Gore because there are riots going on and there
weren't in 2000.
Sure.
This man did not hear this story from a staffer.
He read it on right wing extremist Hal Turner's website.
Someone wrote Hal Turner anonymously claiming to be a Supreme Court staffer and told this
story, which Hal reported on December 12th, with absolutely no verification whatsoever.
There's also very strong reasons just on its face to not believe this story, like what
was posted and pointed out by Snopes, the fact that the Supreme Court justices have
not met in person for months because of COVID-19.
There is that.
There's not really a closed door meeting that this staffer, alleged staffer, could have
overheard.
Yeah.
But you could almost, you could almost buy John Roberts just because I'm sure, at least
in some small way, he has to resent Barrett and Kavanaugh because his job used to be so
much more solemn and like respected.
And now with Barrett and Kavanaugh on there, he's kind of an idiot.
Yeah.
You know, whenever you have Notorious on there, you know, it's like she gives you a gravitas
of the Supreme Court of like, look, this is what the Supreme Court can do.
And now, like, Barrett writes her decisions in crayon and it's like, I don't think you're
supposed to be here.
Yeah.
And I can't think of Kavanaugh without thinking of Squeeze.
Poor Judge Roberts.
Oh, I'm so sad for him.
I'm so sad for- Or maybe not.
But going down in history as a moron is going to be a real bummer.
Speaking of people who are going to go down in history as morons and are looked as such
now, David Icke is not on the show.
However, his son is.
Then I'll take calls for a couple of segments.
And then David Icke's son, who's quite the filmmaker, is going to be joining us with
some big breaking news.
I love these guys talking about like merits and like getting by based on what you do,
what you produce.
Bootstraps.
We're going to talk to David Icke's son.
We're going to talk to someone who- Someone who's such a great filmmaker that
you have to introduce him, not by his name, but as David Icke's son.
Yeah.
David Icke's son.
Wow.
Oh, bad.
That is sad.
Yep.
I would not like to be David Icke's son.
He seems to enjoy it.
Sure.
So Alex has noticed that Howard Stern has been doing some segments where they make fun
of Alex.
Sure.
They have been doing that for a while.
Oh.
And lately, I guess, Alex wants to talk about it.
I don't know.
This is really interesting because they are making fun of Alex.
Yeah.
It's very clearly mocking him.
Alex might have a different angle on it.
Interesting.
But Howard Stern still has a gigantic show, number one show on XM, probably just 5 million
people a day conservatively that tune in.
And he's up there every week now doing these puppet show videos.
They're very viral and send us a lot of new listeners.
So I don't want to attack Stern too much so he gets in trouble and can't make it.
I know Stern said he was a listener before and had me on a few times as a guest.
I was used to go on his network like once a month for years till somebody killed him.
And so I think overall, Stern's trying to actually warn people through the show.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Yeah.
Maybe you're wrong.
Oh, man.
So I think that Stern is like subtly trying to get Infowars messages out on his show by
making fun of me, and I don't want to get too much attention on it.
So he can't do it anymore.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What the fuck?
Oh, man.
Yeah, the character of Alex is largely like selling shit.
Yeah.
I need to, I like the way that he brings me more attention and doesn't actually affect
whether or not people believe my bullshit, but I don't like having to say nice things
about it.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
So Alex has got this idea about Justice John Roberts.
He's being a coward and all this.
He's yelling behind closed doors.
And actually, Alex knows why.
Well, that's Roberts getting a call from Holder that's got all the, and Obama that knows about
him and his kidnapped kids and how his adopted kids were kidnapped reportedly.
And so he's on a very short chain.
And so he's there going, we got to do this.
We got to do this.
And so he's a big problem.
I guess.
I guess there's blackmail, a good thing Alex threw in reportedly there.
Yeah.
Yeah, the Supreme court, notoriously a friend of the Obama administration.
Obama and Eric Holder are really coming through right now.
Yeah.
For...
Good timing.
I mean like what, what, why?
Why?
What are they doing?
What have they been doing?
They want to get the individual mandate back.
We're going to do it this time guys.
Now that we know his kids were stolen and that's why he's got them, Holder is ready
to pull the trigger now.
Yep.
That must be it.
You'd assume that a number of things would have gone differently if Eric Holder had some
blackmail on.
That would suggest that when Holder lost, he also was telling him, Hey, look, I'm planning
on losing this one.
So make it convincing, I guess.
Jesus.
Ridiculous.
Yeah.
So Alex takes more calls.
And, uh, this, uh, this one, this caller here, uh, wants a civil war.
If they don't do anything about this, I say, we need to just have a civil war because there's
no way we'll survive under Biden.
It's not about us.
It's about future generations.
We need to make moves now.
Sacrifice our lives.
Well, I know people are ready to fight and that's what scares the enemy.
My issue is, and thank you for the call, God bless you, Heather.
I wouldn't even call it a civil war.
And I mean, this is a foreign occupation with collaborators.
So this is a recapturing of America operation.
So I don't, I think, I think there are a lot of forces that aren't going to put up with
this.
The Chicom is pissing on us.
His problem seems to be semantics.
Yeah.
It sounds like that.
I do not appreciate how casual so many people are with banding civil war about.
It's pretty fucked up.
Yeah.
I think we need a civil war.
You know, just, that's one of those things you talk about in the, you know, we just lay
down our lives for the future generations.
We should all just die fighting against our fellow citizens.
Yeah.
Look, my problem is terminology.
Yes, exactly.
My problem with your...
Exactly.
That's the real problem.
I don't like Alex's rebuttal.
No, no, no.
It's not good.
It's not a civil war.
It's a recapturing.
It implies that he's okay with everything but the word.
Yes.
Pretty much.
So we get to David Icke's son and we're not going to listen to this interview.
I just have one clip because it's classic Alex.
They're not going to stop until we stand up as a race, as a species and stop them.
I mean, I've heard so many times through this.
I'm sure you have as well.
You've been asked the question is, when does this end?
And the simple answer to that is it ends when we stop doing it, ends when we stop allowing
them to control us.
You know, a bully...
Did you know that's basically a Thomas Everson quote.
He was asked, how bad will tyrants get?
How bad will they...
How far will they push?
And he said, exactly as far as you let them.
Oh God.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, totally.
Yeah.
Fake Thomas Jefferson quote.
Still doing the TJ.
Yeah.
Well, boy.
So we have one last clip here, Jordan, and this is a mic down clip because it is a return
to form.
Okay.
It is Alex talking over You Belong to the City.
Sure.
I'm excited.
Yeah.
We haven't heard a good one of those in a while.
And then I think it just ends perfectly.
This is like a nice little ride.
It's not his best rant over the song, but the coda to the end, much like the piano in
Layla.
Sure.
Great.
Makes the song.
Okay.
The only thing you need to know is that this
enemy attack is a desperate counter offensive.
We are winning.
Humanity is awakening.
Humanity holds the keys to human destiny.
And so as long as you don't submit and as long as you don't hate yourself and as long
as you know how amazing you are and that spark and that splinter of God's mind that created
you, there's nothing they can do against you.
As your life is closer to death, every minute becomes more valuable every second until you're
finally gone at the next level and then there's eternity and nothing but consciousness.
So you need to transcend that fear.
He's about to take over here in just a minute or so.
Kathy in Alaska, go ahead and thanks for holding.
Hello?
Oh, boy.
Oh, man.
Oh, just like Alex is like an angry Alan Watts, life ticks away and then there's just eternity
and then...
I don't know why I can't get this.
I just want now to hear Carl Sagan's pale blue dot speech, but over you belong to the
city.
Is there something really great about that song and Alex's weird rambling space nonsense?
It's just so good.
One day we will all fly away on Saturn's rings and there's nothing that evil can do about
it.
It is great and then just like the reality that comes crashing, crashing.
The music dies.
And then she's like long pause.
Hello?
It's just so great.
Are you going to keep playing You Belong to the City?
I wanted to talk over it.
So great.
I would probably listen to Alex talk over that song for like an hour on the treadmill.
It would get me there.
Yeah.
It would help me.
Oh, totally.
Yeah.
If he was just going to switch to Eckhart Tolle tapes, but only over music, just like
a banging soundtrack that he talks shit over, I would listen to that.
You referenced, I think it was on our last episode, the album of Paul Stanley song introductions.
Yes.
Yeah.
People let me get this off my chest.
I think it would be awesome if Alex would record just an hour of freeform improvisational
100%.
speeches over that sax.
Sweary Carrie basically did it.
Yeah.
I mean, she sang.
A little.
She sang, but yeah.
Yeah.
I would love to hear Alex do a William Shatner spoken word style album over You Belong to
the City.
The entire, that's the entire background.
Yeah.
Oh man.
Just constant.
That would win back a lot of hearts and minds, I think.
That would win a Grammy.
Open mic eagle is snubbed again, but AJ winds up in the top pop charts.
This is going to be his first step to Egon it.
He's going to get a, what would it be called, a delayed Oscar for his star turn in A Scanner
Darkly.
Naturally.
That cameo of him yelling into a bullhorn.
Yeah.
They're going to mistake his end game for Avengers End Game and give a retroactive Oscar
for that.
Okay.
You can have two Oscars.
Yeah.
And then he's going to get a Tony for his version of Hamilton.
Right.
But it's Jefferson.
I don't know.
It's all not true.
Jefferson's ripped.
It's shirtless the whole time.
And then he gets an Emmy for that time he was on The View.
Yeah.
I would give him an Emmy.
Egon.
Egon it.
So this, somebody is not going to get any awards for as the American Journal.
That show sucks.
I hate to say it because I got really excited.
I'll be honest.
Whatever like the David Knight firing happened I was very confused.
And then when I learned the next day that Alex was like really showing some go get em
spirit.
Yeah.
Some vim.
Some vigor.
I was pumped because I was like this could be really fun.
And instead he just complains about David Knight and takes boring calls like it's not
a good show.
Yeah.
It would actually be a better show with Harrison Smith hosting it.
Right.
Because he's boring as hell.
Yeah.
He's the guy who can just be a cardboard cutout with the callers.
Right.
That's what he is.
That's what Washington.
Yeah.
That guy has a little bit of competence though.
I'm not saying that he's just.
I think he's great.
Yeah.
He does what he does really well.
He's like you know the straight man in a comedy team where you think they're doing nothing
but it's.
Yeah.
No he's Dave Foley.
There's nuance to that nothing.
Yeah.
Harrison Smith would just be nothing.
He's not going to.
I think the power of this entire time was in yelling about conflicting reports about
David Knight.
Totally.
Just because he's petty and he's angry and wants to save face about firing old Greybeard.
Oh man.
I don't know.
It's weird.
I still am not convinced 100% that it was Steve but like his performance makes me think
it was.
Yeah.
And that's not good.
If I was 50-50 now I'm at 70-30.
But every time he denies it it goes up 10%.
You know?
That kind of thing.
Yeah.
And I guess it can't be financial because if Alex is doing this it would require the
crew.
Yeah.
That would be there for David anyway.
So I guess salary if David Knight was making a bunch.
I don't know.
Yeah.
I don't trust.
I don't trust any of this shit.
Well I mean Corsi whenever we found out how much fucking money he was making.
Yeah.
But he had juice.
Yeah that's true.
Corsi was a name.
But Knight had a long career there.
I assume he hopefully got a 3% a 3% raise every year.
I bet he started in 2009 at 5.15 an hour.
Give him a cola at least.
No benefits.
Cost of living man.
No no no.
No insurance.
There's a soda machine in the break room.
I yeah I don't know.
I would assume it's so hard to say.
I always think like man they must be getting paid a lot because this is degrading work.
Totally.
But I think if you're in you realize you can't go anywhere else.
Sure.
Now David Knight could.
Like we said he could go to Newsmax or OAN really easily and probably get a decent contract.
Sure.
But 2010, 2011 there wasn't anywhere that David Knight could go.
Maybe the blaze but that didn't exist that whole thing.
No no no.
He was once he once he walked in the door he was stuck for a while.
Yeah.
And David Knight so he wasn't going to cause enough problems elsewhere to justify a firing
until Steve Pajitnik says something batshit.
Yeah.
And he's like guys.
Another thing that was batshit.
We can't do this.
This is my final straw.
And it kind of makes you think because David Knight was saying that like the last straw
for him and Steve was the Las Vegas shooting.
Yeah.
And after that Steve didn't appear on Alex's show for quite a while.
Right right right right.
So it makes you think that maybe Alex listened to him at that point.
Yeah.
And since David was the one who was being like look this is really fucked up.
Well I mean.
We can't allow him to.
We do know that David has told him not to have certain people on in the past.
I know I heard Alex complain about that.
Exactly.
Yeah yeah yeah.
He was very offended.
Yeah.
And that's why Black Lives Matter made 10.6 billion dollars.
Exactly.
And we had to fire David Knight.
Yeah.
I think this story will unravel further in the coming days.
But since Alex is theoretically taking a week off that leaves us without anything for a
while.
So I was thinking maybe we should do a Project Camelot on Friday maybe.
Ooh that might be fun.
Or we'll figure out something.
We'll see.
I'm not gonna do a David Knight episode on Christmas Eve.
No no no no no.
That's not a present for anyone.
I know that not everybody celebrates all the same holidays but for those who do that would
be a shit present.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Sorry about that.
Don't want to do that to you.
No not interested.
Anyway we'll be back.
But until then we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yeah.
Or else on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledge underscore fight net.
Go to bed Jordan.
Or else whoa whoa whoa on Facebook.
We are Facebook.
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work.
Yeah.
Or else we'll be back.
But until then I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I'm not ending this show because of Steve Pachannik.
I swear.
I swear I'm not ending this show.
Right now we're about to finish this show and it has nothing to do with Steve Pachannik.
It just has everything to do with, look, Jordan has been tired for like the last 30 minutes
or so and he wants to end the show.
I would like to keep the show going.
You've got to fire Jordan.
I would like the show to keep going for another half hour.
Replace him with Melania.
But look, everybody needs a break.
Jordan looks like he's gonna have a heart attack.
He's ashen.
Anyway, finances are tight so we can't do another half hour.
It has nothing to do with Steve.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.