N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledgefight
knowledgefight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Shang, we are the bad guys, knowledgefight
Dan and Jordan, knowledgefight
Riddle her, riddle her, riddle her
Need, I need money
Andy and Kansas, Andy and, Andy and
Stop it, Andy and, Andy and Kansas
It's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding
Hello Alex, I'm a victim caller, I'm a huge fan
I love your work
knowledgefight
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're couple dudes, like to sit around, drink novelty beverages
and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are, Dan
Jordan
Dan!
I have a quick question for you
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today is something I've actually told you about already
and I'd like to continue my celebration of this
and that is Rolled Gold put out a flavor of pretzels
They had two different sort of limited time flavors
One's a zesty buffalo and I dare not try that
Oh yeah, of course not
Of course not
But the savory butter, I tried that, is so good
So good
It's so good
Is it like buttered popcorn, like that feeling where you get so much butter on that
It is right here, you can experience it, but don't chew into the mic
I will attempt to
Don't chew into the mic, I would like to get your reaction
It's so good
It's like a real, it's like a harsh butter
It's a lot of butter
It is a lot of butter
Yeah
It is maybe too much butter for me, but it is, it's good
Yeah, it's good
It's good, I have eaten half of one and I am full
You're done
It's very, very heavy
Yeah, I expected it to be like an almost non-existent flavor
Yeah, yeah
Like just a little suggestion of butter or something, but nah, it's in your face
Yeah
Well done Rolled Gold
No, when we were talking about this, I was like, oh, this sounds like a flavor-blasted goldfish
Yeah
That is exactly what it tastes like, it tastes like a regular rolled gold pretzel
And then they were like, what if we just covered it in shit?
What if we just
Just doused it
With butter
It does feel injected with butter
So what about you?
My bright spot this day is actually the original Final Fantasy VII
Ooh, not the remake
No, on Christmas they had like a half-off special, so it was like five bucks
So I was like, screw it
And I started playing it again, and I am so happy I did
And I'm happy that I did it after the remake, too
Is because once I got out of Midgar, I felt the same way I did the first time I played it
Which was just, oh, thank Christ, I'm out of that fucking place
Yeah, that's the feeling, I guess, the game wants you to feel
Totally
The moment you leave Midgar and you can see the entire world in front of you
And it shows you the world map, you're like, oh my god, I thought it was all gonna be in Midgar
Like, remake is great
Yeah
It's really great
But it's all there
But it's all in Midgar
Yeah, yeah
Like the moment you escape and you're like, it's just amazing
It really is beautiful
Well, you make a strong case for me to give that game a shot, and I may in the future
It's great, it really is just fucking great
I may, it's definitely a big blind spot for me, it's pretty much all of the Final Fantasy series
Yeah
Except for the remake, which you made me play, and I enjoyed
You did enjoy, right?
Yeah, yeah
That was pretty good
Well, I'm glad you're enjoying that
That is fantastic
Good way to end, wrap up the year for you
Absolutely
So, we did not have an episode on Friday
And I'm gonna say, I think it's probably good that we didn't
I hope everyone, you know, celebrates Christmas, had a nice Christmas
Everybody celebrates other holidays
Have a great holiday time
Or if you just don't celebrate anything, hope you had a good weekend
I felt it would be emotionally draining for us to do an episode on Friday
That was covering what Alex was doing
Yeah
And that was not taking his week off that he said he was going to take
Yeah, the week he said he was going to take off, instead he did not take off
He did not take off, and uh, because kind of just not having a fun time
Not surprising
Um, I didn't watch all of his content
Turns out firing everybody made it very hard for me to take a day off
Whoops, my only friend is Harrison Smith
This sucks
I'm fucked
Yeah, um, I thought that there would be a little bit of schadenfreude in it
I think there would be a little bit of us wallowing around in the mud watching a guy be miserable
It'd be great, yeah
I mean, there's some fun to that
We like watching Alex be miserable
I know, but we did that already
That's true
We already did that with the first American Journal episode
Yeah, that's true, that is true, there is that
It just felt almost repetitive and not like it was going to bring anything new to the table
And I worried that once we came to Monday, what would we have to cover?
Totally
Like maybe there would be a Project Camelot episode we could have done for Friday
But if Alex actually had taken that week off, we'd need that for Monday
True
Or whatever
Could have been dangerous
Yeah, and so it left me kind of in a lurch of what to do
And so, you know, we took that break and here we are back on Monday
And I think that this is going to be a slightly different episode
Because we're just going to be covering a special report that Alex put out
Okay
And he put it out on Christmas
There's hatchet throwing that's implied
Implied hatchet throwing? Ah, that's a little disappointing
Yeah, no, there's no hatchet throwing
I need explicit hatchet throwing to get the fuck out
No, nothing shall ever top 2018 Christmas Eve
No, that's too good
Um, we are going to be talking on this episode about
Alex's immediate response to the bombing in Nashville
Right
That's going to be what we take a little time to discuss on this episode
Because I think it's, you know, it's in that vein of things that I think are really important
to understand about Alex
And as we go into 2021
I'm Dan, this is 2021
Oh, yay!
Now I'm confused
I'll have to figure something out for actual 2021
How's that one? That's my new catchphrase
I'm into it
That's the demon coming through the portal
Exactly, yeah, yeah
Um, I feel like as we get into that year
One of the things I really want to stress and really want to redouble my efforts on
Is looking at these things that like are really actually important about Alex
Yeah, okay
It's always fun to make fun of him breaking down in the studio
Sure
Always fun
Always fun to laugh at like Alex with guns
Right
But those are things that are almost trivial in a certain way
Right, we do still have a job to do
Right
Yes
And I think that this is part of that
This is part of like looking back at that focus
Yeah, yeah, yeah
And so we'll get down to business on that
But before we do, I'd like to take a moment to say thank you to the folks
Some folks who've signed up and are supporting the show
Great idea
So first, Amber Z, thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Amber
Next, Josh O, thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you, Josh
Thank you
Next, Bry F, thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Bry
Next, Amanda M, thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, Amanda
Thank you
No Last Initial Lindsay
Thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Lindsay Lohan
Could be
Until mentioned otherwise
Yeah, until we prove it's not
The star of Herbie Fully Loaded
Lindsay Lohan
We got parrot trapped, Dad
Next, Emma M, thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Emma
Thank you! Next, Nick S. Nick S, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk!
Thank you very much, Nick.
Thank you! And then finally, I'd like to say thank you to a couple of people who donated on Elevated Love and we appreciate that very much.
So, Pyrae, thank you so much, you are now a technocrat, and I say this with disdain, you are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate, that's fantastic. Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
Alright, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, alright?
Let's just get down to business. We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good? My neck is freakishly large. I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much, Pyrae, and thank you so much, I say this with disdain.
Yes, thank you very much to the both of you.
If you're out there listening and thinking, hey, I enjoy this show, I'd like to support these gents,
you can do that by going to our website, knowledgefight.com, clicking the button that says support the show, we would appreciate it, or...
Or what you could do, if you are feeling like your generous spirit is oppressed by a massive global corporation,
literally sucking the life from the planet, then what you should do is escape from that place,
take your generosity to, I don't know, Junin, and then give it to a local charity or bail fund in, specifically, Junin.
Sounds good.
I would say so.
Alright, so, Jordan, I have a special report for you here, released on Christmas.
I've not cut anything out of the special report that Alex is playing, except for one point where he plays the audio of the bomb going off in Nashville.
It doesn't really add anything interesting to the episode to hear an explosion, and the audio mix is terrible, it is so loud.
It would just blow out people's ears.
It does make me think of that Bill Cooper episode, though, the day after the Oklahoma City bombing.
In that episode, Bill made a point to play the audio of the explosion, and there's kind of echoes here,
except for Bill was doing it dramatically.
Bill played it repeatedly, and kind of almost like a chorus, and then he would say something in the middle.
It was a call and response to the bomb.
Alex just plays it, and it's very loud.
All I've done here is I've just cut every time it's clear that Alex is doing a different take.
Because, you know, the audio shifts slightly, and you can tell that Alex just ran out of steam, and they're like,
So he did a couple of takes? Well, that's better than we've seen in the past.
True, true. Let's do another sentence. Try another sentence, Alex.
Yeah, try it one more time.
I get the sense he was recording from home, so maybe his wife is a better producer than Rob Dew.
You can't say that!
Oh, God damn it, honey.
So here's where we start. Here's the beginning.
Today, in the early morning hours of Christmas, a large truck bomb housed inside an RV
exploded outside the AT&T main communications building in Nashville.
The individual, organization, or group behind the attack went out of their way
to warn the public to get away before the bomb detonated by broadcasting for more than ten minutes
that there was a bomb on board the vehicle that was about to detonate.
911 also received a call claiming that gunshots had been fired in the area minutes before the explosion.
The FBI is now reporting that human remains have been found in the debris at the blast site.
So you can already tell those are multiple takes?
Yeah, the 911 cut was almost Paul Joseph Watson-esque, of coming in before the breath is finished.
The hole was cut in the middle of a sentence, though.
Yeah, so infuriating. I hate it.
So on Christmas Day, in case people did not hear about this,
a bomb was detonated in an RV parked in downtown Nashville.
At the time of our recording, one of the working theories that people have
is that it's possible that the person was targeting the AT&T building,
which was quite nearby the blast site.
This, as a possible motive for an act of domestic terror, makes complete sense.
If you were going to go through the trouble of carrying out a bombing,
you would likely want whatever damage you do to have maximum impact.
AT&T's operations in Nashville are housed at that building,
so the potential disruption you could cause by damaging that would be huge,
as we've seen from the fallout of the bombing itself,
with some people still being without phone service today as we're recording.
This is all a very tragic turn of events,
and my heart goes out to the people affected by this act.
Thankfully, there weren't any civilian casualties,
and the human remains that were found there,
literally right before we started recording,
I saw it was being reported that they have matched the DNA
to the person they suspect is the bomber.
There's a lot of stuff that's on my own still about this event,
but there are definitely some fair assumptions you can make about it.
Obviously, this wasn't an accident, so there was an intention behind this bombing.
It was clearly meant to be a spectacle and something that would be traumatic,
given that it was planned for Christmas morning,
which is a very solemn time for many in this country.
My gut tells me, based on these pieces of information,
that this was an ideological act.
But who knows what that ideology is at this point?
Right. I mean, it's unfortunate that the vibe I'm getting from this whole thing
is Vietnamese monks self-immolating,
but because they believe that the Laotians are going to sneak in through the earth,
where it's like, yes, you are making a statement.
This is a problem, though. This is an issue.
I'm not sure I quite follow what you're saying.
5G isn't going to hurt anyone. Do you know what I'm saying?
Well, but I don't know if that's the motivation either.
No, no, no, totally.
That's making an assumption there.
No, of course. That's why I said the vibe I'm getting,
not like, I know for a fact that this is why you did that.
But that's the general feeling that people are passing around.
Some people are speculating on that.
What I'm trying to clearly delineate here is the idea of what is responsible speculation and what is not.
Oh, totally.
Speculating that this was motivated by some sort of an ideology
based on the actions, the circumstances, responsible speculation.
Sure.
Claiming that you know exactly what it is or choosing what you want the target you think it might have been.
And then why would they do that?
Sure.
That's not great.
No, totally.
That's not grounded.
And I think that, you know, I see that possibility.
Yeah, sure.
It could turn out that more information comes out and he was someone who was worried about 5G.
Yeah, no, I don't know by any stretch.
And nor am I making a claim that that's what's going on by any means.
But from what I understand so far, it does have that feeling of somebody who is,
I guess, sacrificing their own life for something they believe in.
And chances are, if you're going after AT&T.
And if you unpack that a little bit more, you're still making a giant assumption.
Oh no, I'm making a massive assumption.
Yeah.
And I don't think that, you know, that is substantiated yet.
100% agree.
It could in the future, and again, this is the issue with the wet concrete.
Right.
You gotta respect the wet concrete until it dries because otherwise you just fuck it up.
Yeah, totally.
It's a point that I've made a lot in that Alex Jones knows that his business model really only works
and is powered by uncertainty.
The moment that the cement is wet and he can write his initials on there before it dries,
that is the time he knows he has to go to work.
And naturally, on Christmas Day, when he's already failing to take this week off,
he records a special report about the Nashville bombing because on some possibly subconscious level,
he knows that if he waits until his show on Sunday, there's a chance that more details will be known by then
and it'll be too late for him to profit off this tragedy.
We watch this unfold in the aftermath of the Boston Marathon bombing,
and it seems kinda likely that this is gonna be another big push for him now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
A couple of things are different, though, which make the end of 2020 a lot more complicated for someone like Alex.
For one, there are tons of people running around online competing for access to that wet cement.
Alex doesn't have exclusive control over the paranoid conspiracy space anymore,
so there are other people who are equally able to put their imprint on stories before the information becomes public.
The other major difference is that people keep suing Alex now.
In the past, he was a lunatic yelling that everyone just thought, eh, it's best to leave him alone.
But he went too far, and finally some people stood up to his bullying.
That had a domino effect of people not being afraid to burden him with lawsuits when he defames them.
And that has a chilling effect on someone's ability to defame people freely.
It should.
Yeah.
So now Alex knows that there are some limitations to what he legally can speculate about without consequences.
Alex knows that, you know, that this is just the reality of his life.
Meanwhile, these other people who want to get access to that wet cement, they're mostly anonymous weirdos online.
They're operating fake-named alias QAnon accounts.
They don't have to worry about being sued because they're essentially internet phantoms.
They aren't bound by the same fear of consequence that Alex has,
so they're free to speculate and craft conspiracies in ways Alex is not, but he used to be.
Yeah, and he can't direct it.
He now has to, if something gets too popular, he has to assimilate it instead of being able to kind of push the narrative in any direction that he would prefer.
Now he's getting pushed.
Well, I think even in the past it was even more complicated that he was assimilating and pushing simultaneously.
Sure, sure, sure.
You know, co-opting hot online trends and then making them, you know, match the Info Wars narrative.
It's too obvious now.
Well, that's the thing. He could straddle the line between the part of the internet that nobody goes on anymore
and then come back to the real world as being that kind of almost bridge between them.
And now the crazy part is the main internet, so what are you going to do?
Yeah, it's all over the place.
Yeah, it's a mess.
It's great stuff. I think we're doing awesome.
So that's one of the reasons why I decided if we're doing this episode it'd probably be good to talk about Alex's immediate response.
Because that's the concrete wet moment, let's see what he can do in this new Info War battle space.
Because it's different now. The elements have changed from when he would be able to be the king of the roost.
Yeah, and it'll be interesting to see how the story changes tomorrow, and we'll have to do a completely different episode.
Sure, but it's still important to check in on this.
Totally.
So here Alex goes on.
Who would have a motive to carry out an attack like this?
Could it be a former employee or engineer angry at AT&T?
Could it be an organization or group, a terrorist organization, angry at AT&T for their politics for surveilling the public?
Or perhaps owning the propaganda outlet CNN?
Rest assured, these are the first questions that FBI and ATF agents are asking right now on the ground in Tennessee.
So if you notice, the two possibilities that Alex provides for potential entities with a motive seem to imply that he's sympathetic to the bombing.
Yeah! Yeah!
It's immediately like, maybe it's someone who's mad that AT&T spies on everybody illegally.
Like, that's weird. That's really weird.
I mean, I can see it.
No, no, all the reasons. I'm not saying those with the same glee he kind of seems to have as to like,
here are the reasons that I would bomb AT&T is kind of what he's saying.
Yeah, that's the feeling that it gives.
Wait, what? AT&T owns CNN? That's why? That's what you've decided?
This is weird.
Let's think of the reasonable reasons to bomb AT&T off the top of my head, the ones that I appreciate.
CNN, obviously.
Yeah, it's got to be CNN.
It's just strange to me that immediately, as this special report opens, the options that he's presenting for why the person did what they did,
like their motivation, are identical beliefs to his.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's strange.
Totally.
He's identifying with and sympathizing with the actor in this case.
Maybe he blew up AT&T because they own Brian Stelter. I don't know.
Maybe they specifically chose Brian. Was there a note that said,
Brian Stelter looks like a pedophile? Because I feel like that might tie back to me somehow.
Stelter may come up later.
Of course he does.
So, Alex, he's planted this kernel of like AT&T owns CNN, and so then he goes from there.
In the summer of 2018, CNN deployed a new talking point that was then adopted by almost every other cable news
or broadcast news organization in the United States that Donald Trump, by criticizing the press's attacks on him,
was going to trigger terrorist attacks on their facilities and the murder of journalists.
They hammered it hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of times with no proof.
So what's going on now is that Alex is trying to implant the idea that CNN said Trump's rhetoric would lead to a rise in attacks on journalists
in preparation for this Christmas Day RV bomb against AT&T's Nashville headquarters since AT&T owns CNN,
even though everyone knows that the CNN center is in Atlanta. This is stupid.
Yeah, I think there have already been plenty of other examples you could point to of their saying that rhetoric increases violence.
Oh yeah, or you could just go check out the US Press Freedom Tracker, which is a little service that documents attacks on journalists in the United States.
In 2018, there were 35. In 2019, 34. Little progress, one less. In 2020, there have been 274.
I feel like that's a jump.
Yeah. Some of this is civilians assaulting the press, but a considerable chunk are police carrying out these assaults.
So surprising!
It's hard not to see this kind of ripple effect as being part of Trump's rhetoric, where he labels the press the enemy of the people
and also constantly talks about how police, you know, if they rough people up, they shouldn't get in trouble.
That's great!
If I were a cop, I think I might get the sense that the president is trying to subtly tell me to hit a journalist, and he'll look the other way.
Yeah. It's a good thing that not all mayors agree. Oh no, all mayors agree that you should hit people. That's great.
Anyway, there's no need for an RV bomb at the AT&T building to pay off the fears that Trump's rhetoric would lead to a rise in danger for journalists.
That argument could be easily made without it.
So this doesn't even really satisfy in terms of like, oh, so you're going back two years to something that you yelled about about CNN being the predictive element of...
That's really thin.
If you go back to the MIAC report, you can see that there has been no right-wing violence since then, and that thing was crazy.
Yeah, thankfully I exposed it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I saved everybody.
Thankfully, Alex is a careful man, so he wants to make a quick clarification.
To be crystal clear, InfoWars is not saying that CNN is behind the attacks.
What we are saying is a known fact that they are the main mouthpiece of the criminal elements of the deep state and shadow government that are battling to recapture control of the United States.
So the clarification is that Alex isn't saying that CNN is behind the bombing, just that they're a mouthpiece for the evil demon globalists who are trying to salvage control of the country.
If you're following his point, he's saying that he doesn't want CNN to sue him.
No.
His theory is that the evil globalists carried out the bombing to retain control of the United States.
Sounds right.
And CNN set the stage for it by saying Trump's rhetoric was a danger to journalists.
Thank you for clarifying that it was not CNN who was behind the bombing.
It seems like they're still in on it based on your theory.
A RICO case could probably get him, but I don't think they're behind it, Dan.
In this next clip, we see another characteristic of Alex's bullshit, and that is the, you know, we've seen this in pretty much every single thing that he calls a false flag.
He's like, well, there's a chance it's real. Maybe. Tiny.
But he likes the reasons the bomber may have done it.
There's a one percent chance it's real, that kind of thing. He says that with everything.
It is entirely possible that a lone wolf or small group carried this operation out for other reasons.
But when you look at the history and the motive and the background, and who stands to gain from this, and all the media pre-conditioning and programming, this thing reeks as a possible deep state false flag operation.
So it's a possible deep state false flag operation at this point.
That's nice. That's nice.
Let's wait till three minutes later in the special report.
I was going to say, the suing does seem to have a chilling effect on the first statement.
I don't know how well it carries over to statements two and following.
Yeah, yeah. It takes you longer to get into it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You gotta warm up to the...
It's almost like if you say it first, then the rest of them don't count, you know?
Like I said this the first time, so you know that I still mean it on the other ones.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So this is really the main thrust, I believe, of what he's saying.
Is that two years ago, CNN did all this shit, showing it's proof that they were planning to do this now. Which is weird.
In August and October of 2018, I went to the airwaves to desperately warn the people
that MSM was clearly preconditioning the population to accept that when terror attacks that they said were imminent
hit mainstream media, that it was indeed the fault of whatever patsy they produced
who would then take credit for Donald Trump, the nationalist and populist movement.
I had seen this exact same rhetoric before, right before the 1995 Oklahoma City bombing
that was then blamed on the Patriot movement and Rush Limbaugh.
Right, so...
Well, had they not done it, I don't think we would have blamed them for it.
Well, there is that matter.
You're not going to get anywhere with Alex on that line of thinking.
Yeah, I don't think I'm going to win that one.
I don't see the connective tissue here. Even as a conspiracy, I think this is soft.
This is really soft.
I think the softest part of it is you are telling me that CNN is a multi-billion dollar a year corporation
and they spent two years planning this bombing, this bombing.
I feel like the hardest part to plan about this was the AV system that shouted,
there's a bomb coming!
It doesn't make sense.
In terms of timing, in terms of motive, in terms of method...
I guess CNN did finally win the war on Christmas. Is that what he's going for?
If Alex's whole thing is that these false flags are supposed to create shock and terror and horror,
then why would there be a warning to get away from it?
Wouldn't the globalists want to kill people? They don't care about human life.
That doesn't make any sense. This doesn't match any of his M.O.'s.
You know what it felt like listening to this? It's just trying to fit a square peg into a round hole.
It just doesn't work. This is grim.
I think this one might be just too confusing to make a good conspiracy theory out of.
Confusing can be done.
It can be done.
It requires finesse. It requires a little bit of trying.
Alex is not ready to try anymore.
There's a certain part of this one that's just so fucking...
Everyone is not scared. Everyone is kind of scratching their head going like,
Why?
I think people are scared, and rightfully.
You think so?
I think it's a very traumatic event.
Oh, totally.
I think some people were hurt. It caused a lot of destruction.
I don't think that it scares people in the same way some other, much more casualty events have.
But I do still think that people see something like that and are scared.
No, I apologize for minimizing the feelings of the people who are directly affected by it.
I meant more the people who would be affected by the conspiracy theories.
Obviously, I'm not going to be like,
Eh, whatever. You got blown up. No big deal.
This, though, is such a thing where all of these Q conspiracies and all of this stuff seem to be swirling together.
But even then, the traction is just more like,
I guess we got to wait until we find out why the guy actually did it.
This one seems tough on Alex. It seems like he's, I don't know,
The way I would describe it is he's trying to walk a little bit fast outside a pool.
His feet are wet.
Holding scissors.
He's just worried about slipping.
You know, it doesn't have traction.
It doesn't.
No.
It's a weird one.
This is a really weird situation.
So now we reach the point in the special report, which is maybe like 20 seconds after he said maybe it's real,
where he definitively says that it was the deep state.
Okay.
Within days of the Supreme Court of Michigan declaring that Governor Whitmer was nothing more than a dictator
and that her COVID lockdowns were illegal,
suddenly the FBI busted a terror cell of militia that had been playing to kidnap her.
It came out a week later that the terror cell was led by two FBI informants
and the whole thing had been a giant setup.
That is a smaller microcosm of what the deep state does when they actually carry out larger terror attacks
like we just witnessed in Nashville, Tennessee.
Oh boy.
So to be clear, I'm not taking Alex out of context at all.
No, that one pretty much says it.
He's not spitballing.
He's not asking questions.
He just literally said that the Tennessee bombing was carried out by the deep state.
It's in the context of his meaningless rambling, but it's still a definite statement.
He's not suggesting it's possible that the deep state did this.
He's explicitly arrived at that conclusion.
And that is being put to the audience.
Also, the Michigan Supreme Court did not declare Whitmer a tyrant
and that was not a fake kidnapping plot.
No, no, no it was not.
You're going to look me in the eye and tell me that the devil said to these people,
Hey, no death.
Yeah, yeah, that's part of the devil's trickiness.
Hey, listen, minor injuries only.
So you might be asking like, what, why, you know?
I would be asking myself that.
What does the globalist gain through this?
What do the globalists gain?
Agreed.
This country is in an existential battle fighting for its very existence
against a chai comm led globalist takeover.
And with 25 days until the attempted installment and coronation
of their agent, Joe Biden, the mainstream media is on the ropes.
People hate them.
They don't believe them.
They don't trust them.
And as massive evidence comes out of collective election fraud carried
by the deep state and their cohorts, the Democratic Party,
the system needs something to turn themselves into victims.
This is designed to silence the American people and their opposition
to the great reset and the huge COVID lockdown.
Really?
That is meant to be permanent if Joe Biden gets into power.
This just seems-
I just don't buy it.
No.
This is stupid.
Isn't it strange, though, like how uninspiring, uninspired this is?
Yeah.
Just like-
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Really?
Yeah.
Come on, man.
That was to make the globalists look like victims?
What is that?
That doesn't even make sense.
That doesn't fit what's going on at all.
No.
You know, like if this was the Boston bombing,
then you can sell me on something like that.
But this is just so different.
It's just so different.
And you can't say the same thing about something that's this different.
And what I don't understand is like the Christmas angle isn't even in it for us.
Yeah, right?
There's no attack on Christmas.
There's no war on Christmas.
Oh, that seems so easy.
It's deep in his rhetoric.
He thinks there's a war on Christmas.
There's a literal bombing on Christmas.
Yeah, but I think he's still of the opinion that when it comes out,
the full story, it's going to be somebody more on the,
I hate the people who have the war on Christmas side.
So he probably thinks preemptively, I don't know if I can pull that one off.
That may be. That may be.
All I know is that Alex is a man with a deep archive.
And he has great employees working for him who can pull up every time
that he said that false flags are coming.
Sure.
I have been on record dozens of times in the last month saying,
we are now in the season of the false flag.
We are now in the season of the establishment loading up truck bombs
to bomb themselves, to be victims.
And I have our archivist looking for it right now.
But thanks to Media Matters, George Soros' organization,
we have two examples from two years ago where I warned and foreshadowed
what we now happen to see unfolding.
So he does not have these, I guess the archivists are working on it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They're working on it.
Harrison Smith is coming in on Christmas to try and find these clips.
It's tough.
There's a lot of our episodes to go through to find those clips.
That's true.
So yeah, Harrison's got to figure that out.
Yeah, yeah.
And instead they just Googled.
Have you got an email yet?
They just Googled on Media Matters.
And searched for times that Alex has said fucked up things.
Oh man, it's really nice of them to keep track for them.
Yeah.
So here is the clips that Alex plays from Media Matters of him
predicting what we saw.
Yeah.
And ladies and gentlemen, this is about taking down America and Trump
and the recovery and the entire free press.
So I'm telling you, like night follows day, the stage terror attacks
are coming on big tech, government buildings, mainstream media.
All the stars will be gone that day.
All the stelters will be gone that day.
All the Lester Holtz will be gone.
And they are going to drive a truck bomb or something into a daycare
at CNN or ABC or something and have people shooting everybody, you name it.
You can see the pre-programming and say, see, the hate did this.
The hate did this while they cover up Antifa and the attack on Scalise
and the attack on Rand Paul and all the calls to kidnap Barron and rape him.
And we've got to get this out to Trump.
We've got to let him know because Trump's not calling for violence.
When they attack Trump and lie about it, he says, you're fake news.
You're lying.
I'm not a racist.
I love Mexicans, whatever.
They go, oh, you're a Nazi.
You're calling for violence.
Blood on your hands.
Same thing with me editing stuff out of context to build this.
They got big tech.
They got the media.
They got the Democrats.
They got Warner reportedly running it all ready to quarterback.
This whole time could happen today, tomorrow, next month.
But understand, here's the big emergency.
These are only probing attacks to shut it up and to test the public.
Will they buy that Soros and Hillary and Bill and Obama and CNN are poor victims?
This is introducing them as the targets.
They can whine and moan and predict if Trump doesn't stop.
You're going to get us all killed.
And then in rolls that big ass truck bomb into CNN Center Atlanta.
Boom.
All the execs will be off on a special meeting that day.
Most of CNN crew would have never expected they'll get hit.
They'll even take out a large group of their top people.
Yeah, they're getting ready to hit themselves and hit themselves hard.
MSNBC, ABC, they're going to hit themselves.
So I have a couple of reasons why I don't take anything that Alex played there as sincere
or a meaningful prediction about what actually happened on Friday.
The first is that Alex literally says the target would be CNN Center in Atlanta.
And it would happen when Brian Stelter and Lester Holt aren't there because they would have advance warning.
Which we've seen played out.
Stelter and Holt do not work in Tennessee.
Alright.
The second major reason that this rings hollow to me is that the specific of Alex mentioning a truck bomb in a daycare center,
that's not meaningful in terms of a prediction.
That's hearkening back to Oklahoma City.
That's very specifically a part of right wing terrorist history.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a huge part of the mythology and zeitgeist of the patriot world,
them being torn between celebrating Timothy McVeigh and pretending he was a patsy.
The third reason I take issue with this prediction is because these clips were from two and a half years ago.
This article that Alex is playing, a Media Matters clip from, is from August 2018.
So it just stretches any kind of credulity to imagine that the globalists are broadcasting their signals,
pushing the programming so hard that Alex picked up on them,
then waited 28 months and carried out a stage bombing that didn't kill anyone
at the building that's owned by CNN's parent company but isn't really associated with CNN itself.
Correct.
This is thin soup.
Yeah, I think what he should be doing, actually I think what we'll see tomorrow or Tuesday,
or when he starts hitting the ground rolling on this,
this is a practice run, right?
You have to call this a practice run before they actually do the real stuff.
You mean like the bombing?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's what Alex has to do.
I thought you meant this video is a practice run.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This video is him practicing trying to make a conspiracy out of this and he's whiffing.
And he accidentally put it, he posted it, this was his daily affirmations, he's just talking to a mirror.
It is all fake.
Yeah, exactly.
So that's possible, but also the fourth reason I reject this bullshit is because Alex constantly predicts false flags
and bombings and shit that never happens.
If I wanted to, I could put together a giant compilation of him doing just that.
And it turns out, I do want to.
How's Chicago doing? Are we a giant whole?
Well, I did want to do this actually.
Usually I'll just say I could do it, but I actually did it this time.
So here's a super cut of Alex making predictions of false flags coming and calling random events fake.
This could have been so much longer. It's six minutes.
It's six minutes?
And it could have been so much longer, but I feel like that's already trying our audience's patience.
That's way too hard.
Breaking in, we were following this earlier just an hour ago.
And the stock market was only down 600 points, which is still big.
It dropped 1600 points today, which is one of the biggest drops ever.
And then rebounded 800 points, but it's still 800 points down.
Doug, you talk about deep state operations.
You talk about Goldman Sachs, JP Morgan, they've been working against the president.
Even though they've had record profits, they openly cheerlead for communist China.
This is the type of craziness we've been saying will come.
Evidence is mounting that the mega fires in Australia are being orchestrated by multinational forces
to clear out key corridors for future development and for light rail going in that's being financed by the communist Chinese.
They are intending to remove Trump one way or another.
And then they're going to trigger a civil war saying right wingers blew stuff up when Trump gets removed.
They're going to truck bomb and mass shoot and say we did it.
When they remove Trump, use that for a total clamp down.
The economy is going to implode.
There's going to be homeless running around crazy everywhere.
All they got to do is have the Chinese who supply 90 percent of the opiates cut those off for about a month.
And it's going to look like a zombie apocalypse.
And remember, oh, Alex, you're a fairmonger.
They'll never try to get our guns.
And I said, you watch.
There's going to be mass shootings.
There's going to be false flags.
A month before Sandy Hook.
I said, this is the season. Get ready. I'm seeing them roll out the propaganda now beforehand.
And so this is the type of time you're going to see bigger false flag event type things happen.
But I can tell you right now, ladies and gentlemen, that communist forces, that's what Antifa is in the Soros funded, Democrat Party funded combine,
are planning assaults on new police stations and federal buildings tonight all across the United States.
And when the Austin police bring photos and video of this to the mayor's office, they are told you are to stand down.
I've seen the photos. I've seen the videos. I've seen the internal memorandums.
This is happening for sure.
We knew Governor Northam was going to try to declare an emergency.
We knew he was going to try to hype it up like people with guns are coming to get them.
And so he'll have to have a law enforcement response.
Then they stage a false flag or they provocateur an action, Jesse Smollett style, but on steroids.
And then they say, look, the gun owners are the evil terrorists or the white supremacists.
And they run the same operation we saw the Democrat controlled state police did a couple of years ago in Charlottesville.
And they have launched more and more escalations.
And the next escalation is assassinating the president or staging giant terror attacks and blaming it on the right wing patriots.
And they're going to do it.
And are we just going to sit here while the Clintons and the Obamas load up a fuel truck again and blow up a federal building?
Are we just going to sit here while they go and shoot up a black church with some mental patient?
They got wound up on psychotropics and amphetamines and amnesiacs in a hotel room right now.
They got brainwashed loony tuners everywhere ready to go.
They punch a couple buttons.
It's over. There's no way to stop their false flags unless the leadership of the globalist is dealt with.
You know what? It's real, folks.
There's nothing fake here.
In fact, I'm so damn real, I can't stand it.
I sometimes want to control myself.
I sometimes want to act a different way.
I can't. I can't control myself.
I'm a maniac. It's all real. I'm totally real.
I've never lied to you.
I compulsively tell the truth.
And these people out there, they can't stand that, you see.
And they also don't like the fact they can't scare me.
And they don't like the fact they can't scare you.
But let me just tell you.
I've studied war propaganda and how the globalists do stuff.
Folks, I think they are probably...
I need to go to your calls, but I need to probably do a special report so I don't cut into the main broadcast time on your calls.
But I think they're getting ready to do a false flag and blame me and they might kill me.
And I'm only saying that to be dramatic.
And if that happens, I'm not a loser. I'm a winner.
I don't want to die, by the way. I'm not going to commit suicide.
But you know what I mean.
I think they could do a nuclear false flag dirty bomb or nuclear attack.
Oh, don't put it past them to kill Trump.
It takes out Trump. Exactly.
It takes out Trump. They blame it on patriots or they blame it on Trump's negotiations with North Korea.
They could say it's North Korea fighting back against...
Or Iran.
Or Iran, exactly.
But they take out Trump and they take out 200,000 Americans at the same time and then they blame conservatives.
And then they use that to blacklist all conservatives, all speech online and any dissenting views.
This is the plan.
This is the plan. They have to silence you, Alex. And they have to silence me before...
Exactly. They wouldn't be taking the risk to shut us down when it wakes everybody up with the Streisand effect if they weren't at a gut level.
I know. I think well before the election, they're going to hit us. And I agree.
I think it's going to be a biological or a nuclear event.
But I think they want nuclear to kill POTUS.
If they nuke a city which is in their plans, it's in their cards.
If they nuke a city and say Patriots did it, you know the hammer just dropped.
And they're going to try to come arrest me, you name it.
I know these murderers.
Just like two people are seen running away from the scene in Sandy Hook.
And then you find a guy shot in the head inside.
You go have a drill. You shoot your mental and patient patsy in the head.
You get out.
I mean this is the oldest. This is a false flag.
And so the next attack, a bioweapon ten times worse?
A nuke in D.C. during the State of the Union?
I mean Congress shouldn't be in session in the buildings.
The President should never be in D.C. now.
He should be moving around the country.
I mean we're in a total war, people.
And if this is proven to not be a false flag, which I think has gone from 1% chance to maybe 5% chance,
I will eat my hat and apologize and be very pleased.
Please eat your hat.
Yeah, please eat that hat.
Yeah, I feel like that was a little bit long, but the reason I made it that long is because I want to drive home this point.
Yeah.
The point is made.
I'm pretty sure it's driven home.
Yeah.
This is what he does.
This is not a prediction that Alex is making.
It's an obsession and a centerpiece of his worldview.
On some level, he knows that his political alignment is just full of cosplaying militia weirdos who lust after the opportunity to commit acts of violence that they can justify as being necessary
to water the tree of liberty or whatever.
He knows that, so the only real options he can do, he can either applaud terrorist acts, domestic terrorist acts, which is tough, or you pretend they don't exist.
If you go the first option, it's a little risky.
Eventually you'll end up ostracizing yourself, even from the pseudo-acceptable world of the fringe.
The second option just requires a mantra you drill into your audience.
In this case, if there's an act of terrorism that looks like it could have been carried out by someone who believes the same shit as me, it's fake until proven otherwise.
It's the evil nebulous group I'm fighting that's just trying to make me look bad, so ignore it and keep pushing deeper into the fanatical world that accepts, rationalizes, and excuses this kind of activity.
And that has nothing to do with what the actual end result of what this event was.
It doesn't matter, Alex's response is going to be to call it fake.
So it was always going to be a fake.
On the off chance that it's something that could implicate his beliefs.
Totally.
And that's just, it's very boring.
It is boring, and it's disheartening.
Yes.
It's really disheartening, and it's unfair.
You can set your watch by right-wing terrorism and so he gets to run interference whenever he wants because it's going to happen, you know?
Yeah.
It's so fucking annoying.
Yeah, and at its core, the narrative here, this false flag narrative, the way that Alex uses it is just a way of weaponizing and making money off denial.
Yep.
That's just what you're doing, and it's, like I said, when I say it's boring, I mean it's really boring when you look at it in the long view.
Yeah, totally.
You look at his career and recognize all this dumb shit you keep saying is researched, I study the globalists, I know their patterns, and then every fucking pattern is wrong.
Nothing ends up happening that he says is going to happen.
And then you, but it's not boring.
The trick itself is not boring.
Right.
The trick itself is possibly very dangerous.
Yeah.
Because the first time you're exposed to the idea of a false flag and that it's not just something that only exists in fiction.
Sure.
Like, it does make you think, like, oh my god, everything could be.
Yeah.
And that's the danger of that tripwire Alex can set out in front of you.
It's the same thing that happened to Rogan.
When Rogan talks to Alex about the only things that he thinks Alex has been right about, it's like, oh, you told me that agent provocateurs exist.
So, like, yes, okay, great, your mind was blown by that.
Yeah.
And the mind-blowing event was used for malicious purposes.
And I think that Alex knows on some level, no matter how stupid this conspiracy is about this bombing on Christmas,
no matter how lacking in connective tissue it is, no matter how sad it looks to look at, it might blow someone's mind.
Yeah.
There might be someone that all they need to hear is a denial of some reality that's in their face.
So infuriating.
Yeah, you can make two bucks off that.
It's, like, the thing that weirds me out, it's so much less believable because every right-wing terror attack is a false flag.
You know, look, I get it, Putin won 97% of the vote.
Sure.
Sure he did.
Alright, 99% of all of these right-wing terror attacks that are people doing the things you say they should do.
Politically.
99% of them are all false flags?
99%.
Come on, man.
And, uh...
At least be like the Oklahoma City bombing with him.
Well, and 99% of things that you make up that don't happen are also false flags.
Yeah, exactly!
Yes!
It's...
Come on, man!
Give me 60-40 at least.
Yeah, yeah.
Something.
It's...
But he can't muddy the waters because then you're not sure that they're all false flags.
Right, right.
You know, or you're not sure which ones are false flags.
Okay, and it comes down to the limitation of his abilities, and that is that once you
introduce the idea of, like, real critical thinking that you engage in with the audience
and allow the audience to engage in, if you're like, well, maybe this is a false flag.
I don't know, let's see.
You can't accidentally encourage your audience to start questioning and you don't want them to do that.
And you cannot have that.
Because your shit is thin.
Any doubt is terror.
It's religion.
Any doubt will fuck you up.
Yeah, yeah, and that's why Alex can say, like, there's a chance that this is real, and then
20 seconds later be like, the deep state did this bomb.
Yeah, totally, totally.
So you give the appearance of questioning and the appearance of critical thinking while
at the same time driving home your predetermined conclusion.
Yep.
It's just unfounded.
So unfair.
So, it has all the signatures, man.
It has all the signatures of a false flag.
There's a signature.
There's a pattern to false flags.
And at the preliminary stages, this fits perfectly into that historical paradigm.
But regardless, authoritarian elements of the system will try to use this event to take more Americans' liberties.
The Democratic Party and their deep state controllers have given us years of looting and destruction
as a message to the courts and the system.
If you don't give us what we want, if you don't let us steal the election and stall Joe Biden
and let China complete its takeover, we will burn every city to the ground.
If I were Alex, I would avoid using the word regardless.
Yeah.
Because he's like, yes, this has all the marks of a false flag, but regardless.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't hand-wave that.
Yeah, I don't know.
Makes me think that you're not saying shit.
Yeah.
Yada, yada, yada.
Moving on.
And he gets to, like, his closing thoughts, which is his refrain that he says on pretty
much every time he wants to say something stupid about a world event that people are
emotionally affected by.
And that is, hey, I got the right to question things.
Americans can question things.
Sure.
And again, this is not questioning.
But in closing, never forget the long history of governments and other organizations staging
false flag terror attacks to blander political opposition.
And remember, it's the American birthright to be able to research and question any public
event.
I mean, yeah, research and question whatever you want.
This isn't that.
Yeah.
This is bullshit.
That's a little bit different.
Yeah.
It is your birthright to research and question things, but it is not your birthright to go
on the radio and tell people that it was a false flag.
Right.
I feel like that's not a, I don't know if George Washington was hanging out being like,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Eventually we're going to invent the radio.
I have a laissez faire.
I have a difficult time thinking that, I mean, first of all, I don't know.
I don't want to get into a first amendment debate, but I don't think it's responsible
at questioning behavior or, you know, like something that has a lot of value in society
for someone to just get on the radio and with no evidence be like the deep state did this.
That's stupid.
That can only lead to negative outcomes.
Yeah.
I mean, regardless of what he's saying, regardless of any of that stuff, when you say I am only
researching and questioning, that is a bad faith lie.
So I don't give a shit about what you're talking about.
It's a deflection.
I don't, this isn't even a first amendment conversation.
This is a, I can toss away your bullshit because you are already lying to me.
Yeah.
You know?
So fuck you.
His enclosing statement is things have happened before and I can get away with this.
So please give some credence to what I'm saying.
Meanwhile, the like, it's just, just, uh, just, uh, I can't even, I can't even come
up with words other than weak.
It's just nothing.
It's conspiracy is nothing.
Yeah.
It's so disappointing.
It's boring.
We have one last clip here as Alex closes out the report where he wants to make you
afraid of Eric Holder.
Damn right.
Never forget that Joe Biden and his would be incoming crew of criminals are part of
the Obama crime organization.
Never forget it was deputy attorney general Eric Holder who helped cover up what really
happened in Oklahoma city in 1995 the same holder carried out the giant confirmed false
flag operation of fast and furious.
Okay.
Alex sounds so self-satisfied when he says fast and furious at the end there.
Uh, I'm going to put that one in the wind column guys cut right there.
Eric Holder even need talks to be in Biden's administration.
Who cares?
He's not.
I haven't heard his name come up.
Rahm Emanuel's name has come up more than Eric Holder's and he should be tossed into
a fucking cannon.
I feel like Alex just doesn't have many specifics left and he's like, oh, I remember how fun
it was to make people scared of Eric Holder.
Let's get back on that.
So I was really struck by how weak and desperate that special report that Alex put out is.
It's absolutely meaningless.
There's no teeth behind it at all.
I almost kind of felt when I was listening to it that he didn't have a theory, but he
wanted to yell into the void to remind people that he's weird and he's willing to call everything
fake with or without reason and he's ready to do it immediately.
Yeah.
He's almost putting out a beacon like the lighthouse is lit guys.
I'm out here.
There's no theory here.
There's nothing except knee jerk denialism, which Alex attempts to justify by pointing
to unrelated rants he went on two and a half years ago about how the media was going to
false flag themselves, something that barely even makes sense with the details of the bombing.
It's unconvincing, it's flat, and it's also couched in so much I'm not saying I'm just
saying kind of language that it's hard to even imagine him caring about this.
Reckless abandon is easy to mistake for passion, but attempts to cover your own ass preemptively
just feel hollow.
I was curious about QAnon was doing with this bombing, so I reached out to Travis over at
QAnon Anonymous and he directed me to some of the theories that have popped up and gained
traction in that world.
They're all nuts, but they're better than Alex.
Okay.
They seem to have theories that surround the idea that there was like a secret NSA server
at the AT&T building that would somehow prove that the Georgia election fraud conspiracies
were true.
So the bombing was actually the good guys setting off a controlled detonation to recover
the evidence and stop Biden from getting into office or possibly to prevent the bad guys
from being able to steal the upcoming run runoff election in Georgia.
Dude.
Next one.
Obviously that's nonsense and it's flimsy as hell, but it makes sense with the larger
conspiracies that are actually being engaged in in the QAnon world.
That's fair.
It fits the needs of the audience that QAnon has captured, whereas Alex's narrative is
just dull and uninspired as well as almost entirely disconnected from anything else he's
been yelling about except for the fact that false flags are coming, which I stress he
does all the time.
Do you want me to play that six minutes again?
Do not, sir.
I won't.
And he doesn't even feel into it.
No, he doesn't feel into it.
He's not selling it.
You got it.
Look, if you got weak material, you got to sell it.
You know, that's the one thing that I've, I've learned from standup so long.
If you got weak material, you perform the shit out of that material and maybe you'll
skate by and help you push up the next level and this you got to elevate.
Yeah.
It's, it's almost like kind of, it has the feeling of a guy and like a, like a recliner
doing like an, I told you so, but there's nothing there being told because that is kind
of the idea.
The, I told you so is him playing these clips from 2018 where he said that CNN was going
to fall flat.
Yeah.
This is like, it almost feels like a victory lap, but there was no victory.
There wasn't even a race.
No, that's true.
Yeah.
He should be petting a cat on his lap.
Just like I told all of you what would happen.
It's almost confusing.
Yeah.
It's almost disorienting how disconnected it is from anything that feels real or anything
that even makes sense as like conspiracy fodder.
Like that's, that's the thing that like when I was looking at these, these QAnon things
that Travis pointed me towards, like I was looking at those and I was like, I get it.
I get where this is going.
Sure.
Media wants to make themselves look like the victims.
Yeah.
What?
It just doesn't, it's, it's not,
I think, I think on this one, the cement is too wet.
The cement is too wet right now.
I think this is going to be the first one where it's like in two days, everyone will
have a much better conspiracy theory.
They've had more time to workshop it.
They got more details to play with.
There just aren't enough, you know, like that's, that's the thing you, with the, the Boston
bombing, they're all immediately, they're pictures, suspects.
There's so many different people you could investigate and go down.
And on this one it's like, I don't even know where to start yet.
That kind of thing.
So all these people are just coming up with downright nonsense.
Yeah.
And it's, it's in the like same like in-between period of an election and an inauguration
and the recount, a runoff election as it were.
And we got other shit going on.
Yeah.
So much other shit to deal with.
So I'm, I'm interested to see where Alex goes with this because I think, I mean, based on
his behaviors, it seems like this is something that's going to have to be something he keeps
going on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I'm interested to see what the narrative flashes out to be, whether he gets in line
with the QAnon theories that are already much fuller than his.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Totally.
Or if it becomes a, I don't know what it'll become.
Anyway.
I don't know.
I just think that there's some value in taking a look at the immediate reaction that he has.
Totally.
I agree.
I mean, you know, it's, he knew he had to do something.
Yeah.
And this is what he did.
Exactly.
It'll be a great document of what he said before he's going to say something different.
You know?
Like we have to at least, this is uninspired, but this is without question an easy receipt
against tomorrow's bullshit, you know?
Most likely.
Maybe even today's bullshit, like that kind of level.
Yeah.
And hey, we'll be back.
Oh, we will.
Yeah.
But please, my apologies if anybody felt anything that we discussed or any of our tone was flippant
about the bombing.
My heart goes out to everybody affected and I don't want you to think that, you know,
my mocking Alex's theories are in any way meant to minimize the experience that people
are having.
Yeah.
It's tougher, but we are not brutish.
Life is not that brutal, so it is just fucking, what are you going to do?
We'll be back.
But until then, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yep.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at Knowledge Fight and at Go To Bed Jordan.
We're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook.
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work right now.
Yeah.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
Thanks for listening to Alex Eat That Hat.
He's got to eat that hat.
He promised to eat the hat.
Eat the hat, Alex.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.