N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying we are the bad guys.
Dan and Jordan.
Knowledgefight.
Riddle her.
Need money.
Andy and Kansas.
Stop it.
It's time to pray.
Andy and Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your room.
Knowledgefight.
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey everybody.
Welcome back to Knowledgefight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes.
We like to sit around, drink novelty beverages, and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh indeed we are Dan.
Jordan.
Dan.
Quick question for you.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, Jordan, is a happy anniversary for our show.
Oh that's right.
It is our anniversary.
We are recording this.
January 7th.
Yes.
Four years ago.
It's crazy.
Our first episode came out.
What are we doing?
I don't know.
How dare we do this for four years?
I'm mad at us.
What is it?
Yeah.
Shit.
Somehow we are also a cancer on this world.
Oh, dammit.
That was unexpected four years ago, but here we are and it's been a fun ride at times.
Yeah.
And we got quite an appropriate gift from the universe.
Yes, as far as a four year, yeah.
But it is nice to still be working on this with you and I appreciate that and so that
is my bright spot.
No, it's beautiful.
It's one of those things where I have a hard time remembering that we didn't do this show.
At some point.
Yeah.
Like there's a part of me that's like remembering-
I did open mics.
No, I remember.
No, no, no.
I was 24.
I was in the fucking suburbs and I was doing an open mic my third of the night and I keep
in my memory.
I'm like, well tomorrow I'm going to have to record.
Like that's how ridiculous it is that we do this show.
The schedule has become something you've super imposed on.
Retroactive.
Yeah, yeah.
Absolutely.
What's your bright spot?
My bright spot is I got new glasses.
Nice.
I got new glasses about two weeks after I got these.
My dog Jake got a whole of them and there's tooth marks and the like all over.
And that was about a year ago.
So I went and got a new pair of glasses.
And Dan, do you want to know how stupid I am?
How stupid?
When I went to get new glasses, I was looking at the frames and I was like, oh, you know
what I'll do?
I'll get some different frames.
I like the same style, but I'm going to get some different frames.
Can I predict what happened?
I got the same exact frame, exact same frames.
Intending to get the different ones.
Intending to get different frames, I got the same one because I am predictable.
That's pretty sweet.
They look good though.
Yeah, they look great.
So something that doesn't look great is our prospects for going to bed at a decent hour.
We're recording this a little bit late because necessity kind of had to.
Yeah, you were, you know, some big news happened yesterday and you decided to sleep the whole
day.
You didn't pay any attention to it.
You've really, like you did maybe two hours of work on this episode, right?
Really phoned it in.
Yeah, you threw this one on the, yeah.
We were talking on Tuesday, we recorded our little bonus scavenger hunt over zoom and
after we recorded that we were talking and I'm like, well, tomorrow's going to suck.
It's going to be a disaster.
I'm going to have to work a whole lot, so I'm going to do nothing today.
I'm going to treat myself to a little bit of relaxation because I know that Wednesday
is going to suck.
I didn't think it was going to suck in the way that it did.
Oh, at that point I was kind of predicting a dumb rally, but what I was thinking was
going to suck was that Alex had interviewed Mike Flynn and I didn't want to deal with
that.
Oh man, how naive I was on Tuesday.
I am the 10th famous person on the plane where the big bopper went down.
Not going to be in the news anymore.
Yeah, Mike Flynn's interview.
You're going to have to be on the back burner.
Yeah, page A-26 my friends.
I did watch it and it's boring, but we may cover it at some point because it is a bizarre
thing to happen because you have Mike Flynn who's like the hero of the QAnon folk who
think Alex Jones is like a CIA massage shill and the two of them are doing an interview
where they're like, Hey buddy, and they won't stop talking about it on the episode that
we're going to be going over today.
It ends with the two of them hugging.
Oh, great.
I love it.
Great.
Tom Pappert describes it as like a really important moment.
Yeah.
Of course.
I don't know how QAnon fans would rationalize that.
Like it seems like it'd be really difficult for their hero to be hugging a CIA facade
agent.
I know.
Here's how I would do it.
I would say he actually doesn't know anything about us, doesn't care and would just like
our money.
Ah, I mean that would be, that would be on the level.
Yeah.
So Jordan, today, what we're going to be doing, we're going to be going over, first of all,
the speeches that Owen Troyer and Alex Jones gave at a Stop the Steal rally on the evening
of January 5th.
Okay.
Then we will be tracking the entire day's coverage on Info Wars on January 6th.
We're going to start with the American Journal call-in show.
Call-in show.
No calls.
Why not?
Well, I mean, nothing had happened by then.
No, I don't.
That's early in the morning.
It's mostly because Harrison Smith is hosting and he's just basically throwing it to...
Just boring.
Well, he's just throwing it to like Don Jr.'s speech and stuff like that.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
Then we've got the Alex Jones show, comes on after that.
Also hosted by Harrison Smith, because Alex and Owen are in DC.
And then we've got The War Room, which is hosted by Tom Papert and also Alex Jones and
Owen Schroyer in DC.
Okay.
So, if I understand correctly, we are playing the Washington Generals today.
Is that what's going on?
It is the B string.
But it's still important.
I do still think it's important to look at the lens of how the coverage on Info Wars
went because you can see Alex's hand, editorial control, you can see the training that these
people have had under Alex, and Alex does show up a bit, and he's yelling.
For sure, for sure.
And it's a load of nonsense.
But I apologize to everybody, I have been working straight through all day yesterday.
I forgot to get names for Wonks.
So I'll tell you what, before we start today's show, I'd like to say thank you to everybody
who supports our show, and also everybody who likes the show but doesn't support it.
I'd like to thank you.
Anybody out there who needs this today, who needs a nice little pick-me-up, you're a policy
Wonk.
You know that?
I'm a policy Wonk.
Thank you.
Thanks, everybody.
Put a smile on your face.
Thanks to all the Wonks, non-Wonks, and I guess people who are hearing this ten years
in the future.
Sure.
Yeah.
So yeah, on Wednesday, there was the planned rally in DC.
We knew that there was-
Went off without a hitch.
I was not surprised, inasmuch as they've been talking about this for a long time, and Alex
has been trying to incite an event like people storming the White House-
Sure.
Or not the White House, excuse me, the Capitol building, for quite a while.
That has been something that has been a predictable conclusion from some-
Sure.
But I would be lying if I said I wasn't still, like, shocked.
Yeah.
I wasn't ready for it to happen.
Right.
I was, I thought it was, like I said already, I thought it was gonna be another dumb rally
where Ali Alexander says a bunch of nonsense, and then everyone goes home.
I was taken aback by how quickly things got out of control, how extremely they got out
of control, and I was pretty surprised watching Alex's coverage of it, too.
Yeah, I'm interested to see.
I was trying to avoid dipping my toe into how the conservative media would react too
much to this, just so I didn't get a whiff of ruining the whole premise of the show,
which is that I don't know what Alex is gonna say.
Yeah.
So I am very curious to see how they all take this as a glaring loss and that they're all
a bunch of embarrassing morons.
I think that's what they're gonna-
I think this is interesting because you and I have very different takes on the events
that transpired.
Yes, very much.
Over our text messages, we've been going back and forth, and there's a little bit of a disagreement,
and I actually think that both of our positions have merit, and there's validity to both of
them.
You believe that this was an optics disaster, and they all looked like dum-dums, and this
is going to be crippling to the right-wing extremist movement.
Yeah, I would argue that.
And I can see where you're coming from, and I think that there is a place for mocking,
and I think that that is something that is valid to be part of the conversation.
Sure, sure.
Personally, I see Patriot lore being established, and that worries me.
I see, you know, the way that Alex talks about Colonel Travis and his time at the Alamo,
and it's like, this isn't history.
Sure.
This is Patriot lore.
Sure, sure, sure.
This is something like a misunderstanding and a misrepresentation of the past.
Yeah.
I see that happening in the present, and I see all of the elements that are necessary
in this event to become a part of Patriot lore that is really encouraging and inspiring
and dangerous for people in the future.
Yeah.
And I don't think that you don't think that's valid also.
No, I think that's one of the weird things about our general disagreements is, I think
you're probably right if a certain couple of variables, like, our worldviews are just
like a couple little variables twisted here or there and we disagree.
Otherwise, I think, even then, we're still coming at it from the same, like, this is
where all of these people think.
Yeah, and I think that some of these differences in our perspective, I hope they can be more
fleshed out as we go along through the episode as we see the Infowars coverage.
I think it's interesting.
I think it's very interesting.
Yeah, so we're going to jump in with the speeches at the Stop the Steal rally, but before we
do, here's an out of context drop from today's show.
God and his consciousness creates the ocean that creates the waves on which Donald Trump
or an Alex Jones or you ride in on.
Yep.
So God creates the ocean, the ocean creates the waves, and Donald Trump, Alex Jones, and
you ride them waves.
Great.
Okay.
Alex might have been fucked up.
He seems like he's gassed, like he's running out of breath.
It's a mess.
He's not...
Oh God, it's another instance of him being the guy at the comedy show you never want
to go after.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You don't want this guy in the middle of the booking.
Not where it's supposed to be.
No, because he's going to burn out the audience with just...
You can't do it.
No.
I mean, even if the guy in front of you is only doing 10 minutes and you're doing 45,
if he gets eight standing ovations, you're done.
Yeah.
You're fucked.
The end.
Yeah.
So we start with Owen though.
Owen opens for Alex.
He does a good...
He does a tight five, let's say.
But he starts off by ripping off Alex.
President Trump is watching this and he's very excited at what he sees.
And he's going to have some big announcements for us tomorrow, I believe.
Thomas Jefferson once said, when the government fears the people, there is freedom.
But for too long now, the people have feared the government.
Well, in January, 2021, that changes.
That looks a little worse in hindsight.
We've been over this before, but that isn't a Thomas Jefferson quote.
It's from a 1914 debate against socialism delivered by John Basil Barnhill that over
the years has been misattributed to a bunch of people like Thomas Paine and Thomas Jefferson.
Perhaps more interestingly though, in that clip, it appears that Owen's trying to promote
the idea that Trump is going to show up at the rally the next day.
This was the first instance of an Infowars employee behaving in a way that led me to
believe that they had no idea people were planning to storm the Capitol the next day.
They are acting 100% business as usual.
Promoting what they expect will just be another afternoon of profitable terrorism edging that
they're going to be playing.
And that's kind of the vibe that I get.
And it's just, this is all like Infowars business as usual, just Owen being a dumb shithead.
And the theme is four more years for Donald Trump.
And while I all think, I think all of us can get behind that, I'd like to see a thousand
more years of human freedom and a thousand more years of the United States of America.
Then deal with climate change?
USA!
You dumb fuck!
It always happens.
Oh my God.
They're so silly.
It always happens.
The USA chants break out so easily.
Do you know, here's, here's the problem.
Here's the problem with these.
Oh.
Here's the problem.
I'm going to give you this right now.
I'm surprised there's only one.
There's only one that I can see.
Okay.
All right.
Here's your audience.
Look at those dumb dumbs.
You can steal anything and they will have no, you stole a Thomas Jefferson quote from
not Thomas Jefferson and they still bought it.
Why wouldn't you go out there and be like, uh, uh, uh, would you rather have a Lexus
or justice?
A dream or some substance?
Okay.
Why wouldn't you go dead press?
Why wouldn't you do something real?
To quote Thomas Jefferson.
Yeah, exactly.
They schools don't teach us shit.
Yeah, just stay awake or try and get really fancy and just completely lie to the audience
is just like grapes don't exist.
Yeah.
Let's fucking shoot the moon.
What's it?
Where's our line?
What's the line?
I think that, uh, the fake Thomas Jefferson quotes are just something that's so in the
pocket for them that it's safe territory.
You can't go wrong.
No.
Um, also I would say that even under like ideal conditions, I don't know if America
could last another thousand years.
Climate change notwithstanding, that's still a long time for a country to, uh, I guess
maybe, but you know, it could still exist in some fashion, but not like super power.
I mean, it'll probably be more like the homie Holy Roman empire was in Germany for a while.
You know, like that kind of thing.
It would, it would be a bizarre to imagine continuing at the, the re like the status
thing.
Yeah.
It's for that long.
Small parts of Montana that cut apart.
It's foolish on Owen's part, but I will say, I think that Owen feels the itch to get into
a line of work that you and I used to explore.
Okay.
I think he wants to start doing open mics.
You think he wants to do a little bits?
Well, you remember when, uh, he took the tank down to the Austin, uh, they're getting ready
to go on the, uh, the caravan and he was workshopping bits to empty traffic.
He was doing jokes.
Sure.
He's got a new bit.
Yeah.
But you know, Nancy Pelosi said that you can no longer say mother and father in Congress.
Did you see this?
Well, I got news for Nancy Pelosi.
Trump is your daddy.
Good bit, good bit solid, solid piece of work right there or doing the, you can't say mother
and father 24 hours prior to the fall of the United States government, a nuclear power.
One of the leaders of the resistance said Trump is your daddy.
Great.
Uh, five years ago they did this.
You can't say mother and father paranoia and panic.
It's great to see them bringing back the hits about time.
So this is in response to Nancy Pelosi, uh, and, uh, the, the house updating their rule
book.
Sure.
The text of the rule book doesn't include gendered language, but that doesn't mean that
you can't say mother and father.
That's not like it's against the rules.
It's just not in the text of the rules.
This is like Skinner, you know, they've been doing new stuff for five years, but whenever
you go in public, you still got to play the hits.
But you know, yeah.
But this would be like, you know, you don't play free bird for a few years and then you
bring it out as if it has never been played before.
They've just been on the radio too much.
They haven't been in public.
They haven't really had that chance to get a free bird out there.
You know?
Um, I would say that a free bird is a long song and Owen Schroyer set is not long.
That's a smart move.
Um, this is no stairway to heaven.
This is a, uh, in and out.
Okay.
All right.
Uh, two and a half minute pop song.
He's getting out of there and he's a, he's a, also another standup reference.
It's a shotgun situation.
He's introducing Alex.
All right.
That's good stuff.
Coming up next.
It's my pleasure to introduce a man.
It's my honor to introduce a man who was the Genesis in many ways of this second American
revolution.
Dear FBI, Alex Jones was in many ways the Genesis of this that started with one man
on public access television will tomorrow turn into millions of Americans in the streets
of Washington DC to take our Republic back and that man's name is really also does not
look great.
Oh man.
Oh, I want that on my wall.
Only one man on public access in Austin, Texas is responsible for everything that happens
tomorrow.
I just want any law enforcement entities that may be recording this speech.
As we speak to know this is all on Alex Jones.
Tomorrow will be the culmination of his professional career.
I'm just saying you want to stop this movement, get Alex Jones.
It's all on him.
It's only him.
I'm throwing him under the bus by way of flattery.
This is the greatest man who is responsible for everything.
I found myself feeling a lot of that like in hindsight.
This is terrible.
But then the other thing that I was feeling was that like there's a lot of stand up shit
in here like Owens doing some stand up getting the crowd to chant USA is pandery nonsense
and Alex basically starts his set with like give it up for yourselves.
He does like a give it up for the wait staff out of here.
I'll tell you who I'm excited to hear to see.
It's you, the American people, unified in resistance to the new world order.
Give yourselves a round of applause for coming out tonight.
Yeah.
Jesus.
What a lovely audience.
You guys are the best.
All right.
Okay.
If I'm, if I'm doing my set, I want to open with three applause breaks.
Doesn't matter.
I want to say, give it up for your wait staff.
Hey, give it up for yourselves for coming out tonight.
Hey, ladies and gentlemen, how about those sports teams like them or a nice gracious
move if maybe you're the headliner, give it up for everyone else who saw tonight.
Totally.
Absolutely.
That's super cool.
That number three in there and then get your set going.
Oh yes.
Um, so Alex at least has maybe learned that as a little bit of etiquette.
Sure.
Which I haven't seen in some of his other speeches, so I think that might be a performance
evolution on his part.
I mean, so many failed right wing comics are these people, so I assume Alex has spent a
lot more time with failed right wing comics recently.
It's possible.
And maybe he's going backwards, maybe he's Benjamin buttoning it.
Now he's going from right wing reactionary to successful comic, that would be the worst
part.
If he suddenly nails it.
I've seen him do stand up.
Okay.
Well, we have to.
Um, but he does have a head start on other, let's say younger comics coming up.
Sure.
And that name recognition.
Well, there's that.
Yeah.
But he's also got a catch phrase and he's got a catch phrase that apparently audiences
will chant with him.
Get the fuck.
They have tried to steal this election in front of everyone.
And as I told them 20 years ago, I tell them again, I don't know how this is going to end,
but if they want to fight, they better believe.
He's got his own get her done.
People will call and response that shit.
Yeah.
Get the fuck out.
That was wild.
I have never heard that before in my life.
Oh, he yells that all the time.
Yeah.
But I mean, if you, if you think, uh, you know, if you want to fight, you better believe
you got one.
That right.
Yeah.
But I mean like that was a long thing for people to remember.
It shocked me.
It's a little, it's a little, the length of the Lord's prayer.
I'm just saying, I don't remember all of the Lord's prayer.
If I was up after this, I would be worried.
I would start with the Lord's prayer to bring the energy down again.
I would be super worried because it's like, all right, either he's going to fuck this
up or I'm not going to be able to follow one of the two.
Yeah.
Anyway, he almost alienates the audience.
Alex Jones is the Lauren Hill of the right.
He all, he almost immediately after this, after getting a getter done style champs,
he almost alienates the audience by accidentally saying that Hitler was bad.
Hitler was a monster.
Stalin was a monster, but what Mao Zedong and Xi Jinping did overshadows their crimes
against us, against humanity.
They commit against a Muslim, a Christian, a Buddhist, an agnostian, a Chinese, an African,
a North American.
It doesn't matter.
I think he's fucked up.
It's a crime in the eyes of God.
You can tell that Alex is a serious scholar of Chinese history and the Chinese Communist
Party because he knows the names of Mao and Xi.
I actually kind of think that he doesn't realize that Xi isn't Mao's successor and I'd love
to bring up Hu Jintao to him because then he would say who and then we'd end up in a
vaudeville bit.
I would, I would legitimately like to ask him if he knows that Chairman Mao had a wife.
I would be interested to know if he thinks that the whole time it was just him.
I don't know.
You know?
I don't think he knows a whole lot more than a couple of names.
I think that you might be right.
Some broad strokes and maybe something he read in a JBS pamphlet.
Could be.
Leaving that aside, it's important to understand that Alex is lying to this audience in a very,
very real way.
He doesn't care at all what China does to the Uyghur population of Muslims except when
he can use their pain as a weapon against his own enemies.
In this case, he's in front of a crowd so he wants to establish the moral high ground
against their imaginary evil enemies who support China's treatment of Muslims.
When he's alone on his own show speaking freely, he sounds a little bit different like he did
on May 26th.
But from Michigan to Texas, from London to Los Angeles, from Rio de Janeiro to Berlin,
there are call to prayers.
I don't like to call it as Chinese but they don't put up with that because they know it's
a group trying to take them over.
Hey, Chai-Coms, do your thing.
Don't try to take me over.
Do your thing.
Do your thing, Chai-Coms.
Come on, man.
Talking about their repressive treatment to certain Muslim populations.
No, he cares.
Do your thing.
He cares.
Well, when it's useful.
I mean, yeah.
What Alex is doing here on stage is exactly what he and his friends accuse the entire
left of doing, virtue signaling.
Alex doesn't care about how China treats Muslims because if Alex had his way, the only Muslims
that would be allowed in America would be the ones who agreed to convert to his bizarre
idiotic version of Christianity.
Quite simply, Alex is using the false impression that he's offended by how the Chinese government
treats the Uyghurs in order to pretend that his criticisms of China come from a sensible
and real place, when in reality, they're mostly just re-warmed up, John Birch society, Cold
War nonsense.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yep.
It's a bummer, but also Alex does seem a little bit fucked up.
He seems a little messed up.
He's having a good time.
Yes.
I agree.
There are currently, I would say, on the countdown of ways to learn, we've gone from ten to about
eight.
Jordan.
When he gets down to a four, we know we're fucked up.
Right now, there are eight ways to learn.
I would say that he's having a good time, and more importantly, he has had a good time
before this.
That's fair.
He's been having a good time.
That's a fair characterization.
And I think, like I was saying, he's gassed.
He has no cardio.
If you're a comic and you want to be a high-energy comic, you'll quickly learn that if you're
out of shape, you're going to have a really tough time with that.
You see comics who are maybe a little bit more energetic.
Sometimes they'll be sweating, and it's because it's hard.
It's hard to keep that energy up.
Oh yeah.
And I think Alex is learning.
I'm sweating now.
We're only a half hour in.
Alex is learning this the hard way.
And just as authoritarians throughout history have bet on the Bolsheviks, and bet on the
Nazis, and bet on every other form of tyranny, their bet will fail.
I guess you're right.
Because there is a God that created the universe, and there is a God that inspired our republic,
and there is a God in the control of the affairs of humans, and that God will see us through
if we are loyal.
I don't know if it came through as well on the audio, but you can tell he's getting his
breath after just about every other word.
And it doesn't look comfortable.
But he also gets into safe territory to start this getting into religion.
Get into God.
Get in or get out.
Yeah.
And once you start talking about religion, it's important that you level with the audience.
You gotta be real.
Sure.
Let's hear this one.
But make no mistake.
Make no mistake.
I'm like being completely honest with you here.
Things are gonna be rough.
I'm drunk.
I'm in bed.
I'm kind of shitfaced.
We've already allowed the murder of 60 million babies in this country.
I took a lot out of it.
We've done so many other evil things.
So we're deep down in the water.
We're hundreds of feet deep.
It's gonna be hard swimming back to the surface.
And not everybody is gonna make it.
But that's okay.
Because in the end, God will fulfill his destiny and will reward the righteous.
Outside of some surface level stuff, this is exactly the kind of speech I would expect
to hear at an ISIS rally.
You know, there'd be some different decoration and some different themes maybe, but this
is...
Totally.
This is culty.
Yeah, these guys are ISIS.
It's really messed up.
I am so happy to remember how many times people told me years ago, don't call them ISIS.
That's offensive.
That's too much.
Mwah!
They're ISIS.
Love it.
I...
Fuck you, the past.
Well, I mean, it's possible for you to have been onto something and also wrong them.
I am aware.
Uh, but maybe not now.
Just as we see in the Bible and just as we see in history, God rises up men who are real.
Not men that are perfect, not men that are above reproach, but real men like President
Trump.
Who has fought hard for our Republic.
Who's fought hard for justice.
Who's done the best job he can and because he has represented us, he is under attack.
So we hold up President Trump before the creator of the universe and we say thank you for trying
to send us a deliverer, though he's not perfect as we are, but we pray for him and we pray
for America and we hold him up in this hour of peril.
Sounds like his voice is about to bottom out, too, like...
Give up the gasoline, road warrior.
Wow.
Thank you.
All right.
Okay.
Thank you, God, for sending Trump as a deliverer.
Oh boy.
It's funny to hear that speech broadcast on TV and know it.
I'm not positive that this speech was broadcast on TV.
Oh, that's fair.
That's fair.
I meant in a more ethereal sense of it, traveling throughout space.
It's sent to a satellite.
Sure.
It's on the right side broadcast network.
To space and then sent back down, sent around everywhere, all of this happening instantly.
In his pocket is a small little brick with all of human history recorded inside of it.
And he's like, we've got Trump as our deliverer because of God.
It's super weird.
What world do we live in?
It's super weird, too, to imagine that signal going into people's homes and then at least
one person is watching it like, damn right.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's very bizarre to me.
Like, seeing this...
You realize a miracle's in your face.
Well, I mean, seeing this speech, it's like, yeah, yeah.
I get what Alex is doing.
Like, I kind of understand what he's up to.
It's baffling to me to imagine that, you know, people are like...
Wild.
Yeah, this is good.
Yeah, man.
This is...
Totally.
This is entertainment.
Absolutely.
Or like, this is inspiring.
You know who my favorite character...
Fucked up.
...in Fury Road was?
Immortan Joe.
I thought he was the guy I wanted to follow.
Ride or die, Immortan Joe.
Well, it could not be worse than Bill Gates.
Okay.
I know that.
Yeah.
I was looking around on band.video.
Okay.
And there's a new section on there, and it's just titled, Bill Gates is Evil.
I guess...
That's also a folder I have on my desktop, but yeah, yeah.
I guess that's what Alex is doing instead of making that documentary about Bill Gates.
He's just got a place where he's posted some shitty videos about him.
That's nice.
Organize it.
Yeah.
But he doesn't run the world, that Bill Gates.
What is God in control of human destiny?
Not Bill Gates, not Warren Buffet, not Lord Rothschild, not the globalist.
And it's that simple understanding that God of the universe is in control, not the globalist
who want to play God.
We recognize God, we connect with God, and we transcend the Satanist by doing that.
I think people were worried about when that sentence was gonna end.
Yeah.
Yeah, that one kept going.
That one kept going.
I think Alex didn't.
He was trying to find his feet.
I don't mind a run-on sentence.
I don't mind one, but there are times when you shouldn't.
Yeah.
It felt like the sentence was as drunk as Alex appears to be, just sort of staggering
forward.
There you go.
So this next thing that Alex says also doesn't look great in hindsight.
Tomorrow is a great day.
We don't quietly take the election fraud, we don't quietly take the scam and believe
they're BS.
We've seen the evidence.
The system has had to desperately engage in this gambit to maintain control, but this
will be their Waterloo.
This will be their destruction.
Doesn't look great.
I would say that if I were Alex and I were confronted with that, I would be like, I wasn't
talking about Waterloo, the battle.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I was talking about the ABBA song.
This is all political.
Political only.
I am not talking about literal events.
Yeah, that would be smart.
Depicting war.
So now here was my concern when I was talking about being the person who comes up after
him is like, he's going to lose the crowd.
This is like, you can't keep this up.
This is like, he's going to, he's burning up, coming in hot and he's going to burn out
fast.
And Ornie Adams up next, wait, what?
Alex starts dipping his toes into COVID denial and he starts losing the audience a little
bit.
They're like, ah, we're just not here.
Come on, man.
This is about this.
Cool.
But we're not here for this.
This is a stop the steal rally.
And the world is watching every thing you do with the big tech censorship and the economic
attacks and the COVID lockdowns and the UN martial law world government foretold for
thousands of years is now upon us and it's pathetic and it will be defeated.
We finally face the world government chicken little witch hunt system and we have the deaths
of 2020 from the CDC 61,000 more people died in 2020 and when you count, when you count
the drug addiction, the drug overdose and suicide, less people died in 2020, 2019 is
broken.
That wasn't me.
Have to go out and you have to expose it.
It's fallen apart a little bit.
Yeah.
I think you should have left that one alone.
The wheels are off the wagon.
I was just making up numbers.
Alex is a little bit drunk now.
Alex is a little bit too drunk to stay on target.
I think he's just, you know, it got good to him.
He was feeling like sometimes you'll be on stage, like your first three bits will land
and you're like, I'm going to try out something new.
I'm just, nope, I fucked up.
No, I think he's in a, I think he's in a nice little world of like, hold on, I'm going to
do one more bit.
That last one didn't land, so I'm going to do one more bit and then that one lands and
you're like, oh shit, I'm going to do one more after that.
I'm going to push it.
I'm going to keep letting this ride.
No one's going to get this, but he's Mike Sheehan again.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
Um, yeah, I would say that's about right.
Um, so when you, when you're in that circumstance, the only thing you can do is retreat back
to what was working.
Yeah.
Try and be like, okay, I was being dirty earlier.
I tried to be like more introspective and observational.
They didn't like that.
Gotta go back to dick jokes.
Don't be mean to Hitler.
I realized that if you're mean to Hitler, it's bad.
Yeah.
Popping the crowd.
Let's go back to religion.
So we must now pray for president Trump and lift him up to God and ask God to give him
the guidance and the discernment and the leadership to make the decisions in God's plan that bring
down the new world order.
Got him back a little bit.
All right.
Yeah.
Back on his side a bit.
It should be harder than that.
These people are not very smart.
They believe things like that, like that fake Jefferson quote earlier, and now Alex pulls
out a fake Churchill quote.
Churchill gave up a famous speech where he said, all I can promise you was blood and
pain and war and suffering, but the alternative is even worse, total slavery.
So we don't care what the new world order does.
We commit to Christ and we commit to war against the globalist with the truth and we will never
surrender.
I may be wrong and I'm open to admitting that if Alex will go ahead and provide that citation,
but I think the quote he's trying to remember is from Churchill's first speech as prime
minister in the House of Commons in 1940.
The part Alex I think is misquoting is, quote, in this crisis I hope I may be pardoned if
I do not address the House at any length today.
I hope that any of my friends and colleagues or former colleagues who are affected by the
political reconstruction will make allowance, all allowance, for any lack of ceremony with
which it has been necessary to act.
I would say to the House, as I say to those who have joined this government, I have nothing
to offer but blood, toil, tears, and sweat.
The blood, toil, tears, and sweat thing is an attempt to stress to his government that
he's working hard despite a short speech.
I'm promising you the blood.
After this, Churchill comments on his strategy for fighting World War II, which is the other
part of what I think Alex is mixing up here, quote, you ask what is our policy?
I can say it is to wage war, by sea, land, and air, with all our might and with all our
strength that God can give us.
To wage war against a monstrous tyranny, never surpassed in the dark, lamentable catalog
of human crime.
That is our policy.
You ask what is our aim?
I can answer in one word.
It is victory, victory at all costs, victory in spite of all terror, victory, however long
and hard the road may be, for without victory there is no survival.
So the elements of- Slightly more eloquent than Alex makes it
sound.
Yeah.
I will give you blood.
I am reminded of the great Churchill quote, what is best in life?
To crush your enemies with blood, see them driven before you, and hear the levitations
of the weapons!
Yeah, that wasn't good.
I think that that is definitely the quote that he's mixing up, because-
It sounds right.
Whenever he does his really shitty Churchill impression, that's the, by land, by air.
That's the quote that he does, so I assume it's the only reference he has.
It's whatever pull he has and however he's changed it in the moment in his drunken, idle
brain.
Yeah.
I know that a lot of people are struggling, I think a lot of people had a tough time with
watching the events that unfolded on Wednesday, and granted this is Tuesday, but Alex still
recognizes that there's a lot of people in pain, and maybe some people in the audience
are feeling in pain.
Sure.
And they shouldn't.
This is his message of- Unity.
No.
No hope.
God no.
No.
This is what he's- He's bringing the country together, this is how he's-
He wants to comfort anybody in the audience who might be feeling alone.
Alright, good.
No matter if you're in a jail cell, or no matter if you're dying of cancer, or no matter
if your car broke down in the middle of the desert, the God of the universe built you,
and the God of the universe loves you.
And the God of the universe will deliver and fulfill you, but you must have faith and open
that channel.
And that's why, in closing, I'm so honored to be here tonight.
Okay.
Alright.
I love the idea of Owen Schroyer sitting off stage left and just being like, this guy's
got the goods.
This is- I will follow- Oh captain, my captain.
You sitting there taking notes?
Or Owen is in the back listening to his set.
He'd recorded his set.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, of course, in order to improve later, because he's got another set to do
later on tonight.
Yeah, yeah.
He's got another set for his buddy to get done with his set, so they can both get in
the car and go to fucking hidden shamrock.
Why not do it?
Although, I do hear that, and I kind of think to myself, it would be really interesting
to see Alex Jones' motivational speaker.
You know, like, hey, hey, you lost your job, you lost your job, that sucks, it sucks, man,
it sucks, but guess what?
You're made in God's image.
No matter what you got, he just minimizes your problem, and he just tells you that God
made you out of stardust or whatever.
Hey, I know you're poor.
God's fine with that though.
Come on now.
Let's get it together.
Let's move on.
So here's the end of Alex's speech, and where we will leave the Stop the Steal rally from
January 5th.
The globalists want to play God.
They are not God.
And the answer to their 1984 charity is 1776, 1776, 1776, 1776.
I'm so honored to be here with General Flynn and Roger Stone and others coming up, but
they are just as important as you are, whether you be black, whether you be white, whether
you be old, whether you be young, God made you, and God loves you, and they will never
separate us.
We will prevail.
Amen.
Whoa.
Wild.
Very weird.
Yeah.
You gotta end on 1776.
You bet.
The end.
End of set.
Yep.
Walk off.
You've completely blanked on who else is speaking.
Nope.
Except for General Flynn.
You don't need to end with amen.
Uh-uh.
It's a weird ramble.
None of it.
Yeah, you can end with the chanting of 1776.
You nailed it.
Although he does still leave the question in your mind, what does he think that means?
You got people storming the Capitol the next day.
Yeah.
You got him inspiring chants of 1776, 1774.
Sure.
It kind of, I mean, look.
I don't understand what you're, are you drawing a connection between the two?
I'm not necessarily.
I'm just saying there's a narrative consistency.
That's one way of putting it.
If these two events were in a fictional story and the author were arguing that one led to
the other, it would make sense.
It would make sense, yes.
I'm not saying that they do.
I'm not saying that Alex did cause anything.
I'm just saying.
From an entropy standpoint, if you were going to put one in front of the other, I think
you know which you would choose.
So now we go to the sixth and we will be here for a while.
We'll be spending a little bit of time in the Infowars Trenches, yes.
But it doesn't happen until almost the end of Alex's show.
Sure.
Actually, it's probably in the second hour, I think is when the actual like going over
the barricades.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
When it started popping off.
And then it proceeded to get wild pretty fast.
And yeah, we'll deal with that as best we can as we go along.
But we're still in this sort of much more innocent time now because we're listening
to the American Journal.
Sure.
Which again is supposed to be a call-in show.
There's no calls.
No calls.
Zero calls?
Not even one call.
I remember Alex saying that whoever's hosting this show, if they're not taking calls, they're
not going to be hosting it anymore.
So bad news, Harrison.
You're fired.
We are going to get a 17-year-old host very shortly.
I think we already have one.
Oh, that's true.
Harrison could be a baby for all I know.
I think he's like a high school sophomore.
He's there on an internship.
Sure, sure.
He's not even getting paid.
He's the AV Club guy.
He's got an extra block free and they let him do a work program.
Yeah, yeah.
I gotcha.
Alex is sponsoring him at the local college or high school.
Yeah, he gets credit.
Yeah, I like it.
The news of the day for him at the beginning is that there's this Trump rally that's going
to be going on, but also Georgia got stolen.
Wow.
What do you expect?
They haven't been punished.
Of course, they're going to do it again.
And so they did it again.
And so Georgia looks like it was lost.
I think one of the, I'll get an update here, but as far as I know, both races are projected
to be Democrat victories, although one is still on that hairline victory margin.
Donald Trump Jr. is live right now on the stage.
I want to go to him.
He, I think, has a major future.
If there's anybody that could succeed his father, I remember seeing him give a speech
at the RNC in 2016 and thinking, I'm putting my money on this guy.
This guy, uh, this guy can carry his father's mantle and keep that torch lit.
Let's go to him now and watch this live feed.
This Don Jr. kid's got something.
Wow.
Yeah.
So he's the future.
I think Harrison's the future for sure.
The way he intro'd that clip made me real excited to hear what I wanted to hear.
Yeah.
Georgia has been stolen again because they didn't get punished for stealing last time.
Why not?
Uh, I found myself very bored listening to Harrison, but I do think that he has a word
a day calendar.
Oh yeah?
Uh, because he would not stop fucking saying abrogate.
He said abrogate a lot?
All right, get the fuck out of here.
I was going to make a super cut of it, but I got to like three or four times that I'd
cut it out and I was just like, I don't even care anymore.
You get at most one abrogate per week.
These people.
Max.
Mike Pence has abrogated.
See, max.
Yeah.
One.
It's a mess.
Yeah.
Anyway, there's a lot of stuff that I was listening to that would have just sounded
like, oh, look at this braggy bullshit if people hadn't rushed the Capitol building.
Yeah.
In hindsight, there's a lot of stuff that doesn't look great.
Here is one of them.
Okay.
Truly incredible stuff.
Of course, what we have just learned and I'm excited to share once again is that president
Donald Trump himself personally asked Alex Jones to lead this March following Alex Jones
a speech.
He will be at the Vanguard.
I guess he didn't want to win to the Capitol and it's a, it's truly incredible.
And guys, let's just go ahead and leave that live feed up.
We can leave me in a box just because it's not me.
People are tuning in for, it's the incredible events going down in Washington.
You're right.
No one's doing it for you.
That's for sure.
God damn right.
You are.
I would say that now, uh, it would probably be, you know, had they have known that people
were going to storm the Capitol, I don't think they would've lied that big.
No, I would assume that the storyline wouldn't be Alex Jones was personally asked by Trump
to leave the March from the speech to the Capitol building.
Yeah.
That doesn't seem like, I would want that one off my resume pretty quick.
Um, also this looks just kind of silly in hindsight.
That's the message that we need to tell the police is you're a human being.
You're not a robot.
You know what's going on here.
You know who the good guys are and who the bad guys are.
Shouldn't be confusing to you.
Shouldn't be up in the air for you when you have hordes of, you know, just black lives
matter, just failures, just supported by the state coming out to the Capitol city to try
to burn down buildings, to try to tear down statues, just yell at police and call them
all sorts of horrible things.
Then you have interest from protesters marching, saying thank you to the cops saying, you know,
we support you.
Interesting.
It's not too difficult to know who the bad guys are and who the good guys are a couple
hours later.
Interesting, interesting things you're saying a couple hours later, not so thrilled with
the cops.
Perhaps, perhaps you may not be viewing yourselves through the appropriate lens.
I think I might be right.
So one of the things I found really interesting is Harrison's doing play by play of this Trump
rally.
And so you had Don Jr. who's this fresh upstart, he's got a bright future ahead of him.
Now there is an actual GOP upstart who's really like kind of a hot commodity in the right
wing, and that is Madison Cawthorn.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, the Nazi who's in a wheelchair.
Yeah, and he's like 25 or something like that.
It doesn't take long for him to go full Nazi.
Like he looks like the person you would want on all kinds of ad campaigns.
Yeah, absolutely.
I mean, if he weren't a Nazi.
Sure, I don't, I don't know enough about his politics to really parse everything, but based
on the speech, I'm not thrilled with him.
But it's interesting.
I do still know who he is, square jaw and all.
Sure, sure.
Sure.
Yeah.
Handsome.
But Harrison doesn't know who he is.
Really?
Madison Cawthorn comes up to give the speech.
He's up like next and he's like Madison something?
That's fantastic.
Yeah, this is, I believe his name is, he's a new, he's a new congressman, I believe his
name is, I'm blanking on his name right now, Madison or something, but he was just elected.
He's promised to stand up for Trump against Stop the Steal.
Wild.
Just the depth of awareness.
I want this to be Info Wars' new entire tone.
I want Harrison Smith to host every show.
I think this is dynamite stuff here.
Greg looks familiar.
So Madison Cawthorn's up there doing his, doing his speech and just to show that everyone
is a dork.
My friends, I want you to chant with me so loud that the cowards on White Washington
DC that I serve with can hear you.
While I leave, let's get a chance so Donald Trump knows who supports him.
USA!
Love that USA chant.
It is a parody of a parody at this point.
It is.
Yeah, it's bizarre.
It really is.
Yeah.
Speaking of parodies of parodies.
Up next, Rudy Giuliani.
Oh!
Here we go!
Rudy is giving a speech and man, man oh man.
So a lot of people took issue with him saying that he suggests trial by combat and then
people stormed the White House.
Yeah, which is objectively hilarious.
It is, it is, because it's a poor choice of words.
No, look, I mean, I get why you would be hand-wringing over that.
I understand it.
I do too.
But nobody says trial by combat meaning storm a building.
Sure, it means one-on-one combat in Game of Thrones.
It means a duel, it means, yeah, yeah.
He was being very flowery and stupid.
But even so, that's not what he was talking about.
No, of course not.
If you actually listen to the context, he's talking about the reputation of Donald Trump
versus the reputation of Joe Biden.
Totally.
And he's just trying to argue-
The Mountain versus the Sand Snakes or whatever, that's what it, yeah, yeah.
He's saying trial by combat, he's not talking about the two of them actually fighting.
Of course.
He wants ten days, his whole argument is he wants ten days for them to go on a fucking
fishing experiment, expedition, and try and find something in the ballots that they can
make an argument, but of course he's not presenting it that way.
He's saying it'll take ten days for them to find the fraud that they already know is there
or something.
What a fantastic, arbitrary measure of time.
Yeah.
I love ten.
Ten days.
Exactly ten.
So over the next ten days, we get to see the machines that are crooked, the ballots that
are fraudulent, and if we're wrong, we will be made fools of.
Too late.
But if we're right, a lot of them will go to jail.
So let's have trial by combat.
I'm willing to stake, I'm willing to stake my reputation, the president is willing to
stake his reputation, on the fact that we're going to find criminality there.
If I were Rudy Giuliani and I could get anyone to gamble against my reputation, I don't care
what I stand to win, I'm taking that bet.
His reputation ain't worth shit.
I can't think of two reputations more worthless at this point in time.
Amazing.
Rudy Giuliani, I'm gambling for like a sandwich against my reputation.
Everything that I have, every bit of my reputation, from 9-11's mayor to standing in front of
the Four Seasons Landscaping Company, yeah.
So I got a little bored at this point, because Harrison is really just, you know, covering
these speeches, and it's a lot of speeches, and so I was actually pretty pumped to see
this.
It was an amazing, exclusive interview.
Right now we have an exclusive, we are on the line with Rob Dew, who is there at the
Save America March, live on the ground.
Thanks for connecting with us, Rob, I know it's difficult to get cell phone signal there
with all of the massive crowds.
What is it like there on the ground, Rob?
It's a sea of patriots, it's a sea of happy people, really.
How do you land this interview?
How do you get the exclusive?
I cannot believe you would describe that as an exclusive.
Oh man.
It is also technically one of the most accurate ways you can use the word exclusive.
Yeah.
I agree.
I just love to imagine that all the networks are knocking down Rob Dew's door.
We gotta get Rob Dew!
Guys, I would love to go on Fox News today, but I've got an exclusive with Harrison Smith.
Sorry, I have an exclusivity deal.
Promised it earlier today.
Because they really want my analysis.
I gotta get the Dew in there, you know?
So Rob Dew, ever the fumbly dum-dum, I can't even come up with the right words to express
how much of a goof this guy is.
I believe he's just schlemazel.
Sure.
Yeah.
He's gotta come in and get a little piece of that pie.
And that pie, of course, is saying things that look really bad in hindsight.
Right when the president starts speaking, about halfway through, Alex is gonna pull
out and then we're gonna lead that march to the capitol to surround it and let these thugs
that are trying to steal our republic know what's gonna happen to them if they do go
through with their dastardly deeds.
Yeah, and you know, I wish I was there.
I mean, the energy must be amazing.
So I guess Rob is expressing that the intention of the march is to scare the Congress into
not certifying the results of the election, which is cool.
What they need to know is that we are a threat to them, physically.
They should be scared for their lives.
What we're gonna do to them.
And we are going to follow through on that threat should they not give us what we want.
Yeah, exactly.
So, Arizona's pumped.
Of course.
All right, folks.
So Donald Trump coming up next, Alex Jones leading the march to the capitol.
What are we doing?
It's January 6th, 2021, and the revolution, the second American revolution has begun.
He can't quite do that out to break like Alex does.
It won't go the distance.
It will go fast.
Yeah.
And Alex does that thing where he goes out to break with some overly dramatic, really
exciting thing.
You can see he's trying to do some of Alex's tricks, but he just can't.
He doesn't have it.
No.
And it's also embarrassing, again, to know that a couple hours after this, people storm
the capitol.
I think it's a little bit weird that...
I understand being nervous, but it's not like this is Harrison Smith's first time on mic.
Like he's been on mic for a long time.
Yes.
How do you not just allow yourself into the joy of following out with music?
I don't know.
You know?
How could you not get pumped?
How could you not even like at least sing a little bit along?
He sounds bored and disinfected.
It sucks.
Probably because Alex would hear about it and he'd beat him up for working his side
of the street.
Sure.
No.
That's fair.
That's my game.
Yeah, but get a little into it.
Get a little hips.
Get your hips into it, man.
If I worked at Infowars and I was hosting when Alex was gone or something like that,
I would come in for a break with Silver Stally and I'd sing along.
Non-stop.
I'd just begging Alex to fire me.
I would have callers call in and then be like, you're boring, and play a song and sing instead.
It would be great.
It would always be the highway.
Everyone would go crazy.
So we sensed a little bit of perhaps racial animus earlier from Harrison, his Black Lives
Matter failures and what have you.
Sure.
You can see a little bit more of that on display here.
If the Democrats are allowed to carry out this fraud, first of all, they'll do it again
and again and again and again and again.
They'll also increase the number of immigrants by magnitudes of 10, refugees by many, many
millions.
They'll completely open the borders outright.
They'll install socialistic programs that reward people that don't work, don't provide,
have nothing but hatred for us.
I think I see Owen Schroyer there.
Do you see him right there to the left of the stage?
Screen left, stage right.
Owen Schroyer just stood up and is looking around.
That's him, right?
I do think that moment is a little cute at the end because if you're watching the video,
you can see almost real excitement when he sees Owen.
Oh, look at Owen!
Hey!
I think that him and Owen might actually be friends.
I think that sounds right.
Because later on when Owen's on the phone and the two of them, I think, talk over each
other or something, there's some kind of a weird thing, they both apologize to each other
in a way.
That's cute.
Well, it's not so much that it's cute.
It seems human.
Yeah.
It seems like how people would interact.
I know.
That's what I'm saying.
Whereas it's cute that these automatons...
Watching Alex interact with people, it's so goddamn rude all the time.
He's got half a mouthful of sandwich.
Yeah, exactly.
It's bizarre to see actual excitement.
See my friend on TV and then also polite conversation.
It's bizarre.
Oh my god, Owen's on The Price is Right.
Owen's on The Price is Right, guys!
Everybody get around!
The standards are so low.
Anyway, I'm a guy who's just shoveling a little pile of stuff that looks bad in hindsight.
Sure, sure.
Just gonna add to that.
Digging that deeper.
Just gonna add to that pile over here.
Yep, okay.
Whoop, what's this?
Oh, it's a big one.
So today is the day that the Congress will vote on whether or not to certify and codify
the so-called fraudulent results of the election.
There are many machinations that could be pulled out here in the last minutes or so,
the last hours.
And of course, it's not really over until January 20th, but today is the day that we've
all been waiting for.
It's the day that Donald Trump himself requested his supporters come to Washington DC to see
him speak and to stand up against the lies, disinformation, and fraud of the mainstream
media and their controllers in the deep state.
Truly incredible stuff.
Of course, the word is that Alex Jones was requested by Donald Trump himself to lead
the march.
Really driving that home.
Oh boy.
I mean, he only said it twice, though.
I would have to hear it three times in order for it to be like, well, yeah, that would
be a pattern.
You know, once or twice is isolated incidents.
In just a few minutes, Alex Jones will actually be leading the march to the Capitol at the
behest, at the personal request of President Donald Trump.
Alex Jones will be at the head of that vanguard as the entire crowd, this massive human snake,
this huge, just unimaginable almost crowd of Trump supporters who have made their way
to the nation's Capitol, will wind its way towards the Capitol building.
Oh, so they're going to the Capitol building.
Wow.
This all looks really bad.
What a just glowing way to describe your friends and people you love.
They look like a giant human snake.
Yeah.
So the mood is jovial among Trump supporters in D.C., or at least that's what Harrison
is guessing, of course, based on his assessment of it from occupied Texas.
Yeah.
Come back, folks.
The mood is still a jovial one here.
And of course, as Rob Doo reported live on the scene there at the Save America March
in Washington, D.C., it's like it's uplifting.
Everybody's happy.
Everybody's feeling good.
But at the same time, there's an underlying aggressiveness beneath the surface and an
unrest, I suppose you could say, pervading the spirit of American Trump supporters.
Everybody's a little bit on edge because once again, we have tried and tried and tried and
tried and tried to play within the rules.
We have tried.
To make the system change itself, to get back on track, to stop having endless drive to
bankrupt and enslave us.
And time and time again, we are met with traitorous and seditious acts blocking us from carrying
out a legal, lawful within the bounds of the game changes.
And now they've prevented us at every pass.
Our last and final outlet was our sacred vote.
And that is what has been stolen from us, or at least is still in the process of being
stolen from us.
So you're making the argument that the jovial mood is pierced only by the recognition that
there are no more legal ways for you to deal with the problems that are existentially threatening
to you.
So you're saying that it's time to do illegal things.
It is a solemn moment that we must decide to extrajudicially take back our republic.
And it just so happens that that's exactly what we wanted to do, so we're feeling pretty
good about it right now.
It's a real jovial atmosphere, we're gonna kill a few people, it's gonna be great.
There'll be some jaunty music playing in the background.
We got a flapper contingent over there, they're doing a little...
So earlier in the episode we already heard Harrison saying that we had the stolen.
The Georgia election, the runoff was stolen.
So this bit of news that he comes to at the end of his show seems almost unbelievable.
Jack Pessobic reports that the Senate races in Georgia attracted 300,000 less votes than
Donald Trump got for president, indicating that the base stayed home.
Why would we go out of our way to support a party that refuses to lift a single finger
for the president of the United States who we all voted for?
These seem to be counter explanations for something.
They almost seem at odds with one another.
It almost seems that intentionally Infowars has self-contradictory narratives.
Right, right, right, right.
Perhaps even one would suggest that they don't even know what they believe is happening.
Maybe they're very confused.
Maybe they just report what feels good.
It feels right that they stole it.
Now obviously people didn't show up.
It also feels right that people would punish the GOP for abandoning Trump.
It makes sense that they wouldn't show up.
Yeah, but also they stole it.
They stole it.
Yeah.
Now, I mean, obviously it might have something to do with us saying that they stole elections
and that elections don't matter, so your vote doesn't matter, so it doesn't matter if you
vote.
Ali Alexander's making a lot of money off the stuff that's stealing the vote.
Exactly.
We're getting a taste.
I like it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So Harrison's hosting Alex's show, so it's basically just a smooth transition into the
Alex Jones show.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to the Alex Jones show.
I'm Harrison Smith.
It's January 6th, and Donald Trump has just begun speaking to the Stop the Steal march
in Washington.
Without any further ado, we go now to the President of the United States in Washington.
So I apologize in advance.
The first hour of the show is just Trump's speech, and so we're going to have to listen
to a little bit of it.
I know that we generally don't listen to stuff, but this is pretty wild.
Sure.
I think that it also sets the stage for a lot of the content and the things that end
up happening.
I'll listen to his words.
Please try not to scream too much.
We're recording this late.
I'm not screaming.
So it kind of begins with Trump rambling a bit about how his crowds are really huge and
fake news.
Unsurprising.
They never show the crowds, so they won't.
Of course not.
Go ahead.
Turn your cameras, please.
Would you show?
They came from all over the world, actually, but they came from all over our country.
I just really want to see what they do.
I just want to see how they cover it.
I've never seen anything like it, but it would be really great if we could be covered fairly
by the media.
The media is the biggest problem we have as far as I'm concerned.
Single biggest problem.
Wow.
Oh, you're making whimpering dog noises.
Oh, what a whimpering whiny- oh, no, the media's so mean.
Well, if that seemed kind of soft, wait for this one.
Okay.
There's so many weak Republicans, and we have great ones.
Jim Jordan and some of these guys, they're out there fighting, the House guys are fighting,
but it's incredible.
Many of the Republicans, I helped them get in.
I helped them get elected.
I helped Mitch get elected.
I helped... I could name 24 of them, let's say.
I won't bore you with it.
What the fuck is going on?
Even just now, this is so bizarre that this is what's happening, that this is the speech
that he's giving.
What a whiny... I never listened to him.
It's so weak.
I think this is something that is underreported amongst all of his terrifying words, is how
much of a pathetic little whiny whiner he is.
He's a whiner.
He's a little tiny whiner.
You imagine anybody else in a leadership position complaining about, I could name 24 people
I've helped who are ungrateful to me.
Oh my God.
Grow up.
I wouldn't respect that in a boss.
I wouldn't respect that in a contemporary.
I wouldn't respect that in anybody who's in elected office.
That is childish shit.
Can you imagine Obama... They made fun of my tan suit.
Everybody's so mean to me.
I helped all these Democrats get elected and they have abandoned me in my time of need
when I need people to stand up for my tan suit.
God, it's just pathetic.
This is so sad.
Anyway, it's been a while since I've heard a president swear.
And Trump says bullshit in the middle of this clip.
And then the audio-
Well, you weren't alive for Nixon.
Well, that's true.
I've heard some tapes.
I don't know if Nixon ever swore and then a crowd of people started chanting the swear
he just said.
Yes, come on, do it.
This year, using the pretext of the China virus and the scam of mail-in ballots, Democrats
attempted the most brazen and outrageous election theft, and there's never been anything like
this, so pure theft in American history.
Everybody knows it.
That election, our election, was over at 10 o'clock in the evening.
We're leading Pennsylvania, Michigan, Georgia, by hundreds of thousands of votes.
I don't understand things.
And then late in the evening or early in the morning, boom, these explosions of bullshit.
And all of a sudden, all of a sudden, it started to happen.
That's amazing.
Do you know why?
Do you know why all of this shit?
Do you know?
Here's what I'll say.
I will say this.
This is what I believe.
As much as the cops are totally complicit with all those people getting through and
all that shit, the reason that the National Guard and all of those people weren't already
at the ready is because of shit like this.
This is professional wrestling.
None of these people thought that any of this was real.
You're telling me that a crowd of people who's listening to the President of the United States,
a goddamn, the biggest economy in the world, a nuclear fucking power, is going to get taken
down by a crowd of assholes screaming, bullshit, bullshit, bullshit.
It's perfect.
Yes.
It's the same shit.
It's weird.
It's pathetic.
Yeah.
There are definite elements of overlap.
And when you're losing in a wrestling match, you got to fight harder.
And that's what Trump says people got to do.
This is keep in mind right before people stormed the Capitol.
And we want to be so nice.
We want to be so respectful of everybody, including bad people.
And we're going to have to fight much harder.
And Mike Pence is going to have to come through for us.
And if he doesn't, that will be a sad day for our country because you're sworn to uphold
our Constitution.
Now it is up to Congress to confront this egregious assault on our democracy.
Donald Trump giving it to Republicans and Democrats alike in defense of the Constitution.
We have to go to a quick commercial break.
It's the Alex Jones show.
We'll be right back.
So now it's up to Pence to save the Constitution, which I guess he didn't do.
Oh, no.
So the audience kind of took the message.
Yeah.
Seemed very one to one.
Seemed very if-then.
It's, again, narrative consistency.
It's kind of interesting how the night before, Owen was trying out a little bit of standup.
Yeah, he was doing a bit.
Yeah.
And I noticed that Trump might have the standup itch too.
He's got a bit.
He's got a little bit.
All right.
And the only unhappy person in the United States, single most unhappy, is Hillary Clinton
because she said, why didn't you do this for me four years ago?
Why didn't you do this for me four years ago?
You changed the votes, 10,000 in Michigan.
You could have changed the whole thing, but she's not too happy.
You don't see her anymore.
What happened?
Where's Hillary?
Where is she?
That bit did not land.
You would have expected that bit to go over gangbusters in that crowd, but no.
I think the problem with that bit is that he unfortunately undid his entire bullshit
for this election.
Yeah.
Why didn't they do it for her?
It's a comedic premise as much as it is a plot hole.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Huh.
Oh, why didn't those gunners on the destroyer shoot down the escape pod with C-3PO and R2D2
on it?
Good bit.
I don't know.
Hilarious.
So this is where things fall apart.
He wants to try and prove that there was fraud.
Sure.
Let's hear it.
It was rough.
Okay.
As you know, the media has constantly asserted the outrageous lie that there was no evidence
of widespread fraud.
You ever see these people?
Well, there's no evidence of fraud.
Oh, really?
Well, I'm going to read you pages.
I hope you don't get bored listening to it.
Promise.
Don't get bored listening to it.
All those hundreds of thousands of people back there.
Move them up, please.
All these people, don't get bored.
Don't get angry at me because you're going to get bored.
Because it's so much.
They do get bored.
Yeah.
He just starts rattling off numbers.
That'll happen.
And stuff.
And the audience, I don't think, is able to pay attention.
It's not exciting.
He loses them a little bit.
In retrospect, if all of these speakers had known that the crowd was more of a stormin'
crowd than a chantin' crowd, you know?
Like they like chantin' for sure.
But they love stormin'.
Well, we learned that.
I don't think the numbers game was really going to inspire them in the speeches department.
You kind of needed like a three quarters Alex.
Yeah, totally.
That's about where you want him to be.
Yeah.
You'll burn out too fast with a full Alex.
Totally.
But that same kind of energy, just a little bit lower.
And if you get stuck in the weeds, you're not coming back out.
No.
Nope.
Start talking about COVID shit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're fucked.
One out of every ten people.
We already stopped listening, buddy.
Start listing off counties.
Yeah, exactly.
Oh, yeah, don't.
Get the fuck out of here.
The only way to save that is you got to start complaining about Twitter.
Every time I put out a tweet, even if it's totally correct, totally correct, I get a
flag.
It gets flagged.
I get a flag.
And they also don't let you get out.
You know, on Twitter, it's very hard to come onto my account.
It's very hard to get out a message.
They don't let the message get out nearly like they should.
But I've had many people say, I can't get on your Twitter.
I don't care about Twitter.
Twitter's bad news.
They're all bad news.
Oh, man.
How funny is it how long everybody has tried to respect the office of the president?
Yeah.
How hilarious is it?
This might have all ended if TV news anchors just treated Trump the way I did.
And every time he whined, just went, oh, no, you're so sad.
And then everybody was done.
Maybe.
Yeah.
I mean, look, I know that generally we don't cover when, you know, Trump's speeches.
But often they don't play these full speeches on Info Wars.
Of course not.
And I had to listen to this.
I'm sorry.
So that's why we're...
That's why I have to listen.
And because there are things in it that are like, really, if you're listening in the audience,
you kind of get a certain message, and that is that Pence has got to seize power.
That's our only option.
Yeah, 100%.
And it's time that somebody did something about it.
And Mike Pence, I hope you're going to stand up for the good of our Constitution and for
the good of our country.
And if you're not, I'm going to be very disappointed in you, I will tell you right now.
I'm not hearing good stories.
He's not hearing good stories.
So I mean, that's pretty clear, but it's even clearer here.
The Republicans have to get tougher.
You're not going to have a Republican Party if you don't get tougher.
They want to play so straight, they want to play so...
Sir, yes, the United States.
The Constitution doesn't allow me to send them back to the States.
Well, I say, yes, it does.
Because the Constitution says you have to protect our country, and you have to protect
our Constitution, and you can't vote on fraud.
And fraud breaks up everything, doesn't it?
When you catch somebody in a fraud, you're allowed to go by very different rules.
I should know.
I've cheated on my wife.
And I hope Mike has the courage to do what he has to do.
And I hope he doesn't listen to the rhinos and the stupid people that he's listening
to.
You know, whenever you have the president up there saying that Pence is the last chance
to really save this and save the Constitution, he has a responsibility to do it, then Pence
doesn't do that thing.
And the president has also said that when something is stolen, you're playing by a different
set of rules.
It's kind of hard to not take away a message of, like, there's no rules.
The rules that are normal are gone.
I do find it difficult to take a would-be strongman dictator seriously if he gives an
entire speech exhorting his second in command.
What is a borderline honorary position?
It's to overthrow the country for him.
That's a little bit sad.
Mixed in with petty complaints about people being rude to him.
Real tough.
And Twitter traction.
Real tough to be terrified of this.
But that's kind of the thing, though.
That could easily be what blinds you to the real danger of a lot of things.
And it's easy to minimize what some real threats are because of that window dressing of, like,
isn't this pathetic?
Yeah, sure.
And shit.
Obviously.
Of course.
So, we're done with Trump's speech now.
That was the most of it that is relevant, because Harrison comes back and he wants to
throw it to a video of what's going on in Congress, where Mike Pence is presiding over
this.
But they actually send it to the streets, where Alex is bullhorning.
Let's go to inside the chamber here.
The report is...
So what does that mean?
It doesn't have a good rhythm.
It doesn't have a good meter.
No, it doesn't.
As far as the chant goes.
But also, again, he's chanting 1776.
I don't know what message you're supposed to take away from that other than overthrow
the government.
What happened in 1776 that he would be referencing?
I mean, there's that revolution...
Did anything else happen, though?
I mean, I'm certain.
I'm certain there were things that history has not recorded that happened.
Let's see.
Did, uh...
Probably someone opened a business.
Yeah, I would say that I think Benjamin Franklin opened up a little side gig grinding lenses.
I think that's also what happened in 1776.
I guarantee there was somebody in, like, Virginia who was also like, everybody cool out!
He's not referencing that.
1776!
The year Sam made his first beers!
Sam Adams!
Somebody in Virginia was trying to get people to have rationality, and calmer heads will
prevail!
Yeah!
That's not what he's referring to.
He's talking about overthrowing the government.
I think a diplomatic solution is in order!
So Alex still is not, like, great with long stretches, he'll still end up becoming really
overwhelmed by...
I mean, it's tough.
You gotta yell into a bullhorn.
Bullhorning is hard.
So Owen's gotta come in here and there.
Sure.
The Democrats have gone so insane that they're now making the words mother and father illegal
in legislative bodies!
Have you heard this?
Nancy Pelosi has proposed that the words mother and father are illegal.
So I got news for Nancy Pelosi!
Donald Trump is your daddy!
Too good.
Do twice.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
He's into that bit.
Oh man.
Yup.
So when I was listening to this action of Alex and Owen on the street, it really felt
like they were trying to juice this crowd up.
It feels kind of like incitement.
Ladies and gentlemen, Trump said in his speech today, he said the Democrats are out to get
us.
They want to destroy us!
They want for the globalist!
They want to bring America down!
But we're not going to let them do it!
This news system is a military high-tech attack, and we need to understand we're under attack,
and we need to understand this is 21st century warfare, and get on the road.
We need to get on the road.
And not just take this country back, but take the whole world back from the communist Chinese!
So I mean, it seems like if you're in the audience, you're probably, this is the kind
of thing that would be like, what you then yell, rawr, and then you charge, you know?
How should I take the country back?
You're not giving me answers.
I'm not getting concrete answers from you.
Supplements.
There's actually a way to take the country back in front of me, so I'm going to go do
that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You need to spread my links.
No, no, no, no.
See, you said take the country back.
Right, by spreading links to Band.video and buying supplements.
I left my phone in the car.
I guess I'll overthrow the government.
Just take a walk.
When you get back to the car, you'll be able to, just be cool.
But I want one of those pictures off that fucking wall, man.
Listen to me.
I went on a tour the other day, and there's this picture.
No, it's on the Capitol building wall.
Stopping the Chinese can only be achieved by more traffic coming to my website.
I don't think you understand.
We're at cross purposes!
We have different ideas of what 1776 looks like.
In your 1776, you get rich!
I feel like that's different than mine!
You're trying to profiteer.
So Owen, I'm sorry, not Owen.
Harrison has been pretty clear that allegedly, alleged, Donald Trump has personally asked
Alex to lead this march.
It's possible.
Now that's weird because while they're showing Alex, you can overhear a producer tell Alex
that Trump told the audience at his speech that they were going to march down Pennsylvania,
which Alex should know, because he's supposed to be leading that march.
He was led, yeah.
President's going to finish.
President's going to finish in ten minutes, and he just told the crowd, let's walk down
Pennsylvania.
Is this Pennsylvania?
Right, folks, this is a live feed from Washington, D.C.
Right now, Alex Jones and Owen Schroer speaking to a large crowd.
That exchange doesn't make much sense if Trump has asked Alex to, but whatever.
I don't care.
Trump is going down Pennsylvania Avenue.
Where am I?
Is this Pennsylvania?
Am I in D.C.?
Where am I?
Pennsylvania's a state.
That's a long walk from here.
So here is where we get our first mention of the breaching of barriers.
And I think it's really interesting because these people have started to encroach over
the line, and at the same time, you have audio of Alex yelling about the New World Order.
On the broadcast that Harrison is trying to put together, you have really an interesting
juxtaposition of these two things.
Mike Pence has rejected Trump's call.
He has failed to show the courage that Donald Trump was attempting to imbue in him and has
begun the counting of the electoral votes.
At the same time, there's word that thousands of patriots have broken through the barriers
around the Capitol and are now moving towards it to occupy this word from Elijah Shaffer,
who's on the ground.
And Alex Jones continues to speak to this crowd.
Let's go back to Alex Jones.
And the great awakening, the great reset is triggering the great awakening and the great
awakening will trigger the great rebellion and the destruction of the New World Order.
Looks bad in hindsight.
A lot of this looks real bad.
I just, I'm starting to see a pattern.
The word, it's thematic consistency.
Yeah, you know, a lot of the times I think the word incitement is overused.
You know, it's a very specific meaning.
This is that specific meaning.
Yeah, it's interesting because this group does, like that Alex is leading, are not the
same people that Harrison is talking about breaching these barriers.
But at the same time, Alex's group is going to go to the Capitol.
They're heading to the Capitol.
So some of the people that are in Alex's group may have gotten involved.
We'll have to.
I don't know, but I mean, they would hope for the time being, these are two separate
things that are happening are a hundred percent in sync.
And to the extent that like a lot of those people who are the first ones that were pictured
inside the Capitol building were QAnon weirdos, Alex is talking about the Great Awakening,
which is such a trademark of the Q followers.
Something that is basically their brand.
And it's just, it's a lot.
It's a lot.
But I will say, in Alex's credit, maybe not in Alex's credit, he's very insistent to make
sure people hear him say we're not politically nonviolent, nonviolent.
Yeah.
Upwards of, as we say, estimated a million people moving to surround the Capitol.
Owen Troyer and Alex Jones now speaking through the bullhorn to the crowds who follow them.
You stabbed us in the back one too many times.
Coming with truth and justice and non-violent civil disobedience.
Good to get that on the record.
No, there's, I think just after that you can hear someone say, you tell them Alex.
I think a producer also was in his ear there saying, hey, they were, they're actually doing
it.
So, uh, I don't know how much Alex would be aware of at this point because you know, communication
would be difficult with that many people in a, such a tight space.
Totally.
Communication could be tough.
I know that Alex does have quite a security detail that probably have walkie talkies and
private bands.
Yeah.
So there is a chance that, and actually spoiler alert, I know that he has somebody who's inside.
So like, I know that like he, I have a hard time believing he doesn't know more than it
appears.
Sure.
But also I don't know if he knows the full scope of things.
Right.
I think it would be strange that he would be very insistent on being like, we're coming
with nonviolent.
All right.
Yeah.
That seems a little bit telling.
But it also seems on brand for him.
I could believe like, cause he'd always says like politically, I want to kill you politically.
Yeah.
So it's hard to say.
Uh, they also, uh, you know, just getting people riled up while they walk.
It's fun.
We're never surrendering!
Until tomorrow.
This is our country!
Not our corrupt politician's country!
They work for us and it's time they got our family to remind us who their boss is!
The communist Chinese and the globalist and Hollywood don't run this country and our children
do not belong in their pedophile trash!
We will not accept the fake election of that child molesting Joe Biden, that Chinese communist
agent Joe Biden!
We know where he belongs and it's not the White House!
So something I think is really interesting about their dynamic, their tag team dynamic,
is like, they kind of have to do this because Alex doesn't have the cardio to walk and carry
on sentences and simultaneously Owen doesn't have the creativity to speak more than like
in little bursts.
Yeah.
So the two of them kind of need each other as crutches.
They're doing a good little two man game here.
I think of it as like a three legged race.
Yeah.
Well, it's no Siskel and Ebert teamwork level of complimentary parts here.
No.
Or some like good trading verses and some hip hop songs you might hear.
It's not that.
It's not fluid.
This is not definition.
No.
No, no Mos Def and Talib Kweli to be found here.
No, but it's the same thing in terms of like they need each other in order to make this
work.
Yeah.
It's blah.
Sad.
So Harrison's back in the studio and he has some other things to report, primarily he's
getting word that staffers are evacuating from these Capitol buildings.
Siskel is addressing the house right now, but here is an update as of less than a minute
ago Hill staffers have been told to evacuate the Madison building.
Things are getting tenuous here as Trump supporters and Patriots continue to pour towards
the Capitol.
Alex Jones himself at the head of a massive column of Patriots moving now towards the
United States Capitol building.
This again looks bad.
The government is fleeing Alex Jones is at the head of the rebellion.
Well, they're going to enjoin the rebellion that is already in progress.
They're the reinforcement column that's coming in.
Alex Jones is flanking the fucking Capitol building.
And to a certain extent, I kind of think that the reason that it's being presented like
this is they still think this is going to stop.
Yeah, no, of course.
They still think they're not going to get inside.
Everybody thinks that someone will stop these people.
Yeah.
But because there's still this like, eh, kind of vibe, this is all very positive.
This is a historic day, ladies and gentlemen, incredible things happening there storming
DC Patriots are rushing and surrounding the Capitol.
They're tearing down barriers.
Police are struggling to maintain the crowd mace and punches being thrown back and forth
to two house buildings have been evacuated.
The House Cannon building in the House Madison building have both been issued evacuation
orders.
Pence has said he cannot reject out electoral votes outright, but the Congress themselves
are objecting right now to the Arizona votes.
The vibe is really positive.
You know, this is, this is someone who's like really pumped to see what's happening.
Yeah, this is great.
This will never go wrong.
Yeah.
And I know that now there are a lot of people who are trying to make arguments that this
was Antifa.
Uh, certainly.
Oh, it was just so super Antifa.
Yeah.
There's a lot of folks who have been on that tip, but immediately as everything is unfolding,
Harrison wants you to know that this is not, these are the Patriots.
This is not black lives matter folks.
This is not Antifa.
These are Patriots and perhaps they finally boiled over.
You see the air filled with the mist of mace, the stinging gas that the police will be implementing
and that is also being implemented against the police as Patriots.
Wow.
So, I mean, he's being very clear that, and if you watch the video, there are people who
are macing cops, which is, you know, that's violence.
Yeah.
So yeah.
Check that just for later.
Totally.
Um, yeah, he's very clear.
This is not, this is us.
This is our guys.
We take responsibility.
They finally had enough.
He's celebrating all that.
Of course he is.
There's a celebratory vibe.
Of course it is.
American nationalists on Twitter, uh, asking president Trump to storm the Senate chamber.
This day is young folks and who knows what will be, uh, what the, what the future holds
for us.
Again, Elijah Shaffer reports Patriots have stormed the Capitol building ground and are
breaching federal barriers and police en masse.
Yeah.
That's what this day will bring.
Maybe exactly what you're talking about.
Could be exactly what you're saying is what you want to happen might happen.
Yeah.
And he's pretty consistently calling these people Patriots.
Sure.
Thousands, hundreds of thousands of people right now moving towards the Capitol.
The mass of humanity continues to grow as the police lash out their thin line of armored
officers, a pitiful resistance against the literal tidal wave moving towards them.
There's a pitiful resistance against these Patriots.
They're so strong.
Now.
Yes.
This is Harrison reporting on what he's seeing, right?
Because he has access to a lot of different information.
Yeah.
Alex may or may not.
So now we go to Alex on the street where everyone is chanting, fight for Trump.
Cool.
Chance of fight for Trump surrounding Alex Jones and Owen Troyer and the rest of the
info Wars crew as they move towards the Capitol here, we see a view from inside the Capitol
of staffers.
They're moving down the stairs, following that evacuation order.
You can't not see this as like two things that are about to intersect.
Sure.
A group of people who are fighting for Trump and a group of people that are being led by
Alex who are chanting, fight for Trump.
Right.
Seems to be.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's weird.
It's very weird.
Yeah.
I would.
Thematic consistency.
I would want this back.
Mulligan.
I would like a mulligan on today.
I don't think they can get that.
This show looks bad.
It's one part because Harrison Smith is hosting and he's terrible, but another part because
like, I mean, you could draw your own conclusions.
I don't, I don't think that like it would be wise or even sensible to say that like
Alex inspired a lot of these actions because I mean, like we already said, a lot of the
people who are the first photographed folks who were there, who had gotten in were Q folks
and they hate Alex.
It's easy to, if you don't have an awareness of those worlds to think like, Oh, it's all
the same.
Right.
It is not.
Those people do not listen to Alex.
Right.
There are similar information spheres in terms of a lot of the themes and the narratives
and the stories that they tell and the reality that they believe in, but they are not the
same group.
Now at the same time, Past Info Wars guests like Nick Fuentes and Baked Alaska were both
in the offices, live streaming, and that's a little bit fucked up.
They're Antifa.
Did you know that?
They are deep state secret Antifa agents that this entire time have been inspired.
Not just, see the problem was they wanted deep state Antifa agents to inspire right
wing violence.
Sure.
Right?
But there wasn't any right wing violence, Dan.
Oh, I see.
They would never existed, so they had to create it from the ground up.
I've got a conspiracy for you.
What's that?
Where do you live?
I live down the way.
What city?
Chicago.
What city is Nick Fuentes living?
Chicago?
Uh oh.
No way.
You're Nick Fuentes.
Stop yelling.
Sorry.
That's alright.
That deserved a yell.
Okay.
So this all just looks, it all looks really, really bad.
And especially thinking about the people who are, you know, it's sometimes tough for people
to get over their frustration with elected officials and feel too much empathy for them.
But then you think about people who are just staffers and people who are just on the job
and the terror that a lot of them probably felt.
Being whisked away to secure locations, I can't even imagine what that would be like.
And it's really fucked up to know that that is what a lot of people are experiencing.
And for this just to be like, they're kind of relishing it.
And Harrison is as well on air.
Now in the least unexpected thing ever, Trump is not going to the Capitol.
After he said, we're all going to the Capitol, they're all going to the Capitol, huge, almost
unprecedented crowd is moving towards the Capitol.
As we speak, as the debate rages inside, President Trump has apparently returned to the White
House.
That's the word that we're receiving from Washington.
He said he was going to go to the Capitol, but it looks like he's gone to the White House
instead.
Many people on Twitter encouraging him to storm the Senate along with his supporters.
And what we're seeing here are the independent journalist videos as the Trump supporters
move once again inexorably towards the Capitol building.
Yeah, I wonder why he would send everybody towards the Capitol and then not go there
himself.
That seems crazy.
That just seems crazy because he's their fearless leader, you know, he's the one at the, no,
they're willing to die for this man because he's willing to die for them.
Yeah.
This dude is a fucking potster.
So you remember that ragtime music that was playing earlier and the joyous, the joyous
tone square that Rob do was describing.
Yeah.
That vibe has changed.
Oh, it's changed.
Oh, no more flappers dancing.
Nope.
The joyous, uh, you know, uh, uh, upbeat atmosphere of the event earlier today has soured and
turned to rage as the fury of Trump supporters and Patriots crossing United States overflows
and expresses itself on the outside of the Capitol.
So the, the, the editorial tone, it appears to me to be pretty consistently righteous
indignation.
Yeah.
That is what is motivating this and they are right to do this.
They are right to storm the Capitol and Trump should be right there with them.
Are you saying that the founding fathers were wrong?
Mike Pence wouldn't stop this.
So someone's got to, or else the constitution has been pissed upon Mike.
Mike Pence is King George.
We got to take them out.
So the vibe is just excitement kind of about this because there's nothing Harrison can
really do other than be the guy who's calling it.
I'm the guy who gets to be on air while this is going on.
Yeah.
And again, this was as of 24 minutes ago and since then we've seen 24 minutes of rising
aggression, rising crowds, more police building evacuations.
And the reaction from across the nation is largely excitement as far as I'm concerned.
This is again, truly incredible and we'll continue to update and bring you more videos.
The vibe is excitement.
Yeah.
It was not the vibe that I was getting.
I took a, I took a slightly different temperature from the country based on the sense I was
getting, um, yeah, I, it seemed like everybody, uh, soured real quick.
Everybody was like, Oh, this is, Oh no, Oh no, that's not, Oh no, I didn't want that.
I saw a lot of people responding in ways that, um, were kind of like, Oh, Oh my, like, uh,
I can't believe I didn't see this possibility coming.
And I think it's a little, which is very funny from, uh, from where I I'm sitting.
Sure.
But I mean, at the same time, I think that had this not have happened this week, yeah,
you and I would have had a show where we would have said, ah, another dumb rally.
What do you, what do you expect is going to happen?
It's more just edging towards the hope that something like this would happen.
I'm not surprised that it did, but I'm shocked.
You know that, that, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think that there's a lot of people who are surprised.
And I see a lot of like scales falling from people's eyes and it would be easy to respond
to that with some kind of like a flippant, like I told you so, or, you know, like I get
on our, I, I, I'm glad that I haven't seen a lot of that because I think that that's
really counterproductive.
Yeah, totally.
And I hope that people who, I mean, I did tell you so though, you want to engage in
that.
That's your business.
But I was facetious.
I know.
Come on.
There's a white right wing extremist storming the white house and they're like, oh, this
is what people have been talking about for a while.
That is fucked up.
All right.
Okay.
Great.
No need to shame anybody as long as they remember that this is a problem.
Yeah.
Tomorrow too.
Yes.
It didn't stop yesterday.
No.
And it doesn't, and today, I mean, spoiler alert, we don't know what Alex's response
is to it, but Trump has basically been like, all right, whatever, it's over.
It reminded me, and that doesn't end it.
Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no.
That does not end the problem.
The reaction to it reminded me so much of, uh, my partner was watching a documentary
the other day and they, some, one of the bad guys, it was like a crime documentary about
a small town that had gotten rogue with the police department and the Sheriff's department.
And she was like, can you believe this?
This guy thinks that the Sheriff is the highest constitutional power in the land.
And I was like, well, baby, you ain't got no idea.
Let me tell you about, uh, one sixth of the country.
Yeah.
And that's, that's what I'm saying.
Like all these people watch this and I'm like, and it's the same reaction of, of like, I,
I know you thought that that couldn't be real.
Yeah.
Oh, but it is.
One sixth of the country is too high.
I was, I was, I was desperately grasping for a number and that's what came to my head.
This is why Trump can't do rallies anymore.
Too many numbers.
Um, so, but it comes down to, for Harrison though, again, is just righteous indignation.
That is the name of the game.
We do know is that the Washington establishment is scrambling any and all officers they have
at their command in order to deal with this massive outpouring of anger, fury, and righteous
indignation coming from the Trump supporters.
You can there see, we have the Fox News feed up and even they are having trouble maintaining
the integrity of their signal.
So yeah, it's just righteous indignation.
These people have been pushed to the point where this, this response is the only, only
thing that can be done.
You have created an imaginary reality wherein I have pushed, been pushed too far.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So there's rallies going on in other states as well.
There's some fucked up stuff happening elsewhere.
Harrison covers this and then says something pretty scary.
Los Angeles as well, a stop the steal rally lining the streets.
Hundreds of Trump supporters, people cheering it on on Twitter saying, drag them out, saying
go into the Capitol building and drag the traitors out.
That does not seem like something that could have been impossible.
No.
Had things gone slightly differently, I could see some harm coming to representatives and
Congress members.
No, there were people walking around with zip ties.
I saw those pictures.
I didn't have a chance to look into them enough to feel really confident, but that was really
scary.
Yeah.
The people who tweeted them out, I trust enough to be like, I have to go search down every,
you know?
No, totally.
I just, for my standpoint, I didn't want to, I didn't, I can't, I can't back that a hundred
percent of my own looking into it, but I don't think it's fake.
I just don't know enough.
But that's scary as hell.
Even the possibility that that is what someone was up to going to take hostages or some shit.
Put a citizen's arrest on Chuck Schumer or something.
Like it's terrifying.
Wow.
I guess we have slightly different takes.
No, I understand.
It is terrifying, but it is also deeply funny.
That's the problem.
That's where I'm, I'm struggling with this because we are looking at a group of people
who stormed the fucking Capitol building, but we are also looking at a series of pictures
of people smoking weed in Nancy Pelosi's office.
So that's deeply funny.
Sorry.
So Harrison is going on and I just can't hear this as anything other than just like, this
is really positive coverage.
There are people such as a Dana lash saying, stop this to Trump supporters who are moving
towards the Capitol.
Other people saying, get in there and tear them out.
Oh, here we see my God, these images are just incredible.
Massive numbers of Patriots storming the Capitol building, Texas flags waving American flags
waving and masses of humanity have apparently broken past the police barricades, which were
keeping them off the steps and away from the Capitol building.
They have been torn down and the people have moved onto that raised platform and are scaling
the scaffolding that was set up.
So at this point, you know, we don't have people inside, but you do have an awareness
that there are people who are a large mass of folks who are not seeming to have all that
much resistance from the authorities who are making their way towards the Capitol building.
You have people online who are expressing a desire for people to be dragged out.
You have people who want Trump to come and lead a charge on the Senate.
So you have that awareness.
And when you have that in the, in the sort of context of what's going on, you hear a
clip like this and you're like, you just want somebody to kill.
You just want, you want somebody to kill someone you don't like.
Incredible.
And the crowd continues to swell.
What was it?
I mean, I've lost track of time.
I think it was less than an hour ago, an hour ago that President Trump finished his speech
and that massive crowd of hundreds of thousands, probably upwards of a million people surrounding
the Washington monuments and all the way to the White House finished watching that speech
by President Trump and moved towards the U.S. Capitol.
And by the time that, uh, here we see an update from Ilhan Omar, currency in the Capitol buildings
are locked down and everyone is sheltering in place.
Hey, so look, that's where Ilhan Omar is, everyone.
Just kidding.
Uh, uh, what?
No, just kidding.
That's not just kidding.
The joke is, hey, from this vantage point, you can tell where she is.
You know that there are tons of people who are, who are storming the Capitol building
and now you're saying, hey, wouldn't it be fun if one of you, wouldn't it be fun?
She's just joking.
That's where she is.
Yeah, that's, that's...
This person who we've expressed extensive hatred for.
Yeah, yeah.
Even if I believed somebody was joking when they said that, that's poor taste.
Oh yeah.
And he's not joking.
No.
So don't give me this just JK bullshit.
Yeah.
I would say that Harrison is pragmatic to a fault.
Um, and that is that he, it does not care at all about the people in the, in the Congress
building.
Sure.
And to a certain extent, I kind of get where he's coming from in terms of like, there are
safety precautions in place.
Yeah.
Like there are evacuation routes.
There are, you know, so I get, I get where he's coming from.
It doesn't seem super callous, I guess, but he is just like, eh, who cares?
They'll be able, the people inside aren't in any danger.
The congressmen and women and senators, I don't think are at much of a threat.
We know there's one thing they take very, very seriously.
It is their own personal wellbeing and their own security.
There are tunnels of course, crisscrossing like spiderwebs throughout all of DC and there's
almost no risk of them having to try to escape through a crowd or having to bunker down in
the Capitol building.
They have escape routes more than they need.
So again, I do not think there's actually a bodily threat to anybody in the chambers
at this moment.
They don't seem too concerned.
They're continuing to argue, continuing to debate without so much as a look over their
shoulder as to the doors being broken down or anything like that.
This is simply a massive protest that is refusing to stay quiet any longer.
That is making themselves known.
That is not stopping at the barricades, not a cow towing and adhering to the police who
have betrayed us time and time again, but instead are pushing forward to take over what
is, at the heart of it, our building.
I find it hard to believe that they would be covering, let's say, Black Lives Matter
protest at the White House similarly.
No, the same way.
Same way.
I seem to recall when, over the summer, when there were those large fences that people
were up against and like, you know, yelling at cops and maybe somebody threw a water bottle.
Right, right.
A water bottle was a dangerous instrument.
Yeah, yeah.
Then it wasn't, you know, a situation where everyone's safe inside, they've got evacuation
routes.
Right.
I don't know.
It just seems a little bit selective.
I do.
I do like the, they have more escape tunnels than they need.
That's such a funny way of putting it.
They're lousy with escape tunnels.
That is such a funny, they've got more than they even need.
Yeah.
This is the type of thing we're wasting taxpayers' money on.
They've got four escape tunnels.
They've got four that don't go anywhere.
It's like that Futurama joke where they're carrying the tanker full of oil and he's like,
this has 5,000 hulls.
And whenever it breaks open, there's like, oh, if only there were 5,001 hulls.
It would be great if there's just like, there's so many escape tunnels down here.
There's like, they go in circles.
Yeah.
It's just pointless.
It's just out of control.
Yeah.
So now.
That's where all, if, if the Capitol building turned into the Scooby-Doo bit, where they're
all going up through the tunnel and exiting one door and then closing it and then coming
back out.
That'd be great.
So good.
So at this point, people have breached the building and this is where I think a lot of
people around the country and the world were like, oh boy, fuck.
Oh shit.
Senators, the vice president, the congressmen now no doubt making their way towards the
security of the underground tunnels to escort them away from the threat of their supposed
constituents, angry, furious, and now venting that frustration on the system that has betrayed
them time and time again.
This is just incredible folks.
You're watching info wars.
So you've got people who have come in and the, uh, the evacuation, they're afraid of
their constituents.
It's an interesting way to frame it.
There's a certain part of me that almost is like good on you for sticking with it longer
than most of the right wing media did.
Well, you know, like they were already at the point where they're like, this is wrong
and all this stuff.
And Harrison Smith is like, this is what we guys, this is what we wanted.
I remember I wanted, I want to disagree with the phrasing.
Good on you.
Yeah.
What you're trying to say, I agree with.
It's remarkable that you are still, you're still on it, buddy.
Everybody.
You, if you, at this point, everyone was cutting bait.
What you didn't realize is that you thought everybody was in a line right next to you
and you took one step forward and they are gone.
There's nobody behind me.
Yeah, no.
Harrison is thrilled.
It's a privilege for him.
Of course.
Uh, at least I would say my estimation, a million Trump supporters having moved from
throughout to DC and are now converging on the Capitol.
This is revolution in progress.
This is a major historic moment in the history of the United States and is a privilege and
an honor to be here sharing it with you and bringing you updates just as soon as possible.
I suspect that he may be more of a true believer than a lot of the people at Infowars.
Yeah, that sounds like true belief.
And I also think he's a dork.
Uh, yeah.
Anyway.
I'm, I'm just saying, uh, yes, it is a historic moment, uh, but it will probably be remembered
more for an idiot in a headdress smiling, carrying a podium than, uh, the, uh,
There will be a resonant image.
Yeah.
But, uh, in order to justify a lot of this, I think, I think Harrison probably has a good
sense that like, well, people aren't going to like this too much.
Hmm.
Going to have to make this palatable, uh, to some of the more normie, uh, parts of the
audience as if Infowars has a lot of that.
Yeah, no ton of them.
Um, the only way that they can do this is by being like, the left protests a lot and
CVS is burned down and stuff.
We've seen six months or more of violent protest burning down entire cities, aimless, pointless
destruction being wrought across the United States by liberal and communist agitators,
all to the point of trying to tear down our system.
Now we see not the system fight back, but those who love America fight back patriots
now taking over the entire Capitol steps, continuing to wave the American flag, the
Gadsden flag, the tree of Liberty flag, the Trump flag.
They've taken it over.
It is done.
This is what happens when Americans rise up.
This is what happens when patriots do what the communists have been trying to do for
so long.
This doesn't look great.
I want to, I want them to eat those words.
I would like to print those words out and I would like to see them eat those papers.
I don't, I don't think this is going to age great.
I think Alex might be needing to fire Harrison soon and it's not because he didn't take calls
on the American Journal.
No, no, no, no.
I think that this is something Alex is- It's because he will be getting some calls
from the authorities.
I think at a certain point, Alex might have to pretend a lot of this stuff didn't, uh,
this wasn't what we did.
This is a rogue Infowars employee who is saying all of this stuff.
I don't know Harrison.
The views expressed by Harrison Smith do not represent-
I never met that guy.
Never heard of him.
He's an independent contractor.
Did you know that, Dan?
We found those Soros contracts with Antifa though, which we love to report on, Alex.
Anyway, this is all just the globalists, man.
They've pushed Patriots too far.
Totally.
I have in my note here, this is dramatically pro-storming coverage.
Time and time again, the American people have shrugged and taken the blows on the back without
so much as a whimper in protest, but finally they have pushed too far after stealing our
last resort.
They always knew in the back of our minds, in the back of our heads, we had the numbers.
We had the will.
We could, through the electoral process, maintain some semblance of control over what is supposed
to be our representative democracy, our republic.
Well, they stole that from us.
They took away the final lifeline.
They destroyed the final pressure valve, and now the rage of the American people overflows
as Patriots storm into the United States Capitol, waving Trump flags, waving American flags,
waving the Gadson flag, taking over the steps, pushing through the doors, and forcing an
evacuation of our representatives as they halt the vote counting process.
He's loving this.
Yeah.
Yep.
This is the best day of Harrison's career.
It is so funny listening to that in retrospect, just because that like, this is an ocean wave
that's coming, and all I can think in my head is, no, you guys have been terrorist edging
for a long time, and your idiots came too soon.
That's what happened.
Yeah, and you're going to end up having to make the best of it, and I think that Alex
can get that sense once he shows up, but Harrison isn't experienced enough.
He doesn't really know how to play the game that Alex needs to play in order to be profitable
in situations like this.
This is going to take some fine threading, if you will.
Because Harrison actually believes that there's a chance that this is going to lead to a real
revolution.
We're going to do it.
We're going to take him over.
Where Trump is going to stay in office.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Nonsense.
So anyway, he tries to go to Alex, because Alex is in D.C.
He's somewhere.
What are we going to figure this out?
Ah, doesn't really, can't quite get a hold of him.
Got to go to break.
But Americans are mad, and so when they stage elections in Venezuela, are they speechless?
These incredible folks live updates from Alex Jones, more on the other side.
The Capitol has fallen, the Patriots are in control.
The Patriots are in control, the Capitol has fallen.
So he's able to get a hold of Alex there, but he can't talk to him.
Alex is just rambling.
Hilarious.
So they go to break, and the fucking Capitol has fallen, is the report.
You know, one thing that I like to do is sometimes while the craziest shit is going on, I'll
split screen it on my computer with just like a stock feed.
The Capitol has fallen.
Patriots have taken over.
Stocks go up by like one point.
Do you think the stocks would just stay the same if the entire United States had been
overthrown?
Well, I mean.
And Patriots had, come on.
I know that the stock market lives and dies by the reportage of Harrison Smith.
Yes, exactly.
As he's the most trusted newsman of our generation.
The Cronkite.
So, the paper of record.
Millennial Cronkite.
That's what they call him.
The young gray lady.
Old wolf in sheep's clothing blitzer.
Yeah.
So, Harrison has a little thought here.
It's like, hey, we stopped the steel.
Just the sheer crowds all over the Capitol steps waving stop the steel signs, waving
American flags.
For the time being, at least the steel has been stopped.
We have, we're no longer counting the votes, no longer debating the certification.
It has all ground to a halt, it has all ceased to continue as the lawmakers and the other
Capitol Hill staffers flee.
I just have this picture in my head of Harrison Smith in a fighter pilot outfit on an aircraft
carrier with a big banner.
Totally.
100%.
Steel stopped.
Big banner behind.
I don't know if we can print up a better Dewey defeats Truman than we stopped the steel.
At least he had the good sense to say at least temporarily.
At least, yeah, I was going to say.
Good work, buddy.
So, there's some stuff going on and it involves protesters, right wing ding dongs, assaulting
officers and Harrison's pretty excited about that.
My God, now the protesters have gotten their hands on fire extinguishers and are spraying
them at the people, the congressional staffers and members of the media who are attempting
to film them.
They're getting a face full of fire extinguisher gas as police continue to radio and we heard
over the radio from the US Capitol Police, we have lost control, repeat, we have lost
control.
Control now seated to the patriots who have breached the Capitol.
Alex did like days worth of coverage about people yelling at Sarah Huckabee Sanders at
a restaurant.
They made her feel bad.
They made her feel bad, it was public.
Every private citizen is entitled to the right to go eat at a restaurant.
What if they had sprayed her with a fire extinguisher?
Well, now that's fine.
What is she afraid of her constituents, Dan?
Strictly speaking, that is assault and we've already heard him talking about punching and
macing coming towards the officers, so that's at least three instances that Harrison is
very keenly aware of, of violence that's being done by these people against the cops.
Now obviously no situation is perfect at any protest and I don't think that you can respond
to the entirety of the group just based on the actions of an individual, but those people
should definitely have been treated differently.
What they're doing is not appropriate and it's not property damage that is directed
towards bodily harm and hurting another person, which is now assault.
Anyway, I just want to make a clear line there because Harrison later will pretend that he's
not aware of any violence.
No violent actions happen.
So also, interestingly, Harrison's thrilled that they've stolen police equipment.
People now ceded to the patriots who have breached the Capitol and are moving ever further
into this Capitol building.
People dressed as pioneers, people carrying riot shields that have been stripped from
the Capitol City police, MAGA hats, Confederate flags, American flags, Gadson flags.
I just can't imagine, you know, the picture, you know, the left-wing protesters have stolen
riot shields from police and they've entered the state out.
I can't imagine you being like, this is protest.
Yeah, yeah.
You would say this is America's fallen or whatever the fuck, but I guess he is actually
saying America's fallen.
Yeah, that's true.
We have now taken it.
Yeah, we're stoked about it.
I guess there isn't that much difference, honestly.
Yeah, man, weird.
Weird to think of the number of dead that there would have been if this was a left-wing
crowd.
Oh, the people who are...
So many people would have been killed.
Yeah, I think you're right.
It's tough to litigate that kind of what-if, but yeah, I think...
You know that whole, like, how is it that so many people could do this?
I thought if you went for the Capitol building, you would just get mowed down, you know?
If this was a left-wing protest, oh, believe me, you would have.
It seems that way, yeah.
So Harrison's still giving positive coverage of this event, and at this point, he does
know that they've shot tear gas in the chamber, and he's kind of aware that someone got shot.
He doesn't know any of the details about it, but he's aware that someone...
There's reports that someone's been shot, and he's still like, eh, it's good times.
From Disclose TV, protesters are smashing the doors to the U.S. House chamber.
That's the image that we saw just a second ago of the furniture being piled up in an
attempt to prevent, or at least waylay or delay, the breaking into the House chamber
there.
U.S. Senate chamber has been evacuated, and senators are being taken to a secure location.
House members are being instructed to put on masks as tear gas is now inside the U.S.
Capitol dome, folks.
This is, again, unprecedented.
This is history being made as we speak.
So this is, like, severe.
Like the situation has deteriorated to an outrageous extent, and Harrison's still definitely
cool with it, to the point where he's saying, like, yeah, they're rioting, but good.
We took back the Capitol.
The security of the Capitol building has been utterly devastated and decimated, and the
rioter...
Well, yeah, I guess we'll call them rioters.
Why the hell not, right?
The rioters, the protesters, the patriots, the Americans, the Trump supporters, the revolutionaries
have taken the Capitol.
The U.S. Capitol has fallen to the American people.
This day will go down in history, ladies and gentlemen, and you're getting it all live
here at m4wars.com.
Make no mistake about it, this would still be the tone if it had been successful.
Yeah.
Yeah, totally.
Like, this is...
It would have been more jubilant.
Yes.
Yeah.
This would have continued if shit did not fall apart, and people didn't just leave.
I want to bottle the feeling of joy that he felt for almost a short period of time.
Mm-hmm.
Because that must have been really nice.
Yeah, but it also comes hand in hand with the embarrassment that he's got to feel now,
because this was recorded.
Oh, yeah.
That's why I would only bottle the joy, and I would enjoy that like a cold glass of water.
Sorry.
Mm, that joy is delicious.
That joy causes the hangover.
Harrison, you can keep the embarrassment and sadness of being you.
And unfortunately, that joy has the hangover effect of realizing you were so naive.
So fucking stupid.
Yeah.
Anyway, at this point, Harrison is heard...
He didn't mention it in that last clip, but he is aware at that point that someone had
been shot.
And so now he's reporting that he's heard that someone got shot in the arm.
Just got this information not confirmed, but we have reports of a woman shot in the arm
attempting to breach the chamber.
So we have guns drawn inside the chamber, furniture piled against the door, the security
is firing out through the door, and is apparently shot woman in the arm.
So this is the reporting that he's giving based on preliminary stuff, which is incorrect,
but you know, oftentimes as information's coming in, you can make some mistakes here
and there.
I'm not going to hold it against him too harshly.
I am going to blame him for being so goddamn boring.
I've got to assure you all, Alex will be coming back eventually.
We'll get to Alex.
How can you think that you are living through a successful overthrow of the United States
government by your side, and still be this boring?
Yeah.
Well, I mean, on some level he knows he took over for David Knight, so...
Well, that's fair.
He knows where the bread's buttered.
He's got to deliver.
He's got big shoes to fill.
Alex probably hired him, he's like, I need a boring guy.
I need another boring guy.
I need a backup boring guy in case my relief...
You're my boring understudy.
Yeah, you're my relief pitcher.
So at this point, there's a video going around of some people commandeering a window washing
rig.
Sure.
Yeah.
And Harrison's fucking pumped.
Oh my God.
This is amazing.
All right, so now we're seeing video of the protesters.
They seem to have commandeered a window washing platform, and are raising themselves up to
the second floor to perhaps breach the windows there.
Trump flags waving, American flags waving.
Shots have been fired.
We have reports of one woman shot from a protester, a female protester, has been shot by the Capitol
security presumably, who is inside the house chamber there, furniture piled up against
the door.
There were protesters trying to get through that door.
Shots were fired through the window of that door, and seemingly struck a protester.
These are the unconfirmed reports that we are receiving from less than a minute ago,
and we'll continue to bring you updates as we get them, folks.
This is the revolution, and it's only going to be televised on Infowars.com.
I'm receiving updates.
Oh.
What a dork.
Oh, what a loser.
What a loser.
You really think this is only going to be covered by Infowars?
So funny.
What a fucking...
Oh, we are getting reports that the Death Star is going down.
Oh, no, I can see it.
Luke Skywalker has commandeered a window washing vehicle, and he is slowly making his way towards
the exhaust port.
We are going to be televising this the entire way.
I love this dumb, dumb ass kind of thing where it would be like someone being like, Richard
Nixon has resigned.
That's the kind of news you're only going to hear on my channel.
No, everyone's going to cover that.
Ladies and gentlemen, I am sad to report that JFK has been assassinated.
You'll not hear that on other networks.
You are only going to hear that on Infowars.
No one else is saying shit about it.
Pretending this isn't a gigantic news story that is going to dominate every news cycle
for a while.
So ridiculous.
Yeah.
So at this point, Harrison, I don't know exactly how it happens, maybe by way of images or
a video, but Harrison comes to the realization that this shooting is worse than he had realized.
And this is not someone's arm.
Now we're not having fun.
The tone shifts dramatically and very, very noticeably.
And here we see the bloody stretcher and a woman, oh my gosh, oh my God, putting pressure
on a wound.
It looked like, we heard before she was shot in the arm, that looked like she was shot
in the chest, perhaps the collarbone, but absolutely covered in blood as she's rushed
away from the Capitol.
This may be the first casualty of the second American revolution.
This woman who is presumably, oh my God, and they're pumping her, wow, they're pumping
her chest.
That means she was most likely unresponsive.
That woman may have died or at least sustained a critical energy.
So Harrison, I don't know if he knows how to handle a lot of this stuff.
This is pretty, this is tough because you've been spending your entire day sort of teasing
people towards doing something like this, celebrating as it happens, and now the reality
that someone has been shot and is probably dead.
It's tough.
It's tough to cover all of that.
Especially when you're someone like Harrison who just doesn't have the skills.
It is in the real world, in his world, in the world that they all believe in, that should
be expected?
That should be an expected casualty of your fucking revolution?
Are you telling me, are you telling me that you think you're going to overthrow a fucking
country and then you're going to get all wingy and sad when someone gets shot and dies?
Fuck off.
And I think there's some decent instincts on Harrison's part with saying like the first
casualty of the American Revolution.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what you should be saying.
That's him keeping it in the pocket of the patriot lore.
Yeah, exactly.
That he needs to build in real time in order to be profitable.
But at the same time, from an emotional standpoint and from a performance standpoint, I don't
see him being able to keep up his character.
No, no, because it's a character.
And because this is someone's dead.
I understand that somebody's dead.
In the real world, that's a fucking tragedy.
What I'm saying is that these people are imagining themselves as fucking revolutionaries, and
then they all quit and cried because somebody died.
You cannot scream 1776 at me and then be like, whoa, somebody got shot?
Oh my god.
Well, I can explain Alex's angle on it much better as soon as he comes around.
Harrison's a little bit more of a mystery to me.
And I think, I'm not entirely sure, I just don't think he's very good.
No, he sucks.
He's supposed to be doing a job, but I just don't think he does it very well.
And that's why you gotta get Alex and Owen on the phone.
Shit's getting real.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So they get on the phone, and Owen's trying to talk to Harrison, his good friend who saw
him in that video.
You know, they're buddies.
Yeah, yeah, they're great.
Alex just keeps yelling in the background, contradicting the entire day's coverage.
Love it.
Dave, I'm on air right now.
No, basically, okay.
I want to get live, Dave, so I'm just hearing this story.
The city is going under martial law, we caught Antifa provocateurs, with witnesses and the
footage that first started the storming, but then triggered all this.
So Alex is going to be breaking that down momentarily.
Yeah, in a moment Alex is going to be explaining that Antifa did all this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because now we gotta figure out a way to not have any kind of involvement.
This is going to look bad.
We gotta thread this needle, baby.
Aw, man.
Yep.
These white people are so fucking entitled, they think they're entitled to a revolution
without getting hurt.
Or looking bad.
Yeah, exactly.
So Alex is decreeing in the background, yelling while Owen's on the phone, that they're going
commercial-free.
They can't go commercial-free on all shows, commercial-free.
I'm telling you folks, this is historic, they've declared basically martial law, they're sending
in National Guard, it's absolutely insane, all because Antifa, the minute Trump announced
he was going to come speak, Antifa, dressed up like patriots but with knee pads and arm
pads, attacked the police to stage the triggered event.
So they triggered this stampede, we have the witnesses, we have the police.
I guess at this point he had taken the phone from Owen, which is probably smart.
It would be smart, because Owen clearly doesn't have the lines yet.
No, no, and Alex can just rattle off this narrative without anything.
No, no, and it could be a switch that he flips instantly and just be like, oh are we doing
Antifa now?
Okay, I'll switch to my Antifa rambling nonsense.
And if I have my timeline right, the National Guard definitely had not been at this point.
This is tough, because this is a direct contradiction of Harrison's narrative that he's been building
for hours at this point, watching this event happen live.
This is patriots who have righteous indignation, they've been pushed too far.
No it's not, it's Antifa provocateur-ing, and they're the ones who stormed things.
The patriots were trying to keep it peaceful, they had not had enough, they could put up
with much more.
God dammit.
So now we have two completely contradictory narratives being sold.
Now, Owen is on the same phone call with Alex, and he is there, he's contradicting Alex.
He's got number three?
It's so tough to really put this into perspective, because here's the deal, we're not violent
revolutionaries, but they've taken our country, our country is occupied, and you can debate
all day long what the appropriate response is, the point is, we finally have a response,
and we haven't had any fight in our Congress, we haven't had any fight in our legislatures,
and so this is what's going to happen, is we the people are going to have to fight.
Again, we did not come here as violent revolutionaries, but the history is definitely being made right
now.
I don't know if today is the turning point that will change the course of American history,
but this is just the nexus of the beginning.
So this is a direct contradiction of Alex, he's closer to the narrative that Harrison
has been selling throughout the day, this is patriots who have had enough.
Now the thing that I have a difficult time with is we can have different opinions about
I don't know whether pasta is good, like maybe you don't like it.
Who, you and me?
Yeah, it's sort of an opinion.
We have different opinions.
Yeah, but we both agree that pasta exists.
I begrudgingly admit that, yes.
They have fundamental contradictions about the reality of what has happened and what
it means and everything.
These two things cannot coexist together, and they're asking their audience to believe
that it's just sort of a little disagreement that we have, sort of an interpretation thing.
No, it's not.
No.
It's very important.
There's something that's underappreciated about, I think the difference that we're seeing
between these and the Black Lives Matter protests is kind of built around the fact that all
of these right wing ding dongs are fighting a different enemy.
Like they all have their own conception of the evil government, whether it's lizards
or anything, it's all completely different from the person standing next to them.
They have same things they chant and same things they scream, but deep down they're
all fighting a different fight.
And in Portland, everybody was fighting the same singular fight.
Sure.
And one of the things that I actually think is at the core of why I disagree with you
about the nature of what happened on Wednesday, where you're saying they all looked stupid
and this is going to have a deflationary effect.
I look at this and I worry that the way that it will be used, this event, will be used
in the same way that things like Ruby Ridge and Waco were used in the 90s.
In the aftermath of those events, you had the Rocky Mountain Rendezvous, where you had
a bunch of different right wing extremist groups who also didn't see eye to eye about
what their enemy was.
Some people thought it was just a big government.
Some people thought it was the Jews.
And they all got together and were like, well, we got to work together.
And that is what emboldened and grew the militia right wing community in the 90s.
I do worry that this will have a galvanizing effect, especially with you have a death that,
spoiler alert, is something that Alex is going to try and use to make a martyr out of.
That is going to be the game that Alex ends up playing.
You have a lot of the essential elements that you would need to try and create this focal
point where you could get people of different, like, how could you get QAnon folks and Alex
to work side by side?
Seems like this is something that we could reach detente over.
I get that.
I think the difference for me between the Ruby Ridge and those examples that you've
given are that they were in response to an aggressor.
There were people coming at them as well.
It was not a, it was not a bunch of morons and the cops let them go.
There was a conflict.
We don't have time.
I know we're not going to do all that.
No, we don't have time to get into all of that, but I will say that perception is what's
more important than reality in terms of Patriot lore.
I agree.
The stories that can be told can put people in the roles that they need to be in in order
to make the story that you would see as a bunch of losers going home and looking stupid
as being exactly what's needed.
I will be interested to see how they do it.
I'm not saying that that is what's going to happen.
As I was seeing all this happen, that was the fear that I had.
That was the worry that I have about the pieces of this and the way that I see Alex responding
to it.
That is, is kind of, but I don't know.
We'll see.
Yeah.
Anyway, um, everybody's contradicting each other in a way that is, um, it's just, it's,
it's incomprehensible.
If you're a listener, I guess you just gotta be on team Owen and Harrison or team Alex.
Yeah, whatever.
Or whomever.
And now Harrison has realized that, uh, shit, someone got shot, probably dead.
Um, you know what?
These protesters, they were completely nonviolent.
Get the fuck out.
That's the only violence I have seen perpetrated so far beyond, uh, you know, one or two punches
in return for a punch thrown by a police officer.
The only violence I have seen has been the cold blooded point blank shooting of a woman
in the chest by the capital city police rather.
Yeah.
That's the only violence.
Gone are the memories of people shooting fire extinguishers at cops, cops, cops, anytime
they punched.
Sure, they punched a cop, but that's not violence.
That's more like, you know, Oh, we're all tough guys here.
Yeah.
So now the entire tone has kind of changed for Harrison and he's in justification mode
and it's almost entirely for a long stretch of time.
Him talking about how the left gets to protest, protest against them, then you get shot.
The leftists are saying, just shoot them all.
You know, if you dare protest against us, we can protest, we can burn your city down
for a year and a half.
And just, you know, for a year, for four years, we can just, um, obstruct everything.
We can destroy everything.
We can murder people in cold blood vice magazine will give us a, uh, a good 30 minute documentary
in order to call him racist and a bigot and a Nazi in order to justify his death.
That's the reaction you get if you are a protester on the left.
This is really hollow for me.
Uh, but it seems to be like their mic drop moment because Harrison just keeps coming
back to that argument and it's just, I don't care.
Yeah.
I get the fuck out of here.
Um, so he hears what Ted Cruz's response is and I think Harrison's a little bit surprised
to learn that Ted Cruz is not on board with this from Ted Cruz.
He says, quote, those storming in the Capitol need to stop.
Now the constitution protects peaceful protest, but violence from the left or right is always
wrong.
I've not seen any violence.
I've not seen any violence from the protesters yet.
Am I wrong?
And the crew tell me, have I seen, have I seen violence from the protesters?
Yes, you have.
You've mentioned some of it.
You commented on it earlier, sir.
And you were excited about it.
You were stoked.
Yeah.
In fact.
Weird.
Things change.
So, um, uh, speaking of things changing, uh, he, Harrison better fucking hope that some
of the people that he's talking about in this clip didn't do what he's saying they did.
Cause if so, they're going to prison.
Oh no.
Uh, the people who have been able to successfully break into, uh, Senate offices and congressional
offices, uh, did so with such swiftness that the protesters there were, or the, I'm sorry,
the, uh, the staffers and congressmen and senators there were unable to even grab their
information, grab their papers or even shut down their computers.
So now unlocked and open to anybody, those computers are being accessed by the protesters
who themselves are gathering information, downloading hard drives or stealing the hard
drives outright.
Uh, we can expect to see the fallout from this continue on for a very long time.
But I remind you again, after a year of complete chaos, a year of protest, a year of literally
tens of thousands of violent riots, I'm not saying, I'm not saying that it's impossible
that, uh, some people took some stuff or might've accessed some stuff, but like that was, that's
a very serious, like national security problem.
That's a, that's a sitcom plot.
That's something that I don't think that people will take lightly.
What did, what did Chandler bring home from the White House?
Uh oh, it's the governor's fucking hard drive.
Oh no.
It's, uh, yeah, Schumer's motherboard.
What are we going to do?
We got to get rid of it.
Yeah.
It'd be good to like, if these fucking ding dongs didn't live stream themselves without
masks on.
I know.
Going into these offices where allegedly they are stealing, uh, maybe, uh, privileged or
classified information.
It's a good thing that they decided to storm one of the least heavily surveilled buildings,
uh, without masks on.
Yeah.
You know, that Capitol building, I'm glad they just don't have many cameras there or
recording equipment of any kind to, to like, the perfect heist.
Anyway, were they filming, was George Clooney there?
Is this like a Jimmy Fallon in that Boston movie?
It's Pawns 11.
So at this point, Alex has suggested that it's Antifa that is orchestrating or provocateering
all of this, but Harrison is, this is still real to him, man.
We have heard time and time again how valuable protests are, how good protests are, how Antifa
is only an idea, how Black Lives Matter is simply a set of beliefs that if you don't
believe you're racist, uh, and we've watched silently because we always knew that the end
of the day, we had our vote.
We always knew that when it came right down to it, the American system was powerful enough,
flexible enough.
Is that what you guys were talking about?
To voting, maintain.
And we knew that if we just trusted and exerted our rights as members of a Republican citizens
of this democracy, that we could regain our footing and get back on track.
Well, that vote has been stolen from us.
If you're wondering what is inspiring the overwhelming, um, activity that we're seeing
here on violent activity, some supporters move into the Capitol building and start to
destroy things, uh, it's that that last release valve has been taken, destroyed, perverted
and prevented from being accessed and used by the people who for so long have patiently
stood by and watched their country literally burned around them.
So I guess it wasn't Antifa provocateur-ing things, I guess it was that people had their
right to vote stolen and they'd had enough and this is the only thing that could remedy
that.
Yeah, but it was Antifa who exploited that to make them do things that they didn't want
to do, even though the things that they did are the things that they did want to do.
I bet, I bet, like, if pushed Alex might be able to come up with that, but that's not
what he said.
I don't think you can sell that one.
So this next clip is really where I found myself saying, oh, Alex, oh no, um, this is
sad, um, this is really indicative of how Alex operates.
Mike down for this because Owen's going to talk about this shooting and he listened to
Alex's response.
People apparently have been shot inside the Capitol.
Now we're still getting intel on what that is.
We've gotten to a safe location because it was just too crazy out there on the streets.
But that was Capitol police.
That's probably false.
That's the left.
Probably we're going to get later and the intel is probably false.
What's false?
The shooting inside.
Well, there was, I mean, a woman came out in a gurney bleeding, so I don't know who,
we don't know who did it.
Point is, it's crazy.
Point is, there's video now of the shooting having taken place.
So Alex, based on nothing, his response is that's probably fake.
Probably fake.
This shooting is probably fake.
Alex, I saw somebody going out there with a girl.
I'm just throwing that out there in case you want to use that later.
It's probably fake.
Things are crazy.
Just in case you were wondering, probably fake.
And Harrison has to come in and be like, there's video.
You can't, you can't deny this.
That's fake.
That's just random.
That's knee jerk.
He's basing that on nothing.
Just anything.
That is just.
That makes us look bad.
Let's say it's fake first and let's just see if we can get away with it.
Let's see how it feels.
Yeah.
Let's taste it in our mouths a little bit.
So he has been now refuted by both of his employees.
Yeah.
Alex, no.
Who are not getting the lines.
We cannot do that.
They are not getting the lines.
There's video.
Can't fight that.
So Alex makes up another detail.
So now Pence has also betrayed President Donald Trump.
So Trump is now a man on a, on a mountain by himself and he has we the people fighting
for him.
By the way, the police just confirmed one woman was shot in the leg inside the Capitol.
Alex is making up that confirmation.
He didn't get that confirmation from anybody.
No.
She didn't get shot in the leg.
That, he's just making that up because he has to, he has to admit that someone got shot
and it's not fake because of the pushback that he got from his employees, but he can't
let it be as serious as it looks like it might be.
So it's someone was shot in the leg.
And he can't also just say he was wrong.
He has to say, I got word that it was confirmed.
Yes.
It's all made up.
Yep.
So Alex has decided that this is Antifa and he explains his evidence for this.
And when I say evidence, I'm being incredibly generous.
Okay.
I would describe this as a, he imagined that it was Antifa.
Folks saw him militarily come in, a lot of vets were over here and they said, yeah, they
were very military.
My elbow pads and knee pads kind of gray outfits.
They came in, attacked the riot police and said, let's go, let's do it.
Got some people to follow them.
Then they all pulled out real quick and I ran to a bunch of experts who were witnesses
to what else happened.
But as soon as I saw the footage, Trump had just announced, I'm going to drive in 20 minutes
over there from his big rally for a peaceful protest here at the Capitol within minutes
of that.
Everybody's like, whoa, whoa, whoa.
People are attacking the police.
All this crazy stuff's happening.
All this crazy stuff's going down.
All this crazy stuff's unfolding.
And then boom, I was like, man, they're going to do provocateur action.
And sure enough minutes later that happened 95% of provocateur.
We have the witnesses.
We have the footage.
We have so much.
We have the witness footage.
We have the witnesses.
We have the footage.
We have the witness footage.
We got it all.
We got all three kinds of footage.
Alex is basically just saying, Hey, I thought that they might do a provocateur thing.
So they did.
They did.
They totally did.
I proved it.
Aha.
We saw it.
There's this guy.
He was dressed.
It's amazing how good Antifa is.
He was dressed exactly like you would expect somebody at this rally to be dressed.
He was screaming things that like, I screamed, so you know that he was Antifa because they
wouldn't say the things that I say.
We all know that the Antifa is mostly out of work theater students.
And they are so good.
They're good at acting.
This guy even had a Nazi tattoo on his neck.
How good is Antifa at provocateuring?
We know that was a stick-on.
Amazing how good they are at mimicking their infiltrators.
So one of the things that was jarring about this is they kind of go back and forth from
Harrison doing some reporting and Alex doing his yelling.
And so Harrison, you know, I would say one of the most important things in a situation
like this is not to just say anything on air.
When you have a tense situation and you have a lot of information coming in, some of it
might be wrong.
Yeah.
You might want to vet some things.
Right.
I understand that there's an impulse to report everything as quickly as you can.
Sometimes it's best to take a breath and wait a little while.
Harrison is from a different school.
Oh, okay.
This is unconfirmed, but it does say that protesters are engaging U.S. Secret Service
hand-to-hand combat.
Okay.
Unconfirmed.
I'm not sure if that's a troll post or not.
Usually not good on your news outlet to read something and then afterwards when you sound
stupid coming out of your mouth, like, ah, that might be trolling.
Ladies and gentlemen, I am just getting word that Olympus has fallen.
Oh wait, no, that might be a troll.
Oh wait, earlier I did say that the Capitol is fallen.
Well there's that.
That might've been trolling.
So anyway, back to Alex yelling.
Look, there's a communist Chinese takeover with the new world order of the country.
They're trying to steal the election.
They're trying to bankrupt the nation.
They're telling us the country shouldn't even exist.
They're telling us the word mother and father can't exist.
This is a communist takeover and everybody knows it.
And South America is starting to push back and GGP and everybody else needs to know you're
the one starting all this, not us.
And you're the ones that are going to pay just like Hitler and just like all the rest
of scumbags.
And you know, this is, this is what happens.
This is the result.
This is like if you don't, if you don't deal with a cancer and you have cancer and you
don't deal with it until it's too late, they basically only have one shot and that's just
a chemotherapy radiate the hell out of you and then hope you can survive.
That's what we're going through.
We've had a cancer in this country for decades.
We've had a communist Chinese takeover for decades.
We've been occupied by tyrants for decades and we've been ignoring it.
Whoa.
That's pretty severe.
Yeah.
I mean, we're at a point now where they have no reason to be like gung ho about this.
Everyone's backed off, buddy.
Yeah.
Um, yeah, it's, uh, it's, it's troubling.
What a bunch of idiots.
Yeah.
This is, they, this is how it was going to go.
How is this taking them by so, so much surprise?
Well, I think that they're used to acting in ways that would conceivably lead to something
like this, uh, and then it never happens.
And so I think that they're pretty used to that outcome.
And so it's kind of surprising to be, uh, the stars have aligned in such a way that
the other influences are actually making this happen.
Oh, um, I don't know if they, they know how to, uh, to react.
And that's why I think you see a little bit of flailing.
You see, um, contradictory narratives being thrown out.
You have Alex trying to insist it's Antifa, but then at the same time, that last clip
seemed to sound like he was saying it's great.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's, it's weird.
I think it's because the only thing they're not allowed to say is the only thing that
would make any sense for any of them to say, which is just, you guys weren't supposed to
actually do it.
Yeah.
This was about stealing your money.
And now look at us.
This is tough for business.
I'm disappointed in you.
Yeah.
I it's, it's, it's weird.
So in order to really thread the needle successfully, one of the things you have to do is cast dispersions
on the people who actually did follow through with it.
So there are people who have speculated that the Q shaman, a weirdo guy.
He was a agent.
He was Antifa.
Yeah, come on buddy.
Who else is Antifa?
Give him more names.
Uh, people are now in vet.
Now looking into some of the people that have broken in, they're seeing a look suspiciously
like a communist, uh, communist things we're seeing, uh, it was incredible shots from inside
the Capitol dome.
So there's a guy who had a tattoo that everyone thought was a hammer and a sickle and it turns
out it's a symbol from like a video game dishonored.
Um, so they were like, oh, he's a commie.
He can't actually, this isn't really.
Yeah.
Oh, so he had Corvo's little tattoo on his hand.
What a nerd.
Dorks.
That's so funny.
Um, and yeah, but Nick Fuentes and Baked Alaska are figures.
They're media figures.
They were on your show.
Yes.
Nick Fuentes was on like a week ago.
He was on a week ago.
He was with you the last time you were in DC.
Was he Antifa then or now?
Pick one.
Yeah.
They just conveniently ignore that.
Jesus.
What a bunch.
Is he, he's going to be back on Infowars, right?
Probably today.
They're going to have to get Fuentes on soon.
I don't know what happened on Thursday.
Yeah.
We're keeping this as a bottle episode of Wednesday and then on Monday we'll cover.
We'll go from there.
Yeah.
Just because of the stupidity of all this.
So stupid.
Um, but yeah, I would assume that at least by the time the weekend's over, Fuentes will
have made some sort of a play for Harrison's job.
Anyway, we end the Alex Jones show and we end up going into the war room.
Smooth transition.
Of course.
It's all hosted by Harrison Smith.
He has to leave.
He's done.
He's okay.
He's tapped out.
He's had a long day.
Oh yeah.
He's, I mean, to be fair, he was on air for a long time.
Seven straight hours?
He did hold up at least in terms of like not completely falling apart, which is faint praise,
but I'll give it to him.
I don't know.
I don't think I could do seven hours.
No.
I don't think I, absolutely not.
Especially this is an intense seven hours.
I don't think he did a good job, but he did a job.
Yeah.
So I would've, I would've been like, guys, we shouldn't be doing this.
This is not for us right now.
We got to stop.
Now what's really funny is that Alex, oh, and also, I mean, not to, not to add more
praise on, but like Alex had said, we're cutting commercials.
Yeah.
So he had no breaks for like the last, like basically the last hour that he's been on
air.
God damn.
But like, uh.
Fuck you boss.
Alex keeps saying, we're going to go into the fourth hour.
Meanwhile, they're in the fourth hour.
They're about to start the war room.
He has no idea, but again, I could be.
Time zones and, and he's, it's, there's a revolution going on.
No, totally.
I get it.
Yeah.
It's a little bit funny because you can hear the producer's voice like war room.
But I'm not, you know, I would make that mistake.
Totally.
No, that's understandable.
For sure.
Now with the mistake I would not make is Tom for a violent revolution, Tom Papert is hosting
the war.
Oh, that was a big mistake.
And this guy sucks.
Um, he's pretty scary.
Uh, local news has reported that protesters have moved inside the Kansas, uh, uh, house
chambers as well.
I'm getting additional reports from Kentucky and Georgia that protesters are making their
way inside the state Capitol buildings.
What seems to have set this off of course is all of this happened mere seconds after
Mike Pence announced his ultimate betrayal of president Trump and said that he would
not fight for him in the electoral college.
So I would say that everybody has like real different vibe.
So that was because, so Pence is Antifa.
Yes.
He was the one who instigated this whole thing.
Well here, here's, here's the vibe I would say, yeah, Harrison is like, yay, no, yay.
That's where he's at.
All right.
He's watching this go down and he's like, this is the revolution, but he's also drastically
affected in a kind of human way about the fact that someone died.
That's true.
And it, it, it ruins a lot of the vibe.
It does hurt his feelings.
Yeah.
Uh, Tom Papert wants everything to burn.
He does not think that he thinks this is great, but he also thinks that we need to do way
more.
Okay.
Good.
It's he's, he's much more acceleration.
All right, Tom.
And then Alex can't quite figure out if it's Antifa or if he's glad.
And Owen, I don't even know what the fuck he's on.
Listen to this shit.
Owen's talking to Tom Papert and like,
hundreds of police cars never did they did it never did they do this once this summer
when churches burned, buildings burned, businesses were looted.
You never saw a response like this once, never once.
Now you could, you could make an argument.
I would even listen to an argument that says, oh, this is the appropriate response for what's
happening today.
I would listen to that.
Great.
Cause that's the argument I would make.
It's the fucking Capitol building.
It's it's people storming the fucking Capitol building of the country.
So you could, you could make the argument that this is a very serious, real thing, much
more so than someone stealing stuff from target.
Yes.
And I would listen to that argument.
Convenient.
Cause that's the argument I would make.
Yeah.
Why would you tell me that you would listen to that argument?
Cause it's the argument that really hurts your, obviously, obviously now, Hey, look,
if you were to make the argument that this was real, I would agree with you.
Yeah.
But.
Now even so I would say that some of the police responses that we've seen over the course
of the summer were pretty severe.
Oh no, no.
How so?
I don't, I don't want to get into a game with scale or playing that cause I don't actually
think that I would be the most credible source on that, but I would say that there was a
lot of police action against people before.
And also whatever they did in terms of defending the Capitol building, you kind of would see
it and be like, well, it's the Capitol building.
Hey, we can talk about how many, how there were almost no arrests and all of that stuff.
We can talk about that stuff.
But I think what's a more telling statistic is how many fucking casualties there were
far.
There were fewer people with broken hands like that type of shit.
Those types of, Oh, I got shot in the face with a rubber bullet.
Oh, I got blood coming from my nose because I was hit by three fucking cops.
There was none of that shit going around.
It seems like there's less that I've heard of.
Yeah.
I mean, it's, it, it's tough because obviously I don't think that the police should be, you
know, or law enforcement.
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not in the business of saying like, yeah, what'd you expect?
I don't like that tone.
Oh no, absolutely not.
But had things gone differently over the summer and people had made it over that barricade
when they were around the white house, sure.
I would not have been super surprised if people got shot for trying to rush the white totally
100%.
I'm not saying that people should have been shot for rushing the Capitol building, but
I'm saying I, what I am saying is I am not surprised by any level of law enforcement
response when it comes to the fucking Capitol or the white house or, or I just don't understand
why they're playing games with that.
I think, I think that's one of the reasons that I'm just not as, uh, I, okay.
When you, when Portland happened, you had fucking stormtroopers against people.
And the pictures that came out were all in the middle of the night and everybody looked
fucking cool.
The cops looked cool.
They looked like the fucking beasts from movies.
They looked so strong.
And the protesters, they were the protesters from movies.
And in this one we have cops standing around going like, Hey, what are you guys doing?
We just got to let you guys get this out of your system.
And we have idiots storming.
We have people fucking putting their feet up on Nancy Pelosi's fucking desk.
Some people might think that's pretty cool.
It is cool, but it's also pathetic and stupid.
I think, I think you're coming at this from a very subjective standpoint.
I understand.
I'm just saying.
You have a particular view of what's cool and what kind of movies you like.
No, no, that's, but they do too.
These are people that are, that guy has a Corvo tattoo, Dan.
These are all people who live in fucking fantasy movies.
That's the guy who's hanging out with the shaman.
Alex is their leader and he is, you know, like they're, these are all fucking sci-fi
nerds.
That is, that is true.
It does seem like there's a lot of, yeah, that, um, but look, the bottom line is this
was Antifa.
Yeah.
Okay.
Alex.
Alex is pretty sure of that.
Okay.
He's pretty much sure.
Antifa started this.
We're pretty much sure they're all wearing the same outfits, shoulder pads, knee pads,
mask.
Ooh.
The people are pissed.
They got them up there.
A few people broke in, went in, could have arrested them, could have tasered them.
Shouldn't have shot that woman.
So they've already committed the big crime there.
This does not need to escalate and we need to have our path to victory by exposing the
fraudulent election with the massive evidence that came out.
So Alex is really at like a point where he's like, let's deescalate and I honestly kind
of get it.
I get, I get his perspective.
I mean, not because I agree.
I do agree.
There should have been deescalation.
Sure.
But I get where he's coming from and it became very clear as I listened on.
What did that cap do?
Sorry about the choppiness.
That's not us.
That was the bad connection for Alex.
Yeah.
He said, don't fire on us.
They're going to get one.
And that's what this comes down to.
And they just fired first.
She met a woman in the neck and if she dies, that's on you.
So Alex is justifying basically now a war on the government because they've taken first
blood by shooting this woman, which I thought he had confirmed is just in the leg, but I
guess that's not the case anymore.
I would argue that if somebody who believed in violent conspiracy theories was encouraged
to go to the mall and then stormed the Capitol building and was killed, that's probably more
on people like Alex.
I think it's tough because people have such similar information streams that are very
separate.
That's why I said people like Alex.
Exactly.
Yeah, yeah.
It's that sphere.
It's the whole sphere.
Yeah.
It's decentralized.
Her death is on the right wing media ecosystem.
Yeah.
It's hard to personalize responsibility or to make it like, Alex, you did this because
it's kind of nebulous and impossible to nail down.
Totally.
But yeah, it does feel to me that you look at what is most responsible for the circumstances
that lead to this.
It's people believing in a fictional reality and there's a lot of people who are responsible
for creating, reinforcing, worsening those things and Alex is certainly one of them.
Everybody on Fox News should be fucking slapped.
If they say anything about...
You can hear them saying shit that people on Fox News said two days before, so it's
on you.
Everybody there should have been slapped in the face while it was going on.
It's your fucking fault.
But now, Alex wants you to deescalate.
He wants everyone to go home.
Such a surprise.
It's time to go home.
I would advise everybody who happens to be watching down there on our feeds, go home
now, because we're not the bad guys that are instigating this and I don't want you to get
hurt.
Okay?
The globalists know they're losing.
They want to show some type of decisive force like Trump's bad, like we started this.
We need to deescalate this and people need to then decide, okay, and then watch what
happens and let them have the debate and let them have the process that we were starting
to win of showing the fraud, okay?
That's why they activated the provocateurs to trigger this, I believe, and we have witnesses
and it looks just like antifa.
So the reason that Alex is saying everyone go home, deescalate, is because he has what
he thinks he needs.
He thinks that everything that he was hoping to accomplish, and trying to make lemonade
out of the lemons that life has given him, obviously the most profitable route is continuing
just the terrorist edging game that he constantly does.
That's super manageable for him.
But now that this has happened, it's tough.
But on the bright side, Alex doesn't realize that Congress will just reconvene in the evening
and certify the election results.
So he thinks that there's a stay of execution that's going on here.
Simultaneously, he has this woman who has been killed by the police that he believes
he can build a martyr narrative out of.
He has all of the optics that he needs to build upon, move forward.
He's decided that this is antifa and he's going to put it on the left.
He has everything that he needs as long as it doesn't get worse.
And so that's what he's encouraging people to do.
He has no real effect on anyone's actions, I don't believe.
No, no, no, absolutely not.
But it's...
Imagine somebody in the Capitol building after having stormed it like, hold on, I got word
from Alex, we all got to go home, guys.
Hold on, guys, I'm listening to the very highly rated War Room program.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, I thought that one was in DC.
Yeah, Tom Pappertoasting today.
Ooh, turn it off.
So one of the dead giveaways that Alex is just like, listen, we can't let this get worse
is this.
I would advise all the great people down here to understand we are contesting, we are fighting,
we've not reached this point yet.
I would advise people to get off the streets by six o'clock tonight.
Alex is telling people to accept a curfew.
Yeah.
What?
Hey, you know what happens when your revolutionary movement is led by a bunch of rich people
and grifters and scam artists and your supreme leader is a fucking coward asking vice presidents
to overthrow a country for him, and then he decided to run away.
He ran away, he fleed from your overthrow capital attack.
And then your hero anti-government guy tells you, hey, listen to the state when they tell
you to go home at a certain time.
Yeah, totally.
Listen to that curfew.
Hey, you know who we're fighting?
The literal Christian devil.
But nightfall.
We only fight in the day.
Now, I have been spending a lot of time on my program yelling about how, you know, curfews
are basically, you know, that and masks are basically slavery.
Yeah, just slavery.
Government overreach.
Go home by six.
Well, it's six.
Yeah, it's nightfall guys.
Gotta go home.
This is actually kind of interesting.
At this point, Alex reports that this woman who was shot has died.
This is way before.
Yeah, I was going to say, we didn't find that out.
No.
We got really bad news.
Try to get her name.
Is that from our police sources or is that, that's exclusive.
Guys, the woman that they shot looks like some type of security for the senators.
The woman they shot died.
So the woman who shot on the screen, she's dead.
I gotta go talk to our folks.
We got DC police that we've got hired off duty.
So I gotta give you the latest stuff and they're talking to Capitol Police right now.
I don't know what to make of this because it did end up being correct.
Right.
But I still don't think Alex had a source on that.
I think that was just a good bet.
Yeah.
I think he knew that there was a good chance she was going to pass and decided to make
it definitive, claim there was a source.
Yeah.
Up until that point, all the confirmed reports were very much like...
Nonsense.
Well, I mean...
Oh, I meant confirmed reports that Alex is saying.
The real world.
Right.
The reporting was like, we saw her get this type of medical treatment, which they only
give in the most extreme of circumstances.
So it would be surprising.
Critical condition.
Yeah.
So it would be, it's a good bet.
It's not, I doubt he knew.
Yeah.
When I said that the confirmed reports are nonsense, I mean the things that Alex has
tried to pass off as confirmed reports.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Totally.
We just had a misunderstanding.
Yeah, totally.
We got to crossfire.
So Alex, now in light of this decision that he's made, or maybe somebody has given him
a tip that she has passed, now we need to set the narrative.
I see it in fullwars.com, I'm not mad, we're just directing live from the air, that it
still says, watch live.
Today's the day Alex Jones leads largest Patriot movement in history through DC.
Let's update that, that DC now under martial law, feds murder innocent woman, Pence turns
against Trump.
Okay.
Let me give you that one again.
DC now under martial law, feds shoot and kill innocent woman.
Pence turns against Trump.
We have to get the narrative out of the truth of them killing this woman.
You got to get the narrative out.
This is the narrative that we need to set.
Pence is now the bad guy, the cops murdered this woman in cold blood, and the city is
under martial law.
And of course the sub-narratives, of course the martial law was precipitated by false
flag, takeover of the Capitol building, it was provocateured by Antifa.
Fight the power, but also go home at six.
Yeah.
Pence is trying to make this work and it's just pathetic.
So he has some footage of this shooting and he constantly describes it as execution style.
And again, that's just the narrative that's being set.
I saw the video.
I just want the footage of them execute the woman.
They just walk up and shoot her right in the neck.
A nonviolent woman wasn't even the woman trying to break through the glass, they just execute
her.
And they're the good guys and it's Trump's fault, it's our fault.
No, it's your fault, globalist, and if you want to fight, you're gonna fucking get one,
you got that?
Fucking bullies.
So, yeah.
I have unfortunately also seen this video, I did not want to, but Alex plays it a bunch
of times, and it seems very clear that he has made a point to have everyone say that
this was execution, because that term is now used almost blanketly.
And get this, this is weird, Alex has found a first-hand witness.
We're gonna, in a couple of minutes, we're gonna have Pepper take over, because we've
got a guest that was one of the first to go in today that witnessed it all, so stay there.
So we're gonna have an eyewitness guest that was in the building and witnessed the whole
thing, but we now have it confirmed.
Oh my god, what a shock, we got a witness, we got a first-hand witness.
You don't get to tell me that you're revolting and overthrowing the government, and then
be like, oh, this innocent woman was murdered in cold blood by the cops.
No, you said you're fighting a revolution, people die in a revolution.
Or conversely, Antifa provocateur'd things, and then she wouldn't be, I don't understand.
So if she's not- It's hard.
It's hard to figure out exactly what the narrative is.
Basically they're all false flag provocateurs except for her, she was a hero, and I don't
know.
Yeah, see, I can care that she was killed, because I'm living in the real world where
what happened was a woman's brain was destroyed and melted, and then here we are.
But they can't care, because they're fighting a real fucking war against the devil.
They should all be expecting to die immediately.
That's what, you're fighting the literal Christian devil.
Yeah, and- Don't hand-ring about one person dying.
It does seem weird, and it also seems weird to go halfway in terms of we have breached
the Capitol building and be like, we'll fight another day.
It seems weird, if you think that you're up against the actual devil, you're already midstream.
It's very weird.
No, it's pathetic.
But that's because that's not really what they want.
They don't want that.
It's like what you were saying, the people who they're probably the most mad at are the
people who followed through with what they keep saying should be done.
We want your money.
We don't actually want a Ron Paul presidency.
Do you realize what would happen if that shit happened?
We would lose our money.
So Tom Papert hosts for a little while, and this is just, he's doing the work to build
up this narrative that this woman was a martyr.
I will completely admit that I am a chauvinist, and I forced all of our female reporters on
the ground to get the hell out of there.
Everyone is on a train getting multiple states away right now.
This is not a safe place.
These are the times that try many souls, and this is, it's not the time to be a martyr.
They've already made a martyr, and that is what this young woman will be.
The police shot and killed a woman because they didn't like her form of protest.
I'd say...
I mean, if your form of protest is storming the Capitol building, I would argue, yeah!
Yeah!
So, um...
This is all the martyr, this is, now is not the time to martyr yourself.
Obviously we're fighting the devil.
Yeah.
I'm going to tell you that I have some real negative feelings about how Alex handles the
fact that he has footage of this shooting.
But there's a really interesting dynamic at play about the provenance of this footage.
And Alex kind of reveals too much, and then it pretends that he didn't say these things.
I have seen a snuff film today.
I just saw footage of an innocent woman that one of our own cameramen followed the crowds
into the Senate, and I watched them execute an unarmed woman with a Trump flag shooting
her in the neck at point blank range.
We are uploading the footage right now.
So one of your camera people, one of your employees, was one of the people who was along
storming the Senate and was there close enough to get this video of this woman being shot.
Yeah.
Interesting.
So that is what he's saying.
Yeah.
Weird.
You would think that the psycho, like, and we had a cameraman in there, all of a sudden
everybody around him would just go, ee, ee, ee, ee, stabbing him through the fucking neck.
Yeah.
Alex, that hurts, that hurts.
Don't do that.
Don't do this.
The cameraman is freaking out about the criminals in Congress, and I don't, I just think this
is a little, I think I kept this clip because it's so out of place.
It's a weird outburst.
Okay.
And this is the biggest frustration, and this is why this is so difficult, why we're on
a high wire here.
We're not at war with the police.
I don't look at the police like my enemy.
I don't look at Antifa like my enemy.
Look, they're choosing the wrong side.
I don't look like BLM is my enemy, but man, the fucking criminals are sitting in that
fucking building, taking my fucking country, and I'm fucking sick of it, man.
And these people are too.
That's all.
And you guys just keep killing women and stuff and see what happens.
Yep.
You're damn right.
Because they take our kindness for weakness.
So now they're on top of a building, I think, at a like a press location.
Okay.
So like, I don't...
This sounds like three dudes at a bar arguing about how they fucking lost, and they're like,
no, no, no, we won the game, we'll get them next time.
It's really hard to tell, but that was bizarre.
Yeah.
So anyway, Rob Doo is there too.
He's hanging out.
Of course.
He's watched this death film.
Yeah, I just watched it a couple times.
It's pretty sad.
She's climbing...
Why don't you come here?
Come here.
Okay.
I understand you just watched it.
When is the network going to have it?
They have it.
They have it now.
I'm not ready to show it yet, because I want to give viewer discretion's advice.
Describe what...
We're going to show you the HD footage in a minute of the execution.
So Alex's big take on this is that the media and the news played the police footage of
the killing of George Floyd.
Yeah.
And so he's like, well, I'm going to play this.
I want you to watch it.
I want it next hour, because we're going to slow it down so you get to see her, because
like George Floyd, that thing on his neck, and he's ODing on heroin.
It's a terrible thing.
The cops are in the wrong, but they didn't do it on purpose.
This is on purpose.
I want you to see her die slow, because believe me, if she was still here and she's with God
now, she'd want to be seen for what she did, executed while she was just trying to execute
her own first amendment.
So we're going to play the footage raw next hour.
That's psychologically so fucked up.
I want you to watch her die slow.
That's so gross.
She would have wanted me.
You don't even know who this person is.
I mean, you can guess some things about her based on the fact that she stormed the Capitol.
But those would be weak assumptions.
They wouldn't be great.
But Tom Pappert is doing his job.
Alex has declared this an execution, and so while he's hosting, he's really trying to
push that.
Again, Infowars has exclusive video of the martyr of DC, the MAGA martyr who was executed
Shawn execution style.
I've seen the video.
I don't know what else you call it by these jackboots of Muriel Bowser by the jackboots
of Joe Biden.
Joe Biden's jackboots.
You fucking nerds.
Yeah.
Get the fuck out of here.
Call them Koopa Troopas.
Yeah.
No kidding.
The jackboots.
Her name is Bowser.
Make use of it.
Good God.
So anyway, Pappert also let slip that the person who got this footage is employed by
Infowars.
I know the Infowars cameraman who was in the room who captured the footage when it happened.
Say his name out loud.
I hope the man is okay.
He's a strong man, but I don't know if I would be.
So Tom Pappert is playing some clips, responding to them, and at this point, there's a group
of Trump supporters who find a media set up, and they start attacking the lights and what
have you.
I haven't seen any violence, though.
None.
But what's really funny here is that I was watching this, and Tom Pappert is playing
this video, and he has to pretend that he can't see Trump flags.
It's so pathetic.
More clashes happening, it appears, between the media and Trump supporters.
Or is that the left?
I can't tell what kind of flag that is, but more clashes happening in DC as the sun starts
to go down a little bit.
Things are gonna get a little bit darker, Antifa will come out, those appear to be lights.
Looks like somebody was maybe doing a stand up, some news outlet was doing a stand up.
That's just dumb as well.
To the media, to my friends in the media, I've given my reporters, and we are the renegade
news outlet that is doing this by the seat of our pants.
I told my people, go home.
I told my people, nobody's gonna get shot today on my watch.
Mainstream media journalists who are out there to get the footage to make us look bad, you're
not safe for Antifa or police either, I'm sorry.
That's not a threat, that's an observation.
No it's not a threat.
Because these people are feral.
I think you might need to go to therapy.
I, okay, here's the problem, here's the problem, alright, okay.
Here's why that's so obviously transparently bullshit.
Because if they were Antifa provocateurs, they would still be carrying Trump flags.
They wouldn't be carrying Antifa flags.
Oh yeah, that's true.
That's a great point.
Yeah.
Also, based on-
Everything else.
Based on what Tom Papert is describing, conflict journalism should not exist.
I can't-
Hey look, look, I understand everyone's curious what's going on in a war zone, but you journalists
are fucking stupid.
Hey, hey, journalists, the cops in Antifa are gonna, they're not your friends and they're
gonna come after you too.
No, no they're not.
You guys are.
So something bad happens on this broadcast and that is they've been teasing this death
footage that they're gonna play, viewer discretion advised, but they get scooped, someone else
releases it.
Oh no.
We will be going live here in just a second with Alex Jones, he's going to come in and
break the video.
Sorry, it's just my cry who was telling them do not upload this video anywhere, it is an
Info Wars exclusive and then all of a sudden I'm seeing it go up.
So not sure what happened there.
Yep, someone else got the footage.
Somebody else got there first.
Some other dude, Michael Codray, I think, a guy from Stop a Steal, got the footage and
he uploaded it and got scooped.
No longer an Info Wars exclusive.
Oh, poor guys.
They can still get Rob Doo though.
Yes.
I don't know.
He might be in the wind.
He might be too high enough.
So I noticed there are similarities in how Harrison is aping traits and patterns that
Alex Jones does.
In-house style.
Exactly.
And I noticed one that Tom Papert is doing an impression of, or just basically Alex does
it so it's totally fine, and that is reporting something based on imagining it.
I guarantee you as we speak right now, they're trying to use the 25th Amendment to remove
Trump and do a full and complete and total coup right before our eyes.
I guarantee you that's the conversation and Mike Pence is leading it.
I can almost, this is without sources, I'm just telling you I know how these people think.
I've spent enough time covering them like Alex Jones has, not nearly as much as him,
but you figure it out pretty quick, they're sick.
I'm making this up and I guarantee you because I know I've followed these people for so long
they're sick and I know what they're doing and it's all just based on nothing.
Just feels so true though.
Yeah.
So true.
This is a coup.
You know, after we stormed the Capitol building, they're going to coup, wait, our guy's the
president now.
Speaking of coup.
So now is the coup, but...
You know who's conspicuous in their absence?
Steve Pechenik.
No, he's, he's got to get those ballots.
We've got to find those ballots, man.
They've got the blockchain.
I would say call number one for me if I'm Alex, Steve, get your ass on air.
Trump has abandoned us, so it's time for Melania to take over.
Also conspicuous in their absence, Roger Stone.
Hey, Roger, do you want to come on?
No.
I don't.
Please leave a message for Roger Stone.
Yeah, exactly.
That shit's going to voicemail.
I am not dealing with Alex's bullshit today.
Nope.
Gotta eat a sandwich myself.
I am drunk in the bunker.
So we get now to Alex's firsthand guy who got the video.
Sure.
Now Alex is going to pretend that he hasn't already said that this person works for InfoWars.
All right, Tyler Hansen is here with us.
He was another witness.
I've seen his footage, absolutely horrible, of this poor woman.
We don't know her name yet, who was executed by some type of security force inside the
North Korean death chamber that is the US Capitol.
Alex conveniently fails to mention that Taylor Hansen, not Tyler, is the InfoWars cameraman
that's been referenced multiple times already.
Owen was hanging out with Taylor the night before, and by hanging out, this is actually
what I mean.
Here's how they took video.
All right, so my good friend Taylor here is going to do a little Black Lives Matter enrichment
ceremony.
Taylor, Tyler, Taylor.
So who wants to see this flag?
To my audience, I'm just going to say, I'm not afraid of any kind of security.
VLM sucks.
What the fuck is going on here, dude?
We're going to get all dirt on it.
Yeah.
Fuck Antifa.
And Tifa can burn the American flag if she can't burn this propaganda bullshit?
Yeah.
So yeah, the night before, Owen and Taylor had gotten together with a group of people
and doused a Black Lives Matter flag in lighter fluid, set it on fire, and chanted, fuck BLM,
BLM sucks.
Didn't we hear earlier Alex say that BLM isn't our enemy in a TV business?
No, Owen said that.
Oh, Owen said that.
Oh, that's odd.
The night before it burned their flag.
That's weird.
Yeah.
It's also weird how they're pretending that this is just a guy who got footage.
Just a patriot out there, Dan.
Or maybe an Antifa provocateur?
Hey everybody, Dan here.
Just wanted to drop in to make a little bit of a correction here.
There is something going on here, definitely, about this dude, Taylor, who Alex is interviewing.
But I messed something up.
I mixed something up and that is my fault and I'd just like to correct that.
I didn't realize this until after we'd recorded the episode, but I didn't want to take it
out but at the same time I didn't want anyone to get the wrong idea.
There were actually two videos that are being referenced and it's very unclear and I made
a hasty assumption.
There was an Infowars camera person who was filming at the Capitol when people had stormed
and the shooting did take place.
And in addition to that, Taylor Hanson was also there and he had shot some video.
So I apologize for the mistake, there's no indication necessarily that Taylor himself
is an Infowars employee, although very much clearly an Infowars associate in as much as
he's hanging out in Owen Troyer's hotel room and he is on video the night before, setting
a Black Lives Matter flag on fire with Owen.
So there's something going on that was really confusing about the social dynamics between
pretending he was a stranger to them, when in fact he was very well known to them, and
the multiple people recording stuff, it was very, it was a mess.
Anyway, sorry I got that mixed up, now back to the episode.
The next day after this, Taylor Hanson was a guest on Laura Ingraham's show.
Taylor better be really careful.
I certainly hope that the video showing him burning a Black Lives Matter flag the night
before doesn't paint his journalistic intentions as being a little bit iffy.
I would imagine that he and Alex should be really concerned right now about him getting
arrested for illegal entry into the Capitol building because he was clearly not there
as some kind of an objective journalist.
No, no, no, he's pressed, Dan, he's pressed.
He's an Infowars employee who was trying to get a sizzle reel.
What, are you against the freedom of the press now, Dan?
So they'll get to this interview in a little bit, but Alex wants to play the video first,
right?
And he's really excited to play this video, but not so excited that he doesn't get distracted.
They're like, Trump caused violence, Trump's bad, remove him, blah, blah, they're not telling
you they executed a woman, I got Joe Rogan calling me, let's just take this call.
Hey Joe, how you doing?
Alex.
I am there, I'm in the middle of it.
So that's jarring.
Yeah.
They play the video of her getting shot while Alex is.
While Alex is on the phone, that's what the shot was?
Yep.
So you play that, cause Alex had already been setting up the clip, and now he's gotten a
call from Rogan that he can't not answer, so he wants to interview Rogan, cause he has
him on speakerphone, but apparently they go, like in the feed, they don't have Rogan's
call on there, which I think is probably good, cause they don't have his permission.
Cause they didn't ask her permission yet.
Yeah.
And so Alex gets a little frustrated.
Call him back.
It's weird, I have such a great crew, but these remotes are very interesting.
They're very interesting, cause they're just seizing up constantly, just seizing, seizing,
seizing.
Try again.
We're live.
That's great.
This is all real.
I'm here while they're killing people down there, so everything's good.
Roll the footage without me talking over it, two and a half minutes, I have a timer.
It's already played.
I do think that he seems more interested in getting Rogan on than he is in this footage.
Yeah.
It's disrespectful.
No, no, no, no, no.
The martyr, the Maga martyr, uh, she's gonna galvanize it.
Hold on.
I got to take this call.
It's Joe.
It's a famous person.
Now this Maga martyr, she's going to inspire the rebel, but I got to take a Joe Rogan call
real quick.
Joe Rogan, I don't know if you know this, uh, is a comedian.
So the Maga martyr, uh, fighting the little Christian devil, uh, hero, but I got to talk
to Joe Rogan, professional comedian.
So now that that is out of the way and he can't get Rogan back on the phone, Alex decides,
fuck it, I'll interview Taylor, uh, and pretend that I don't know him.
Wild.
Sir, thanks for being here with us.
Tell us who you are.
Tell us what you witnessed.
My name is Taylor Hansen.
I'm an independent journalist and she was the first one that actually had, uh, had headed
into that hall.
I was right behind her.
This is nonsense.
Why are they pretending that they don't know each other?
Like literally listen to this, listen to this.
This is just a little bit later.
I was sitting with Taylor last night in my room.
We were watching them steal the Jordan.
I mean, you, I mean, I said it's over.
Even when the Republicans were at, we were both like, we literally watched them do a
switch.
When we first sit down and watched it, Owen and Taylor were clearly friends.
They were hanging out in their hotel room last night.
It's so bizarre.
So Owen's got an interesting theory at this point about the stealing of the election.
Sure.
Oh, by the way, we're not going to listen to much of Taylor cause he's really boring
outside of the fact that it's clearly a charade.
It's clearly a ridiculous dance.
Yeah.
This is an interesting theory.
I think that Owen suspects that the communist Chinese are going through an elaborate conspiracy
just to make him mad.
The election is completely fake.
It's not that they steal elections.
Of course they steal elections.
They rigged this election last night to make it look like they stole it intentionally and
to make it look like it's close intentionally, all being done by the Chinese who run the
voting machines so that they could get this anger, get this ill sentiment, get these fake
people in, and then have us mad that they just stole our presidency and stole our Senate.
Yeah, man.
That's pretty, that's pretty ambitious as a conspiracy theory.
So if I understand correctly, the globalists both made the election look like they stole
it.
Yes.
While at the same time actually making the election look as though we're close while
at the same time actually stealing it.
Yes.
And they wanted to make it close because they knew if it wasn't close, it wouldn't anger
people like Owen.
And it had to be obvious that it was stolen cause that would also piss them off quite
a bit.
Cause it was a come from behind victory cause it was one of those gut punch losses, you
know?
It's like when LeBron sunk that three to knock out my beloved Bulls.
They're imagining that like she is just sitting around and being like, Owen's going to hate
this.
Owen's going to be so pissed.
Oh, he's not going to like this one.
So they'd, they covered Trump's video that he put out.
I'm guessing you saw that where he called everyone special and I love you all go home.
Yeah.
That was great.
That was a really good way to de-escalate.
Fucked up.
Hey, listen, they stole it.
Everything you're doing is right and I love you, but it's time to go home.
Yeah.
It's 6 PM guys.
Fucked up.
So they do cover that, but it's basically exactly what you would expect.
Yeah.
The only thing that I find shocking is after Trump had put out that video, he more or less
tweeted something pretty similar.
Yeah.
And even Tom Papert is shocked by this tweet.
Listen to this.
Tom is like, what?
We just have a, a breaking a tweet from the president.
President Trump tweets, which is one of his first tweets of the day.
Really?
These are, wow.
President Donald Trump breaking.
These are the things and events that happen when a sacred landslide election victory is
so unceremoniously and viciously stripped away from great Patriots who have been badly
and unfairly treated for so long.
Tom Papert's a shithead and he believes all that stuff.
And even he was like, holy shit, Trump said that.
So then how is it Antifa agents?
I guess it can't be.
I don't know.
These people are, it's all just like, whatever.
We'll figure it out tomorrow.
Let's do all of it.
Yeah.
100%.
Throw it all out there tonight and then we'll pick something to stick with tomorrow.
Yeah.
And at this point.
That's shameful.
That should not be.
That's I know it's, look, we're on sin 10,000, but I mean, really.
It's our fourth anniversary.
Yeah.
That's fucked up.
That's crazy.
Yeah.
So, um, Alex is really trying to push home this idea that the woman who got shot is going
to be covered up by the media.
The media is not going to talk about it.
Just going to pretend that didn't happen because it's too threatening to the globalists because
she's a martyr for the cause of the Patriots and the revolutionaries.
I'm sorry.
I would love to hear more about her, but I got to take this call.
Joe, Joe Rogan is calling me.
No, I know I care about the martyr, but I got to take this call.
So Trump's the real deal.
One in a landslide.
We got to find this woman's name.
Does anybody know name of the woman killed in DC?
Name of the woman killed in DC.
Say her name.
Cause we, cause they're not going to want us to know.
No.
They're gonna try to suppress us for a while.
By this point, uh, people were already figured out who she was on Twitter and everything's
fine.
We know where she lives.
Yeah.
Uh, that other voice is Ali Alexander.
She is also hanging out on the roof of this hotel.
Of course.
They're all just getting drunk after a fucking boat parade.
It does seem that way.
That is what's happening.
Yes.
These people are fucking stupid.
It does seem that way.
So Alex tries to sign off here cause he's, uh, he's done it.
He's tired.
It's been a long day.
He took a little walk leading that parade earlier.
I know it's hard to remember that happened on this episode.
Um, but uh, yeah, so he's signing off and uh, they seem like they really care about
this woman who got shot.
They're demonizing Trump with this narrative.
They're demonizing that he caused the violence.
No, protesting is good.
We were peaceful.
The federal police attacked the protesters first, eliciting a response.
Now they killed a woman in cold blood and they hope nobody gets that out, but you're
going to get that out.
Truly sad what's going on here.
Well, they, they just full of empathy and care for their common person, their fellow
human.
So Alex is signing off, but he throws it to Owen to wrap it up.
Oh, of course.
Cause they still got a little time on the war room or something.
I don't know.
That's necessary.
People are definitely going to want to make sure they get the last 10 minutes of this
shit.
Yeah.
So Alex is gone.
Theoretically.
Owen tries to get reflective about like, what do we call this?
What do we call what's happened?
I'm wondering what to call this situation.
So we pushing and pushing and pushing and no one ever pushes back and they freak out
when we push back.
They burn the country down.
We push back, they kill a woman and we're the bad guys.
Don't you take our kindness for weakness.
You are the bad guy.
Go ahead.
I'm sorry.
So wait, was it Antifa or not?
Wait, did you just barged back in to yell that the globalists don't like it when you
push back and what?
That's the problem.
They want a violent revolution, but it looks stupid and they can't make money off of it.
Yeah.
So now we're trapped.
They want it both ways.
Yeah.
And it's no good.
And they also want their violent revolution to be non-violent for them.
They want to play a video game in god mode.
They don't want to actually, oh, it's just like fucking democracy.
Oh, we live in a republic, but I don't want to risk losing an election.
Sure.
You know?
The tyranny of the majority.
Oh, I can't stand that.
But I mean, yeah.
So Owen wants to wrap up now because he was only supposed to say a few more things and
Alex won't let him.
A million or at least, I mean half a million minimum at the Trump rally by 9 a.m. today,
they sat there and stood there, cheered all day long for all the great speakers and then
president Trump, president Trump was on the phone with Mike Pence before he spoke.
My guess is I don't, I mean, demanding, begging.
I've got some more witnesses to her getting executed and now that's what people got mad
and fought back.
So bring these guys in.
Bring this other chair in.
Hey guys, we're shutting down soon.
Come up here, you came here, pull your chair in right there, get up there with Owen.
Introduce yourself.
Go ahead, gentlemen.
So you got some more witnesses.
Oh boy.
So Owen tries to interview these people.
Also, Infowars employees.
It turns out they're not so much witnesses.
All right, so you guys were, you guys were in the Capitol today.
Um, are you guys both eyewitnesses to the lady's execution?
Uh, the immediate aftermath.
Yeah.
Okay.
So why don't you talk about what you saw?
Um, I don't, I mean, it was pandemonium there.
Yeah, you'd assume so.
Wild.
Yeah.
So you didn't actually see the thing that we're presenting you as a witness of.
Well, I didn't see the per se.
Also, unfortunate, you guys have put yourself in a place you're not legally supposed to
have been.
And these witnesses are not witnesses, they're right-wing blog types.
One of them is Lucian Wintrick, who's the former White House correspondent working at
the Gateway Pundit, and somebody who's been on Infowars a bunch in the past.
There's no way that Alex and Owen don't know who he is, yet they're pretending that they
don't know each other, and it's just a random person who witnessed the shooting.
It's so bizarre that no one knows each other.
Also, the other guy, his name is Matthew Foster, I have no idea who he is, but he's probably
a shithead because he's hanging out with Lucian.
Yeah, that would make sense.
But like, both of them are now like, we were in there when that shooting happened, well,
guess what?
You committed a crime.
Hey, there you go.
So, a lot of people making these investigations pretty easy.
They really don't understand that they're wrong, and that crime is real, even if they
do it.
Yeah, yeah.
And I don't think white people can revolt in the United States, they're too goddamn
entitled.
And part of, you know, sort of non-violent civil disobedience is the recognition that
there will be consequences, and you will have to bear those consequences, and that's part
of it.
So like, if you're doing something where you invade the Senate chamber and you do a sit-in
or something like that, you recognize that there are consequences legally for that because
what you're doing is technically illegal.
And so these guys have decided to engage in some form of the protest that they feel is
appropriate.
They have committed crimes, and now they will have to bear it.
No, but they're not supposed to be illegal, and I'm not supposed to be punished for it,
Dan.
I have no feelings, Lucian, but unfortunately- No, but I'm the good guy.
There should be a warrant out for your arrest.
No, look, I'm the good guy, see, because they stole the election, I'm good.
Anyway, their interview is very boring, and we have one last clip where Alex encourages
Trump to use this woman's death as a weapon.
Sure.
I'm gonna call General Flynn, I'm gonna call Giuliani, I'm gonna call all my contacts and
Trump's lawyers.
Trump has to say, we had a great event with over a million people, it was all peaceful.
Riot police attacked folks, they pushed back a little.
If you want to arrest those people, that's fine, but you don't shoot him in the neck,
and he needs to know the name of that woman, and humanize her, and turn that against him,
because they're blaming Trump for everything right now, and 25th Amendment.
The fight is now.
So we're gonna end this transformation in five minutes with your final comments, Tom
Pappert's gonna take over, and then I'm gonna go to work tonight calling influencers and
tell the president, don't cuck on this, go on the offense.
Don't cuck on it.
Later in the evening, Alex did a report about how Pence is gonna invoke the 25th Amendment,
basically just taking Pappert's imagination and reporting it as news, and by that point
he still is unaware of what this lady's name is, and I know what her name is, but I just
don't care, I don't want to get involved.
If there is one skill that Donald Trump absolutely does not possess, it is getting people to
care about human life.
That is true.
So, if you are asking Donald Trump to shit all over her for being dead, and failing in
her mission, if you wanted the president to go on TV and say, he loves insurrectionists
who don't get shot by the cops, you can get that.
Yeah, he's skilled at that.
I don't think you're gonna get anybody being a martyr, but Trump.
Yeah, and if it's not personally involved him, I don't think he would care.
He doesn't give a shit.
So, I watched all this, and I lived inside this a bit, and it was really weird, because
I was experiencing a lot of stuff that was like what everyone else was experiencing,
and reality-based, and at the same time I was seeing and paying attention to the reportage
and what have you on Infowars, and the gap between the two is staggering.
And it really, I mean, lack of talent aside, because he had people like Papert and Harrison,
who just aren't good at this, that aside, there was a noticeable rockiness to trying
to figure out what to do, how to cover this, and then there was a singularity of purpose
that Alex had that I really felt, as I was listening to this, it fit that idea that he
is trying to create patriot lore.
He's trying to create a myth out of this, that is, this woman was murdered for the cause,
and the globalists shot her to make us look bad, Antifa probably agitated.
But also we were right to do the, yeah.
In case it wasn't Antifa, we were right to do it.
I felt the first pages of narratives and first pages of things that will affect people down
the road, be rallying cries for people in fucked up ways, and I hope that that's not
the case, but that is the general sense of what I felt Alex's intentions were.
Now, at the same time, everybody else around him is working across purposes.
Everyone else, I have no idea what the fuck they're doing.
Tom Papert seems insane.
He's nuts.
Harrison Smith seems like a true believer, Owen Troyer.
Splits the difference somewhere between just being angry and also wanting to make daddy
so happy.
Yeah.
So he's like, I want to kill everybody, but also daddy needs money, so I'm going to back
off because he said so, but I do want to kill everybody.
And also I've recently realized that I'm pretty good at standup comedy.
I'm pretty great.
I got one bit, give me 15.
Yeah.
Hey, look, I'm unemployable if Info Wars goes away, self-employed is a comic, baby.
That's where the money is.
I know this guy named Joe.
He made millions doing standup.
I'm going to go on tour with Nick DiPaolo.
Everything's going to be all right.
I'm going to middle for Rob Schneider.
So I think that we've taken a bit of a, I don't know, maybe a lighter tone than maybe
some people would feel and maybe lighter than I feel at times.
Sure, sure.
And I think a part of that is just, we're looking at Alex and this is scary, but he's
also a fucking idiot.
Right.
And this is idiotic.
And I'm, yeah, I mean, I'm in a place, I feel like I am coming at this from a completely
different point of view than everyone.
And it freaks me out.
I feel a little insane because I have never felt more confident that we are not going
to be overthrown because the reality of actually overthrowing the United States is that you
would have to have the military on your side.
And the most important thing about the military is that it is an arm of the economy.
And there's no way that the economy is going to be collapsed by those fucking morons.
And there's no way that the military leadership who could, I mean, it's entirely conceivable
that that could have, that a coup could have happened if it was planned appropriately,
if the military saw signals that this is actually some real shit, if Trump didn't fucking run
away like a coward.
Right.
And if the right wing politicians, if the right wing politicians who are all up in arms
about doing anything like that, if they joined the rally, I, all bets could be off.
But everybody who's important in terms of running the world saw those people do that
shit and went, oh fuck, they did it too soon.
They blew their wad too early and now they're an embarrassment.
Yeah.
I see where you're coming from and I think that I can agree on the, on the sort of short
scale.
Sure.
The fear, the fear is the longer scale.
The lessons that can be learned by the very serious people who are among these groups
of ding dongs, the lessons that you can take from this, the image of, you know, these people
flying Confederate flags, invading the fucking capital.
It's meaningful from an optics standpoint.
It's emboldening.
And so even if it doesn't encourage an actual like coup, those are the sorts of imagery
and the sort of things that you would need in order to inspire people to take other kinds
of actions that could be destructive.
Right.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Let's, let's, let's not go crazy.
Yeah.
But I hope everyone is doing all right out there.
We will find out what happened after this on Monday.
We'll figure out whatever Alex decided.
Maybe it was Antifa.
Maybe it's not.
Who knows?
We'll see if by the next day Alex had figured out who this woman was.
And yeah.
But then, but until then we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yeah.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledgefight.net.
Go to bed Jordan.
We're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook.
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work right now.
Yeah.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Leo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I'm the juiciest ice cube.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.
Thank you so much for being with us today, and I'll see you in the next one.