I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying we are the bad guys, a knowledge
fight.
Dan and Jordan, knowledge fight.
Riddle her, riddle her, riddle her.
Need, I need money.
Andy and Candace, Andy and Candace.
Stop it.
It's time to pray.
Andy and Candace, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding us.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first-time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your room.
Knowledge fight.
Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey, everybody.
Welcome back to Knowledge Fight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're cool dudes.
I like to sit around, drink novelty beverages, and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are, Dan.
Jordan.
Dan.
I have a quick question for you.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, Jordan, is hoodies.
Hoodies?
I got a new hoodie.
You did get a new hoodie?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, Miskatonic University.
Is that a real place?
Arkham, Massachusetts.
Oh.
What happened?
That's Lovecraft University.
Yeah, I imagine so.
Yeah, it takes me forever to buy clothes.
I just never end up doing it.
I've had the same clothes forever, and I've needed some new hoodies.
It's winter, basically wearing a sweater pretty much every day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And so I've added some spice to my life.
I like it.
And this one, I got also another one that's at the Miskatonic University Antarctic Expedition.
Sure, sure.
That's the Mountains of Madness reference.
Very, very... I got too much Lovecraft hoodies.
No, no.
You're golden.
You're golden, Dan.
I just couldn't decide on anything that I wanted to get that would be like, I can handle
wearing this in public, and it's something that I like.
Yeah.
Like, I can wear this, and no one would look twice at it, but if it was like Cthulhu or
something- Sure, sure, sure.
I would feel very uncomfortable.
People would have to do a double take, and then they'd be like, oh, I get it.
Yeah.
Otherwise, it just looks like it's a college hoodie.
It's a normal college shirt.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Absolutely.
So I made that compromise.
That's better than what I do with clothes, which is just every six months, I buy five
different colors of the same shirt and wear it.
That's not too bad.
I think that there's a lot of decision paralysis that you get rid of when you do that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
When you model your clothing choices on Calvin from Calvin and Hobbes, I think it solves
a lot of problems before they begin.
Yeah, yeah, because then you're just like, oh, grab this same thing, put it on.
It's a great shirt.
This one's blue, and the other one's teal.
It's a different shirt.
Yeah.
So Jordan, how about you?
What's your bright spot?
My bright spot, Dan, was this year, they just ended the GDQ for 2021.
They just ended Games Done Quick, and it was a bunch of fantastic stuff, a lot of good
runs, and they raised over two million even in this kind of fucking year, so that's really,
really cool.
That is cool.
It made me happy.
That is a lot of fun.
So it's a bright spot.
Yeah.
I'm still wishy-washy a tiny bit about watching video games.
I can watch some of the people who put up Mario Maker videos.
See, those are the ones that I watch.
Yeah.
Because those are so hard.
Oh, yeah.
It's offensive almost how hard those levels are that people make.
Yeah, no.
Because that's the point.
That was one of the things this year, I don't think it closed it, but it was one of the
last four runs, and this dude was playing the hardest Mario Maker level that wasn't
even Mario Maker.
It was a hack.
It was a kaizo hack, and the previous world record was 35 minutes, and he did it in 18.
Wow.
And everybody's watching that just going like, what the fuck just happened, man?
We just saw history.
And nobody even registered for a while.
They were like, that was just a really good run, man.
I think part of my concern is that I think I might get too into it.
I might enjoy watching people play video games competitively too much, but I just can't.
I can't do it.
Right, right, right.
I don't want to enter the territory lest I disappear into it.
Yeah, it's one of those things where I've never been that good at platforming games,
so they've always seemed like a struggle whenever I play them.
And then whenever you see these guys play them, it's actually a very kind of beautiful,
almost dancing kind of feel where it's like, oh, I get it.
If you just do all of the steps perfectly, it's pretty to watch.
It's like if you're bad at dancing and then you watch Somebody's Good, you're like, oh,
I get it.
That's what it's supposed to look like.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
For sure.
Yeah.
So something that's not how it's supposed to be is the world.
Well.
Smooth.
Fucking transition.
You're great.
It's a mess.
And so that's why we're here on a Wednesday.
It does seem like that.
Doing a little special middle of the week episode, because we got to keep on top of
things.
We figured it'd be too much if we waited till Friday, things would pile up and they may
be important.
So we're going over January 10th and 11th today, 2021.
I don't have anything to say about 2021 yet.
Not yet.
Nope.
We'll figure that out.
I think this is 2021.
I'm Dan and there will only be lone survivors.
No.
Nope.
I feel like that one's pretty good.
Today we're going to be going over January 10th and 11th, 2021.
I'm Dan.
This is no longer 2020.
Oh, okay.
Nah, that's not good.
That's not that good.
Nah, it didn't feel that good.
Nah, it didn't feel right.
We'll come up with something.
Okay.
But yeah, there's a lot of, lot of horseshit on this episode.
And actually we get a really interesting return from somebody who's been out of pocket for
a while.
All right.
There's somebody who we have not heard hide nor hair of.
Health Ranger?
Seen?
Hide nor hair of?
I'm not sure what the expression is.
Okay.
Well, we'll see what happens.
How'd you hear a hide or a hair?
Yeah.
That's kind of what I was concerned about.
I'm not entirely sure.
Okay.
But we'll get down to business on that here in a second.
But first, Jordan, we're going to take a little moment to say thank you to some folks who
have signed up and are supporting the show.
That's a great idea.
So first, don't dare call me a policy wonk.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Take that.
Thank you.
Next, Nina Z.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Nina.
Thank you.
Next, Finn B. Not Finn Balor.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Finn.
Next, Tom K. And it's T-H-O-M, which I enjoy quite a bit.
Oh, okay.
So it's not Tom Kenny?
No.
Oh, damn.
Tom K., you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you.
Thanks, Tom K.
I like that thom.
Yeah.
I don't know why.
You don't know why?
If I were Thomas and I went by Tom, I'd definitely keep that H in there.
You'd like the old English H in there.
Yeah.
I enjoy it.
Okay.
Next, Michelle H. Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you. Next, Snug Doo with Rob Doo, which I think is the new morning show on Infowars.
Okay.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you.
And then finally, I'd like to thank a couple of people who donated on an elevated level.
I appreciate that very much.
So, the Giuliani Brain Trust.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
And Kelly M. Thank you so much.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate.
That's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right.
We got to go full tilt boogie on this Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why are you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare Infowar on you.
Thank you so much, Giuliani Brain Trust, and thank you, Kelly M.
Yes.
Thank you very much to the both of you.
We have another special little shout out to give today.
All right.
And first, I'd like to give a shout out to Wednesday and Biscuits, who are a couple of
cats.
Oh, okay.
That are just apparently adorable.
They're very sweet.
Oh, okay.
I got you.
But I'll take the owner's word for them.
And here's the thing.
I would also give a shout out to the concept of Wednesday and to Biscuits.
I prefer Biscuits to Wednesdays.
That's fair.
Biscuits are great.
Oh, you ever go...
First of all, Cheddar Bay Biscuits, fantastic.
Wrong.
Second best biscuit I think is Cracker Barrel.
They have great biscuits.
That's pretty great.
Oh, buttermilk.
So Wednesday and Biscuits are a couple of cats, and the people who take care of them,
I guess feed them, house them, are Kara and Andrew.
Okay.
And I got reached out to because at the end of last year, two of them tied the knot.
Oh, congratulations.
Got married.
Congratulations to the both of them.
And I got a message hoping for a happy one month anniversary message in December.
We can't do that.
Missed that message.
No, we don't do that.
In December, we didn't speak to anyone.
No.
I feel very bad about that though, so I want to make it up and wish a happy two month anniversary
to Kara and Andrew.
Happy anniversary to you both.
Ah, man.
You should have hung onto it for a full year.
In December, we could have been like, ha!
You thought we forgot, assholes!
Happy one year anniversary!
See, now the problem with that is I almost certainly would have forgotten.
We would absolutely have forgotten.
Yeah.
I doubt the internet will be around at the end of this year.
Give Wednesday and Biscuits some treats to celebrate.
Hope you all are having a great day.
Indeed.
Hey Jordan, today, let's start here on January 10th.
Alex seems to be looking at the world and he's seeing like, hey, a lot of people are
saying I'm right about stuff now.
Oh, that's not good.
They shouldn't do that.
The internet is really waking up, meaning the people are really waking up, and the saying
Alex Jones was right is being written on the walls, spray painted on the government buildings,
festooned to people's t-shirts and typed in to Twitter and Facebook accounts by the millions
a day.
And it's become a maxim.
And I'm very honored that the fact that I predicted all of this and now we're getting
the credit for it only because I want people to then realize that we know what's coming
next.
Uh, probably nuking a city is what he's going to predict, but, uh, I too would be honored
to have, uh, uh, Jordan was right directly next to, for a good time called Clarice.
I think that would give me a lot of honor, you know, that would make me feel good.
I think Alex is just responding to the fact that a bunch of people got kicked off social
media.
That would make sense.
And he's like, yeah, I told you they're going to kick you off social media if you keep behaving
in the ways that gay people kicked off social media.
Oh, what an amazing prediction.
Um, I think that I personally would never like to be in a situation where I'm celebrating
something that I said or did, uh, being memorialized in a way that I decided to call it festooned.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's not good.
If you ever catch me slipping and I use that term to be like, my words are festooned on
billboards, uh, I'm not doing well.
Things have gone bad.
My words emanate from the excrement of the ground, Dan.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
But, uh, you know, he's, uh, claimed, uh, on our previous episodes, Alex has, uh, laid
out the, the, uh, the foundation for the Antifa did the storming of the Capitol.
Yeah, that's great.
I like, uh, I like getting people killed who had nothing to do with it and, uh, it's your
fault.
Sure.
And now Alex is, uh, he's proved it.
Oh, good.
He's good.
Hear that.
Let me hear it.
That's the globalist that maneuvered us to destruction.
We slipped Trump in there.
He valiantly fought to at least keep the country sovereign and now they hired provocateurs.
We've proven this.
We have a report coming up at the end of the hour with all the evidence, two out of a million
demonstrators at the white house, the elliptical, the Washington monument stretched all the
way down to the Capitol, some other paramilitary groups were still identifying, showed up,
attacked the police.
And then the police on the other sides of the Capitol opened it up to the general public.
There was very little violence, very little attacks, except for a few people that were
provocateurs and who they were able to manipulate to go along with them, some useful idiots.
They videotaped with antifa camera people we've identified in every case, the National
Geographic camera people, the few violent events to then say that the Capitol was stormed
by terrorists, quote, and then the Capitol has fallen to the Patriots, Joe Biden end
quote.
Yeah.
I don't know.
We just see the laying out of the narrative here.
And that is basically that, okay, you, so you had antifa, they started things off these
provocateurs and they were working with some other shade, a shadowy group, uh, was the,
the big, tough guys that the skinny Jean folks had hired.
Um, sure.
It's all just provocateur stuff to make us look bad, man.
So what's going to happen at the next one?
Well, Alex is warning that, uh, there's going to be a lot more.
He's basically at this point been like, all right, they set us up.
It was all fake, but also I'm fucking out.
Oh yeah.
He was planning on going to the inauguration and now he's like, hell no.
Well that's smart.
That's smart.
Yeah.
That is very smart.
He's, he's changed his tone quite a bit.
It's a, it's all like, oh no, no, no.
Isn't that, isn't that a surprise?
They're all going to be setups in the future.
So wild.
So wild how he would completely change his tone the moment he got exactly what he wanted
and now realizes it's time to, uh, time to pivot.
Yeah.
Time to pivot.
Hmm.
Uh, but you know, Hey, there's a lot of other folks who are, uh, are coming out here and
uh, you know, they're, uh, making some, uh, some insightful inciting claims and statements.
All right.
So you have all these leftists, all these members of Congress, and I've got their quotes
right here.
We'll play some of the clips at the moment.
Ted Lou threatened widespread civil unrest.
We need to see some fires.
So Alex is referring to a 32nd clip of Ted Lou from, uh, 2018 where he's being interviewed
by Chris Hayes on MSNBC and is discussing the potential firing of Robert Mueller.
Not fires.
Fuck you.
He doesn't call for fires and he doesn't actually call for anything.
He just says that if Trump fires Mueller, it would likely lead to civil unrest and protest.
Great.
That's not a threat.
But that's how the comment and stuff like this is reported on Infowars.
No, no, no.
If somebody says this is the logical result of what this person does, they're like, see,
Mueller telling them to do it.
Yeah.
And you're like, God damn it, guys.
You're stupid.
Yeah.
So also Alex has found an Antifa leader, uh, that, uh, he's going to, uh, pinpoint as the,
uh, the, the villain of January 6th.
And I have an Antifa leader that was one of the first to break in who said, we're going
to go there and pose as patriots as Trump supporters.
And we're going to burn the Capitol down.
He said it in Utah, where he lives, where he's been arrested and charged for inciting
riot before.
We'll show you who he is.
He said it in DC the day before the event in a speech to Antifa, who was then getting
into manga outfits in the Capitol, he was arrested, but then they dropped the charges
on him because he did a good job.
This supposed Antifa leader Alex is talking about is a guy named John Sullivan.
He's not an Antifa leader.
I don't know what that means, but he's, uh, he is somebody who's had some history and
involvement in anti-fascist and social justice activism.
Sullivan was one of the people who was there and was recording the storming of the Capitol,
supposedly as an independent journalist, documenting history, PolitiFact reviewed his footage.
And there are some questions about how disconnected from the story he managed to be with him occasionally
seeming to express encouragement about what was going on around him.
But that's a far cry from the accusations that people like Alex are making as an independent
journalist who agrees with all of what you guys are doing.
I would like you to continue storming the Capitol building.
And somehow I'm the bad guy here.
What are you talking about?
The way it looks is that Sullivan is a bit of a bad player in the game.
He probably felt like he was doing an impartial piece of journalism documenting a monumental
moment, but he didn't show the poise and discipline to actually pull that role off.
That's what it appears like to me.
He said that some of his encouraging words were meant to help him blend in and that very
well may be the case, and I think that's what Alex is talking about with him, like we're
going to pretend to be MAGA people, like you do want to blend in with the crowd.
Yeah, I mean they will tear you limb from limb.
They did have that kind of Scrum vibe to them.
Scrum.
Yeah.
Whatever the case, it's nonsense to take whatever dubious behavior Sullivan may have shown on
January 6th and take it as proof that he was somehow an Antifa leader who was responsible
for the storming of the Capitol.
That is what I would call a desperate attempt to scapegoat.
Yeah, that's not good.
I can't find confirmation that he's been arrested in relation to the Capitol storming, but he
is facing charges related to an earlier protest in Utah that is still going through the courts.
So as far as I can tell, Alex is just making up the part about him having charges and them
being dropped related to this, and he's doing that because of things like what Joel Skousen
said on our last episode, that is if the provocateurs themselves get arrested, they'll be let off
because they're in on it with the authorities.
And that's just sort of building up that narrative, but I can't find any evidence of that.
I still don't understand how they're getting around the fact that, regardless, fuck it,
say Antifa did the whole thing.
You guys do still realize that they only followed because it's what they want to do and what
you told them to do.
Well, there's a couple of thoughts on this, actually, that come up over the course of
this.
Okay.
I think hypnotism may be involved.
You know, I should have seen that one coming.
Mass hypnosis.
That's what it was.
Yep.
Shit.
So it turns out...
You just red-pilled me is what it turns out.
Alex has, I was trying to figure out a way to talk about, like, come up with a pill,
but it's just a jelly bean.
Never mind.
Okay.
I'm kind of understanding here that he's, like, proven everything.
Like, everything is...
We got this, man.
Sure.
It was Antifa.
Easy.
And an unnamed fake militia.
Done and done.
That was going around.
They're working with the feds.
We just finished, right before the show went live today, a very powerful special report
that details the false flag, how Antifa staged it with some other shadowy paramilitary groups
that we're starting to identify.
That'll be in a report tomorrow, because they got to have a right-wing chair group as well.
So when it comes out, they can blame both groups.
This is about coming out for everybody's liberties.
So this is how it goes.
This is the way that you explain the fact that there were groups that look almost exactly
like your buddies.
Yeah.
Yep.
I mean, you might as well just come out and say, if we'd won, I'm happy that the Patriots
won, and since we lost, it was all Antifa.
Just say that.
Since the bottom fell out.
Yeah.
That is not us.
Now that it turns out everybody doesn't like this, it wasn't us.
Guess what?
We get it both ways.
Coming, going, forward, backward.
We get it.
Yeah.
It's fine.
We're white.
So the narrative here is being set, and it's fairly well said, I think, by Alex at this
point that it was just these other people.
It's not...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Not me.
Not Trump.
Who could pull some sort of visual and audio evidence of me doing exactly the thing that
I'm saying that I never did.
It's all the deep state, and the deep state has a bunch of tendrils, and some of them
are Antifa.
Q is also deep state.
How about Harrison Smith?
Is he deep state?
No, but he wasn't actually even on air.
That was a deep fake.
Oh.
That was a big deep fake.
Whoever made that was good.
They must have been working on that one for a long time.
And he just pretends that...
I haven't heard Alex talk about that broadcast at all.
Oh, that's unsurprising.
Yeah.
But look, so you have those deep state actors in the form of Q, Antifa.
But there was another group there, and that was the Trump folks.
And you might be surprised to find out what they were up to.
Okay.
This was meant to bring in the 25th Amendment, the impeachment of Trump, but it failed because
unlike any other football fans, or basketball fans, or liberals, or whoever, even though
they had hundreds of paid provocateurs trying to riot, trying to lead this, instead of the
Trump supporters, now we have dozens of these videos, were kicking their ass when they attacked
the cops and tried to break in the windows.
But they got overwhelmed.
So now the narrative is becoming that Trump's people tried to fight off Antifa and Q folks
who were trying to storm the counter.
All right.
This is bullshit, get the fuck out of my face forever.
I'm done speaking to anybody who's like, no, no, no, that's what happened.
Not only did Trump supporters not try and take over the whole fucking country, but they
actually tried to stop the takeover of the whole country.
If you say that to me, I will never speak to you again.
Love the constitution in America so much that they were willing to stand up and fight against
these malevolent communist invading forces like Q and Han people and Antifa in order
to protect the Capitol building that they respect so much.
Say it to my face.
I've talked to real army intelligence, highest levels, I'm not going to say the names of
the groups, everybody knows the highest level the army is, army special operations, Delta
Force, all that.
I mean, we had live feeds of that when we were there.
They're not like magic people, they're just like us, but they concur.
This was a failed false flag, pipe bombs found outside.
It was meant to be hundreds dead, hostages taken, Q-tards believing it all, Q-tards can
say they were going to go take hostages online, but they didn't because the simulation broke
down once they actually got there in the real world, it didn't happen.
A lot of it because patriots fought them off and stopped them.
So an alliance of Q-tards with Antifa and some shadowy synthetic militia group, the
feds control is what we now know.
So that's, hey, look, that's quite a showdown.
Yeah.
Quite a showdown.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
People still doing the tards.
Yeah, I don't like that at all.
I don't like that at all.
No, and it's kind of interesting that Alex seems to have given himself the green light
to say that a lot about Q-folks.
And I think that there's a real sense that he's realized this is not profitable for me
at all anymore.
Great way to throw them under the bus and I can maybe get some of the people back and
at the same time, you know what it feels like to me?
It feels like the relationship between Alex and Glenn Beck in like 2009, but in reverse.
Yeah, yeah.
Now Alex is...
I'm not Q.
At least I'm not Q.
Yeah, yeah.
You can hire me for Fox News.
I'm better than some of your fucking hosts.
Yeah, exactly.
Glenn Beck got a lot of mileage and legitimacy out of being like, I'm not Alex Jones.
At least I'm not him.
Yeah.
And now Alex has Q to point to.
He's finally freed himself up to do that.
That's disgusting.
And I think that it actually works on some people.
You saw flying around on Twitter all these people being like, I can't believe Alex Jones
denounced Q.
Oh, totally.
Because it's an effective thing to have some other thing that's farther and more extreme
than you that you can point to and be like, you know you hate that more.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Get some heat off you.
Everybody's acting like the tide just came in and everybody's moving up a level and it's
unacceptable and I won't fucking allow it.
No.
So, after this storming of the Capitol, you know, a lot of people have had some soul searching.
They've had some people asking difficult questions.
Sure.
And, you know, a lot of conversation has gone around about like what it would actually even
mean and what it would take to be together as a country again.
Like unite and Alex is afraid about truth and reconciliation committees.
Yeah, I would say we're probably gonna have to do something along the lines of the end
of World War II combined with de-bathification or, yeah, something like a better version
of that for all the white supremacists in our goddamn...
I don't know if you've heard, but John Brennan has called for truth and reconciliation committees.
Has he?
He would get fucked up if there were real truth and reconciliation committees.
If there were 100% real ones, we would be fucking decapitating Brennan.
So I doubt he's calling for that shit.
There would be some truth and some reconciliation coming of both directions.
Brutal.
Brutal shit to him.
By the way, Brennan has now said if you were a talk show host, a member of Congress, you
must come to communist reconciliation things on TV and say you're bad.
But once you do that, then things really collapse.
People cannot do this.
They're following a tried and true communist takeover.
I think that Alex is misreading a headline here.
Oh, yeah?
So John Brennan didn't say that there needed to be reconciliation.
Unsurprising.
But I think I found the quote he's talking about.
Okay.
I'll tell you that there can only be reconciliation with repentance.
And I think the single most important thing that Republicans in Congress who helped facilitate
this widespread conspiracy theory that somehow the election was stolen and the most important
thing that Donald Trump can do in those remaining 10 days is to stop those lies and to persuade
their followers and supporters that the president elect Biden is the duly elected president
of the United States.
Great.
That was said by Senator Chris Coons on Sunday's edition of Face the Nation.
I think that Alex just skimmed a headline that mentioned reconciliation and the host
of Face the Nation, whose name is Margaret Brennan.
I would bet that Alex saw the name Brennan and decided that it was John Brennan calling
for communist style reconciliation committees.
Dan, Dan, it is infuriating to me that that happened.
And two, that you're good enough to figure out exactly what happened.
I think that's a frustrating truth.
I think that's what happened.
It's totally what happened.
It seems on brand for him.
100% what happened.
To see the name Brennan and just assume instead of the host of Face the Nation.
You are inside his mind to a terrifying degree.
You're fucking Hannibal Lecter, Dan.
You're Hannibal Lecter, and he's the guy from Red Dragon or whatever.
Um, maybe.
Yeah.
I don't like to cook though, or at least I'm not good at it.
Hannibal but for frozen pizzas.
To be fair, I have no evidence that Hannibal is good at cooking.
That's fair.
Yeah.
And there's no like reviews of his cooking.
Well, I mean, you have to have some sort of talent to cook a brain and eat it to the person.
Yeah, I guess so.
And pair it with wine.
So, Barnes comes in.
Barnes drops by, and his entire appearance here on this Sunday episode, this January
10th episode, is that, hey, Q sucks.
Just there to beat up on Q.
Great.
Um, and so he describes it as a psy-op, which I have some questions about.
Okay.
This is the most dangerous time in the history of our constitutional republic.
It faces more risk than it did, frankly, in 1860.
That's the kind of threat that they want to impose by ramrodding, using the pretext of
this staged event that was heavily facilitated by a psy-op operation of QAnon and with infiltrators
and instigators involved as well.
So the thing that I run into, and I hear this, they're like QAnon is a psy-op.
One of the things that really fueled it lately, and in the last year at least, has been Donald
Trump retweeting QAnon accounts, and Donald Trump himself giving tacit acknowledgement
of and support of this because it, you know, narcissistically feeds his ego or whatever.
So I have to ask if Trump is running a psy-op on himself.
Is Trump running a psy-op on you, Robert Barnes?
I think what's obvious is that Trump is Antifa, Dan.
Oh, shit.
And that's why Antifa, that's who really fucking Antifa-ed us at the Capitol building.
Right.
Who, if Antifa inspired the attack, the only answer, Dan, is Trump is a black bloc.
Sure.
So you had those people there who were looking real mighty scary.
You know, at the Capitol, you had the looky-loo types, the people who were maybe just there
to take pictures of themselves.
Right.
Foot fetishists of AOC.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then you had terrifying people.
Right.
And the terrifying...
Like the foot fetishists of AOC?
Okay.
Well, they're terrifying in a different way.
Yeah.
You had the real militia-trained looking type people.
Right, right, right.
And so in order to explain this, Alex has already said that this is some militia that's
working with the feds, but now we get to pivot that over and like, that's what the Q people
were.
Yeah.
Right?
Sure.
So that explains everything.
God, I hate this.
Because there were people there with zip ties.
They arrested one of them in Nashville.
So there are people there that had ulterior agendas that misled other people who were
partaking, who didn't realize what was happening.
Well, they told them, we're Q secret agents under Trump's orders and we're going to go
in there.
And then now I heard that day one, oh, they told them they were about to get Pelosi and
grab the proof.
And then sure enough, oh, there's experts, oh, this was done for special ops to get Pelosi's
laptop.
I mean, this is so scripted, folks.
If you're online, you pledge allegiance to some made up letter of the alphabet, and then
it tells you to go take over the White House or the Capitol or whatever, you're being set
up for death, just like Arlington Road.
Go see Arlington Road.
If you're talking about the people that pledge allegiance to Q being stupid, I would ask
you what about General Flynn and his family?
Sure.
They posted a video of themselves pledging allegiance to Q and saying, where we go one
we go all.
Nah, nah, they were manipulating the deep state into thinking that the deep state had
manipulated them into believing what the deep state says.
And that way they can run this counter, counter, counter, counter coup, which is going on right
now, after the first coup from...
I'm so tired, Dan, I'm just so goddamn tired.
They also posted that video of themselves pledging allegiance to Q on the Fourth of
July.
Explain to me what exactly you think is the difference between pledging allegiance to
Q and pledging allegiance to Trump.
Not much.
No.
I don't see too much difference between that and pledging allegiance to a fucking flag.
What are we doing pledging allegiance to shit, Dan?
Let's not dissect that now, but I agree, patriotism can go astray.
So Robert Barnes apparently works for Trump, apparently.
Sure why not?
I don't know if that's true.
No other lawyer will work for him anymore.
I don't know if that's true and I don't care, because there are ethical problems whether
it's true or not, like, it's still like, he still should be disbarred for his behavior.
Oh yeah.
But he...
Is Larry Klaiman free for this one?
He might be.
He might not be able to practice.
I hope not.
But Barnes, I just love this.
We heard this before and I just wanted to play it because it happened again.
Alex being like, he works for Trump, he doesn't want me to tell you that.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, I do not need to lay out my curriculum vitae or my
27 years of the fight, but I am true to America.
I make mistakes, but I believe in human justice and freedom and promote it.
Robert Barnes does not even want it known that he's worked for Trump for months during
this election fraud, battling at the highest levels or that talks to Trump on a routine
basis.
But we're going to put that out now because we're 10 days out from the inauguration of
Biden.
So...
You're not putting that out now.
You've put that out a bunch already.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
A whole bunch.
You're not good at keeping secrets.
No.
Especially when they're made up bullshit.
Right.
Or when they're true.
True and ethically very not good.
I don't know too many lawyers who would be like, okay, my client is the president of
the United States.
Right.
I think it's a good idea for me to have a radio show with Alex Jones.
Yeah, it's a good idea for me to moonlight as a pro-Trump propagandist.
I don't think that is good for the legal profession.
It's iffy.
Yeah.
So Barnes, I will say, you know, just looking at everything purely, you know, take morals,
take just everything out of it.
Sure.
He has some accurate points that he makes about QAnon, which, oh, shocking.
A lot of people have been saying for a while.
Yeah.
The first thing that he says is not really one of those.
He talks about how this is a brilliant psy-op, which I take issue with some of that.
But he has some other points that I think are pretty good.
Q is a brilliant disinformation campaign that is unique.
If you look at other message boards and anon posters that claim to be government agents
on those message boards, they do not communicate in the way Q did.
So people who study disinformation campaigns very early on were telling me this was not
just a sort of conspiracy theorist of people going down a rabbit hole on a random message
board.
This was showing signs of a sophisticated disinformation psy-ops campaign being run
by somebody with institutional influence and backing.
I do think that there is a point to be made about how different this is than other things
like this.
Sure.
The message gate got to a certain point and then it fizzled out.
Now granted, it sort of metastasized and evolved into what this is.
Sure.
But there were a bunch of other attempts at doing something like this on message boards.
Right.
Right, right, right.
And it even goes back to earlier conspiracy times when you'd have people who would have
these, essentially, huge role-playing things where they would have like...
No, this is like an augmented reality participatory storytelling thing that a bunch of people
are...
You know, it reminds me of Gravity Falls, weirdly enough.
At the end of the cartoon, they had a little statue that was somewhere in the Pacific Northwest.
That's where the show was set.
And then a bunch of fans put together all of these clues together and wound up finding
out that it was actually something that they had hidden in real life, like this little
statue there, and they found it.
And it was a bunch of people all working together, finding out all of these clues to...
And it's functionally the same thing as Q, it's just this time there's nothing at the
end of the rainbow but storming the fucking Capitol building.
Yeah, there are some things like that that are outside of the realms of political conspiracy
and propaganda.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then there are also versions that are conspiracy and internet message board based
things that could have turned into stuff like this and made it into an augmented reality
kind of thing.
Totally, totally.
But it didn't.
I do think that that's fair.
I don't think it makes sense to say that it's brilliant and institutionally supported.
No, I would even argue that the main reason that it works is because it's kind of stupid.
It's at the level of the people participating in it.
Yeah, and it's malleable and decentralized to an extent that you can just... anything
can be anything.
Yeah, which is why you don't want anybody with institutional control anywhere near it.
Yeah.
You know what I said?
I think when I said that he had a good point, I think I was basically just remembering this
next clip.
Yeah.
And that's him talking about the element of it being like a game.
And a lot of people have talked about that, about how one of the things that makes it
so insidious is the way in which there's like, you're involved in this, in the way that that
Gravity Falls thing is actually a fun, immersive experience.
This is a false carrot in front of you on a pole.
Some people catch Pokemon on the corner and some people find out that there's a secret
conspiracy on the corner.
It's the same fucking shit.
And Barnes is now talking about that, but it's something that other people have been
talking about and warning about for a long time.
Since the beginning of the fucking thing.
And these people, like Alex and like Infowars, were perfectly happy to, I guess, ignore any
of these warnings to the extent that this was possibly profitable.
Let's see if we can exploit some of it.
It's all just supporting Trump.
So like, Hey, let's let it be.
But now somebody's got to go onto the bus and it's going to be Q and A.
Yeah.
They would, let's say they were trying to find something in a scavenger hunt and that's
what it was.
It was part fiction, part reality.
And they went to a real house where something was hidden or a clue was located for them
to find the next clue.
Well, they would go there and they would find, say three pieces of wood, all pointed at a
particular part of the wall.
And they'd be like, Oh, that can't be a coincidence.
It must be something behind that wall.
When in fact it was purely coincidental.
They were seeing patterns that did not exist.
Well, what QAnon brilliantly did was use the questioning technique without ever giving
answers, use vagueness and ambiguity while appearing to give specific secrets to, because
with Pokemon Go and others, you shift into the VR, VR is a fake template over reality.
So, you know, reality's real.
You're in a garage, you're in a gutter, you're on top of building.
But then they found people, if they told them there was a bridge off a building, someone
would just jump off the building because suddenly there was a bridge there in their overlay
through the Pokemon Go.
That's exactly right.
I know that they think that there's a substantial difference between what they do and what their
describing and I don't think that there is.
There's none.
I know that, you know, factually there's a difference between saying there's a bridge
in front of you and then you jump and you fall, but Alex just tells people that headlines
mean something and he has never read the article.
It's the same, it's the same amount of faith that's being demanded of.
He's sufficiently vague about his predictions.
He gives you secrets that aren't really real.
Yeah.
Basically everything he's describing.
You know, like I used to have bigger teeth, but now I just grind them every time we do
this show.
So now they're much smaller.
You don't even have teeth anymore.
I don't even have teeth.
I just have ground down nubs.
So it turns out Alex, a couple months back, had threatened to reveal who Q is because
he knows all of it.
Yes, of course.
He never did do that.
It was all just probably an attempt to get attention.
Yeah.
So this conversation becomes even sillier knowing that he's pretended that he knows
who Q is and he can expose all of it.
Right.
Because apparently, I don't know if you know this, Q tried to enlist Robert Barnes.
All right.
I hate everyone.
And they targeted people who they thought would otherwise be potential active sources
of support for crowdsourcing Trump support.
So they looked at people who did independent investigative journalism.
Explain this.
They actually approached you, and I don't know if you want to get into this, but not
at the Q level, but above that, we're the intel group and we're with Q because again,
they give you a virtual reality where you actually think you're fighting for freedom,
but you're working for them.
Exactly.
Okay.
So now Barnes, if you are agreeing with Alex when he says that Q tried to enlist you, it
now is your all's responsibility to be like, who the fuck are you talking about?
Who are you talking about?
Provide us the name.
You've already said you can throw them under the bus.
Yeah, exactly.
You could clear up a whole lot, Alex, if you wanted to.
Oh, if you hate them so much.
I fucking hate these people.
Yeah, they're terrible.
So Alex gets a little bit of breaking news in the middle of this broadcast, and it's
not breaking news.
That police officer, the Capitol Police, who died by suicide, Alex has decided to turn
that into a conspiracy.
Sure.
All right.
This is breaking news.
I'm not ready to give all of it out yet.
I'll do it next segment because I've got one more question from our sources, but we have
this from inside the DC Police Department.
There has been a high level suicide of one of the deputy police chiefs.
I'll leave it at that.
They're trying to cover it up.
We don't know if it's actually a cover up.
They may have killed them in the DC Capitol Police.
So Alex is turning this police officer's death into a story where he is said to have committed
suicide, but it might be a murder because he happens to be the cop who told these cops
to stand down and allow Antifa to attack the Capitol.
So he's basically cast this guy in this role, and it's just disgusting.
I can't imagine being anywhere near someone who was affected by the Capitol building like
that without like instantly being like, does anybody have a template for how to sue Alex
Jones?
Oh yeah.
There should be at this point.
I haven't heard him say anything yet, but does anybody have like a Mad Libs for the
way Alex Jones is going to need to be sued for this?
There should be like a whole section on legal zoom just dedicated to suing Alex for the
right shit.
Yeah.
There's a dropdown menu and they'll fill in the rest for you.
It's like, if I were this guy's family, I can't imagine what I would be like how pissed
off I would be if you trying to imply that someone I cared about who I just lost just
days ago.
You fucking killed.
Yeah.
He, uh, it was, he, you know, it's all suspicious in a conspiracy because he ordered to stand
down.
Like go fuck yourself, man.
No.
How cruel.
Keep his fucking name out of your mouth.
I'm not even saying the dude's name out of respect.
Absolutely not.
So anyway, Barnes, uh, is still on and he thinks that, uh, that whole thing where everybody
was like taking the pledge, like Flynn, uh, it was all a setup so they could get a conspiracy
charge.
So I was right about that.
It's a double double kind of starting the late fall where the queue was asking people
to take oaths to have the, have them broadcast videotape themselves, taking these oaths,
have them broadcast other people that they were taking these oaths.
Uh, and that was beginning to set up a, basically a future, uh, seditious conspiracy allegation
against all participants and then try to motivate other ones to become more and more violent
because the goal was to feel like this election was everything and whatever happened that
this was the end of the world.
So they had to take whatever.
So they would either feel futility and frustration and fear and lash out or they would convince
a portion of them that the, the insiders on the government and the insiders in the military
and the insiders and the intelligence branches really wanted them to take action.
How's that any different than Infowars coverage?
Dan, I keep repeating in my head, violence is not the answer because the moment he said
they wanted to make you feel like this election was the end of the world, the only response
that I can, like I went red, like there is, there is flashing lights behind my eyes.
No, I, I, you told me these people are run by the fucking devil and that if Trump loses,
it's the end times.
It's the end of all civilization.
No, it's, it's not, it's not fair to treat audiences like this.
You know, it's, it's not, look, violence is not the answer, but sometimes it could be
part of the answer when it comes to Robert Barnes.
I don't know.
I would just get, get rid of that license of his, I think that that's the solution.
You can't say that.
You can't.
I want to write one law for that word specific, just for the, not infringing upon freedoms
of speech whatsoever, but if you say that before the election, it's the end of the world
if you lose it.
And then after the election you say, uh, these people were trying to lie to you about that.
You lose something, you lose something, a foot, a hand.
I don't care.
Robert Barnes would just say like, I didn't say that and that may, maybe that's true.
Unfortunately you worked for a news organization, quote unquote news organization that was their
editorial stance and Alex screamed it on air for months.
So I don't know.
It's not even the pot calling the kettle black.
It is just both of them are the fucking kettle and they're just arguing with each other.
Who's more kettle-y.
Yeah, exactly.
You're fucking both kettles.
So Alex has now got confirmation, um, that, uh, this, uh, this cop who has passed away,
uh, ordered the stand down and I don't know where he got this confirmation from, but based
on the other news he's reporting, I'm not positive if I'm going to trust this.
Let's get down to brass tacks.
I have guests on that actually know stuff.
We don't have to have sources.
Most of the time you and I have people asking us what's going on.
I don't mean that arrogantly.
It's not like there's magic sources here, magic sources there.
We're smart people.
We've lived this, Bob.
You're smart.
I'm smart, but, but absolutely what you said last night is more targets.
I have confirmed that a Capitol police supervisor, the one that ordered the stand down has committed
suicide.
There is an internal bulletin that at least four governors mansions in the U S have been
overrun governors driven out.
This is not too crap.
This is real.
Uh, and that there are attacks happening in governor's mansions right now, and that there
are more attacks plan the next 24 hours, and it looks like deep States using Antifa and
program Q tards who think they're part of an insurrection, uh, for Trump to actually
bring in martial law against us all.
That's why big tech is shutting Trump up ahead of actually declaring martial law that will
probably kill Trump.
So Alex is reporting that there were four unspecified governor's mansions that have
been overrun and the governors have been fled.
Dan, what day is today?
Is the 12th we're recording this.
What day did he say that 10th okay.
How many governors were his mansions or all right, so we're, you know what happened here?
I think I figured it out.
So this isn't like Q no, it's not.
It's not some kind of false reality is not at all.
And he's reporting this as like in the present happening right now.
I just got an internal bulletin.
I can't believe they kept that quiet cause I haven't heard anything about, I think what
he's talking about is on the sixth there were protests at capitals at governor's mansions
and there were a couple of incidents where governors felt a threat.
And I think that he's taking those bits of information that maybe he didn't know about
until this point and pretending that they're happening in the immediate.
That's the only thing I can think of because otherwise I would suggest if you're going
to report that for governor's mansions have been overrun, you have a deep responsibility
to name the States and have a little bit more fucking information about it.
But Hey man, it's not a false reality like Q Anon.
I was working with the president for real, you know, not in a fantasy world, not online,
not not in a lie, but in the real world.
So was Barnes on record.
So I know we're not as cool as the game, but we're in the real world.
We're not in the simulation.
But those that are already in the simulation want you to only worship the simulation.
It's very sick.
It's very sad.
And now I have this horrible news that governor's mansions, a bunch of them have been attacked.
They're using this to go into martial law.
They're not given up with only 10 days left of Trump, nine and a half days because they
want to repudiate everything he did before he leaves.
This story does not evolve over the course of the show and it is dropped on Monday.
Yeah.
That makes sense.
Because Alex is just unsurprising.
Yeah.
So Alex is not jealous of Q, but I think a lot of people are saying that he's jealous
of Q.
People like me.
Yeah.
I would also say that.
And he, he wants, he has some things to say about people who think that.
And by the way, there are all these idiots that send me messages and I see it online.
Jones is jealous of Q. Q took over his audience.
Q man hits the money.
I was persecuted for supporting Trump and almost went bankrupt.
I could have co-opted the Q thing.
I tried to be nice to him and educate him.
Don't believe people you don't know.
Don't go to random places.
They didn't listen.
So he could have co-opted them if you wanted to.
Of course.
Here's him from a year ago talking to Joel Skousen.
Let's hear it.
I was thinking, I was thinking I'm just going to endorse it and then, and then co-opt it
publicly and go, Oh, Q says this, Q says that, cause everybody loves a little magic stuff
because it's, it's, it's, it's, it's definitely a delusional issue and it's sucking up so
many good people into it.
Yes.
Yeah.
So he was thinking about using Q like a puppet.
Q says this, Q says that.
And he did.
He did try that.
Yes, he did.
And it did not work.
No, it did not.
Which led to him being more jealous of Q.
And very frustrated.
So Barnes gets down to the, the, like really the matter at hand.
He cuts through the bullshit and this is really what it's about.
Those people who are out there, you know, continue to crowdsource investigative independent
research and review, continue to do independent grassroots journalism independent of and separate
from and divorce from Q, continue to be proactive and productive, continue to support places
like Infowars.
Infowars is the model for independent information and a free press and free speech to stay alive.
That's what it's really about.
It's about transitioning people back from that, you know, making them feel safe and
not judged for coming back to Infowars away from Q.
Yeah.
Because Q, I don't know if you know this, Chinese operation.
Great.
I'm glad to be here.
Anybody's part of Q.
You're part of a ChaiCom operation.
Disown Q and return to Americanism.
That's right.
It's Manchurian Candidate 2.0.
And folks, we have storeable food at the 2020 prices.
Only a few days left.
Good.
Good stuff.
So we got a real, just a scathing broadside attack on Q on this Sunday episode.
And that's most of what it is.
But I think that it's pretty important for Alex to lay this all out because he's got
to disavow and get away from the stuff that happened at the Capitol.
And people have got to take a fall for that, and the people that are going to fall are
going to be Antifa, who are already villains.
And QAnon is now not just some kind of a, hey, it's good, but oh, whatever.
It's not the same.
He's not just jealous of it anymore.
They're bad now.
And also apparently some hired militia who's unspecified.
But yeah, so you can get away from that.
And now when we get to the 11th, which is Monday, I really felt like it's Alex trying
to turn to the direction that he's going to be going in.
I felt an amazing return to like, this is so fucking familiar.
This is like right before Obama got elected.
He's just pretending that mere days ago people didn't storm the Capitol.
Yeah, it turns out like, you know, you got nine days left till the election.
And Antifa, they're going to rule you.
Nine days from now, the globalist will be swearing in their installed puppet leader
in exactly nine days to the minute, basically.
Things kick off at noon Eastern, but they say about 20 minutes in, he'll be sworn in.
Joe Biden, the open communist operative.
And that's why from L.A. to New York to Austin, Texas, Antifa marched to the streets with
shields and guns and weapons, saying we own this country, it is ours.
And next, they're coming to your houses because by day and by night, they're Antifa.
But their real job is contact tracers for the Clinton Global Initiative on record.
These are the graduate students and students who are now your rulers, most of them pedophiles.
So now we just kind of have a more extreme version of how he was trying to scare you
about like job, or not, what is it, AmeriCorps and like civic work programs that Obama wanted
to put in place.
It's just kind of the same thing.
It just feels like you just, you're just going to pretend that didn't happen.
Yeah.
Hey, I'm not going to talk to a Republican about tax rates because I don't care because
guess what is underneath that conversation?
I want to kill the left, so I don't give a fuck.
Don't you dare talk to me about some program.
The end.
The programs are done.
It's hard to, it's hard to engage on any argument that it's hard to believe that it's really
what's being discussed.
Yeah.
Here's what's being discussed.
You want to kill me.
Now we need to deal with that and you have nothing, like I don't understand why any Republican
is allowed on TV to say anything other than we're sorry for wanting to kill you all the
time because I don't give a shit what they have to say on laws.
I don't give a shit what they have to say on fucking taxes or voting or anything like
that.
You guys want to kill me.
I think that the issue is that the ones who do want to kill you don't feel bad about it.
Yeah.
So they're not going to go on TV and say any of that stuff.
Well guess what?
That's the only thing that other people get to talk about.
All Republicans only get to talk about how they want to kill us.
That's the only questions I have for them.
It's an interesting policy.
I don't think the media is going to take you up on this.
Yeah.
I'm not surprised because they're also failing us in this regard as well.
So speaking of media that's failing, Alex is failing himself and reality, but the reason
that he's able to, I think, try to pull off moving back towards like just making you afraid
of Joe Biden.
Sure.
Um, is that he's just decided that, uh, Hey, that whole thing at the Capitol was Antifa
and Q and like we tried to stop it.
We're the good guys.
Those are terrorists.
They don't hate the police.
They don't want to be the police and they're the ones that went over a hundred of them
on record.
You know, their names dressed up like Trump supporters and Trump supporters tried to stop
them breaking into the Capitol.
Once they broke in, there was another contingent of morons there.
We've tracked it to eight Jan and all the sites.
So yeah, all of it is just that all the, uh, the good Patriots, they tried to stop them.
It didn't work out.
They were the ones who look like they were Trump supporters or just people in disguise.
It's no big deal.
We're still the heroes.
We're the, uh, the oppressed where the aggrieved or even more aggrieved because they tried
to make us look bad by storming the Capitol.
Yeah.
There's no moving forward until all of these people admit that they lied.
That's it.
You're like, honestly, I, how there's no change to Alex's programming unless he like, there's
no change to those people listening to him unless Alex has to say he's a liar.
Well Laura Ingram has to say she's a liar unless Lou Dobbs has to go on TV and say to
the world, I lied to you because I want money.
Yeah.
But I don't think that even that would be that helpful.
I mean, it would be nice because maybe it would ruin their careers.
I mean, it's not going to, it's not going to solve anything, but nothing's going to
change until that happens.
But I also don't think anything will change after that.
That has to, no, I mean, then we can start with other shit.
Well, that's the first step though, but these media figures have to have some sort of accountability
for their bullshit because they're the ones who inspired this.
I agree that there should be some accountability and maybe they wouldn't be able to work anymore
if they had to admit that they lied and that might be a positive.
I would like that.
However, they just get replaced by somebody else who's craven.
And the audience would be...
But at least they would know that eventually you have to admit you're lying.
Well, yes.
Eventually.
Once people storm the Capitol, you will be forced to admit, you know.
Sooner or later you have to admit you're a liar.
At least you know that's in the, in your head because these people aren't going to.
Enjoy your run.
Enjoy, you know, it's going to be all great.
Yeah.
Gravy and tell people have an insurrection.
It's just like Trump.
Like, Hey, I get it.
You were, you got what you got.
I'm sorry, government and everybody failed and allowed you here, but this can't happen.
This can't happen.
Well, I, I, I'm of the opinion that even if those media figures were to come out and be
like, I lied because I was trying to make money or whatever, it wouldn't matter that
much because the audience wouldn't be disillusioned.
They'd just be like, well, I got to find someone new.
This person sold out or something.
And Alex has the same complaint about the Q people and you're still saying Trump will
be in office in nine days.
Well, let's sit back and watch.
And I know you Q folks aren't going to go away even once that happens because you bought
into a lie, just like you sent the Nigerian email scam or that first thousand bucks and
your family says, that's a scam.
They need 5,000 more.
You'll never get that either.
No, I'll get a million now.
And I send Prince of booboo, the 5,000.
And after you've said everything you've got to the scammers, you'll hate your family for
warning you.
It doesn't matter.
We're going to move on from that.
I think Alex got tricked by those emails.
Wow.
Yeah, he is right.
They will hate your family for warning you.
I am aware of that type of situation.
So I always enjoy it when Alex gets in reporter mode and he reports things that were brought
to his attention by his wife's tennis partner, hard hitting scoops.
In this next clip, we get some second or third hand information from somebody who works in
security for Alex, who heard something from his mother.
And now Alex is reporting it on air as news.
I talked to one of our security guys that, you know, bonded security, armed security.
We have her at the office and his mom is one of the head nurses at a nursing home.
And she said, wow, they gave all the old people the shots and now a bunch are sick and none
of them are getting up and coming to eat.
They just got the shots last week and they're real lethargic and they're worried they're
going to start dying.
So I'll tell you next week, I'll tell you next week, how many, how many you're dead.
How about you not talk about this until next week then, because the number could be zero.
Yeah.
You dick.
Oh no.
But then you won't spend the next week in fear of the number not being zero.
Oh yeah.
But it's so important because my security guy talked to his mom and I heard this third
hand that I've got to try and make you scared of something that may or may not happen.
Sounds right.
I think Alex is probably only reporting this because of his media diet.
And he read something in the Ron Paul Institute website that is important.
A nursing home at zero coronavirus deaths is then at vaccine residents for coronavirus
and deaths began.
Ron Paul Institute.
So this article is about a nursing home from around New York called the Commons on St.
Anthony.
The most recent report from CNY central has the number of deaths there at 32 since December
21st, which is when an outbreak of COVID-19 began.
The outbreak predates the first vaccinations.
Many residents and staff received the first dose of the vaccine on December 22nd, and
the second doses weren't begun until January 12th.
It's an interesting case here where the actual line that Alex says might not actually be
factually inaccurate, but it's still a lie.
It may well be the case that the deaths began after the vaccination started, but the headline
is being used by people like Alex and like Ron Paul to suggest that there's a causal
relationship there.
This story is not interesting to Alex, except as a means to convince his audience that vaccines
are a deadly plan from the globalists.
So he wouldn't be covering the story unless the message you were supposed to take from
it is that vaccines killed the people in the Commons.
And that's just not earned.
That information is not there to be reported.
Yep.
You can listen to your security guy's mom, or maybe the security guy making stuff up
about what his mom said.
Who knows?
Yeah, I despair for the possibility of anyone learning anymore.
Nope.
It's just not gonna happen.
And I'd like to convince you even more of that.
I can't wait, because I have got nothing but bad news on that front, Dan.
Because it's over for humanity.
Yes, thank you.
There will only be lone survivors.
I knew he was back!
I said it earlier, fuck yeah.
You did call it.
Now then, it's over for that-
Mike Adams.
Oh, fuck all of these people.
Fuck all of these people!
Well, Mike Adams, the health ranger, noted rapper, weirdo, Ebola curer.
Sure.
Yes, he did cure Ebola.
That's true.
He was sort of exiled from Info Wars, because he had an approach to the pandemic after a
while.
Right.
People should take this seriously.
That should be-
This is not good.
That should be boiled down to, a lot of people are gonna die if people-
People keep saying the shit that I used to say.
He joined up with Alex for quite a while in doing COVID denialism and COVID paranoia,
alternatingly, and then they had a little bit of a disagreement, and he was not seen
for quite a while.
Quite a while.
He is back, because now it's time to just complain about Biden, and the two of them
can do that just fine.
All day.
Joining us is Mike Adams at NaturalNews.com.
Appreciate him coming on with us.
He's written an excellent article, 25 Insane Crazy Agendas, Joe Biden and Kamala Harris
will push on America if they seize power after rigging the election.
Mike, thanks for joining us.
What is your big takeaway about the state of the nation and where we are and what's
unfolding before we come back next segment and get into your report?
I would expect, if this is happening, that the two of them should really get into and
discuss what their differences were and why he hasn't been on for so long.
Right, I guess we'll just pretend that didn't happen.
Let's pretend that-
Nope.
He didn't learn.
Well, who's right?
Because he had factually different-
Nah, nah, it's fine.
It wasn't opinions.
No, it was opinions, because they were both making everything up.
That could be.
Yeah.
So, Mike is thinking that maybe Trump, right?
Sure.
So, maybe he doesn't want to be president, again, not of America.
Maybe he wants to start a new country.
I'm removing Trump.
He has a very, very narrow window of opportunity to stop this now, but Alex, for all we know,
Trump may have thrown in the towel at this point and said, you know what?
The swamp is too deep to drain.
You can't fix the system from the inside.
That is probably true.
I'll give you that.
Perhaps Trump is deciding that the only way to really fix America is to let the corrupt
system implode and fail and crater and then start a new system on the other side.
That may be what he's thinking.
We don't know.
He may be thinking, let's start a new confederacy.
Yeah, that does kind of sound like what he would be thinking right now.
And what you guys are desperately hoping he's thinking.
Yeah.
I'm kind of, I'm getting to the point where I'm like, yeah, you guys should go somewhere
else.
All of you.
I don't think, I understand that thought, but I just don't think it's functional.
There's uninhabitable places in Australia that could use a lot of Republicans, Dan.
You meant uninhabited, but you said uninhabitable.
No, I did mean uninhabitable and that's where Republicans should go and maybe they can terraform
it.
We could send them to Mars and then we could move.
We've got options, Dan.
I understand there's some of that elusive free market over there.
There's a lot of manpower that we're wasting that could be on Mars leaving us alone.
So Mike is on, but he has a little bit of a time window and that's because Trump is
supposed to give a speech in the middle of when this episode is on.
Right.
And it's happening because it gets pushed back and then there's a speech for the next
day at Alamo, but it's not the Alamo, it's Alamo, Texas, which is all very confusing
and it plays out over the course of this episode.
That did not happen.
We did not have a city version of the fucking Four Seasons.
It's not for sure because Alamo, Texas is also like a border town and so there's a possibility
that that still feeds into the messaging that Trump would want to send with the border.
It should absolutely, his time in public should begin and end with being racist towards our
southern border.
You would think.
That's great.
But also, you would expect that he would want to give a speech at the Alamo.
Yes, you would.
Just like he would want to give a speech at the Four Seasons hotel.
Right, right.
It does seem like a pattern.
Anyway, this speech, Mike doesn't think it's going to be anything big.
Trump set to speak in about 30 minutes.
What do you think he's going to say?
Well, I have no idea what he's going to say because all the options are on the table.
I suspect it's going to be kind of wishy-washy because he's still got a week or more in office
and he's still got options on the table and there are a lot of things that can happen.
So I suspect he's not going to concede, but he's also not going to commit.
I'm sad to say, but we'll have to wait and see.
He doesn't need to concede and he's already accepted that he's lost.
So I don't...
I don't care what he does at all as long as he's quiet.
So you know who Mike doesn't want to be quieted?
That's Pompeo.
No, he should absolutely be quieted.
It turns out that he wants Mike Pompeo to seize a bunch of URLs.
What if he instead got sent to Mars?
Well, I guess that would be fine as long as from Mars he has a Wi-Fi connection and he
can seize Amazon's...
I don't know if I want that.
What I do want to mention, Alex, is that Secretary of State Mike Pompeo has a move that he could
make right now to fight back against this big tech deplatforming of Parler and other
conservative platforms and individuals.
Mike Pompeo could order the State Department to seize the domain names of Amazon.com, Google.com,
Facebook.com, YouTube, Twitter, and so on.
Seize the domain names and charge those companies with acting as part of a foreign cyber warfare
attack on the United States of America to rig our elections.
That'd go well, I think.
Yeah, I think that's a good idea.
I think people would respond positively towards that.
I think it would give everybody peace of mind.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, the government is taking over some of the largest websites as a hostile
action.
Yeah, I think that's good.
10 days, 9 days before a president who lost an election is supposed to go out of office,
his State Department is attacking.
Yeah, that'd be good, that'd be awesome.
I'm liking everything Pompeo's doing right now.
It's really great.
I love the way he's trying to convince people that it'd be a good idea for him to be president
someday.
Yeah, good work.
So Mike Adams, the health ranger, might not have gotten the memo that Alex hates QAnon
now.
Sure, sure.
Because he's coming in with some Q shit.
He's got material that he could declassify.
We know they have.
Sidney Powell routinely spoke about the information, the Kraken details from the 305th Military
Intelligence Battalion.
That wasn't just fiction.
So Sidney Powell submitted information in an affidavit that was supposed to be provided
by an anonymous source that she had codenamed Spider with a Y.
Unfortunately she did a bad job of redacting her documents, so she accidentally doxxed
her source, who's an IT consultant named Joshua Merritt.
He claimed to be in the military intelligence, working in the 305th Battalion, but that's
all bullshit.
Merritt was never an intelligence analyst and didn't even make it through the appropriate
training courses in the army.
When confronted about this statement and the fact that it's clearly not true, he basically
said that he hadn't really read the statement he signed before signing it, which raises
a whole lot of questions about who in Powell's team wrote it.
Doesn't that mean that you, isn't that, can't you be like, barred or something held in contempt?
Put Sidney Powell in jail!
So part of the recent QAnon lore is that this 305th Battalion, nicknamed the Kraken, had
raided the server host in Germany and they'd seized a bunch of evidence of election fraud
and proof that like the CIA was involved and shit.
This naturally all traces back to a Facebook post by some random QAnon follower making
shit up.
That's the story that Powell's affidavit was looking to reinforce, by way of assigning
the story to a meant-to-be-anonymous person in military intelligence.
The story is shit when you know that it's just coming from a QAnon Facebook account,
but if you can pretend that there's some real deep insider named Spider, you can make more
people like Mike Adams buy it.
Anyway, the point here is that people like Alex and Mike want whatever benefit they can
derive from believing the same stuff that Q followers do, and they want to use the same
sources of information that QAnon people do, but they want to pretend that they're somehow
above it, and it is pathetic.
Yeah, the only, like when people are tweeting like, I can't believe Alex turned on Q.
Believe it, but also what we should be doing is sowing as much division between the two
as possible while recognizing that both of them are complete liars and full of shit.
I want Q people and info-warriors to fight on the streets.
And they will on their own.
Yeah, exactly.
You don't have to do anything for them to end up at loggerheads.
I know, but it'd be fun to fan the flames a little bit.
It's interesting because it really felt like there was an opportunity after the 6th where
they could get past whatever differences they had, but instead it seems like there's now
an irrevocable difference.
You would think that until next week when they all decide that there is no difference
between them and it's all fine.
I think that some groups could end up finding common ground, but I don't think Alex and
Q are going down that road.
We'll see.
So Mike, he's learned that some hackers, some liberal hackers, have gotten all the data
from everybody who's ever done anything with Parler.
I imagine he would be worried about that.
Yeah, I bet.
There's credible information coming out today that then left-wing Black Hat cyber-hackers
have been able to hack through the authentication system that ran Parler and that they are right
now downloading enormous amounts of data from Parler users, perhaps including the driver's
licenses and metadata geolocation data that people had uploaded.
That's a breaking story right now.
I've been getting that from multiple sources.
It's my understanding reading up on this that this is not accurate at all.
This is an exaggeration of what happened.
And it's just what people had posted on Parler, people were able to archive.
Not that you had access to all the people's driver's licenses and shit, but I did try
to sign up for a Parler account because I wanted to follow people like Alex and it had
those kind of requirements.
I'm like, fuck no.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Absolutely not.
Good God, no.
Why, why would you, if you're a Nazi, why would you give somebody your driver's license?
Right.
That's insane.
Yeah.
And it's like the same people who are all up in arms about like gun registration.
Insane.
Yeah, I also had a picture of my driver's license to get a place where I can tweet violently.
Just insane.
Yeah.
And so like I understand why there would be fear and concern about that, but my understanding
at the point of when we were recording this episode is that that is a deep embellishment.
And I think that the reason that that embellishment works really well for someone like Mike is
that it allows them to talk about this kind of stuff.
They are going to go door to door.
There are going to be death squads under a Biden-Harris administration.
Cool.
And they're going to try to literally carry out a genocide against conservatives across
America.
So because they took all the information from Parler, they got all the addresses of everybody,
now Biden's going to take Antifa and they're going to go door to door death squatting.
Okay.
Dan, I have a question for you.
Yeah.
All right.
It's bad.
What happened on the 6th?
Right?
Yes.
According to Alex and this, because it's Antifa provocateurs.
Well, everything until that point was good though.
Right.
Now, if you don't want that to happen.
Yeah.
Right.
I would say you would not use inflammatory language towards your political opponents.
But if you did want that to happen again, you might, you would say that your political
opponents were planning on murdering you and that, uh, you know, I'm not saying that he's,
he's immediate.
I didn't say that.
He just said, Hey, we should go storm the Capitol building again.
But if I was somebody who believed things like say that Biden and Kamala Harris will
be sending death squads to my house door to door, I might think maybe what I need to do
is get a bunch of friends together and go storm the fucking Capitol building.
Yeah.
You've arrived at the thesis of my, uh, uh, neighbors.
It's only five, but neighbors, I'm just a little tense, Dan.
Right.
I understand.
And it's, it's weird because like you could hear a lot of the stuff that they're talking
about and be like, do you not recognize what, like what world we're living in now?
Cause like, listen to this, this could have been on his show in like 2010.
Yeah, absolutely.
And I've even, I've got a contact, a very reputable, a former military contact on the
ground, uh, in Maryland today texted me and said that they are setting up the FEMA operation
there in, in Maryland, a specific County, I don't want to name setting up tents and
emergency equipment.
I've had army special operations current call and confirm they are preparing for gun confiscation.
They're preparing FEMA camps right now.
Yep.
They are setting it all up.
This is all in place.
We're back.
We're back to this.
What's happening again?
They, we've talked a bunch over the years about taking them off the air and whether
or not yada, yada, yada, this needs to be taken off the air immediately.
Yeah.
It's outrageous.
Immediately.
It's, it's, uh, it's outrageous because it is the exact kind of behavior that would incite
people towards the sort of behavior that we saw last week off the air now immediately.
And it's so intentional, like, yeah, absolutely.
It's absolutely intentional.
You are very clearly setting the stage for another of the same thing that you're pretending
you didn't fucking want in the first place.
Yeah.
And it needs to be off the air immediately.
Well, I mean, let's go, let's go back to the terrorist edging analogy.
Totally.
You know, it's not, it's, it doesn't work if you let everything go back to normal.
You've got to turn the temperature back up pretty quickly.
And that's what we're seeing here.
We're seeing the exact same things that Alex always does.
Uh, just as if, as if that event didn't happen because to Alex, it didn't, it was
Antifa, it was all fake, it wasn't the natural, it wasn't the natural result of this kind
of rhetoric where they're going to put us in camps and go door to door and kill our
families.
I'm a good person.
I absolutely am not at least partially responsible for the deaths of multiple people.
That's definitely not Alex Jones's fault because Q and Antifa working together at the behest
of the deep state.
Uh, yeah, he's, he's absolutely directly, uh, partially responsible for the deaths of
all of those people.
No, no, no.
Listen, they're very, they're very clear about this.
They don't want any violence.
Should be arrested.
One hundred percent should be arrested and charged with conspiracy.
They don't want any violence.
I just want to reiterate to everybody here, you know, never initiate violence.
We always have the right to self-defense.
If commanders engage in violence against the American people, they're a general, a general
is more in command than the private that pulls the trigger.
They must be held accountable.
Well, I hope that Trump will announce shortly, although I doubt it, but I hope that Trump
would say we are in a state of war.
We are now enemy occupied territory and that Trump would invoke every, every American citizen
to defend the Republic.
I hope that's what he says, but I don't think he will.
I mean, let's be clear.
I'm saying if they start arresting and gun confiscating and killing Patriots, the generals
that are running this are, are, they started the war.
I'm all about defensive defense.
I'm not about offense, but Americans need to know that, uh, you know, these guys are
already violent, the Nuremberg cove, the Geneva convention, but the forced inoculations are
trying to push.
They've already put us under COVID martial law and it's clear they're going to make their
move.
Mike, I'm not about, I'm not about offense, but all defenses actually are all offenses
really actually defense.
Yeah.
No violence offensively, but all violence will be justified.
No.
Um, I am challenging the health ranger to a fight whomever wins gets to storm the Capitol
building.
No, I will not sponsor this fight.
I can't believe that this is, I know I was listening to this episode and I'm like, is
this like from a two years ago, do they recognize, like it doesn't feel like they're living in
a world where people just stormed the fucking Capitol building.
Nope, Nope, Nope.
I mean, you either have to completely lie to yourself or you're a complete psychopath.
I think it's the latter.
Yeah, it has to be.
And it's just like, that's just shit that you can't, we can't have this.
They're doing it again.
Yeah.
It's outrageous.
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah.
Mike down for this.
Cause you're going to feel like you're losing.
Mike down for the rest of the show.
Yes.
You're out.
Uh, you're going to feel like you're losing your mind a bunch more.
Yeah, it is really happening and the way you can survive it because perhaps about 10% of
the human population will make it through is you have to be entirely self-reliant off
the grid as much as possible.
You need to be able to grow your own food and to defend yourself and then, uh, survive
the onslaught of the mass illegal immigration that's coming, the troops, the Chinese troops
that are going to invade at some point, the, the, the government, uh, you know, jackbooted
thugs that Biden's going to unleash against them.
They won't invade.
They're already calling them helpers that they're visiting helpers.
That's right.
And, and by the way, they're going to, they're going to attack the churches, uh, just like
communist China.
They're going to try to burn down the churches and arrest the pastors who don't go along
with the globalist agenda.
So, uh, if your pastor is truly teaching the word of Christ, he or she will be under attack.
If they're, if they're telling you to surrender, then they, they will be allowed to exist.
So underground churches, underground farming, everybody needs to understand now we're losing
the country, we're going under longterm globalist occupation.
The Republicans didn't know what hit them.
Gorilla food farming is going to be a very big thing.
Smuggling seeds.
It'll be just like growing marijuana, growing tomatoes, growing pumpkins, growing squash,
growing.
Everything's going to be under the radar now, including money, by the way, because the dollar
will collapse.
Money will move to alternative systems, including crypto systems.
I'm sorry to tell you this, but this is the world government takeover.
We warned you about it's now here.
They're coming to kill you and your family.
Sorry, folks.
I didn't make it up.
I mean, they mean business.
Bill Gates wants to kill you.
We'll be right back.
Stay with us.
I don't know how you could behave in this way after, after an event like what we saw.
I just don't, I don't know how you can allow yourself to behave this way.
I am just reminding myself of something that the great thinker, uh, uh, Robert Barnes once
said, which is that, uh, they made these people feel like that election was the end of the
world.
Oh yeah.
The most important thing that ever happened.
And that's how they convinced them.
I remember when Q was talking about smuggling seeds.
I remember all of those things being very important just a short period of time ago.
Yeah.
It's almost jarring.
I don't, I mean, I, I just genuinely don't know how to like, I, I'm, I'm shaking, I'm
just shaking.
Like I'm in constant, you've motioned something needs to happen and I can't, I can't do anything
right now.
I'm listening to him speak and I'm like, how much is a flight to punch Robert Barnes in
the face?
Shouldn't you want to punch Mike Adams?
Sure.
Okay.
I put it, get them all in the same, put them in a line, put them in a line, I'll walk down
it.
Look, I know that you're frustrated with Mike, but I just, he just told me that only 10%
week, Oh, he's right, they should go underground.
All right.
We'll dig a giant hole beneath Texas.
We'll put them all in there and then just close it up and then they'll, the mole people
will eventually come to the surface and take us over.
That's too similar to FEMA camps just underground.
No, they'll take us over.
I understand.
The Morlocks will rise once more.
Look, you might be mad at Mike, but this is the last time maybe that he'll ever be able
to come on Info Wars.
Good.
Mike Adams, you're dead on.
We are not exaggerating one Centella.
It's frankly worse than you even said worse than I can describe.
And I just won't lie to the public.
This is the Megaton attack.
This is the biggest salt.
People better get ready.
Yeah, absolutely.
And if I could just say on a personal note, because for all we know, this may be the last
time I can ever even appear on your show, who knows?
But on a personal note, Alex, I'm one of the very few people in the world who, who I think
can have just an inkling of an understanding of the personal sacrifice that you have made
in order to continue to express your voice and, and to fight for humanity.
And Trump has made the, you know, the greatest sacrifice.
Deep breaths, Jerry.
I've made, you know, I've been vilified and I've, I've had a sacrifice, but not to the
extent that you have.
And I just want to thank you for holding the line and speaking for humanity.
Yeah.
He wants to thank Alex for speaking for, on behalf of humanity, at least my section of
it, which is my person, I'd say that Alex doesn't speak for me.
Yeah, this is, this is a mess.
Also, like you can't, you can't say stuff like we're not embellishing at all when you're
talking about death squads coming door to door to have a genocide on conservatives if
Biden gets into office.
You're playing with fire.
This is, this is not acceptable.
No, they're trying to do it, but bigger this time.
Yes.
They're trying to do the sixth, but bigger this time and the fact that we're allowing
this to happen as though that this is fine is insane because it's getting people killed.
And Jordan, they're laying down the preemptive justification by saying that like, oh, the
Q and Antifa, they're planning to do, that's why Alex is going to go to the inauguration
on the 20th.
Nope.
Like they're planning to do more and do the same thing.
It's just...
No, they're killing people.
As they speak words, people are dying due to them.
Well, look...
We have to deal with that.
The reality is that, you know, Trump might get a second term, maybe, tiny bit.
And if he does, maybe they'll get some of the things they wanted.
If we survive this, then we are the real media for America.
Because if Trump, if Trump gets a second term, if he pulls this out somehow that we don't
yet know, he, he would take down probably the...
Well, that's the thing.
He's been surrounded.
They've ignored him.
His spirit was good.
He did so much good.
And everybody got mad at him that he wasn't perfect.
Well, they're about to find out with Biden what Trump was holding back.
Well, yeah.
And also, I mean, I've got very good, incredible intelligence that Trump has been threatened
with detonations of dirty bombs and nukes and all kinds of things.
And you know, Trump doesn't want to see America turned into a radioactive wasteland.
Oh, he looks so strong at Wednesday's speech.
So defiant.
I was there like 20 feet from him.
They don't like me.
I'm so strong.
And I was like, my God, this is...
He looked like a superhero up there.
I'm serious.
Superhero who whines a lot about evil.
This is great.
Mike's like, yeah, if Trump somehow magically manages to get a second term, he'll finally
do the things we want him to do.
And then Alex is like, yeah, you know, the only reason he's disappointed, disappointing
is because he had, he was under threat.
Mike's like, yeah, they were going to nuke cities.
Get the fuck out of here.
Grow up.
Man, if Trump holds public office again, I'm storming the Capitol building by myself.
That's what I'm doing.
I don't want anybody else there.
It's just me against the government.
Just banging your head against the wall.
That's all I'm doing.
I don't care.
So Trump needs to give an emergency broadcast, according to Alex.
Sure.
And then we get into some secession talk.
I think that they want to succeed.
Great.
Good.
There's an oval office, not a farewell address, but an emergency address saying Biden's a
Chinese agent.
Here's the evidence.
He's going to cut our power off.
This is a foreign takeover.
You've got, the governors must mobilize.
You must have a constitutional convention, whatever you got to have.
We just have to America's under attack.
He must raise the alarm.
He must just tell it like it is exactly right.
And if for whatever reason he is unable to do that, then the American people need to
make it known to Biden and Harris and Pelosi and others that we, the people do not consent
to your tyranny, to your rigged elections, to your, your fraud, your false flag operations.
We do not consent.
In fact, we withdraw our consent from you and we, the people will declare a new independence.
I believe all across this country, we will set up a new government, maybe starting by
storming the Capitol building.
Yeah.
I'm going to have to go with this.
This is fucked.
I know it's, it's, this is fucked.
Yeah.
I mean, like we, the thing that's really difficult about this is that like, we've heard talk
like this on info Wars a bunch over the years, but never.
In the aftermath of something like what happened last week.
Yeah.
Like that should be a wake up call for people, particularly people like Alex, that, Hey shit
can happen.
Yeah.
And you need to be careful.
You can't talk like this.
You can't, you can't say that Trump needs to get into like an emergency broadcast where
he calls Biden, a terrorist, a Chinese agent.
And if not, then we need to send a message that we're not going to consent to be governed
anymore.
Yeah.
I mean, I can't think of any way to send a message better than storming the Capitol building.
But I guess that wasn't good enough is what Mike Adams is saying.
Right.
Mike.
So there we go.
Mike is a real fucked up dude and Alex is really fucked up too.
Yeah.
But again, he just wants, I mean, largely it's about selling food.
Sure.
If you're going to buy your storeable food, I'm not going to lie to you.
I've already started lying and put it and put the trailer up as we speak because I had
a feeling Trump was going to have it stolen from him.
I'm already moving outside of Austin and already dug a well and the solar panels and all of
it going in.
What's your address?
I mean, this place is all going to be like when Christ pointed and said in 70 years,
none of this, there won't be one stone on the other tie to sacked at 70 years later.
I mean, I'm just telling you now, this is going to be here anymore.
All the cities will be gone.
So buy your storeable foods.
Um, yeah, Alex keeps having very different stories about whether or not he has this bunker
set up.
Yeah.
I don't care.
Um, anyway, we get into more secession talk when we come back from break and uh, Mike,
what he wants to do is he wants Texas, right?
Cause they're cool.
Sure.
He wants them to force social media companies to have like a million dollar fine every time
they censor somebody to put them out of business.
And also he wants Texas to make their own money.
Uh, Texas could also pass a new legislation or even via a governor executive order to
say that any instance of censorship by big tech against the citizen of Texas will result
in a $1 million fine against big tech.
And then Texas could use that, uh, well, it would very quickly be at least a trillion
dollars in fines.
Uh, Texas could to defy, uh, the rigged election, Texas could launch its own currency.
And remember, Texas has its own, its own gold, uh, repository that it constructed a few years
ago.
Texas could launch its own currency so that people, and this could happen in any other
state.
I'm just using Texas as an example so that the people could conduct e-commerce and transactions
in an honest money system owned by the people rather than the fake Fiat currency that Biden
will use to hand out more bribes and kickbacks to governors like Cuomo and Newsome and so
on.
It's a great idea.
Let's have States make their own money.
Man, have we ever had a situation in American history where different communities printed
their own money?
It gets very confusing pretty fast.
Did it work last time?
It didn't.
Oh shit.
I think we just didn't try it hard enough.
I think that that's what they think about the Confederacy, because it really sounds
like they just want another Confederacy.
Yeah, yeah.
As you know, Mike, even foreign governments and the IMF World Bank say only Texas could
lead a successful breakaway because of its energy, its oil, its infrastructure, and then
a large constellation of States from Arizona to the West or New Mexico to Colorado to Oklahoma,
Louisiana, Mississippi, Tennessee, Florida.
It would just be instant.
Texas could reconstitute the Republic.
Well, absolutely.
There's a mechanism for doing that.
Texas could elect a new president of the new United States and bring together Louisiana,
Oklahoma, Kansas, and other States that want to participate.
And then Texas could order its citizens to stop paying federal income taxes to Washington.
And by the way, this was done before.
We can do it right now.
So yeah, this doesn't sound like a good plan.
So Dan, so if I understand correctly, I'd love to hear your breakdown.
I mean, I don't want to hear you break down.
I'd like you to break that down.
No, no, no.
I'll break down often.
I'm already watching you break down.
I'll break down later.
So Texas is going to declare a new president.
Yep.
And then, so the United States government is going to watch Texas declare itself a foreign
power.
Yes.
All right.
And then they're going to be like, well, of course you can have Louisiana and Florida
naturally because, you know, they would...
Colorado would be thrilled to join up.
Right, right, right, right.
And then they're going to get territory and money from a...
Oh, I mean, I imagine trade relations would be really wonderful.
Have they ever met the United States?
I feel like there's some issues that they might not be considering.
Well, I mean, there's that.
There's that.
And I think you make a great point that I also think that there's just a logistical
issues that they might not be considering.
Like what?
Trade.
Like trade?
No, no, no, no.
They're going to be able to sell their oil to foreign powers immediately.
There's no way that they couldn't just immediately start exporting oil.
You know, there's no kind of United States that would be like, hey, that's our money.
So we'll block you from selling this oil because it's ours.
Yeah.
There's some problems with this.
That sounds right.
But you know what?
They've got the biggest issue taken care of already.
Sure.
And that is who should be the new president.
Oh, good.
But it's going to be states like Texas and like, you know, Idaho and Wyoming and so on
that are going to really lead, I think, the the new society out of the collapse of the
old corrupt America swamp, the the old empire that's just being looted in its final hour
by Democrats.
And maybe you're right.
You know, maybe Trump doesn't want to be at the helm when that happens.
Trump would rather lead the new America out of darkness with a whole new honest money
system, for example, and new laws written for the people, by the people, rather than
for the corrupt criminals that are in the Senate and the GOP.
And by the way, I'm now part of the never GOP movement.
I will not vote for any member of the GOP ever again unless their name is bullshit.
So that's my statement.
Only Trump.
Bullshit.
All right.
Yeah.
This is fucked up.
You know what?
I was listening to this and I was like, is Mike Adams more fucked up than I remember
him being?
I guess.
Maybe it's just because I haven't heard him in a long time, but he seems really fucked
up.
I mean, he did say that there would only be lone survivors in the past.
Yeah, but that makes total sense.
That's true.
That's exaggerating a medical situation in order to help sell survival food and shit.
That makes total sense.
Now he's just calling for open secession at the end of the United States.
In the aftermath of people storming the Capitol building.
That's the part that doesn't make sense to me.
This doesn't even work for what Infowars is trying to do.
Here's my vibe from all of them right now, which is that they are a bunch of whiny babies
who want to take their ball and go home after they saw that they lost.
And unfortunately it's not their fucking ball.
You don't get to just go away.
And their home is shared.
Yeah, exactly.
We all fucking live there, so you have to deal with it.
I...
Yeah, it's maddening.
My politics are not divisive, Dan.
You're trying to murder me.
There's a difference.
So Mike leaves, and Alex gets to complaining about foreign leaders, but not the ones you
think.
This time, take shots at Canada.
Sure.
Trudeau, you're in the crosshairs.
Yeah, why not?
They said we want to end America as an idea.
We want our globalist system.
We want the Chinese system.
We want dictatorship.
So when they tell you they're liberal and they're good and, oh, Alex has hurt people's
feelings and needs to be banned, all the idiots rolling over to tyranny think they're part
of the power.
You're not.
You're called useful idiots in the words of VI Lenin.
So here's what Justin Trudeau had to say.
There's a level of admiration I actually have for China because their basic dictatorship
is allowing them to actually turn their economy around on a dime.
Let's hear that one more time.
Boy, that clip really cut off abruptly.
It's almost like there would probably be some sort of context to that.
That's weird.
Yeah, it really cut off quick.
Yeah, that was a sharp cut.
Alex has some commentary though.
Oh, okay.
And again, he's asked by a woman in the canned question, what is your favorite politician?
What's your favorite government?
Oh, it's communist China.
They were on a date.
Yeah, yeah.
So first I want to say that these comments were made by Trudeau back in 2013.
So it's a little old of a clip.
Second, although they're not great comments and they did cause quite a bit of embarrassment
for him, Trudeau didn't actually say that China was his favorite.
Here's his full answer.
Okay.
Quote, you know, there's a level of admiration I actually have for China because their basic
dictatorship is allowing them to actually turn their economy around on a dime and say,
we need to go green fastest.
We need to start investing in solar.
I mean, there is a flexibility that I know Stephen Harper must dream about having a dictatorship
that he can do everything he wanted that I find quite interesting.
But if I were to reach out and say which, which kind of administration I most admire,
I think there's something to be said right here in Canada for the way our territories
are run.
Nunavut, Northwestern territories and the Yukon are done without political parties around
consensus and are much more like a municipal government.
And I think there's a lot to be said for people pulling together to try to solve issues rather
than score points off each other.
And I think we need a little bit more of that, but Sun News can now report that I prefer
China.
So at the end of that quote, he literally said, people are going to do what Alex is
doing right now.
Cool.
Cool, cool, cool, cool.
The end of the quote is him making a joke about how right-wing media outlets would report
the story as he loves China.
Guess what?
Seven years later, Alex, fulfilling the prophecy.
Yep.
I don't know if anybody who studies government would disagree with the idea that a centralized
monarchical power structure allows for quicker reaction times.
Yeah, I mean, if you're saying it- You don't have to get a bunch of people together
and vote.
Yeah.
If you're saying it outside of it being a prescriptive thing, like we should have that
because- No, no, no.
If you're just studying it, then you'd be like, well, yeah, obviously, because that
guy just gets to say, do this instead of being like, well, we need to talk to our constituents
and we need to have a vote and we need to write a bill and do all that stuff.
Yeah.
Descriptively, it's pretty hard to argue with.
But yeah, if you listen to the rest of that quote, it's really clear the thing that he's
bringing up is that phenomenon, how they can make their economy much more eco-friendly
because of that basic dictatorship, as he calls it, but the government that he actually
says is what he admires is the territories in Canada.
It's a completely different message than what Alex wants to give across because he's a liar
and he might not even know.
Yeah.
I bet he doesn't even know what the rest of that quote is.
Doesn't care.
That's bullshit.
He just listened to the Sun News report that he liked China.
That's all you need.
Yeah.
So anyway, these people who like Q, they're fucking stupid because they think that they're
talking to military intelligence and that's what Alex keeps...
He keeps running into people at events and they're like...
Like Zack?
I've literally been at rallies and they always have this weird look like they're in a trance.
They walk over all...
It's always like a guy wearing a Q shirt and he goes, Alex, I used to like you, but now
I'm with Q. I know you're bad.
And then they'll always go, army intelligence, I'm with the intelligence.
You're like, well, really that's funny because the highest levels of army intelligence call
up and ask me what's coming next and so does the FBI, those that are good, and you think
there's like some magic mountain up there, the president calls us to see what we think.
So he's making fun of these people for thinking they're talking to military intelligence and
then he immediately starts talking about how he's the one who talks to military intelligence.
All I hear him say is just like, I know I'm lying.
You guys believe what you're saying.
I know I'm lying because I'm not stupid.
I can weaponize this stuff.
You guys are following.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't you think?
You're not making any money off of this bullshit.
You should be giving me money.
I hate them.
So he's just fed up with these Q folks, but it's really important to understand that the
reason that he's behaving in the way he is towards them and about this whole narrative
is throwing them under the bus because he needs somebody to be the people who had the
zip ties.
He needs somebody to be the people who are scary and he's taught his audience not really
to be afraid of seeing Jean wearing Antifa.
So I assume he's going to denounce the Oath Keepers, right?
No.
Oh.
I have arguments with family.
I have arguments with so many people where they believed all that delusional crap and
it really defeated us.
And then now I see how it's a robot army they control through 8chan who will do violence
and now they're planning to attack a bunch of the capitals during the 20th, which denies
us the ability to actually protest peacefully because they're going to have Qtards out there
with their zip ties and their guns, believing they're about to overthrow the globalists
and they're being secretly commanded by some magic group that is the globalist.
Q thinks it's good, but it's commanded by the enemy for sure.
And it's roped in so many people that are now delusional.
All I want, man, you know, I really figured things out in the last couple of days.
I kind of went next level and I already knew all of this, but now I'm totally in the dialectic.
I get the whole Machiavellian plan even better.
Stab yourself in the ears.
I'm sure they're operating according to it.
With chopsticks.
And God, is it diabolical.
Absolutely diabolical.
What?
Oh, man.
And people take kindness for weakness.
And I just can't believe it.
I've always been so loyal.
I'm such a loyal person.
The people that treat me good, I treat them good.
And I've just experienced so many people that don't treat me like that.
But I finally, through the years of working hard to found a crew that treats me loyally,
I treat them loyally as I can.
I appreciate them.
But I've gotten to a point at 47 years old that I can't take this loyalty anymore.
And rat bastardness.
You know, I was watching...
Next, we have Roger Stone.
They're only blind hands, you know.
I just go with my wife.
What are we doing?
I don't know.
I wouldn't expect that Alex would like, ah, I finally get it.
Now.
Yeah.
He's supposed to have known all of this.
It just makes me want to start barking.
Yeah.
No, totally.
I almost just broke down and just started going, ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff.
Yeah.
It's so nonsensical.
Those moments when he's just like, oh, I see everything in the dialectic.
I went next level recently.
It's just like, get a journal.
Yeah.
I mean, it does go a long way towards explaining how he tells himself he's not a serial killer.
You know.
No, no, no.
I just got it.
I've seen something new.
I'm not a serial killer.
It's a different thing.
Well, we know that he's taken responsibility for multiple killings.
Yeah.
In the past.
I don't know if he can talk himself out of that one.
I don't know.
Anyway, these Q people, they were at the Capitol and they trained themselves to think that
Trump was going to send the special forces in, right?
And so they saw Antifa and they thought that they were the special forces.
This is the story now.
It was the Q people under Antifa's control who went in there like a group of morons.
Antifa breaches it, they start it.
The Q people thought there's the special forces right on time.
They told us to invade at this time.
They would attack first.
And they thought Antifa was special forces for Trump breaking into the Capitol.
So they then flooded in behind waving in the masses.
But luckily by the blessing of God, 99% of the hundreds of thousands did not go in with
them.
But I saw that and it made me sick.
Yeah.
And this is, I guess, how the narrative is going to land is the Q people thought that
Antifa were special forces, but I thought that they were being directed by the deep
state also.
Like, what's going on here?
Yeah.
Yeah, Dan, what is going on here?
I don't know.
Bunch of nonsense.
It's everybody's fault but mine.
I'm blameless.
Now excuse me while me and my health ranger friend try and make this happen again.
Stir up a rebellion.
Hey.
So I told you there would be hypnosis involved and Alex does go to calls.
You did promise to be hypnosis, Dan.
He wanted to talk to people who were there and one guy believes that...
Give them your name and address, please.
You were there?
Well, maybe not inside, but at the rally.
And there's one guy who calls in who believes that there was a guy on a megaphone who is
basically hypnotizing the crowd.
Alex, do you remember the media tower right there up front and center in the back?
Yeah.
There was someone on that megaphone.
I know a little bit about neuro-linguistic programming, NLP.
Whoever was on that megaphone was literally, by the power of suggestion, hitting all those
trigger words, take it now, people.
It's now or never.
This is China.
This is our house.
Storm it.
Push forward.
Hold the line.
They were saying everything that would rile anyone...
And also read they said Alex Jones and Trump say so, did you hear that?
I did not say that, but I hear that, but I can tell you what I felt and the things that
I did hear.
So this guy is saying that someone was using neuro-linguistic programming to convince the
crowd to act in ways that it wouldn't have.
But I also think that all the things that he's saying, the person said, are exactly
what they would be saying in a bullhorn.
You guys want this.
You're just mad because it happened before you could get enough people together to succeed.
That's what's angering them.
And you're gonna be mad when people start to take this seriously.
Yeah.
You're gonna be real mad whenever you start to get it.
For a very long time, people have not taken the issue of right-wing media and how it feeds
into extremism.
They've not taken that seriously at all, which is, I mean, why we have any relevance.
Why there's any reason for a show like ours to exist is because no one takes it seriously.
Yeah, exactly.
And I think that there is an unfortunate, for them, trend, and that is that people may
take this seriously now, and that's threatening.
Yeah.
It'll be good, though.
Because imagine if somebody was like, I don't know, on every TV show just sitting there
being like, hey, hey, that's bullshit, next.
You know?
Just like, hey, strike that from the fucking show, next.
That's why I think I speculated about this back in the day, and I actually don't think
this would be a good idea, but if Alex is going to do his show, I have to be his co-host.
You have to.
Totally.
That's his version of net neutrality.
You need a fucking shot caller.
That's what you need.
And there's some other callers who talk about boring stuff, about being there at the rally.
I didn't find any of it too interesting, but there's one other caller that made me chuckle.
You know, you do have an alternative.
It's called magazines.
You need to start a magazine to where we can leave it at dentist's office, Walmart, call
it Lifestyle of the Free.
And that's-
You know, I tried a magazine, sir.
Lifestyle of the Free sounds great.
Do you understand that it had one one-millionth the response of a digital format?
Yeah, but the digital format is not doing anything either.
Look what it done.
The country's still going down.
I appreciate your call, sir.
I've got to hang up on this asshole.
Dan, here's my solution.
Yeah.
Print media!
This guy, I love that call because he's like, yeah, you know, we need magazines.
Look, I've done a magazine, cost a lot of money, didn't make anything off it.
No one gave a shit.
Do you know anything about the publishing business?
Yeah, yeah.
It's a loss.
It's bad.
I'm just going to throw money in a pit.
Yeah.
And hey, look, the digital stuff, lots more people see it.
And the caller's response to that is amazing.
Digital stuff's not doing anything either.
Yeah, which, fair point, fair point, sir.
Alex can't reply to that, so he hangs up.
Get rid of that guy.
You're fucking worthless.
That's what's happening.
Yeah.
So we come to the end of this and, you know, we needed to do Wednesday episode because
this is a pretty fucked up, but at the same time, it's like, you know, we, if we waited
until Friday, this would pile up and there wouldn't be, and who knows what's going to
happen tomorrow or, you know, this is, we're not a news show, but the news backs up fast
now.
We've already, we've already forgotten that Alex interviewed Mike Flynn.
Yeah.
Who gives a fuck about that?
Who gives a fuck about that shit?
Yeah.
So, um, anyway, we'll see what happens.
I'm sorry to do this to you.
Yeah.
You're worked up in a tizzy.
Yeah, I'm not, I'm not, you get to process all of this and then the show and you have
to edit it, you know, and that's, that's, but I, I'm just shaking with rage and then
I walk away into the night.
Some would argue that your job is easier in that sense.
Some would argue that.
I think you're describing me having to live with this stuff for a lot longer.
Exactly.
But you're better able to emotionally process it, Dan.
I'm a loose cannon.
Somebody should take my gun and badge away right now.
Well, good thing you have neither a gun nor a badge.
That's true.
Yeah.
That is true.
That is a bonus.
If you're not able to emotionally handle this much better, it's that I steal all the candy
that our listeners send us.
That's what gets you through.
Yeah, exactly.
If I got some of that candy, I wouldn't be shaking with rage right now, Dan.
Well, I need it all.
So unfortunately, no candy.
Well, you're the more valuable resource.
Fine.
So we'll be back on Friday, Jordan, but until then we have a website.
We do.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yep.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledge underscore fight and that go to bed Jordan.
Yes.
We're on Facebook.
We are on Facebook.
If you could please find a local charity or a bail fund in your area to help out people
who are still doing God's work.
Yep.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm the juiciest ice cube.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.