N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys.
I love you.
Challenge Fight, Dan and Jordan, Knowledgefight.
Need money, Andy and Kansys, Andy and Kansys.
Stop it, Andy and Kansys, It's time to pray.
Andy and Kansys you're on the air, thanks for holding me.
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan.
I love your world.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes that like to sit around, drink novelty beverages, and talk a little
bit about Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are, Dan.
Jordan.
Dan!
Quick question for you.
Yes, sir.
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today is I'm talking into a new microphone.
Oh, that's right.
We are talking to a new microphone.
They look the same.
I completely forgot.
Exactly the same.
They're the same.
Still cheap as a pad microphone.
Yep.
But they're new.
I noticed some poppling and crackling in a couple of our recent episodes.
I decided it was time to get at least new cords, and man, this new windscreen feels
good on my face.
It does.
It's much smoother.
It doesn't have years of other people's faces on it.
Yeah, pre-COVID.
Pre-COVID, other people's faces.
You're the only one who's touched it since then.
For four years, we're the only ones who've touched it, yes.
Yeah, it's nice though.
I bought a desk mic stand as well, but it does not attach to the mic holder, so I still
have some work to do on that, but yeah, it's my weekend warrior type project for today.
I love it.
How about you?
Similar weekend warrior type project, Dan, I have for probably 13 years lived in apartments,
in apartment buildings with people around me.
And so when I left for apartment living, I also left my drum set behind.
I miss it.
Your guy likes to throw some sticks around.
I played drums since I was like eight years old, and then I had to stop at 19 for the
aforementioned reasons.
And it has been difficult, and finally I realized that you can get an electric drum kit for
like 300 bucks.
So I got one.
Wow.
And it's fantastic.
Wow, how about that?
It's very cheap.
It's garbage.
I'm going to break it in a week.
Yeah.
It's going to be like when I played rock band.
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly.
Just destroying those pads.
Yeah.
I'm going to die to death.
But it is so good to get back to drums.
Somehow it's still going to be too loud for your partner.
Totally.
She's still going to be like, keep it down.
Well, I've also, here's the weekend warrior, the last time that I tried having a conversation
while she was at work, our rooms share a wall.
Right, right.
And I am me.
Loud.
And I have a tendency to toss language about in jest.
Not to fit for the classroom.
No.
Her high school students have heard me speak, so I bought some soundproofing shit, so my
entire room is going to be turned into a studio, essentially.
Good luck with that.
Soundproofing is kind of tough unless you can get inside the walls.
Yeah, I'm working on it.
Well, that's fun.
I hope you have some nice fun Dave Grohl-esque drumming adventures in your future.
Love it.
Hey, who hasn't played along to Queens of the Stone Age songs for the dead?
I have, only on rock band.
Yeah.
But see what I'm saying?
You're not even a drummer and you've played along with it.
You've never played Everlong on rock band.
Well, that one's fairly easy.
Not on expert.
Yeah, you don't know your sixteenth notes, brah?
No, I don't.
It's very fast.
My foot gets tired.
I miss rock band.
You let the sticks do the work.
That's what a lot of people don't know about drums.
You think you gotta hit it with your arm.
You just move your wrist up a little bit.
You say that and it's like a cryptic mystery or something.
No, it's not a mystery.
You let the sticks do the work.
You let the sticks do the work, Dan.
I don't know.
I loved rock band.
I spent hours, hours trying to 100% helter-skelter on expert.
I don't think I ever succeeded.
You never succeeded.
I think I tried it hundreds and hundreds of times because you get an achievement in Beatles
rock band if you're 100% on expert.
I just couldn't get it.
Couldn't get it.
Couldn't do it, huh?
Ringo, gotcha.
Yep.
The classic drummer that throws people on.
Look.
I'm sorry.
A lot of the other songs are pretty easy, but helter-skelter is a little complex.
Sure, sure.
I'm also not very good at rhythm based stuff.
No, that's fine.
I'm sorry if I... I don't mean to make fun of you.
I'm just a bully.
I'm a bad person.
That's all right.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Okay.
So, Jordan, today we got an interesting thing on our plates in front of us and that is that
we don't really have an episode.
That is an interesting thing on our plates.
Yeah.
So, here's what happened.
What's that?
I did not want to do another episode for today about Alex.
I wanted to push that to Wednesday because I needed personally a break from him.
I was tired of his bullshit.
Last week was emotionally exhausting.
Yeah.
Starting on the preparation for Friday's episode on the 8th straight through to present, it's
been a lot.
It's been a lot of stuff that I grow weary of and then at the same time the payoff of
the interview with Steve Pechenik on our last episode was almost two.
It was season ending.
Yeah.
It felt like it was a fucking season finale.
We got CVPs giving us the fucking cliffhanger.
And telling Alex to his face.
When is he going to come back?
Yeah.
I have been lying to you for 20 years.
I decided to anoint you as the vehicle by which I would set off a military coup.
Wait.
Hold on.
Hold on, doc.
I have been the puppet master.
Yeah.
You think you're in control.
No, sir.
Hi.
Yeah.
There's something about that that was so satisfying and narratively interesting to
me that I found myself having a really tough time going back to Alex.
Yeah.
And I know it'll be temporary.
I'll be able to get back on the horse soon, but I sat down to try and listen to other
episodes and I just like, I can't do this.
Yeah.
And so what I wanted to do, naturally in times like this in the past, what we've done is
we've gone to various other online space weirdos.
Sure.
Yeah.
If we could.
And so yeah, I checked in on Carrie Cassidy over at Project Camelot and she had a video
the day after the storming of the Capitol.
She's on some Q bullshit for 100.
You bet.
Yeah.
100% zero, zero possibility that that wasn't going to happen.
No.
I got really bored listening to that too because aliens weren't in play.
Yeah.
Why would it, what did you say?
Get the fuck out of Q and get back into space, lady.
I did find out from listening to this, but it wasn't worth getting too deep into.
There's apparently an Archon alien, a singular one.
Okay.
Just one.
That runs the CIA.
Okay.
It did not know that.
All right.
Okay.
I didn't learn that.
And it used to be this guy Archon, right?
Right.
But I think Carrie has some intelligence that he might have died and now there's a female
Archon that's in charge of the CIA.
All right.
Unclear.
Prove that he's dead and not a shape shifter.
Can't do it.
Yeah.
Carrie, bring it to me.
So then I was like, well, I bet Jim Baker's disappointed and I still don't like talking
about Jim Baker.
I don't know why.
I just don't, it still makes me a little bit uncomfortable.
Yeah.
I think that I'm not going to be able to go back to that well ever.
Eh, fuck Jim Baker.
I just, I don't, what is he going to say?
God does shit.
Well, we moved on.
Talk about how great his big ass bucket of oatmeal is.
You and I have both read the Bible and eaten survival food.
We can just move on.
Yeah.
So then of course I, I was, I was kind of like in a bind.
I was like, I don't know what I'm going to do.
Got to get something together.
And then I remembered that when I was looking at pictures of the Capitol on the sixth, yeah,
I saw somebody wearing a pass the salt shirt, which of course is the name of Dave Dobenmeyer,
coach Dave.
It's the name of his radio ministry, his YouTube broadcast ministry.
Pass the salt.
I saw that.
I was like, whoa, there's Dave Dobenmeyer shirts at the protest at the people storming
there at the Capitol.
Yeah.
Was he there?
That would be amazing.
Who else is wearing a Dave Dobenmeyer shirt?
Well, it wasn't him.
I would have recognized him in the picture.
Okay.
But I was like, coach Dave had to have been there, right?
And so I went and I checked.
Sure.
Dave Dobenmeyer was at the Capitol.
He could not possibly have been there.
Really?
He was at the Capitol.
Dave Dobenmeyer decided to go storm the Capitol.
Coach Dave.
Son of a bitch.
Yeah.
He led the football team in through.
I can't come up with a metaphor.
Hey guys, win one for the Gipper.
So today I wanted to take a little bit of a look at that, but it's not really much of
an episode.
I wasted a lot of time watching these streams for what will ultimately be kind of, I don't
know, a little bit deflating.
It's not going to be, look, if you like our show, tune back in on Wednesday.
We will have a full episode if you're expecting that.
But we're going to listen to a little bit of Dave Dobenmeyer.
What if an episode of like Battlestar Galactica was like, hey guys, this is a bottle episode.
We couldn't afford to really do much here.
Listen, if you want to see some space shit, come back next week.
So one of the things that I thought was really funny is on the sixth, Dave is, uh, coach
is a recording, uh, and doing a live stream from the Metro, from the train in DC.
So it's a little bit iffy, the sound is not great.
The connection is eh, but one of the things that he does that I think is really maybe
unfortunate in hindsight is he literally doxes every single person who's on that train with
him going to DC.
Like if any of them went in the Capitol, his broadcast could be identifying information.
It will, it's look, it's obvious.
This was always going to be the case that this would happen, but the fact that the people
most afraid of Bill Gates tracking them all the time have docked themselves so completely.
It's just, it's never not going to be obvious.
He's just going around like, Oh, this is Greg from Idaho.
Totally.
Yeah.
Don't do this.
Oh man.
I love it.
Yup.
So, uh, Dave gets to, gets to talking about how many people they're going to be there.
I do like how it seems the only people who are uninterested in doxing each other are
Antifa.
They're the only people who are like, Hey, if you're going to video people, don't put
their face in it or say their real names.
Everybody else is like, I'd love to be on TV.
Yeah.
Here's my social security number.
Exactly.
Are you from Nigeria?
I met a guy once.
So he gets to talking about how there's going to be so many people there.
And this is, this is big.
This is not just a protest from what I, what I saw Dale, 4 million, they said there's possibly
4 million people that are going to be here in downtown Washington, DC, very, very strong,
powerful message.
And most of the people have not come just to chant for more years.
No, I don't think so, coach.
I think it's, it's far beyond that once again, Donald Trump is not going to call.
He called for this rally.
He has a platform at nine this morning.
I believe he is going to talk.
He's not, it's not a pep rally.
I do not believe this is game on.
Remember we talked about, you know, we always have 11 men on offense and 11 men on defense
in the field.
This is like, this is like the, the coach turning to the stadium and saying, get on
the field.
Now's the time I think I might be feeling inspired to write a book, your honor exhibit
eight.
I feel like there'll be, there's a great book to be written about like all of the right
wing media stuff prior to the Capitol storming called this looks bad in hindsight.
Yeah, totally, totally.
But ultimately the thing that's really interesting about it is it's not really that different
than the way they talk normally.
You know, it's, it's pretty much hubris, a Nazi tale.
So there's a guy on the bus there and Dave goes around and he, he, he checks in on the
temperature of the people in the crowd.
Sure.
Hey, how are you doing?
Yeah.
And this guy says it's now or never.
Well, I'll tell you what, it's time.
We stand up.
This is it for our country.
I'd say either now or never.
I've enjoyed the blessings of the United States of America for 74 years.
And I, I just don't want to see it go basically to the communists.
That's what we're looking at.
We've got to hand it off to our children.
It's our children, grandchildren.
That's it.
Yeah, man.
The commies, they're coming and it's now or never, you got to stand up and fight these
commies or else your grandkids aren't going to have a capitalist country to live in and
have a great time with.
I like, I like the real low tier of these guys because I recognize how they talk and
that is exactly like comedy producers who have never put on a good show.
Hmm.
I think we're going to have about 4 million people here tonight.
Oh yes.
Yeah.
That is, that is awesome.
I think we're going to have so many people here tonight.
I'm telling you, I've heard, I got so many Facebook messages.
People are committed to showing up.
Yeah.
You should have been here last week.
Oh, well actually it was going to be 4 million, but it rained.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Oh, I forgot that there was a Bears game today.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
Oh no.
It's Sunday.
There's always a good one.
Yes, exactly.
Your show is weekly on Sundays.
You got to know there's football.
Got to know there's football, man.
Um, so yeah, they are a little bit, uh, there's a little bit of pride or a little bit of expectation
and excitement.
It's definitely palpable.
You can tell like they feel like they're getting ready to go do something more than chant for
more years.
Yes.
Yeah.
For sure.
The electricity was clearly in the air.
Yeah.
And, and, and, and interestingly, I mean, I think that, um, the people who are there
have a lot more to say than just that Biden stole the election.
Um, there's certainly some ideas that are being trafficked on this bus that are interesting.
Great ideas.
Any highfalutin ideas?
Clyde's going to tell us how to become a citizen of our local state's revenue.
Actually what you're doing is you're moving from the admiralty and a jurisdiction of the
sea to the jurisdiction of the land and the soil.
And it's just very simple.
You just remove yourself.
You go through the process of the paperwork to remove yourself as a U S citizen and become
a citizen of the state you were born in.
Sure.
And join the assembly of states in your state.
That sounds right.
And then you become a state national or a state citizen.
Oh, of course.
There are rumors that Trump is a state national and has already gone through this and understands
all of this.
And what we have to do, we've talked about succeeding.
We don't need to succeed our states.
We need to succeed ourselves one at a time and move over to the land jurisdiction.
And what we're doing right now is thanks to judge Anna von Reitz.
She's done all the paperwork so that we're now right now are repopulating the original
constitution of 1787.
So I think Anna von Reitz, if I recall correctly, is somebody that I've heard Carrie Cassidy
bring up quite a bit.
So there's a nice little overlap.
Sure.
Of that.
Yeah.
I wrote in a scream.
That's why we're in the room, can't tell those are big old letters.
Those are big old letters.
What do we got there?
He just basically said, all right, that the president that they love most is not an American
citizen.
Yeah, that is a problem with his theory.
Yeah.
But that's because sovereign citizens are higher up on the ladder.
So you're going to come at me with Obama wasn't born here and then you're going to tell me
that your president isn't even American?
Well.
Get the fuck out of here.
Paper American.
What is that even?
Constitution of 1870.
Sure.
That's all just QAnon sovereign citizen shit.
It's a bummer.
It's a real bummer.
It's amazing to me how important paperwork is to these people and how unimportant reading
is.
Yeah.
It's fun too because you know, you got Dave here, coach Dave on the bus and he's having
this guy explain how you become a citizen of the land.
Yeah.
You got to take your away from the admiralty.
And he's not like, I don't know about that, man.
He's like, oh great, I can't wait to have you on the show again and talk more about
this.
Yeah.
What?
So good.
But look, this guy knows what he's talking about.
I think he went to law school.
So our whole movement, I believe, is going to be about teaching people how to get out
of the jurisdiction of the admiralty law and the law of the sea and the Vatican, which
is the law of the air.
The law comes from L-A-W, land, air, water.
That's where the word law comes from.
The three jurisdictions.
The Pope figured this out in 1300.
That's who we're living under right now.
The Vatican.
The same pope?
All of this is under that.
The only way to get out of it is to go and land in soil and get back under the constitution
of 1787.
Sure.
Land, air, water.
That's what law means.
Are we doing this?
Are we doing this, Dan?
We're not.
The Vatican is the law of the air.
Right.
And then I think the British empire is the law of the sea.
Sure.
The maritime law is under the British common admiralty law.
And then I guess the land is just everybody.
The land is freedom.
The land is just the constitution of the United States.
Freedom.
Yeah.
But not the United States, individual states.
Right.
Because we're also the articles of people?
Does this apply to people in other countries?
Like the law of the ground?
The Vatican owns their air, so they don't have any choice.
See, the pope figured this out in 1300.
Figured what out?
That law means land, air, and water.
In what language?
It's not spelled that way.
Oh man.
All right.
Earth, fire, water, air, long ago.
My father.
Was the avatar.
Talk about elements.
Oh man.
J.K. Simmons.
Fantastic!
Elements equal jurisdictions.
You ever fuck with Avatar, Dan?
No.
Not the Cameron bullshit.
I'm talking about young boy with air powers.
I watched the James Cameron movie because I was brought along to it by friends who insisted
I go see it.
That was a terrible idea.
No, wait.
That's Serenity.
Serenity's great.
But I also saw Avatar because it was too big to not see.
Well.
You know, it was one of those things that like, you gotta-
You didn't see the last, the Rise of Skywalker.
I'm an adult.
It's a joke.
There was a time when that came out, I was of the age where it's like, yeah, you gotta
see this.
Well, sure.
People are going to be talking about it.
Yes.
And I don't care about that now.
No.
So, I think I did see the last Skywalker.
You did not.
I think I did.
When?
Tell me when.
When did you get it on DVD, Dan?
Yeah.
It's under the red box.
No, I think I did see it though.
We'll deal with this later.
Okay.
Anyway, there's three jurisdictions.
Sure, sure.
Law.
Okay.
We're all under, wait, he's saying that we're under maritime law, but apparently the Vatican,
that's air law.
Yeah, I would like to- That's avian law.
Before we go any further, in any conversation with this guy, I want to know exactly the
laws of air.
Mm-hmm.
I want to know what air law is that the pope has control over.
Yeah.
If I were to go any further in this conversation with this guy, which I wouldn't, here's how
I would go.
What's over there?
And I just walk.
Smoke bomb.
I had a friend who really perfected that move, like pretending that he saw something somewhere
else- Oh, really?
And just would walk off.
I really admired the hell out of his ability to get away from things.
You know, I've done that many times.
You know you get into those party conversations where it's four people and the three of them
start having a conversation and you're like, I want to jump in, but it's just not going
to happen.
You look over and you're like, oh my God.
And then you just walk away.
You saw a friend.
Yeah.
I think the key to pulling that off perfectly is that you have to end up somewhere that's
not in direct eye shot of the people you just left.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because otherwise you're just going to be milling around over there.
Yeah.
Anyway, Dave has heard that there's a lot to be worried about.
There's a lot of threats- Sure.
On the ground.
There's like Antifa and what have you.
Yeah.
All right.
He's not worried about any of that shit.
I'm not worried that they may have bricks down there that they're going to throw at
us.
I'm not worried that they're going to shoot pepper spray at us.
I'm not worried that the governor is going to call in this person and the mayor is going
to call in this.
I'm not worried about any of that stuff.
Huh?
We're at war.
We're going to war.
We're prepared for war, spiritual war.
But if the physical war breaks out, there's going to be 4 million of us.
They better have a bunch.
They better have a bunch of people because this is a boiling-
Well, here's a true work of authority.
The mayor of D.C. has no military authority, not over the National Guard or anything.
All she has is D.C. police and guess what, D.C. police will step, they will step aside.
There's too many of them.
So this doesn't look good in hindsight.
Well, well, well, well.
These sort of conversations certainly seem to be pre-, pre-, pre-, what would you call
that?
What's the right word I'm looking for?
Uh, premeditated?
Is that a way to go?
I mean, it's very much like, oh, you know, like, if you accept the idea that like, oh,
they kind of are planning on fucking storming the Capitol, you'd kind of be like, oh yeah,
this is the kind of conversation you'd expect to hear before that.
Before you storm the Capitol.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, look, hey, we don't want any trouble, but if there's trouble, there's four million
of us and the cops are on our side, so what the fuck?
If the Capitol was the Constitution, these assholes are the preamble.
Yeah, preamble was probably one of the words I was trying to look for, and I just couldn't
figure out a way to make it work grammatically.
So there's, there's these Capitol police, sure, and there's not enough of them, man.
There's just not enough.
There's not enough to stop Dave.
Hey Dale, how many policemen would you say there are in, in, uh, DC?
I'm just going to throw out another thousand.
Yeah.
You know, listen, Jefferson parish, Jefferson parish, we have, we have 1500 officers that
not just officers, people who work in the desk and detectives and everything.
And that's for a population of a half a million people.
I don't necessarily know if they can have a thousand in DC.
Here's my point.
Do they have enough to push back?
What if, uh, 500,000 people said they'd had enough of what if just, what if just 10%,
what if 200,000 people said they had enough and decided they were going to storm the Capitol?
I don't know if they're going to, I don't know if they're going to, what, what if that
were to happen, folks?
We don't have any idea what might break loose here.
Now we, none of us want violence.
None of us are advocating violence, but the truth of the matter is there's violence all
around it.
The Bible says that the kingdom of God suffers violence in the days of John the Baptist until
now, the kingdom of God has suffered violence and violent men have taken up by force.
See, listen, it's not the violence, it's the force.
They're forcing us to take vaccinations.
They're forcing us to close our shops.
They're forcing us to not travel.
They're forcing us to not go visit our parents in nursing homes.
They're forced.
You understand?
Do you understand this?
It's the same argumentation style that you hear from folks.
Like we don't want trouble.
We don't want any kind of violence, but all violence that could be seen as offensive is
secretly defensive because they want to give me a vaccine.
It's not great to hear this from someone who's presumably a religious leader.
I would argue that spreading a disease is violence, Dan.
Offensive violence.
There's an interesting argument that you could make with that.
And it seems like they are doing it.
I would actually maybe, yeah, you'd want to probably have some qualification for like
negligence.
Sure.
Or something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Unless you're spitting on people.
And then it's...
Well, there's that.
Then you're out of line.
Eh, I don't know.
If you're aware that wearing a mask can save somebody else's life, and you're like, I'm
never wearing a mask, you have now committed violence.
Yes, but how do you prove that the person actually believes...
Even under your own libertarian nonsense, no, yeah, fuck off.
But you would have to then prove that the person is aware that the masks help.
They believe that, and are choosing to not do it.
Because the denial could be strong.
Sure, sure.
I don't know if I care about denial.
You may not.
The court might, though.
The court might, but it's kind of like a math problem.
Like I don't care if you think that math doesn't work.
It still does.
So you have to live by math.
Right.
Fair enough.
So they spend some more time on this bus, the reception gets bad, and then it goes to
the guy in the studio, and when I say studio, I mean his office, and he's another preacher,
and he just has some people pray and stuff, and I don't care.
Then later, they arrive at the Capitol.
There's at least one picture I saw that was of someone in a Pass the Salt shirt, so they
were around.
All right.
And the D-heads is what I'm calling somebody who wears a Pass the Salt shirt.
Hey, would you pass the salt?
So we get to the next day now, the 7th, and Dave comes on his show, and there's a little
bit of reflection going on.
We are over the target, and as Alex Jones said about 25 years ago, it's an info war.
It's an information war, and boys and girls, we are a dead center target in this information
war.
I'm not trying to... I'm just a fly on the butt of an elephant.
I understand that, but I'm going to tell you something.
We are over the target like we've never been.
So he's just using Alex's language, he's directly referencing Alex.
This dude's just a fucking info warrior.
Man, I don't want to be killed by a bunch of cowards like this.
I don't like the idea that this extremist political anti-communist ideology is being
so successfully marketed under the veil of religion.
I really, really think that that's terrifying.
I would rather be killed in a fight with ISIS, because ISIS is at least like, I want to kill
you.
One of this wishy-washy cowardice from the conservatives just like, I don't want any
violence, but I'm going to have to kill you guys.
And then when violence does happen, whoa, whoa, whoa guys, we didn't ever want... At
least ISIS is like, I'm going to kill you.
There is a... terrorist groups generally do take responsibility for their actions.
Yeah, for shit they didn't even do sometimes.
Well interestingly, Dave has a very similar take on things after the fact that his hero
Alex Jones does.
Strange.
Part of the information war that's going on, and here's going to be your greatest battle
and my greatest battle, is you're going to have to convince the people that you come
in contact with that what happened yesterday in Washington DC wasn't this.
This wasn't what happened.
The storming of the Capitol building, the infiltration of Antifa, BLM, as part of that
infiltration.
Yes, patriots did break through.
They did break through and get into the Capitol building.
Yes, but can I tell you something?
Are you listening to me?
They let us.
Folks, listen to me.
They let us break through.
They let the patriots break through and then embedded BLM in the group.
And all the wicked, crazy stuff that happened inside that Capitol building, that was not
done by patriots, folks.
That was not done.
I love the idea that he's saying on the 7th, it gets suspicious that the cops let them
through when the morning of- On the 6th.
The cops are going to let us through.
Yeah.
It's very strange.
It implies a real change of perspective about like, oh, this actually happened.
Oh shit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just see that so universally with these folks that you look in on.
We got to find a way to not take responsibility for whoever shit on that desk.
If anybody comes at me with like, listen to any conservative in the media now, it's just
no.
What are you talking about?
Don't even.
I can't engage with it.
This was the moment where it's like, no matter what you do, you caused this and then you
disavowed it, so go fuck yourself.
You're a coward.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
A complete coward.
You're worse than ISIS.
Quite a ride for you in comparing things to ISIS.
I'm enjoying it.
They were good as, they were as evil as ISIS for a while.
It was equivalent.
Now they're worse.
Wow.
Yeah, it's bad.
I think that one of the things that I found when I was looking at this was, first of all,
I find Dave Dobenmeyer incredibly boring.
Oh, he's bad.
Yeah.
And I don't know, maybe it's been a long time since I've looked at any of his actual shows
or anything.
It just struck me as like, you're just taking notes from Infowars shows and preaching with
it.
You're just doing that.
It's stupid.
It's almost like the idea of covering his show actually feels kind of like drinking
backwash.
Yeah.
I'm not interested.
But he was there and this is an interesting set of circumstances, an interesting set of
behaviors.
He would be like, hey, Trump is telling us all to get on the field.
You know, like, well, I mean the three jurisdictions thing, that's just good, clean fun.
That's fantastic.
Yeah.
They're literally talking about the possibility of storming the Capitol and how the police
will stand down.
There's not enough of them.
Yep.
And then the next day there's a conspiracy afoot.
It's somebody else's fault.
They're trying to set us up.
No, we didn't do anything.
The police let us in and when they let us in, they embedded Antifa and Black Lives Matter
in there.
We're doing this.
We're so strong, but we're the victim.
It's really dumb.
Bunch of fucking cowards.
It's very dumb.
And perhaps so was this.
Who knows?
That's what I'm saying.
I want a higher quality of criminal.
I think I've said that before.
Yeah, exactly.
It's just that whole thing of just like, really?
This is who we're up against?
Come on, man.
It is.
This is the shittiest fascism I've ever seen.
Yeah, I bet all of them have been disappointing in the moment.
Yeah, well that's probably true.
I bet over time they take on more of a serious character.
Yeah, I imagine if I went and went back and watched a serious documentary about Mussolini,
they'd be like, look at this fucking idiot.
What are we talking about with this guy?
How did he take over?
Yeah, probably.
Anyway, Jordan, I apologize that we don't have a full episode for today, but...
Absolutely, this is a bottle episode.
Battlestar Galactica is over.
It's like that Breaking Bad episode with the fly.
Yeah, exactly.
But the fly is a coach.
The fly is just Dave D'Aubenbier whispering like, hey man, it's gonna happen.
Would you pass the salt?
It's gonna happen.
It's just a fly asking for salt.
Alright, well, we'll be back on Wednesday with a full-on Alex Jones episode, but until
then Jordan, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yep, we're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledgejones.com.
Now go to Matt Jordan.
We're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook.
If you could, please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work.
Yeah, we'll be back, but until then, I'm Neo, I'm Leo, I'm DZXClark, I'm Daryl Rundis,
I'm the Juiciest Ice Cube.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.