N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
knowledgefight.com
It's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledge fight.
Knowledge fight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying,
We are the bad guys. Knowledge Fight.
Dan and Jordan, Knowledge Fight.
Rattle her, rattle her, rattle her.
I need, I need money.
Andy and Kansas, Andy and, Andy and,
Stop it, Andy and, Andy and, Andy and, Andy and, Andy and,
It's time to pray.
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
Knowledge Fight.
knowledgefight.com
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight, I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes, like to sit around, drink novelty beverages,
and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are Dan.
Jordan.
Dan.
I have a quick question for you.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, Jordan, is, so I mentioned not too long ago,
a little while back, Policy Wonk Lisa signed us up for the
Hot Sauce of the Month Club.
Indeed.
And I got the second installment of the Hot Sauce of the Month Club.
I like it.
And I think, I think it's called FYM Sauce.
Okay.
I don't know what it stands for.
Fuck your mother.
Or, uh, fuck your mouth, something.
Yeah, I hope it's not that, that's creepier.
Well, I mean, it's, you're putting spicy things in your mouth.
I understand that, but somehow it's just, unfortunate.
I don't mean, I mean fuck your mouth and like fuck your feelings.
I understand that.
Forget about your mouth.
Well, I mean, you can say that a lot of different ways.
Sure.
Um, it's very challenging, the sauce.
It's, it, I had some on some chicken nuggets last night.
Would you say it's a real motherfucker?
Yes.
Okay.
Yes, it definitely is.
I, I tossed the nuggets in the sauce.
Uh huh.
And for a good couple hours afterwards, I was sort of like, oh Nelly.
Oh boy.
Oh, sweating from the face a good bit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Took me for a ride.
I really enjoyed it.
Although stomach, stomach had some.
All those, all those noises that you made are, do not denote a joyful ride.
No, generally not, but I enjoyed it.
It's a, it was good.
It was good.
The first month was really, it was good.
It was hot, but it was, it wasn't like, it wasn't a trial.
Sure, sure, sure.
Kafka had nothing to do with it.
Yeah.
This came fast.
It ramped up really fast and it creeped on you too.
I see.
Good, good stuff.
I believe you.
I'm ready for month three already.
Yes, I believe you.
What about you?
Uh, uh, Dan, my, my bright spot is I, uh, I finally got my equipment worked out.
I finally got it all set up and I did a little bit of streaming today.
Video games streaming.
I did a little bit of video games streaming.
Congratulations, over on Twitch.
Played, uh, Final Fantasy 7, the remake.
Awesome.
My plan is I've decided to riff the, the whole game.
Yeah.
Like MST3K, but for Final Fantasy 7.
That sounds fun.
That's my plan.
Very difficult.
I mean, paying attention to playing and trying to talk at the same time.
It's very hard.
I think it's a, I think it's an acquired skill too.
You get better at it as you go along.
Yeah, I enjoyed it.
It was, uh, it was good times.
Good times.
Well, I was, I look forward to joining you at some point while you do these video game
streams.
Oh, indeed you will.
And make fun of your terrible play.
I can't wait.
It'll be great.
Oh, look at you.
It's, uh, yeah.
Using that materia.
I, I realize that, uh, just randomly saying I'm going to start at 2 central on a, on a
day, but, but it's like I finally got everything worked out so that it would work.
And you know me, I don't do well with like delay.
Oh, we're going to start doing that now.
I was like, now begin it.
I'm releasing my book.
I don't give a shit.
Yeah.
And I don't think there's a problem with that.
You'll work out a schedule eventually.
Yeah, that'll be good.
And I'm sure some people came in and enjoyed the time.
So some walks get to hang out.
That might be a better thing to do for a live stream.
If anyone in our audience is interested in it, then us live streaming episodes, quite
frankly, that might be better because you can be distracted while you're playing a video
game.
It's much more frustrating when I'm distracted trying to host a podcast.
That's fair.
That is definitely fair.
Can't, uh, can't quite keep up with the chat.
Yeah, no, that's a, that'd be interesting.
I look forward to it.
I don't know if I've completely figured out how to set it up so we can all be on there
together without the lag screwing everything up.
Uh, but I think I can always just come over to your house too.
You can just come over to my house.
That's true.
Yeah.
We're in a, we're in our COVID bubble.
That's fair.
I'm a little bit cramped in my, in my tiny little room.
That's fine.
Um, so Jordan, today, uh, we got an interesting episode to go over.
We're back to talking about Alex Jones after Monday's little, uh, salt break, as I've decided
to call it.
I don't think that's bad.
Um, so we have to do a little bit of catch up.
And so what we're doing today is we're going over January 14th to 17th, which is, uh, uh,
Thursday, Friday, Saturday, and Sunday of last week, all within the year 2021.
Blackjack!
Blackjack, baby!
I want to add a baby to it.
I like it.
I don't know.
I feel like it's forced.
All right.
We'll see.
Um, so what my plan is, is to go over this period of time.
And then for Friday's episode, we will witness the end of Trump's presidency on Alex Jones's
show.
Oh boy.
So that will be, uh, you know, I mean, just the sound of silence.
Yeah.
Hello darkness.
But for two to three hours, as we listen to one man lose his mind.
That'll be fun.
Um, so I got, uh, I got an interesting, uh, stretch here.
There's some really, really troubling stuff.
Some really stupid stuff.
Sure.
And Alex realizing that Steve Pachanik has been fucking with him for 20 years.
Finally.
Thank God.
I am looking forward to the moment that I get to hear that happen.
He has a dark moment of clarity on Saturday.
I love it.
Give it to me.
I'm not going to go into business on all of this, but first Jordan, we're going to take
a moment to say thank you to some folks who have signed up and are supporting the show.
Oh, that's a great idea.
So first Rory loves a low low.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
RLL.
Thank you.
Yeah.
My, one of my aunts is a Lois.
Lois.
But she goes by low low.
Oh, I like low low.
I like low low.
Yeah.
It's a good name.
Next Harold drop dead.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
HDD.
Thank you.
Anderson Intel extraordinaire.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much MPIE.
Next.
The Hills Have Thighs.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
THC.
Why is everybody doing it in acronyms?
They requested that I say it really ominously.
So I did my best ominous reading there.
You did great.
Thank you.
Next Morrissey's finger.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much Morrissey's finger.
Thank you.
Next Talon from Minneapolis.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks Talon.
Thank you.
Then finally I'd like to say thank you to a couple of people who donated on Elevated
Love and appreciate that very much.
So Andy B. from Minnesota.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
And Ghost Panda of Coal Creek.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey mate.
That's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing bro?
We gotta go full tilt boogie on this Watson alright?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much Andy B. up in Minnesota.
Thank you so much to Ghost Panda of Coal Creek.
Thank you very much to the both of you.
Yeah!
Is Coal Creek in Minnesota?
Uh I don't know but it is.
I think Minnesota has a Coal Creek.
Minneapolis, Minnesota and Coal Creek.
We got a lot of Minnesotans.
We got a whole, yeah yeah yeah.
All the Canucks that are slightly lower.
Sure.
That's what I'm gonna call them.
All I can, the only reference I've got is I guess Prince and Ryan Sayers.
Alright.
Okay.
That's all I got.
Musical references.
I like it.
I think I've been to Minneapolis.
You think you have?
I have.
There are so many cities in the US that I think I've been to but I'm not positive.
I got kicked out of a billionaire's house in Minneapolis.
Really?
Yeah yeah yeah.
What happened?
I used to work for, I used to sell hearing aids and the like.
Okay.
And one of the owners of the biggest hearing aid cartel in the world is stationed out of
Minneapolis.
Was it Prince?
Uh no.
Oh.
It's a guy named Rogers Nelson.
Something.
But the company's name is Starkey and we got invited there because my cousin has his whole
thing and we got invited to his house as like a reward for people who sold some number of
hearing aids and he and I got way too drunk and we were asked to leave.
Oh wow.
So it was nice.
It's an experience.
Yeah.
I peed on his floor.
I'm proud of myself.
Jeez.
Alright.
Were you proud of yourself the next morning?
Yes.
Fuck that guy.
Oh wow.
Okay.
You and I are different.
Also I mean at the same time my boss at the time was my cousin so I had a little bit more
of a.
Little wiggle room.
I can be on the floor of a billionaire's home.
Yeah.
You know.
So Jordan we're gonna start here on the 14th.
Let's do it.
We got some bad news to start things off.
Alright.
The left is on a rampage.
Sure.
I've been here since very early this morning.
I've been doing a lot of research and then we had the FBI contact us just about 30 minutes
ago and then I found out why Roger Stone is in hiding.
It was worse than we thought.
Somebody came to his house and then waited for his wife who was handicapped and hearing
impaired and beat her up.
So she's been in the hospital and they also sent somebody to Laura Loomer's house to try
to kidnap her and so this is the Bolshevik takeover.
You just need to understand that.
You need to know that.
And they are actively trying to say that we masterminded the attack at the Capitol with
the U.S. military.
So that's the line they're going with now.
Haha.
Unbelievable.
On the 14th news that Roger Stone's wife was attacked by a leftist activist went huge all
over the conservative media.
Blogs ran unconfirmed articles about how they were targeted for political violence and commentators
opined about how the mainstream media was covering it up.
Then on the 15th there was an article in the Floridian Press that sought to clear things
up a little bit.
They reached out to Roger and reported quote we learned that media outlets today began
to fudge the facts of the incident and as the story was recycled around the truth of
what happened was distorted.
Here we go.
Here's the statement they published from Roger about the truth of the incident.
Quote on December 23rd my wife Nydia and my Yorkie Mimi were attacked by a pit bull.
Our beloved dog was badly injured requiring two surgeries and Nydia was bitten badly when
she attempted to get between the pit bull and our baby.
This incident was reported to both Fort Lauderdale police and Broward County Animal Control.
Nydia sustained substantial injuries in the pit bull attack.
Last week there was an incident in front of our home when we returned from dinner.
A man on a bicycle recognized me and started screaming numerous political epithets which
are not fit for a family newspaper.
While there was a scuffle Mrs. Stone sustained no new injuries in the event.
Reports that she was badly beaten or hospitalized are incorrect.
This event was also accurately reported to the Fort Lauderdale police.
Seems like Alex is kind of embellishing the story a little bit.
Poor dog.
He probably should have reached out to Roger for a comment considering how close the two
of them are.
Not answering his phone calls.
I'm sure Roger would have been happy to clear things up so Alex wouldn't have to report
a completely false story about Roger's wife on air.
Not interested.
Seems fucking disrespectful as hell.
In answering Alex's phone calls.
So I would say this is not good.
And as for the story about Laura Loomer I'm gonna need to see some evidence before I even
start caring about whatever's going on there.
Anything that's reported about her on Infowars is an attempt at a publicity stunt until proven
otherwise.
Yeah all I can think is that Roger himself is on a rampage and has been dressing up like
a pit bull.
That's the only thing that makes sense to me.
He's attacking people left and right dressed up like a pit bull.
His day drinking has evolved.
So now we get to the new framing of the storming of the Capitol back on January 6th.
Alex has some historical parallels.
I feel like we're on the fifth new framing of an event that doesn't need any new framing.
We're gonna get a couple ones on this episode.
We're gonna get a couple framings.
This is frustrating.
And one new patsy.
Okay good.
The headline of Infowars.com is confirmed January 6th capital attack was Reichstag 2.0.
If you don't know about the Reichstag attack we're gonna be covering that when we come
back because right in that printer snuggled in that warm printer is the little printout
where I'm gonna read you about what happened in the Reichstag attack.
But that's what this is.
This is a Reichstag attack that happened right when Hitler got elected.
He was very unpopular.
They thought he'd stolen the election and he firebombed that bitch.
So this isn't good.
I like the idea that something's getting printed out.
I'm excited to find out what that's gonna be.
Wow they gotta print it out.
It's got the little hooks on the edge.
They gotta perforate the thing and tear it apart.
Yeah.
So Alex has a couple of details wrong about the Reichstag fire here.
Sure.
That's surprising.
The most important element he's completely making up is that the fire happened after
Hitler won an election that people thought was fraudulent.
That's nonsense.
Alex is saying this because he knows that his audience is gullible and if he paints
a one-to-one comparison of Hitler and Biden it stands to scare them more and drive more
profits to info wars.
In reality the Reichstag fire occurred on February 27th, 1933.
In January of that year Hitler had been appointed Chancellor of Germany's government which was
still under the control of the country's president Paul von Hindenburg.
The structure of the government was that the president was the elected leader of the country
who would then appoint a chancellor who would be responsible for introducing legislation
to members of the Reichstag who were also elected officials.
At any point the president could dismiss his chancellor, you know, that he had control
over that position.
Or so he thought.
Well, according to the Smithsonian Magazine, quote, Hindenburg reluctantly appointed Hitler
as chancellor on the advice of Franz von Papen, a disgruntled former chancellor who believed
the conservative bourgeois parties should ally with the Nazis to keep the communists
out of party.
Man, I have heard something like that so frequently in the past.
Fear of communism leads to aligning with fascists every time.
It does seem like it happens every time.
The reality of the Reichstag fire is that it was an event almost certainly committed
by the Nazis which they blamed on communists.
This allowed Hitler to use the event as a rallying cry against the communists and as
a justification for why the government needed to assert dictatorship level powers to crush
the threat they posed.
Sure.
There's no better way to put this than this.
What Alex is doing right now is attempting the same political maneuvering that the Nazis
engaged in in 1933.
Yes, correct.
There was a terrible event that drove home the sobering reality to a large portion of
the country, and that terrible event can be incredibly useful if you can blame it on your
enemies.
This is why Alex is now on air fudging details about the Reichstag fire.
And if you did it, it is wise to blame it on your enemies, otherwise people will think
it's your fault.
True.
Yeah.
It's definitely true of the present situation.
You don't want people to think it's your fault.
No.
So Alex really has a bad handle on history.
Oh yeah.
I've heard him, I mean, like, you know, the fake quotes are one thing.
Sure.
But like, man, he's way out of line here.
February 27th, 1933, from the front lines of the information war, it's Alex Jones.
That was the date.
February 27th, 1933.
Adolf A. Lewis Hitler had narrowly won the presidency of Germany, but von Hindenburg
was not stepping down as the chancellor.
The most powerful position in the Weimar Republic.
This is crazy not true.
Yeah.
Hitler had not won an election for the presidency of Germany.
He was chancellor beginning in 1933, at which point he began maneuvering to seize more and
more power for himself in the Nazi party, who had had a great showing in the Reichstag
elections in the 1932 election.
People like Nazis.
Yeah.
Hindenburg died in 1934, at which point Hitler dissolved the office of the presidency and
combined its powers with that of the chancellor, essentially making himself both chancellor
and president.
In the 1932 election, Hindenburg had soundly defeated Hitler, but the Nazi party itself,
like I said, had gained a large number of seats.
The scenario that Alex is painting is 100 percent revisionist history, because he needs
his audience to think that they're living through a direct parallel to Hitler's rise
to power.
Paul von Hindenburg wasn't chancellor, and there was not a contested election for president
in the way that Alex is describing.
This is just an idiot making stuff up because he knows his audience doesn't know any better
and won't bother to look into it.
Does not care either way.
Yeah.
This is one of the things I'd really like to drive home to anyone who may have some
inclination to take Alex Jones seriously or think he knows what he's talking about.
If he has this little a grasp of basic facts, like who was in what office when the Reichstag
happened, and he's so willing to confidently assert really fundamental inaccuracies, why
would you ever give him the benefit of the doubt with more complicated stuff?
If he can't be bothered to understand really simple arithmetic, you shouldn't listen to
him about geometry or algebra or trigonometry.
He doesn't know how to add.
No, no, no, absolutely not.
He doesn't have a basic grasp of the fundamentals of existence.
He doesn't know grammar.
Don't let him tell you how to edit your paper or whatever.
I don't know what the metaphor would be, but if you don't know the building blocks upon
which understanding can be built, you- Right.
I feel like one of the fundamental things that he doesn't get is that some things are
and some things are not.
Everything seems to be fungible there, but some things have to be and some things have
to not be.
And the things- They cannot just be whatever you want them
to be.
Right.
And if he wants me to take it all seriously, the idea that he knows this secret information
that Hitler was set up or all this nonsense that he throws around all the time, this revisionist
World War II history, and he doesn't know who was in what office, that's embarrassing,
man.
You can't do this.
You know what is blowing my mind, and it's just going to be so painful.
It's going to be so painful, Dan, if you recall, oh, those early days in 2017, whenever you
would call Trump a Nazi, and people would go, whoa, whoa, whoa, you can't just throw
that word around.
That's a terrible thing to do.
It needs to be used correctly.
And now we are about to begin a long stretch of literally everything Biden does-
Nazi.
Making him a Nazi.
Yep.
That will be screamed at us from all corners of the world, including the ones who screamed
at us to not call Trump a Nazi.
I would say almost exclusively from those corners.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But if they come from Alex, one of the good things you can always fall back on is he knows
literally nothing about World War II history.
That's fair.
But days after the election that Hitler won by a very slight margin, fire bombs hit the
Capitol and was blamed on his enemies, the communists.
At least he's not pretending it wasn't the communists who got blamed.
Yeah, that's nice.
Yeah, it's almost like he's trying real hard to thread the line where he's like, the Nazis
were the good guys here.
Oh, so what's he saying?
The election days, what is he saying?
The election prior to the Reichstag fire was in April 1932, about a year prior to the fire.
360, 330 days prior after the, yeah.
There was an election for Reichstag members scheduled for six days after the fire, but
that's the opposite of what Alex is describing.
Alex either knows nothing about World War II history and is pretending he does in order
to scare his audience, or he does know what the reality is and he's willfully lying to
them in order to make it more closely match this scenario also to scare them.
You betcha.
You really should stop.
This is pretty bad.
It's bad.
It's real bad.
Congratulations though, Alex.
You have a real depth of, remember when you said you read a hundred books on World War
II?
A thousand books on World War II?
Are there any Nazis in the United States willing to sue on behalf of the Nazi party for Alex's
bad portrayal of them?
I mean, it's just-
Slander, sir.
Yeah.
Slander.
I mean, there's things that are interpretation and there are things that are like, what was,
who was where?
What power alignment-
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Some things are and some things are not.
You can't just say that that's how-
It's staggering to me.
It's embarrassing for Alex and he never has to pay any consequences, even in terms of
embarrassment for not knowing any of this shit.
Yeah, and the people who believe him are so, so sad.
So Alex mentioned earlier that the FBI called him.
Yeah, we might learn a little bit more about that.
Man, wow, I've hit Twilight Zone, Twilight Zone.
Like in the world of Twilight Zone, for something to be even weirder, like imagine what people
in Twilight Zone, when they watch the Twilight Zone, it must be even weirder or like in the
Twilight Zone of the Twilight Zone.
That's just regular-
Yeah, we'd like you to come in and talk about-
It's a double negative.
You don't know math, man.
Your people in the military have quite distinguished records that work there and you notice this
and that, yeah, we want you to know about what you know about what happened in there.
Wow.
Wow, ladies and gentlemen.
I'm guessing that, first of all, you're right, the Twilight Zone and the Twilight Zone would
be just normal life.
Yeah, normal.
I would assume.
They cancel each other out.
It's a regular zone.
Yeah, and no one ends up getting a harsh lesson about anything.
That would be the version of the show they watch in the Twilight Zone.
No, in the regular-
There's no poetic consequences for things.
Yeah, exactly.
It's just random like everything else.
Yeah.
Well, I was talking about the FBI contacting him and I think I might know why that is.
You remember that he said he had an employee who was there and got footage of the woman
getting shot inside the Capitol?
Maybe.
Well, that means he had an employee who was illegally entering the Capitol.
That sounds like something the FBI would look into.
Alex's employee, Sam, released his raw footage of entering the Capitol building.
I'm just going to play you the minutes where he actually walked through the doors of the
building, thereby committing a crime, and see if you can see any reason why law enforcement
might be interested in talking to Alex.
Okay, I think that's a good idea.
Come on.
Mic down for this.
All right.
We have had enough.
We're not going to take your fucking vaccines.
We're not going to take all your bullshit.
The people are rising up.
To be clear, that voice is the cameraman.
Welcome home.
Folks, I am now on the steps of the Capitol.
Here we go.
Having a good time.
Everybody's having a good time.
Look at this.
I don't think it costs them what to do.
This is the first time they've seen a peaceful protest succeed.
They're dumbfounded.
Here they are.
All right.
Folks, I don't know how I made it out of there without getting hurt, but your boy ain't hurt.
But I got to be honest.
This is not a peaceful protest.
So I just want to be accurate about that.
But for whatever that means, you heard it.
As I was going along, I tried to ask a few people what that's going through their mind or what they're feeling.
I don't know what to say.
But they've had enough.
You heard that last gentleman?
He feels like this is the people's house.
And so the people want to take it back.
See?
So here we go.
We got SWAT gear over there.
Everybody in.
Keep the line moving.
All right.
This is your boy Sam with Infowars.com.
Support the war.
Infowarsstore.com.
We got sales to go.
We got sales for days.
Please, it's because of your support that we're able to get into things like this and show you the real news that the media won't.
That they will spin tomorrow.
They're going to spin it.
But guess what?
Guess what?
We are in the Capitol, baby!
He's doing a plug as he enters the Capitol.
I just don't.
These people need to be babysat.
I don't even know if they need to be punished or if they need to be babysat because they clearly have no ability to process reality.
Like none.
It's amazing.
Just none.
You walked into the Capitol building doing an ad for the thing that you're not supposed to be doing.
I'm going to add that to my quickly growing collection of things that really don't look good in hindsight.
This is not a peaceful protest.
Infowars.com.
We're in the Capitol, baby.
Oh, man.
You can't really be doing this.
I got to assume that there's a lot of people who have been arrested for breaching the Capitol.
Even people who were just recording, people who didn't break anything.
It's still illegal entry.
That is true.
I don't see why Sam wouldn't be arrested.
Oh, well, you can't arrest him.
He works for Infowars, the tip of the spear, and the FBI is afraid of pissing off Alex.
I would also assume that should Sam be arrested, there might be some interesting questions about,
Oh, you work at Infowars.
Why did you record going in?
Did Alex send you there on an assignment?
Well, I can only say it's with your support that Infowars continues storming the Capitol.
Certainly it does imply that little clip of video tends to indicate that he was there in an official capacity.
It would suggest that, yes.
As part of his duties while promoting Infowarsstore.com, he committed a crime.
Yeah. Yes.
That might be something that people would want to talk to Alex about.
I don't know.
We're in the looking glass here, Dan, we're in the twilight zone of the twilight zone.
Sure.
Yeah.
Everything's normal.
So anyway, Roger's wife's going through some things.
Sure.
This is the real world.
You cannot make this up.
And Roger Stone, a man ran over his wife.
Jesus.
And she got back up and he knocked her over again.
And she has major, and then he knocked her over again.
And so Roger now is going into hiding.
This isn't a joke.
His wife is in the hospital to have emergency surgery because a man beat his wife up.
Just randomly in their little condo area.
Nobody's around.
Randomly.
She's walking the dog.
A dude pulls up on a bike and starts knocking him over.
She gets up.
He knocks her over repeatedly.
That's the left for you folks.
If I were Roger, I'd be pissed about this.
Yeah.
I'd be really not happy about Alex's behavior.
Don't fucking embellish stories about my wife in order to make people scared of the left.
Jesus.
You dick.
I know that's the job.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on.
I'm not saying that I hope someone screamed cut his dick off at Roger Stone, but I'm not
not saying it did.
So if I were Roger, I'd be mad about that.
Yeah.
But I'd also not be thrilled about this.
That's where we are right now is beating up a 75-year-old or whatever she is.
She's older than Roger.
Look how old his wife is.
Still looks great for 77 years.
Oh, my God.
His daughter's not bad looking either.
I mean, I mean, that's like God made beautiful women.
I'm not hitting on them.
I'm married.
I'm saying nice ladies.
Wow.
What are we doing?
What do we got?
Do we got to do that?
We don't have to do these things, Alex.
We don't have to say his daughter's hot.
We don't.
Well, I mean, it's it's an interesting way.
He was trying to recover from saying that Roger's wife was hot.
Like, oh, I'll save this by saying his daughter's hot.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let me objectify his child instead.
That'll make it better.
Ah, what a good save, everybody.
Why isn't everybody reaching up for high fives?
I got high fives going on.
Where's everybody else's high fives?
So we get back now to the Reichtag fire.
And I was so glad that this paid off because I was worried that that stuff that he was
printing out wasn't, you know, it was going to be the opposite of Chekhov's printer
paper, but we do find out what he had an intern print out for him.
This is Reichstag 2.0.
Reichstag fire.
The Reichstag fire German.
Fire was a arson attack on the Reichstag government building, the capital.
Home of the German parliament in Berlin on Monday, the 27th February, 1933.
Precisely four weeks after Adolf Hitler was sworn in as chancellor of Germany.
Hitler's government stated that it goes on, Marinus van der Lib and all the rest of it.
So this is the Wikipedia article about the Reichstag fire.
Great, great.
If you ever want to tell yourself that Alex does any work, please call this image into your mind.
Great.
He doesn't do shit.
He has his interns print Wikipedia pages for him to fumble his way through blindly reading.
When he said German of fire, that's because on the Wikipedia entry, they include the German
word for the fire, which confused Alex while he was cold reading.
There we go.
This is pathetic.
Wow.
Anyway, more revisionist history about Hitler coming up.
You know, it's one of those things where by having papers, you assume a legitimacy that
somebody ostensibly from the internet doesn't have.
Something about having physical papers suggests, look, we at least did the work, and then you
find out they just printed out the internet, and that's ten times less interesting.
And it's Wikipedia.
Yeah, I mean like it's the newsmen of days of yore might have desk papers that they're
looking at, or like you might, you know, I don't know, maybe I've only seen this in sitcoms,
but like somebody comes running in with a piece of paper.
Oh yeah, breaking news, sir.
Yeah, breaking news.
Yeah, typed up, there's transcriptions because you couldn't even do shit like that.
You just had to read it out loud like a man.
Yeah.
And I think Alex is trying to emulate that to give himself some kind of like the appearance
of that, and it's just Wikipedia articles.
Not good.
All right, here's more bullshit.
Hitler first only got elected president, it wasn't enough, and then there was people were
fighting over him trying to become the Fuhrer, and have the former head of the Weimar Republic
step down, and so they had to stage this event that came out in the Nuremberg Trials.
Hitler was not elected president prior to the Reichstag fire.
He'd been appointed chancellor by Hindenburg.
The title Fuhrer didn't really even exist at the time, and I guess he was the Fuhrer
of the Nazi party, but it wouldn't come into being like a state role until after Hindenburg's
death, when Hitler combined the offices of president and chancellor into a new title,
Fuhrer and Reichschansler, which eventually got shortened to Fuhrer.
And then they got shortened to senate majority leader.
Yeah.
I hate to sound like a broken record here, but Alex is just making shit up about Nazi
history for his own benefit here, and then pretending that the Nuremberg Trials back
him up.
The thing that I think is most transparent as an aspect is that Alex knows damn well
in that moment, he's making this up.
He knows he's making this up.
That's why his citation is something like the Nuremberg Trials, which is absolutely
useless as a reference.
So general.
What part of the trial?
How many months long?
Years long?
What exactly came out in those trials even?
He's not even saying.
It's in the white papers, but the trial papers.
When you try to pull the thread there to determine how reliable a source he's being, you have
nowhere solid to go other than thousands of pages of testimony, and you're not even
really sure what you're looking for to prove Alex right or wrong.
That's a big part of Alex's game.
One of his favorite things to do is make absurd, completely false claims, and then insist that
some impossibly long text actually proves him right.
He's never read those texts, but it doesn't matter, because he knows that his audience
hasn't and won't either.
That's why he'll constantly just point at thousand-plus page books like Tragedy and
Hope or Ecoscience and just insist that those things actually prove him right, and it's
all in there.
Yeah.
It's a way of trying to railroad criticism and make it impossible for anyone to actually
engage with the things that are being said unless they've read these really long books
that Alex is pretending to have read.
I would dig through the Nuremberg documents to disprove what Alex is saying, but he gives
up his right to be taken seriously when he completely fabricates history like this.
Yeah.
But I couldn't help it, so I did dig around a little bit.
Sure, sure, sure.
This is from page 110 of volume 2 of the trial of major war criminals.
This is spoken by Justice Robert Jackson, the chief U.S. prosecutor at the Nuremberg
trials.
Quote, the burning of this symbol of free parliamentary government was so providential
for the Nazis that it was believed they staged the fire themselves.
Certainly, when we contemplate their known crimes, we cannot believe they would shrink
to mere arson.
It's not necessary, however, to resolve the controversy as to who set the fire.
So I guess if Alex is saying that it came out in the Nuremberg trials that the Nazis
themselves set the fire, the chief U.S. prosecutor doesn't seem to be even making that indictment
in the Nuremberg trials.
And in fact, though it's generally accepted consensus that the Nazis did probably start
the fire, definitive proof is hard to come by even today.
Even the U.S. Holocaust Memorial Museum says, quote, the origins of the fire are still unclear.
Sure, sure.
I mean, I think the prosecutor really makes a good point, which is just like, ah, just
add it.
Just, Amy, take it off, add it.
It doesn't matter.
Yeah.
Anytime.
No, no, no.
It's better just to be like, it doesn't even matter.
Yeah, yeah.
Who cares?
What they did was horrible enough.
That would be a genocide.
A fire is not, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Anytime somebody is engaging in World War II revisionism, where they're like changing
a little bit of the story away from Nazi genocide is to me like that sign that you're eventually
going to try and get me to think that even if there was a problem with Hitler, it wasn't
the genocide or the fascism part.
I see you coming, sir.
Yeah, Alex is really fucking weird on this.
Like this really struck me as like, this is unnecessary.
Yeah.
He really is exposing of a either complete and total ignorance of history on Alex's part
or a willingness to lie to his audience in a way to make history look like what he wants
the present to look like to them in order to convince them of a lie about the present.
No, totally.
Which is like either of those are pretty bad looks.
Yeah, I mean, what's that old saying?
He who lies about the past controls the present and then becomes Senate Majority Leader.
So we get a guest at this point on the 14th, he's a guy who hides in bushes.
He's the Batman.
It's John Rappaport.
It's the Bats.
John Rappaport hasn't been a guest on the show much in the recent history.
So people who have just discovered our show recently probably won't know of our obsession
with John Rappaport.
He followed us on Twitter for a while.
Several hundred episodes and then boom, much like the Bat, gone into the night.
He is a guy who is a quote unquote investigative journalist, is an HIV denialist, is a real
dick.
I think he's hypnotizing Alex.
Alex has an intense emotional reliance on him.
Oftentimes whenever John hosts the fourth hour, Alex will do five minutes with him where
he is just like, John, John, I need you, John.
Just tell me I'm doing good.
John, we love you so much, John Rappaport.
Tell me I'm a good man, John.
John, I just need to hear that I'm a good man.
So his interview is not really all that great.
It's kind of just about how like, you know, Aunt Aoife did that shit.
Why do I feel like they went through the Rolodex of Infowars guests and were like, I guess Rappaport's
the only one who hasn't been documented as saying we did it.
We took over the Capitol in a positive way.
There are there are a fair amount of like, wow, they're back.
Like Mike Adams was back.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like just the last couple episodes, Rappaport's here showing up later.
We're going to get Steve Quayle is fucking back.
Who here was against the coup?
Who?
Anybody raise their hands?
Anybody?
Oh, boy.
Oh, not a lot of faces.
OK.
All right.
So here's here's a little taste from their talk.
Who is this guy standing next to him?
Oh, well, he was arrested over here.
You know, all of this comes tumbling out and arrested and let go.
They've got this Antifa leader that you mentioned saying, burn the Capitol down on video.
He was released.
You know, it's like the Keystone Cops.
So Alex is referencing John Sullivan, who is not an Antifa leader by any stretch of
the word.
Initially, Alex had been saying that this dude had been arrested and let go and he was
making up both things.
Since then, Sullivan had been arrested, but he wasn't really let go.
He was released from jail without bail.
But whenever Alex brings that up, he fails to mention that conditions of his release
included surrendering his passport, having his computer activities monitored, being not
allowed to go on social media and being under house arrest.
He's definitely still in huge trouble.
But the phrasing that he was released from jail is being misrepresented by people like
Alex to imply that the charges have been dropped when that is not the case.
Yeah, the legal system is not really their interest in portraying accurately.
No.
Capital letters and stuff.
Yeah.
Also, I don't know all the details, but Sullivan's not someone who left-wing activists seem to
like.
They hate him!
And have for a while.
Long good time.
Yeah.
There's an article on The Intercept that cites a number of activists from the West Coast
who have raised concerns about him long before he went to DC.
But anyway, weirdly, you know where I actually first saw John Sullivan?
Where?
The one that was shot at him for the first time?
The Whole Foods?
It was in the footage from inside the Capitol that was shot by the Infowars employee named
Sam.
Interesting.
Here's Sam talking to John Sullivan just after that woman got shot, trying to get the footage
that John Sullivan had shot of the incident.
He actually saw her die.
He actually saw her...
I'll post the video.
I have the video.
I have the video of the guy with the gun and the shooter.
I want to get with you.
I'm with the Bullers.com.
Just J-
I haven't, but I will look it up.
Okay.
Infowars.com.
I got you.
I want to get your info right now if you got that shot.
I have it.
Oh, I was right behind the door.
Okay.
I need that footage, man.
It's going to go out to the world.
This has changed so much.
I cannot believe that shit.
So there's a couple of interesting things here.
The first is obviously how ghoulish it is that these two are so interested in talking about
how good their footage is of a woman being shot so soon after and so close to where the
shooting happened.
There's a real grim voyeurism on display here that I think reflects poorly on them both.
Yeah.
Secondly, it's interesting to me that John seems unaware of Infowars.
If he were really an Antifa provocateur who was there to set up the Patriots and make
them look bad, it seems strange that he would sound completely unfamiliar with the name
Infowars who are supposed to be the patsies and fall guys of this whole thing.
Conversely, if he really were a left-wing activist, it seems unlikely that he would
be unaware of Infowars in that circumstance, too, given that they're a media organization
that proves and poses a very real and relevant threat to left-wing activist communities.
I honestly don't know what to make of their exchange, and I can't possibly imagine how
difficult it would be to process information after seeing someone get shot.
So not recognizing a name could just be a brain lapse.
I have no idea.
But I do think it's pretty funny to look at the dynamics here.
On the 6th, when Alex was on his own show, he was touting this footage that he'd gotten
from inside the Capitol of the shooting.
That footage was shot by Sam, the Infowars employee, and John Sullivan was the other
footage that Alex had, who has now turned out to be an Antifa agent provocateur.
I honestly wonder if Alex even realizes that the person that Sam got footage from to send
to Alex was John Sullivan.
Plausible deniability.
I bet Alex doesn't even realize.
He doesn't care.
No.
Yeah, it's bad for him to know that.
Yep.
So now we get another guest on.
It's an online right-wing talk show host.
I'm not sure if I've ever heard him be on Alex's show before.
He might have been.
I'm not sure.
Pete Santilli.
Okay.
The Santilli Lace.
I couldn't help it.
Yeah.
I don't like this guy, but I also am not interested.
Then on January 20th, our commander in chief hasn't called us to a peaceful protest to
Washington, D.C.
He just said, wherever you protest, protest peacefully.
I believe that they're setting the stage.
The FBI said that they forewarned the Capitol Police that there were going to be some agitators
coming in.
How do they know that?
Because those agitators worked for the FBI.
They had let the Capitol Police's guard down.
They allowed this thing to take place.
They had their operatives breaking the window.
And then obviously the emotion involved in just walking.
Well, we got three years ago from 2018, but it was from 2015.
The headline info wars was Obama planned martial law in Maryland.
How'd that go?
And the documents are there where they plan to like go provocateur and get it to be triggered.
And we actually have the anti-fidocuments.
That's what they do.
Yeah, those documents still aren't real.
They're still definitely just something that Harrison Smith found when he was cruising
around 4chan.
No contracts with the Soros son, Dan.
So Pete Santilli is a guy who's like a radio show host, but he's only relevant at all because
he was arrested at the Malheur Wildlife Refuge occupation.
Sure.
The charges ultimately were dropped against him, most likely because he was both occupying
the refuge and pretending to be a journalist.
So they didn't even want to fuck around and try and figure out how that first amendment
needle gets threaded.
And like, ah, who cares?
Much like who set the Reichstag fire, they're like, Jesus Christ, that's just too much.
It's too much.
And he's on just to try and help Alex convince people that the feds set people up and that,
you know, like coming weekend, it's all going to be a mess.
There's going to be agent provocateur events, mass shootings, bombings.
And now that we're here recording this on Tuesday,
I think it's, I think it's fascinating to me just because in some ways this is kind
of the only way that these people would be able to try and keep their people from committing
mass acts of violence because they can't come out and say, we were lying to you because
then the people will be like, uh, no, you weren't.
Or you're lying to us now.
Or it doesn't matter.
We still want to overthrow the Capitol.
But if you say that, if you go, you're going to be a provocateur and then blamed, that's
more likely to cut through the, it's like, it's like when you're talking to a child in
pretend land, you have to talk to the pretend land child, not the regular one.
Yeah.
But if you just say something along the lines of like complete denunciation of violence,
you stand to lose a certain amount of your audience who will think that you've sold out
or something because that is how information is filtered for a lot of these communities.
Yeah.
You have to be like, okay, yeah, yeah, you want to do this and you're right to want to
do it, but if you do it, it's a trap and you'll be a symbol that'll bring all your brethren
down.
Totally.
That is probably the only way.
Yeah.
It's, it's weird.
You have to play the game.
It doesn't really work for everyone.
I don't know.
Yeah, we'll see.
Anyway, this was pretty fun.
Uh, Pete Santilli has one big message and it's like, yeah, all right, I believe I can.
What I want everybody to understand right now is that your most trusted people that
you have around you are going to be the ones that you will, you will be shocked that they're
actually working for this entity.
There's trillions of dollars at stake.
Your security person may be paid a hundred thousand dollars to set you up, to gather
enough information in order for you to make a statement on recording, uh, and, uh, and
essentially be used in an indictment.
So Pete's messages, nobody in the right wing can be trusted.
Hey, listen, everyone, everyone will absolutely abandon you the moment that it is expedient
for them to do so.
Yes.
Everyone in this right wing community has a fucking price tag and you can't afford them.
Yeah.
Have you guys, did you guys ever hear about Stalin's closest, uh, Politburo friends and
all that stuff?
Did you ever notice how they backstabbed each other all the goddamn time?
Well, guess what?
That's what fascism is.
Well, I know that, uh, Stalin burned down the Reich tag.
Yes.
Why not?
We don't have time to figure it out, Dan.
So, uh, Pete, uh, makes a bit of an accusation here that, uh, I found distasteful.
I believe, and we're getting information now that there were maps that were put out.
A guy named John Sullivan, who is a known BLM and Tifa, uh, activist just so happened
to be present with her, uh, how she was able to determine that going through the labyrinth
of the, you know, the hallways in the halls of Congress, how she was able to get to that
one particular spot where secret service would be, I'm sure was provoked by John Sullivan.
She's very emotionally involved.
They break the window, she goes up there, she gets shot.
I gotta say, it feels kinda like defamation to just randomly imply that just because Sullivan
was near Ashley when she got shot that somehow he led her there.
If the standard for making that accusation is that low, then it could easily be said
that Alex's cameraman, Sam, must have led her to where she got shot since he was right
there too.
Oh shit, Sam's Antifa.
Oh no.
God damn it, Sam.
Oh, and Troyer's Black Lives Matter flag burning friend Taylor Hansen was right there too,
so he must have been the one who led her there.
Antifa.
There's a very serious accusation that Pete is making based on nothing, and the only reason
he's doing it is so that he doesn't have to feel bad about being an active participant
in the media ecosystem that misinforms and radicalizes people like Ashley to the point
where she thought it was a good idea to storm the Capitol.
He can't take that really hard look in the mirror, so the best way to put that off is
to come up with a convenient story where someone else is the bad guy who actually secretly
had machinations to lead to this.
Yeah, at no point in time can that man just say, wait, I think it was me and my ilk that
led her there.
Oh.
Maybe there are real world consequences for bullshit.
Oh no, if I have that reflection, I have to change my behavior or recognize that I'm a
villain while I profit off it.
Oh no.
Yeah.
Oh.
Anyway, good luck, Pete.
So Alex keeps lying about Roger's wife, and we don't need to hear more of it because it's
basically just the same thing over and over again.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
We've got another guest on, and I think that this guest has listened to our show.
It's Ezra Levant from Rebel Media, and I really think, tell me if you know why I think that.
What happened at the Capitol?
What's your view?
What's coming next?
Ezra Levant of Rebel Media.
Well, look, we all know the phrase fake news, and you can battle fake news on a daily basis,
but what happens when the news cements, when that cement hardens, and it becomes history?
You can't even unargue or dislodge it.
I'm not saying that I came up with that metaphor, but it's something that I've used in this
very specific context many times, and he uses it multiple times in this interview.
And I was just sitting here like, you motherfucker.
You can't weaponize my own shit against me?
Dickweed.
So anyway, that guy sucks.
Very interesting.
As an interview, we're going to jump to the 15th.
So the 15th is Friday.
I hope he does listen to our show so we can find out how little we give a fuck about it.
Yeah, don't care.
Piece of shit.
Go cry to Tommy Robinson about cement.
No shit.
Fuck you.
Anyway, so we had some vaccine-possibly-related deaths in Norway, and Alex is covering that
story.
I can spend an hour just on this little darling right here from Infowars.com, which is the
Just got links to mainstream Reuters, you name it, foreign news, Norway TV.
23 dead in Norway after taking COVID vaccine, and they said, that's okay, it's going to
kill some people.
See, they're now just normalizing the death.
That's just one article here.
So this is an instance where the headline can look pretty scary, but the actual story
might not actually be as much of a cause for alarm as it seems.
The first thing to be clear about is that these deaths that have happened in Norway
are obviously being studied.
And at the time of this episode, there's not been any causal link that's been made between
the vaccine and these deaths, which is important to nail down.
If Alex had actually read some of the underlying information that this Infowars article is
based on, like there's a CNN article, you would have read this explanation from Stephen
Evans, professor of pharmacoepidemiology at the London School of Hygiene and Tropical
Medicine.
Quote, Evans told the UK's Science Media Center that when people who are at high risk of death
get vaccinated, there will be a certain number of coincidental deaths that occur shortly
after vaccination.
Regulatory bodies across the world are closely monitoring these fatalities, Evans said, and
are able to calculate the expected number of deaths within various time periods.
Quote, we do not yet know, but it would seem that the observed numbers of deaths is not
notably above the numbers expected, he said, adding that there was, quote, no need for
anxiety but complacency is equally mistaken.
If we're vaccinating people who are going to die soon, some of them are going to die
soon after we vaccinate them.
People who are in high risk categories may have a higher expectation of coincidental
death.
That is a factor that needs to be taken into account.
Also the possibilities brought up in these articles of minor side effects possibly being
much more serious issues for people with more complications.
Anyway, I think that if you look at something like how this guy, Steven Evans, is explaining
the situation, I think that sounds very responsible.
Because he has both sides sort of reflected there, which is like, there's reasons why
this number would be there.
People are looking at it and will understand this better.
This is not a reason to be super worried, but it's also not a reason to just be like,
eh, whatever.
And I think that's fair.
I remember when I was young, when I was little, they had kids Bibles, you know, that were
illustrated and they simplified a lot of the stories and they left out all the rapes.
And I think that's what we need for like science news journalists.
We need to give them like the kiddie version of real science and they can disseminate that
so people don't get too scared, you know, because we can't be having people with headlines
like vaccine involved in two deaths.
That headline is true.
Yeah.
Well, no, it's not.
I mean, 23 people died after getting the vaccine.
It's unclear if it's related or connected in how many of the cases it is, is unclear.
But yeah, the headline itself can be weaponized so easily by people with the wrong information.
Yeah, it'd be good.
Messaging is critical at this point with medical information, I think.
I would change that headline to tens of millions vaccinated without dying.
Unsurprisingly statistically relevant, but unsurprising so far at this point in time.
Let's go back to the old tracks from the 60s.
I want Thomas Paine to start writing our fucking headlines.
That's what we got to do.
Okay.
We'll take that under advisement.
Yes.
Alex has another headline.
Okay.
Study.
COVID lockdown harms are 10 times greater than benefits and causes more people to die
from suicide, drug addiction, drug overdose, and more, but that's okay.
I can tell from the phrasing of the headline that Alex is reading there that it's a post
in an outlet called the Dhaka Tribune.
I didn't know that Alex kept up with the Bangladeshi media.
Ooh.
One of his interns just has a Google alert for lockdown studies and this one hit the
filter.
Sure.
This was an article published on January 11th about a paper put out by a Canadian doctor
of pediatrics named Ari Joff.
The paper is called COVID-19 Rethinking the Lockdown Groupthink and it's not been published
by anyone nor is it peer reviewed.
Odd.
Also it was written last October.
Alex absolutely didn't read this paper.
One of his interns just sent him the headline from an outlet in Bangladesh covering a Canadian
paper that no one cared about three months ago.
Great.
Bad work.
Just great.
Now Alex gets to a point where he kind of thinks, well, maybe we've got to move on.
Maybe we've got to move on from Trump.
Okay.
I think he's starting to have those feelings of like, we must move forward.
I could snap my fingers and come out against Trump and come out against the second amendment
and I can't get into details because it's private things that are done.
This is how the law works as long as something is illegal, I will go have private meetings
with the globalists and their minions and, but I mean, I can snap my fingers and betray
the second amendment, betray America, betray Trump to make it so easy.
Just come out against the second amendment just a little bit, come out for red flag laws
or, or, or come out for just against Trump a little or, or just leave radical Islam alone
or just stop harping on this pedophilia thing all day and all your problems will stop Jones.
Yeah.
Jones, you can come back into the fold right now.
Jones, you'd come back in.
Really I can.
Great.
No, I don't.
I don't want to come back in your fold.
I've never been in your fold.
I don't want to be in your fold, but that's where this is.
People say, well, Jones, you just said red flag laws is one of their stipulations.
Trump said he was for that.
Trump said that.
So they would say we want total gun confiscation.
And so he would shut it all down.
I agree.
It was a mistake.
I said it was whenever I talk about something Trump did, why he thought he did the right
thing.
I'm so you can get my take on why he did it.
Doesn't mean I agree with him.
He said, hey, you shouldn't have to take the vaccine.
But oh, here it is.
Let's turn the economy back on.
Cause he gets, that's the main mission is shut the economy back off.
Doesn't mean I agree with him trying to defeat them in that capacity.
And it failed and he failed to do the right thing when it came to the censorship.
And now he knows that.
And now the whole world knows that it doesn't matter.
Now we move on.
Now it's Joe Biden who is a fraud who we will never accept, who is going to come after us
hardcore.
He's going to get on the offense against him because he runs a globalist crime family against
our nation as fully compromised.
So Trump will be gone in five days.
Trust the plan, right?
Unbelievable.
We'll be right back.
I'm Alex Jones.
Tomorrow's news of the day.
Infowars.com.
This dude's so mad about QAnon.
Man, that's just bad writing.
That's just bad fanfic is what we just heard right there.
There's also, there's something interesting and paradoxical about Alex ranting about how
the globalists want him to turn on Trump, but he won't do it only for him to then end
his rant by saying we have to move on to fight Joe Biden.
Well, sure.
I guess it's not turning on Trump, but leaving that season of his show behind, maybe?
Yeah, just toss it.
If you're Alex, you don't get to do this.
You don't get to whip your audience into an apocalyptic fervor about how Trump was appointed
to be ruler by God and this election is a spiritual battle between Trump's godliness
and the literal devil.
Then when it's time to move on, you just say, we move on.
Personally, I'm stoked the devil won.
He's a good dude.
I guess we've talked a little bit.
He's everywhere.
Alex promised the end of days and the fucking devil if Biden got in and guess what?
It's probably just going to be a slightly disappointing government that Alex is just
going to make a bunch of money yelling about.
Fucking bullshit.
Also, I want to point out this thing that Alex has been doing a lot lately that I find
really offensive.
He keeps talking about how he could join the globalists so easy.
They want him on their side and at any minute he could be one of the elites.
This is meant to be heard by the audience like an abusive spouse yelling about how they
could do so much better.
The message is really clear that Alex could join the globalists whenever he wants because
he's special, but no one listening has the same offer extended to them because they are
not special.
Yep.
And you should be glad that I'm not joining these globalists.
You are fucking lucky I choose to shine my light on you assholes.
Yeah.
It's dark.
It's really narcissistic and gross.
Yeah.
I don't enjoy it.
I would prefer he didn't do that or exist.
Well, I mean, if he didn't exist, I know there's at least two people in the world who would
miss him.
I got the wrong clip here.
Thinking real hard.
Later Alex says that two famous people told him something.
This is a clip where two people tell him about one single famous person.
Okay.
Alright.
We gotta talk famous people.
Rewind.
Didn't hear that part.
There's one person.
2021.
Blackjack.
Yay.
There's one person.
Maybe.
If Alex didn't exist, one person who's very famous who would be very sad.
Oh.
Christopher Watson?
Paul Watson asked me like, what's going on with Jack Dorsey?
He says he's for free speech and he hates the fact that Trump was censored, but then
now there's this video where he's admitting it all, that he is censoring to his employees.
He's like a man with a gun to his head and I think that's basically it.
He's blackmailed for whatever reason it is.
And so I told Paul, why not just tell you this now?
It's not like a bragging thing.
I don't care.
It's actually weird.
I think it's strange.
I've been told by two famous prominent people that Jack Dorsey says Alex Jones is always
right and that I'm like his guru.
And then there's this big famous Hollywood producer.
I'm not going to go any further.
This big music producer that like is like their guru and then he's like, I'm being told
this by two separate really famous people.
And this is like a while back and I'm like, okay, all right.
I mean, you can't make up the weirdness level.
This is right before Phil Spector died, right?
Yeah, I think so.
This famous music producer fucking loves me.
He's my, he loves me.
He's a famous music producer.
He's saying this was a while back, so it could have been Manson.
That's fair.
Yeah, man.
I don't know.
Let's imagine this is true.
Do you have something better to do with your time on the show?
No, no he doesn't.
Why are you talking about Jack Dorsey?
Jack Dorsey looks at me like I'm his guru.
I'm really, really done with anybody treating a rich person like they're real.
Like what's going on with Jack Dorsey?
No, no, no.
What's going on?
Don't care.
Money!
The end.
Jordan, I don't even care about Jack Dorsey.
I want to talk about Alex Jones being his guru.
Sure.
Okay.
All right.
So in a sense, money is the only thing he cares about.
Well, I mean, it must have felt terrible to kick your guru off of your own platform.
Yeah.
Ban him.
Multiple times.
Absolutely.
And leave David Knight on.
David Knight is my nightlight.
I just think about this like you get kicked out of a bar and later you're like the bouncer,
I'm his hero.
He's my, he loves me.
Guy fucking loves me.
Broke his heart to kick my ass out of there.
Yeah.
But hey, look, Alex didn't tell that story to be powerful.
By the way, folks, I didn't tell you that Jack Dorsey story to sound powerful or cool.
I don't want to be part of Hollywood.
I want to be part of the Washington power structure.
It really is true that you cannot register or fathom how popular Infowars really is now.
And that was all God's plan.
And that was all you keeping us on air.
All of us together.
It was a team effort.
It's extremely dangerous position to be in as well, but almost all these liberal talk
show hosts attack me.
They actually listen.
I remember Mike Cernovich about five years ago, four years ago, he was visiting here.
He says, don't you know, they all love you and they all listen all the time.
And don't you know, all those big people like Jack Dorsey and all them are huge fans.
And I'm like, dude, stop trying to build my ego up.
I don't want to hear this.
That's bull.
It's all true, but I appreciate it.
It is all bull.
Can't believe anything Mike Cernovich says for one and then for two, uh, man, this is
sad.
This is really grim.
This is bad.
I guess, you know what?
The only people that I could really make a solid case who really dislike him, but do
listen to him are me.
The yeah, that would be us.
So Alex is a confusing man in many ways.
Agreed.
He has certain tastes.
Disgusting ones.
He has a crush on somebody Roger Stone's daughter.
This really happened.
I remember about a year ago visiting my, a little bit over a year ago, my, my wife's
mother in San Diego.
And so her house is little, so we said, well, let's go to this nice country club that has
a hotel.
Beautiful place.
It was the Fairmount beautiful hotel on a golf course.
We could walk around the golf course and stuff.
I'm rich.
All the chemical spraying that they add to the jet fuel and it's all in the patents and
Solomon.
It's all in the Nobel prizes.
I mean, it's been going on since the mid nineties.
It's a perfect case of this industrial globalist takeover houses there and general public doesn't
know, but it's hidden in plain view.
I said, man, I want to have a website or a podcast.
I told my wife this called Kim trails and country clubs because you're in this beautiful
country club, these beautiful pools, beautiful statues, five star hotel.
I never stayed somewhere that nice.
And there's Kim trails everywhere and it's just raining down everyone.
And it's that symbol of how this has happened to everyone.
So then I get up about 5 a.m.
I've got to go get on the computer and research and I see, oh, well, that's it.
This big pop star.
She must be an Alex Jones lister because her new album is called Kim trails over the country
club.
Lana Del Rey, Alex continues being super still going on into Atlanta, Del Ray, super into
Lana Del Rey.
It's awesome.
He's so into this Kim trails over the, over the country club and he can't even enjoy it.
He can't even enjoy it.
He loves it.
He loves her and he can't publicly, he has to spend a fucking 10 minute jag on how famous
he is to God damn tech people, but he can't even come out and say he loves Lana Del Rey.
Now Alex, I would like for you to challenge yourself and explain to me how much you love
the song born to die.
Oh, Hey Alex, why don't you watch the national Anthem video and tell me what you think about
that.
Separate the art from the artist.
This is what you got to do.
You got to separate the art from the artist.
It's just so great.
It's so great that he has just out of like the last two albums just decided, I fucking
love.
He's into it.
Yeah.
He's fallen for this Americanist, I guess maybe found out that she was dating a cop
or something.
Oh, that could be.
I don't know.
I don't know exactly what it is, but it is really weird.
Is that what we should be doing?
Should we, should the, should Antifa focus more on biplanes and crop dusting mind control
over a resort towns?
I don't know.
I think that's a good idea.
I listened to this, this chemtrails over the country club song and I don't know.
I still like Lana Del Rey enough, but I think I might be a little bored.
It's not, there were a couple of good songs on Norman fucking Rockwell, but like as a
whole, I thought that song was really kind of just standard Lana Del Rey stuff.
It didn't do anything that really intrigued me much.
It kind of felt a little bit, a little safe, a little down the middle.
Is this alphabetically the sequel to Bombs Over Baghdad?
Yes.
Okay.
Moving on.
So Alex interviews Larry Pinckney, uh, it was a Black Panther back in the day and they,
it's nonsense.
It's more just about how the FBI is running Antifa and Black Lives Matter and stuff.
But then Alex gets back to talking about Roger's wife and this is the next day now.
This is the 15th.
He's still talking about Roger's wife.
Already had a clarification.
Roger Stone's wife got beat up, didn't actually happen on Thursday, the day before his wife
didn't want to tell him.
The guy ran her over with a bike in her front yard.
She got up, he pushed her down two more times and she knew that Roger would go crazy.
So she just said, a guy hit me with a bike.
Then she had to go to the hospital the next day and then she told him the rest of the
story that he told me.
And he's so upset.
He can't even come on the air and she's going to have an emergency surgery probably today.
So that's a 74 year old wife and then they got beat her up.
Okay.
So, and they're trying to get Roger to go crazy.
I mean, I understand that that's what's happening here and they did that to Larry Pinckney and
others.
Uh, I need your support.
I appreciate your support.
Wow.
Alex, you can make up shit about my wife, but I'm not going on your show to lie.
And please just whatever you do, don't use, uh, fabricated stories about my wife to sell
pills.
Oh wait, you did?
Oh, how predictable.
I think that's just, if you meet Alex and talk to him for more than an hour, you have
to sign a waiver that says he's allowed to lie about your time together.
You're probably, you're probably right.
It's like a, like an NDA, but I'm going to lie about this.
So Alex has another guest on and it's Steve Quayle, who is a noted weirdo.
He is someone who has, uh, he has a long history with Alex and shows like Coast to Coast.
He's also a guest on Jim Baker's show.
He's vice president for a while.
He's written books about giants.
Sure.
Apparently there's another book coming out soon about giants that Alex wants to not talk
about.
The Nephilim?
Is that what we're talking about?
We're talking about those giants.
We're talking Bible giants.
We're not talking giants.
We're not talking about, uh, centers in the NBA.
No, we're talking young earth creationism giants.
We're talking about, uh, the angels who fell and breaded with human women.
Good stuff.
Got too big.
Yep.
Got too big, Dan.
Alex, in the past, when we've listened to episodes from like the 2009 era around, then
Steve Quayle is around a bit more and Alex always talks about like how he's a prophet
and like he knows stuff ahead, man.
He's just really right about stuff.
So Alex asks him how he knows the stuff that he knows.
I'm interested in finding out.
I don't know if you could predict this and it's not a good answer.
My testimony is simply this.
I went from the gunner most, the uttermost.
I was a president of attorney.
This is important.
Oh, that was wild on Montana state university.
I went to how Lindsay talking about Jesus, never knew about Jesus, never knew anything.
And I accepted Jesus in my heart.
I went home that night.
I was living in my mother's house and uh, Tim, Tim blocks from the university and Jesus
literally, and I know this is going to flip, flip people out, but he literally appeared
to me.
I fell on my face.
He gave me a panorama of history and told me he was calling me.
Now understand, I just found out who Jesus was the day that that spirit of God convicted
my heart.
But here's the thing.
He gave me a panorama of history.
I saw it in the future.
Just imagine a motion picture and then he gave me a statement.
He says, Steve, I am going to hide the things from you until they're shortly to come to
pass.
And he told me, he said, I want you to prepare my people for the end of the age.
I'll bring people that know to tell you what you need to know, but you must be faithful
to warn them.
Alex.
That's true.
From that and that launched me.
Oh boy.
You are such a good medium.
You do not need to do voices.
I, uh, the reason that you don't know things is because I'm going to hide them from you
and tell, uh, I have appeared to you Jesus from beyond the grave and I shall give you
convenient excuses for why I am not explaining things to you.
Also if, uh, you know, the Lord came down and gave Steve a panoramic view of history,
you should probably explain to Alex that Hitler wasn't elected president before the Reich
Tech fire.
You know, Jesus did left out that part for some odd reason.
Now everything's in the panorama.
He should know everything about history.
But if you're seeing a panoramic view of history, uh, one, that's a lot to take in.
Sure.
How long was he there for?
I mean, a day to God is a thousand years.
Totally.
But like, if you are there, like if we had some academics.
By the way, by the way, I'm not quoting scripture.
I'm remembering that because it's the name of a RZA song.
Oh, the places that you learn.
Sure.
We see through a glass darkly.
Indeed.
None of us have the full picture, but the RZA has a clearer picture than the rest of
us.
That's true.
Yeah.
So Steve talked to God who gave him a panoramic view of history and told him that he was going
to lead God's people or something.
Now Alex had a different visitation.
Sure.
You see, you got a visit from Jesus.
I got a visit from the other guy.
So why did you get a visit from the Jesus?
I got a visit from the devil.
Because I was serving the devil wholehearted and somebody somewhere touched God for me
because I was totally beyond.
You're wiser than I am anyway.
So why did I get a visit from the devil, which I'm not going to get into on air, but I got
the other visit because I was pretty, I love God actually, but I got a visit from the other
guy.
Well, listen, you only get a visit from the devil.
Even Jesus was tempted by the devil.
I'm not saying either one of us are Jesus, but I think it's really important, Alex, that
people understand something.
This is a spiritual war.
I don't know.
I feel like everybody who's ever been interested in Alex Jones, again, should lead all their
stories with Alex Jones, comma, guy who believes the devil visited him.
Yeah.
I just have a heart to, I want to know the rules of this universe.
It's really getting annoying.
It's like whenever, it's like when you're watching a superhero movie and then at the
deus ex machina, somebody already, all of a sudden has a new power.
I'm annoyed by that.
It's like heroes.
Yeah.
Set up the rules for me, exist within the rules of space.
When they started to get to the point where they could give people powers and heroes,
it's just like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on.
We can't do this anymore.
No.
What's going on with that eclipse?
We can't do this.
We can't just, everybody's claiming that they got visits from superpowers and shit.
No, come on man.
I got visited by Hephaestus.
No, no, no.
You don't get it.
The god, the blacksmith god.
See, it's actually proof that you're a good person that you got visited by the devil and
that I was a bad person that I got visited by Jesus.
You see how it works, man?
It's like yin and yang, but we don't believe in that bullshit.
Yeah.
Great.
So that's the kind of conversation that's taken place.
Yeah, I believe that.
And I've been listening to this and I'm thinking to myself, boy, this show is dumb.
This is really dumb.
Yeah.
Oh boy.
So Steve's got a prediction that has nothing to do with giants or visitations from other
worlds.
And I want to make this statement.
Seven years ago, before President Trump even obviously became president, I made this statement.
Before God allows China and Russia to destroy the United States in a nuclear attack, he's
going to reveal the sins of the leaders to the people and the people's sins before a
holy God.
Cool.
Everybody has watched the narrative, some of the sickest SOBs on the planet.
Those are sons of Belial, meaning Baal.
We've seen it.
We're seeing the deep state.
So I guess get a bunker?
I prefer the Silquarian Belial.
Thank you very much.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I guess China and Russia are going to nuke us.
Yeah.
Why?
I don't know.
Aren't they heavily invested in us?
Yeah.
I think they want us to live.
Anyway.
Huh.
Weird.
Steve is an insufferably annoying weirdo.
No, he's doing great.
I love him seven years.
He's had visions.
Listen, if I want to just hear somebody talk about being visited by God and how Belial
is going to nuke the earth or whatever the fuck.
I could call my wife.
No, I'm fine with that.
I'll listen to that.
Sure.
I'll listen to that same person tell me about Antifa.
Well, there's probably that.
I'm just not playing that game.
Anyway, we go on to the 16th and that's Saturday.
Okay.
What?
Alex has an episode on Saturday?
That must be an emergency episode.
Emergency.
Emergency episode.
I think Alex has had a little bit of time to think.
Uh huh.
We got a new reason that the 6th happened.
There will be another reason.
Gotcha.
But that doesn't come until actually Sunday.
Okay.
But on Saturday, Alex has had some time to think after that Steve interview.
I think he might not be feeling good about it.
We all know the false flag is the scoundrel's ace in the hole.
They're ace of spades.
And now they've played it.
Why isn't good governance ever their ace of spades?
And it gives me a just surreal feeling.
Has anybody tried that?
To have walked right into it.
And then to have Steve Pacinek on a few days ago.
Chortling and celebrating that fact.
But not in the way he said.
It's a little bit different.
But see that's the thing about the globalist mindset.
As the terrain changes and they flip sides and engage in Machiavellian behavior.
They think that's intelligence.
They think the cold, hard, social, Darwinistic way they carry it out is proof of their righteousness
and it's not.
So that seems to imply that Steve is a globalist.
Yeah.
I, what's going on here, and this will sort of play out as the episode goes along.
Alex is saying that Steve was chortling but not in the way he seems.
The way he seemed to be chortling was that Trump had won and everything was totally fine.
The way he was actually chortling was at Alex's expense.
Now it should be pointed out that our episode mocking the shit out of Steve's interview
with him came out on Friday, this is Saturday.
So I don't know if maybe, I don't know if that's what led to this emergency episode
of Reflection.
Probably not.
I would doubt it.
But Alex is kind of realizing that Steve is fucking with him.
He is talking about 1984 and about how Emanuel Goldstein is a set up, it's QAnon.
And then he starts talking about other characters in 1984 and how they interacted.
When their torturers came in to torture them, they thought that they were actually their
friends because they couldn't believe they'd been conned.
Just like in 1984, O'Brien, and it's all just a fictional account of this, is torturing
him to death.
But he still thinks O'Brien's a good guy and he's like, oh, O'Brien, they got you.
When O'Brien comes in his jail cell, he goes, O'Brien, they got you.
They got you too.
And he goes, oh, they got me a long time ago, Winston.
See, the difference is with somebody like me, I know Paciniks and O'Brien type.
I'm just observing him and watching him.
I'm not Winston Smith.
Oh, boy.
Okay.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not getting manipulated.
I am the master manipulator.
I am observing him as in a science experiment.
Yeah, you are.
Sure, I've been doing this for 20 years and the fact that he's complimented me has allowed
him to say whatever bullshit that he wants to.
But I was observing.
I was keeping a close eye on that sneaky O'Brien.
Keep your friends close and keep your enemies closer, Dan.
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
Ooh, this is sad.
I am glad I'm not a narcissist and this would really, you know what, it would really fuck
me up for a good day or two, you know, but I wouldn't need to create a mythology around
it.
I'd be like, I got had and I would learn from it and I would move on with my life and then
I can't do it.
And then you would bring up the Nigerian email scam.
Totally.
Repeatedly on air as a metaphor.
Exactly.
I'd be like, this has happened before.
Yeah.
So Alex is still talking about 1984 and he gets into talking more about this Emanuel
Goldstein character.
Here it is.
Emanuel Goldstein.
Emanuel Goldstein is a fictional character in George Orwell's 1949 dystopian novel, 1984.
He is the principal enemy of the state according to the party of the totalitarian Oceania.
So he's just reading the Wikipedia page for Emanuel Goldstein.
Did they print it out or?
I'm not sure.
I wasn't watching the video.
All right.
But the reason that he pauses there when he says the 1949 novel is because on the Wikipedia
page it inaccurately says the 1984 novel, 1984.
They have the year wrong.
Right.
So Alex was correcting that as he was reading.
Sure, sure, sure.
He hasn't read this and it's just a Wikipedia page.
I have no interest in his analysis of 1984.
Uh, no.
Anyway, he's, he's, he's bummed out cause you know, on the one hand they got false flagged
and he's pissed off about that.
No they didn't.
Well, according to him they have.
Sure.
And he's experiencing that tough.
Um, and you know, Biden's gonna be president.
It's it's tough times all around for the Patriots.
Yeah, sure.
And there's literally only one solution.
Thank you so much for joining us on this Saturday evening.
The only way we stop this globalist operation and foil their storm, storm busters, is by
you taking this live feed and the archive feed for band out video and telling everyone
that they've got a martial law plan for the next few days and that only getting the word
out can stop it.
We need this report to get 10 million views by Monday.
Hit your email list, hit your text message list, tell your neighbors to watch it, run
down the street with a sign saying, watch it.
The productive solution is just get me free publicity.
It's dumb.
Man, brutal.
Yeah.
It's brutal.
Mike Adams is back.
Great.
Yeah.
For an emergency episode.
Yep.
All right.
So we're going to be told how we're going to die?
Yeah.
Okay.
Uh, oh my God.
It's very easy to know why Mike Adams is on an emergency episode.
Mike Adams is so goddamn dramatic.
Yeah.
The owner of It's Over for Humanity There Will Only Be Lone Survivors is dramatic.
He's like a junior high student.
This guy is going through some things.
He's the dark end wizard writing poetry all day.
Yeah.
It's behavior unbecoming of an adult the way he acts.
It's maudlin.
It's over the top.
It's just not cool.
It's like how you imagine Edgar Allen Poe in high school.
You're like, Jesus, that guy must've been exhausted.
I think more annoying, probably.
Probably.
There's a smaller head.
There's artistic craft.
That's true.
Edgar Allen Poe brought to the table.
So Mike wants to explain why there's so many troops in DC.
Now my argument would be that a bunch of people stormed the capital.
I don't understand.
And, uh, you know, there's existing threats and, uh, you know, continuing people saying
they want to do it again.
No, I'm pretty sure that the Patreons are universally non-violent, Dan.
That's what I've heard from them.
Well, it turns out there's a whole other explanation for these troops.
Oh, interesting.
30,000 troops.
Now, remember in Afghanistan, we only have about 3,000 troops, American troops there.
So this is 10 times the size of an invasion force.
This is using a cannon to kill a fly.
Right.
So the explanation that this is just for the inauguration is complete nonsense.
There's something else happening.
I've been sent photos of Patriot missile banks being set up, uh, in other States in America.
And as you know, there, there is legitimate concern about, uh, Chinese troops in Canada,
uh, Chinese troops in Mexico.
This is just Q shit, man.
Intimate concern about Chinese troops in Mexico does not sound like something I, uh, I believe.
I don't know why there would be an amassing of troops in Washington, DC if it was in the
Mexican border, but, uh, uh, you know, I don't know.
This is just dumb.
Yeah, that does sound dumb.
So Mike.
I would argue also one of the reasons there are so many more troops is just because it's
easier to get there.
You know how hard it is to get 30,000 troops to Afghanistan?
That's a long way away.
And hasn't Trump been scaling back the number of troops?
They're more available.
Isn't that part of Alex and Mike's narratives?
So you shouldn't use that as the number.
No.
Anyway, who cares?
Um, Mike has evidence of somebody who's saying that Trump is going to win.
Uh, they're a CIA shill.
I think he's talking about Steve Pacino.
I don't know though, because he won't make names.
There are some bad faith actors that, uh, even in the last 24 hours, I was able to...
Confirm a particular bad faith actor.
I don't want to mention any names, but someone who had fooled a lot of people with online
videos that were popular saying that, no, Trump's going to be sworn in on the 20th.
That person is a CIA operative.
I've been able to acquire his ID number working at the CIA.
So that's an op.
If you had evidence that somebody was running operations and you had definitive proof they
worked for the CIA, like you would put that out.
You would have to put that out.
You'd have to think that like, it's probably dangerous for me to have the, I mean, that's
what Alex would say, right?
That's what Alex says all the time.
If you have this information, you have to get it all out.
Yeah.
Otherwise you're dead.
I mean, isn't that, isn't this the Mission Impossible?
If you identify an undercover operative, that's the biggest thing that will get you killed
until you release that information.
Yeah.
That's the whole movie.
The only thing that can protect you is coming out with that information.
Exactly.
Yeah.
So I think this is about Steve.
Anyway, uh, we have some pretty serious things on the horizon.
Sure.
There's possible Chinese invasions, uh, also another threat to consider.
Okay.
I'm very, very concerned that the deep state is going to set off a dirty bomb in a US city.
Sure.
And they're going to blame that on Patriots.
And that's why they're desperately knocking on doors looking for somebody to recruit.
Somebody who actually has a history of appearing on videos and podcasts and so on talking about
guns or Trump or what have you.
You?
Yeah.
Yep.
All of this stuff is you.
You realize this is you.
Are you speaking to a mirror?
Are you threatening to dirty bomb me?
I am, I am loving all of these.
I'm concerned about what they're going to say the Patriots do because part of me is
like, do you guys think the Patriots are capable of building a dirty bomb?
Cause that concerns me.
I think they definitely are.
I mean, what's that Oathkeeper guy who was arrested a couple of years back with a napalm
bomb.
Yeah.
I think, uh, I think what we're all really hearing from these people is, Oh my God, I'm
worried about what we created.
Yeah.
It might be out of control.
This, uh, uh, you know, this thing is an uncontrollable, completely out of line group that we thought
would just be fun.
Yeah.
Unfortunately all of our fanfic about history didn't warn us about what real history would
have warned us about an uncontrollable mob.
I think it's kind of like me starting the year of the seltzer.
Sure.
I thought it would be good fun.
Right.
And I thought that, you know, we'd just have seltzers and I'd try them and it got out of
hand.
You picked a, you went 500 is too big and a year is too long.
Yeah.
It's an unwieldy amount of time.
It's an unwieldy amount of seltzer and requires commitment.
I had it for a long time.
I'm not saying it's over.
We still got the fiscal year's end.
I created something that I thought was fun and it was fun.
It was a lot of fun.
They had a lot of momentum for a while.
It was great.
But it was uncontrollable.
Flagged a little bit and then it came back.
It's still back.
It's uncontrollable.
Let's say you can't just force it.
Yeah.
This metaphor doesn't work, but, uh, neither does democracy, apparently, because Mike has
to tell you the country has fallen.
This guy is so dramatic.
Sure.
Well, the rule of law has collapsed in this nation and whether you're arrested just depends
on which side you're working for.
So, uh, if you're, if you're a pro-Trump patriot, you're going to be considered guilty no matter
what you're doing.
If you're a radical leftist, you can throw Molotov cocktails and set fire to federal
buildings and burn police cars and shine lasers at federal agents.
In your mythology.
Or you'll be arrested and the charges will be dropped within 24 hours by a George Soros
funded district attorney in your local city.
So we have now entered the era of complete lawlessness.
There is no controlling legal authority that is legitimate in this nation, which means
the constitutional republic has fallen.
Damn.
Wow.
That happened.
Yeah.
Wow.
Big news.
Yeah.
That's a real bummer.
Huge if true.
Yeah.
I love all the...
There is no legitimate legal authority in America anymore.
Well, I mean, I guess that would mean it's game on, right?
I mean, all the things that would stop you from doing things like storming the Capitol,
that would be laws.
Yeah.
And there's no legitimate legal authority.
And the constitutional republic has fallen.
Wow.
I mean, I guess the...
Do what thou wilt, if you will.
As Mike is saying, smoke them if you got them.
Yeah.
It does feel like that.
It reminds me so much of all those 2021 articles where it's like, cops have been proven to
hurt leftists at three times the rate of white nationalists.
And it's like, guys, I'm glad that you have new hard data, but come on, this is America.
We didn't need a new Guardian article in 2021.
We had Guardian articles in 1914 saying the exact same thing.
All right.
But it's good to have more articles.
Sure.
But you could have just put up a picture of the flag and been like, see, this is what
we do.
Fair enough.
Now, one thing you're not going to see an article about is the evil eye.
I don't think that's true.
I once saw a documentary about this guy who actually had magical powers.
He could hypnotize people with his evil eye.
With his evil eye.
Yeah.
He was like a really rich dude.
Was it narrated by Vincent Price?
No, it was this really rich guy.
He had a great mustache.
I think...
Mesmer?
I remember that one of his employees was a guy who would watch films and then review
them poorly.
That guy who was the film reviewer, his son went to the UN school.
Oh, that's strange.
Dr. Demento?
Please tell me that you know what I'm talking about.
No clue.
The critic.
Was that the critic?
Yeah.
Duke Phillips.
Oh, man.
He could hypnotize people with his evil eye.
You were referencing Duke Phillips.
I forgot about the evil eye.
Oh, shit.
Look into my evil eye.
That's right.
He could do that.
I should have said something about the...
He had country bears.
Yeah, that's what I would have...if you'd said he has the country bears.
We're the bears who sing for Duke.
So, yeah.
Evil eye.
Yes.
Apparently is a real thing.
I don't want to have a George W. Bush moment with you where he said, you know, I think
Putin's a good guy.
I looked in his eyes.
He has a soul I can trust, but everybody knows it's the eyes.
Everybody knows it's the wind of the soul.
I look at your eyes and I see a serious, intelligent, focused person that's really concerned.
You look at my eyes, you basically see the same thing.
I look at the eyes and it's increasingly worse at the grocery store or in public.
And I'm seeing more and more agitated, crazy looking people that look like schizophrenics
or demons.
And let's just put a photo up of a composite of some of the Democrat leaders' eyes.
And folks, it's not like we're cherry picking photos.
It's every photo of them, they look like they are from another dimension.
Back this out.
I mean, I've met some of these people.
I've been in rooms with these people.
And what is it about the eyes?
What is going on?
I know you study the medical issues, the 5G, the GMO, all of it.
But what is causing people to look like this and to act like this?
Medical weed.
In this case, it's not a medical issue.
It's a spiritual issue.
They are demonically infested.
That's no joke.
It's not an exaggeration.
There are actual demon or demonic entities that are possessing these people.
And then what happens is the body, the physical body begins to mirror the internal dark spirit
structure.
This is the health ranger.
If you don't understand what led to the situation on the 6th that you created and fucking caused,
this is what you would say.
Your political enemies are literally demon possessed and the constitutional republic
has fallen.
You are not fighting-
It's not responsible rhetoric.
Bananas.
I just think it's funny that this guy runs a natural news alternative medicine site and
he's sitting here on air talking about how people's eyes can tell you if there are demons
inside them.
That's another thing.
Lead every article about Mike Adams with this.
Mike Adams, who believes you can see demons in eyes.
I'd hate for him to look at me.
I have a cross eye.
What would he think about me?
Oh, you're a demon.
I obviously would say something terrible about me.
I mean, the cross eye is the sign of the demon.
I was born this way.
With a demon.
Oh.
Sorry.
So dumb.
These people are stupid.
So anyway, Alex starts talking about Steve and I would say that he describes Steve kind
of like how you might describe a lunatic.
Let's talk about Steve Pacinek here.
I've been interviewing him for 19 years.
He is a big spook.
He was involved in a lot of incredible stuff and he did help write Tom Clancy's novels
and he has that twisted side where he laughs at you and says, you know, oh, we co-opted
you and he exaggerates and, you know, does all that condescending stuff.
But he's an interesting guy, so I have him on, but he's done a lot of good things.
Exposing 9-11 as an inside job and wow.
All right.
You fired David Knight.
Jesus.
You dumb motherfucker.
It hasn't even been that long since he fired him.
Really has not.
It really has not.
It's such a great turnaround too.
So fast.
It's like if David Knight was like a goddamn Twilight Zone twist.
If David Knight wasn't so boring, like this could be a huge boost to his career.
Totally.
No, his credibility would go off the charts if anyone were still listening.
I did actually listen to a video of David Knight talking about Steve after, I believe
it was after the 6th, and I was like, man, scathing stuff.
So boring.
Yeah.
Couldn't even get any clips from it.
No.
But he does say that Alex fired him because of Steve.
Well, yeah.
And he says that Alex doesn't care about anything except traffic to the site.
Damn.
Coming with them boring swings.
Jesus, David Knight.
Thanks for speaking obvious to power.
So Mike and Alex get to wrestling with the idea that Steve made this bet about the election
and like how if he's wrong, it doesn't matter because then he can never come back on the
show again.
This is fucking 1910s people discussing like, well, if she is a witch, then unfortunately
we're going to have to burn her.
But we don't know yet.
You got to look her in the eye.
What Pacenik was promising you, what I noticed about that, he made a bet with you and you
were going to offer to employ him if he's right and he was going to offer to never come
on your show again.
If he's wrong.
Well, there's no downside for him to offer that because this is this.
If he's if he's playing us, it's his final play.
He will never want to come on your show.
He was laughing at me and was very obvious that was the final play.
But I knew weeks ago that's what he was doing.
I know I predict it's the final play.
That's why you fired David.
And I'm going to demand he come back on whenever what he said doesn't come true.
Yeah.
You know, if Biden's sworn in, he can he can just say no and what are you going to do?
You know, go find them and put them on camera.
No, no shit.
Yeah, no shit.
Why?
By the way, it's not the final play.
Steve will be back in like a couple of course.
Pretend this didn't happen.
It didn't.
I've done this rodeo too many times.
No kidding.
I guess this is a little more severe than other times, though, because like, it's clear
Alex's feelings are hurt.
Oh, severely.
But he's hurt Alex's feelings in the past.
Sure.
I just haven't heard him be like, I've been using you, man.
I know.
That one's too good.
That was great.
That was just too good.
Mm hmm.
That eclipses four stars for sure.
Yep.
Not as pithy, though.
Not as much of a soundbite.
No, that's true.
That's true.
So Mike is worried about a dirty bomb, worried about Chinese invasion.
Sure.
And he also is worried about anyone going to protest.
OK.
Don't do it.
All right.
To everyone listening, do not participate in any of these capital protests.
Not that there are really any actually being organized by patriot groups, but don't participate
in those.
If you go to the capital, this is all false flag operation you're being set up.
What you can do is legally and lawfully prepare to defend your home, your family and your
local neighborhood or community against any kind of aggression that may that may happen
if the left believes they can carry out a local uprising and go door to door killing
people like what happened in the Cultural Revolution in China.
And that's a very real possibility.
This guy is so dramatic.
This is this is painful to listen to.
Do these people not hear themselves?
Like I know they don't care about words.
I know they don't care about the words that they say, but I cannot imagine listening to
somebody who tells me that my political enemies are literal demons.
And then in the same breath tells me that I shouldn't protest.
Don't do anything but barricade your doors.
Don't do the protesting because that's a trap.
But you should be ready to kill people who are coming door to door totally to kill conservatives.
I mean, we are going to have a dearth of Jehovah's Witnesses if they go to the south.
Oh, no, I wouldn't do it.
So Alex is worried about migration.
He's worried about immigrants coming in.
I can't believe we can just change topics to immigration right now.
He has an interesting theory.
By interesting, I mean, absurd and probably motivated by racism.
You look at Europe and the model they want here.
Every home they say is going to take a African or Middle Eastern migrant, then that's a spy
on your house that works for the U.N. so they can do whatever they want and further break
down your home.
I mean, this is literally the takeover of civilization.
That's messed up.
I don't know why you would assume that any immigrant that you allow and agree to have
in your home out of the charity of your own heart would be a U.N. spy.
Yeah.
Cool.
You could just say, OK, well, first off, you could say no to this, I imagine.
But second, if you do have somebody in your home, don't they know how insanely hostile
you are towards them?
Wouldn't they have some idea?
Or even the government who's like, OK, we're going to put you in all of these homes, one
per home, but not this one.
Those people are going to kill you.
Yeah.
It doesn't seem like it's in anyone's best interest.
No, it's not.
Yeah.
It's a paranoid fantasy of white nationalist types like Alex, and that's all.
They're U.N. spies, though.
Yeah, we can't quarter soldiers in our homes, God damn it.
Keep that in mind.
Oh, of course.
Because that might come back.
Naturally.
So Alex was sort of going down this path, but he gets distracted by thinking about Steve
again.
He doesn't like that Steve-
He really hurt his feelings.
Yeah, because Steve was laughing at it.
Yeah.
So we'll track this together in what could be the final shows.
I mean, you heard Mike, like you said, this could be your last time coming on.
Steve Quayle said that, but notice Pacenik thought it was funny about, oh, yeah, just
don't worry.
I won't be coming back on your show probably again, ha ha ha ha, because, you know, very
maniacal or because I don't think he's delusional.
And I think he knows something really, really big is coming up here.
And then he wants to just put that last laugh in of, oh, and by the way, Jones, thanks for
helping us get martial law with what happened to the Capitol.
I think that Steve was laughing at Alex, but I think he's also delusional.
Yeah.
The problem with the way that-
They're not exclusive.
No.
But they are for someone like Alex.
That's true.
Because he's built up Steve over the years far too much to sort of penetrate the facade
of like the fake version of him that he's presented to the audience, which is really
easy for someone like you or me because we're like, this guy is crazy.
He's a very high functioning, very smart, delusional person who has forest gumped himself
into every single historically important thing.
And Alex has just allowed him to do that and reinforce his credibility over and over and
over and over again.
And now it doesn't look so good.
Yeah.
It's not like Steve is a pathological liar that is aware of his pathology and is laughing
at you for buying anything that he says.
He might be.
He's a liar, he's a pathological liar who is laughing at you for not believing his lies.
Maybe both.
Yeah.
And you know what?
Steve wasn't like laughing at Alex when he said he wouldn't come back on his show.
He was being dismissive.
Yeah.
He was like, well, if I'm wrong, I'm not coming on your show.
Don't have me on your show anymore.
He was asserting confidence more than anything.
I think it's so funny how much Alex condescended to the Q shaman who is a fan of his, who believes
almost identical shit to Steve Pechenik.
And then how much he got his ass handed to him by Steve Pechenik, who is supposed to
be his friend.
Yup.
And the Q shaman is going to prison.
Maybe that's why these people just exist is because it's not possible for them to have
good relationships with people.
Like they simply cannot do it.
What they believe is friendship is exploitation and what they believe is a love or affection
is actually a secret plot to kill them.
Well, I mean, you know, I'm quoting Pete Santilli here, you know, everybody in the right wing
is they're just waiting for the right bidder to sell you out.
Ain't that the truth?
So at this point on this emergency Saturday broadcast, Alex gets into what I would describe
as incredibly familiar territory.
My goal, I woke up about 3 a.m. this morning and couldn't sleep.
And you know, you're so clear at like 3 a.m. when you've went to bed at like 8, I went
to bed early, got up at like 3 a.m., had some coffee and I was really clear, was out on
the back porch.
You look at the mist and I thought, I need to go on air tomorrow like it's my last show
ever and say that to people.
And then I forgot to do that.
You just said that.
And so people download this to hard drive, save it.
This show, next week's show, literally there's a good chance it's our last show.
It's not drama.
Okay.
So Mike, speak to that and then after you're gone, I'll have my messages if it's my last
show because this is the knowledge now that if they just have this knowledge in the future,
they're going to win and beat the globalists.
We did this already.
This is so frustrating.
Yeah.
You know why?
Because it was a running bit on our show because he kept saying this and then on November 24th,
he actually did it.
Yep.
And it was sad.
It was a failure.
Complete.
It was a great failure.
Fucked up.
Yep.
And I understand why he'd want to do it over.
Oh yeah.
Just call them all again.
But it's just so annoying.
Nothing.
Nothing matters.
We, we did the payoff for this joke already.
Why are you doing it again?
Why are you hurting me?
Yeah.
This feels like it's personal.
This is a personal attack.
I'm not a good enough comedian to pull off doing this joke again.
We already did the season.
Totally.
We've, we've like, look, I had one joke that I told for longer than three years.
And even that was a little bit too long.
This was, this is over.
We move on.
We write new material.
We got to go.
Alex, you're a hack.
You're a hack.
It is.
It's hacky.
It's like, okay, you're a writer for home improvement, right?
I don't know why this came into my head.
Maybe it's because Tim Allen's a conservative dude.
Sure.
Tim Allen is the star of the show.
So there's an episode that you do and like a season later, he insists that you do the
same story and pretends or seems to not be aware that you've done this story already.
And now you got to try and find a way to make this episode happen because he's the fucking
star and what he says goes, now you got to try and make it funny again that Alex is doing
his goddamn fake last broadcast again.
I'm, I'm, I'm furious.
It's terrible.
Just terrible.
If there's one thing that does work and is really funny, it's that Mike Adams is taking
it very seriously because he is very dramatic.
He's a dramatic man.
He's like, it is such an honor to be here.
Oh my God.
No, no.
Yeah.
Come on.
You fucking.
It's really silly.
All right.
And so he gets to talk to you about how, and all this goes down, right?
When the fascist state that comes and puts us all into a bind, once that falls, people
like Alex, people like Mike and the info warriors will be needed to rebuild society.
The evil fascist regime will eventually fall.
It will fall under its own arrogance.
It will fall under its own mistakes under the weight of its own deception.
It will eventually fall as many evil regimes have fallen in the past.
You know, we defeated the third Reich, the USSR fell, and this American, I can't even
call it American, this globalist coup against America will not last forever.
It will fall.
And when it does fall, it's people like you and I and the listeners to the show who will
be necessary to rebuild the next society in the image of Christian principles and values
with added new freedoms that weren't in the original bill of rights, such as health freedom,
the right to always say no to medical interventions, to say no to vaccines, to say, Medicare for
none.
That right, which was, I think, Dr. Benjamin Rush, wasn't it?
Who wanted to put that in the initial bill of rights, but it didn't make it in there.
We need that to be the third amendment, for example.
You know, we need the first amendment, freedom of speech and religious expression, second
amendment, but we need a third amendment, freedom, health freedom.
You always have the right to control your own body.
The government can never force anything upon you.
I mean this sincerely, I don't know if Mike Adams knows there's already a third amendment.
I genuinely agree with you.
One hundred percent believe you.
That means he might not know about the other ones after it.
That's fucking scary.
I'll tell you the one that he definitely doesn't want to know about.
Anyone that involves slavery.
Some of those later ones he's probably a little bit iffy on.
Very against.
That was weird.
I don't, I mean like I understand that he dwells in a media space that really obsesses
about the first and second.
I mean the third is pretty important too.
That's that quartering soldiers one.
Yeah, I was going to say, I really remember that being quartering soldiers, but then I,
see this is the problem.
Whenever people like him say stuff so insanely confident and I'm, I have to be like, I swear
to you, I know what this is, but there's a question for one second of like, maybe I just
mistook it.
Maybe I could be wrong.
It could be the sixth amendment.
Maybe I don't know.
Even if you're in this extreme right wing world, like there was a real long stretch
of time during Obama's presidency where they were obsessed with the 10th amendment, you
know, about state's rights and all that nonsense.
And so like, I don't, I don't understand, like, I mean it would be so easy just to say
we need another amendment instead of a third.
Jesus.
Oh boy.
There are, the people who have spent so much time slapping a constitution, telling you
to read it, and putting it in their pocket have never read it and definitely couldn't
understand it if they did.
Also, I think that Mike's imagined health freedom amendment would guarantee access to
reproductive health care, including abortion.
No, no, no, no.
It would guarantee the right to not have access to those.
I know that he's considering that like, it's like a thing where the government can't force
you to have medical things done, but wouldn't you also want to make sure the government
can't force you to not have any medical procedure you think is necessary done?
That seems like an important element of health freedom.
These people are fundamentally stupid.
I just can't stand it.
I hate, I hate this dramatic weirdo.
This guy is so weird, he thinks evil eyes exist.
I just, I just don't know.
I love the deadpan, just junior high guy going through puberty, kind of like, everything
is so serious, kind of delivery of, they're gonna dirty bomb us.
It's an honor to be here with you, Alex, on your last show.
After the fall of the American fascist state, people like you and me will be needed to rebuild
society.
Oh god.
Whether it is nobler in the mind to suffer the a-slings and arrows of outrageous dirty
bombs.
Yeah.
So now Alex is supposed to be doing his last episode thing here, but instead he has Robert
Barnes on.
That would be his last episode.
Barnes just talks more shit about Q. He's just on to talk more nonsense about Q.
I hate him.
But he's talking about, okay, so Barnes is laying out like what QAnon did.
And one of the things that they did was they, they targeted certain groups.
Now, if you listen to this, it sounds almost identical to the Infowars business model.
They also targeted three groups in particular, QAnon targeted first, people that otherwise
are crowdsourcing grassroots investigative journalists.
Second, they targeted soldiers and ex soldiers.
Third, they targeted cops and ex cops and people that also were religious.
So there are people that are accustomed to believing in a source of authority independent
of and separate from the state, incorporated references to religious rhetoric, incorporated
references to Bible verses, incorporated references to God.
This is gnostic, gnostic Roman cult stuff.
Explain that.
You're describing Infowars.
That should be his last broadcast because it's Barnes explaining what Alex does.
Yeah.
More or less.
Unreal.
So Alex gets to complaining about the FBI.
If this was Shakespeare, he would give that soliloquy and then immediately be stabbed.
That is how this works.
Okay.
So Alex is talking about the FBI and he's made a big deal about how they're like saying
that he caused the uprising.
He planned the storming of the Capitol.
He comes clean a little bit about what they actually had questions about.
Sure.
Let me bring this up to you now.
I'm talking about myself.
The FBI contacted our security people, wanted to bring them in, wanted to talk to them.
Oh, we don't care about Alex.
We want to talk to you.
And then we refused to get lawyers.
And so they go, okay, don't worry about it.
We just got false reports that you guys were in the Capitol.
Just tell us you weren't in the Capitol.
Yeah, we weren't in the Capitol.
So, so Sam was, your camera man was, he was doing a plug when he went in.
Do you know how we know that?
It's on your website.
On your website.
It is being broadcast on your website.
I got it from bam.video.
Also, if I were the FBI, I too would be like, let's talk to your security people.
Not you.
You lying piece of shit.
Yeah.
I've seen your depositions.
You're not helpful.
Yeah.
No, no.
We did hire Larry Klayman for this one though, so it's pretty exciting.
Alex talked to Barnes about how bad Q is for a while and it's annoying.
And then he gets on his own and he reads a fake Cicero quote.
Okay.
He reads a real, uh, quote, uh, his favorite quote, the man in the arena.
The, uh, uh, Teddy Roosevelt quote.
Yeah.
The bystanders and the, the, the, the reviewers, they matter not the man in the arena, he falters
and that is okay.
All right, Teddy.
That kind of shit.
He does, he reads that quote so much.
I think it's the only thing that gives his life meaning anymore.
Yeah.
Then he goes a little bit off track.
Okay.
So we got, we got Roosevelt.
We got Cicero.
Sure.
And now this, then a friend of mine sent me this text message this morning, subject forwarded
from a friend, a man named Tom Nicholson posted on Facebook, his account, the sports car that
he had just bought.
Now a man approached and told him that the money used to buy the car could have fed thousands
of less fortunate people, but the industry and the factories that built it also built
the factories that built the tractors, dumb ass, and also built the desire for people
to have nicer things that then to build a desire for better medicine and better technology
and a better future.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm not ready.
When he said his response to the man made him famous on the internet, read a story as
stated on Facebook below, a guy looked at my Corvette the other day and said, I wonder
how many people could have been fed for the money that sports car cost.
I replied, I'm not sure.
It fed a lot of families in Bowling Green, Kentucky who built it.
It fed the people who made the tires.
It fed the people who made the components that went into it.
It fed the people in the copper mine who mined the copper for the wires.
Alex is reading a chain email that your grandma would send you.
Yup.
This is nuts.
Uh, yeah, I believe this is the meme.
This is the same meme that it's like the military man was in the professor's room and the professor
was like, war is bad and the military man stood up and was like, I hate liberals.
And then it was outrageous.
Yeah.
I was like, I don't know.
Fuck off.
I thought this was supposed to be your last broadcast.
You're reading a chain email.
What is going on?
You know, I said this would be my last broadcast.
It really could, but I, it's just too heavy of a subject to say this is my last broadcast
and then do it here.
I'm just too tired already, but I'm going to write some notes tonight and tomorrow and
come on the Sunday show four to 6 PM and give you my view on the world.
So Sunday's going to be the last show.
So here we go.
Let's do the last show.
That's catnip to you, Dan.
It is.
Yes.
And that's why we have to include Sunday.
Of course.
But we're not done with Saturday yet.
Oh God.
Saturday ends in just a remarkable way for anybody who really thinks that Alex Jones
is like, sincerely religious, enjoy.
So I will end the transmission with this, the Lord's prayer.
Our father who art in heaven, hallowed be thy name, thy kingdom come, thy will be done
on earth as is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread and forgive us our debts as we forgive our debtors.
Lead us not into temptation, but deliver us from evil for thine is the kingdom and the
power of the glory forever.
Amen.
All right.
I appreciate the crew.
I appreciate their work.
I would just ask the listeners, I don't know how long we're going to be on air.
We got great products you need.
A lot of them are about to sell out winter sun for your immune system.
It's about to sell out.
I don't know about the Lord's prayer going that quickly into an ad, but Jesus went into
the temple and said, guys, get the fuck out of here.
I am selling t-shirts.
That's interesting because Alex is also selling a t-shirt and we have this new shirt designed
by one of our veteran friends that says trader Joe's and it's got Joe Biden with China and
Russia and Ukraine and Iran that he sold us out to says trader Joe's.
It's a fun shirt.
It's fun info wars.com in all sizes for adults and children.
And so I suggest you get the shirt at info war store.com.
It's a limited edition shirt and it lets us have a little bit of fun with the new puppet
dictator that they are installing.
That's why Steve Pacinich said, oh, it's my last show with you.
Cause it's the jokes on me.
He thinks, or he really believes what he's saying and he thinks he's going to get a job
here if somehow Biden designs and Trump's the president.
Well, yeah, he's got a job here if that moonshot happens.
Wow.
People want to listen to Pacinich anyways, interesting guy, but I think he's a little
more on the devil side of the angel side.
And I'll tell him that the way he talks down to people, the way those guys act like they're
the big gosh, they're in the system.
I'm the outsider.
I'm not the system.
That's who I'll always be because I'm here changing the system and that's my job.
Not to be part of the system.
Okay.
Again, great job to the crew.
He seems really mad.
I hate, I hate how comfortable these people are with demons existing on our plane and
running things to the point where you would be like, Hey, here's a fun t-shirt about this
demon that's running the world.
Yeah.
It is, it is a little bizarre for him to be like, we made this pun t-shirt so we could
have a little fun with the dictator.
It's the devil!
Yeah.
It's a satanic globalist dictator.
Oh man.
It's very weird.
That's so annoying.
A demon is an existential threat and you're like, eh, we'll make this fun little t-shirt.
So we're on to Sunday now.
Sure.
Last broadcast.
Final broadcast ever.
This bit is finally going to be put to rest.
Well, Alex can't get to it right away because there's news and he has a new group to blame
for what happened on the sixth.
Now we knew it was Antifa that told you that the day of the event.
After?
He told you who the operator was, where he came from in Utah, how he led over a hundred
Antifa addresses to Trump supporters.
A hundred?
When?
What?
I saw folks that didn't look like meth head Antifa on the videos.
I got there about 30 minutes after it started.
My employees.
That looked like right wingers, you know, that didn't look like they'd been grown in
their mother's basement.
It looked like I employed them.
It looked like that actually had some steak and potatoes and dumb little fight.
And sure as hell we identified who they were.
They were telling the crowd they were proud boys, but I checked them.
They weren't proud boys.
They were boogaloo's.
No.
Boogaloo boys going under the bus.
Slaps.
Slaps all around.
Yep.
Got to throw, uh, throw the boogaloo boys overboard.
Oh man.
I really like how Alex said boogaloo's there.
Boogaloo's.
He really, he really enjoyed it.
He really did.
Yeah.
So apparently this is how he's going to get around the fact that there were a bunch of
people who were oath keepers and are in trouble.
Yeah.
I assume Stuart Rhodes isn't on this Sunday broadcast.
Alex is going to soon be making up a story about Stuart Rhodes wife getting run over.
That's something about their dog.
Yeah.
Cause he's going to be in hiding.
Oh boy.
Anyway, Alex has a new video of the boogaloo boys.
Sure.
Oh God, this is so funny.
Like Alex, he is so bad at this, this whole thing.
And it's just so incredible because you try to get this out, the only place it gets out
is here.
Gateway Punnett's got an article about it, you name it.
But now it's very clear.
Wait, what?
I don't know what happened, but let's hit the first big one I just told you about.
You can bet your bottom dollar.
You'll be seeing this on Tucker Carlson tomorrow night because Tucker's the first one to send
it to me.
I don't leave it at that.
But you know, those that are in fight club, don't talk about flight club.
You know, the second rule of fight club, don't talk about fight club, but I send him stuff.
He sends me stuff.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's exactly against the rules of flight club.
I just, I just, that's
I don't know if I could come up with a more Alex Jones sentence than Tucker Carlson sent
me this clip.
I'm going to leave it there.
You just said everything.
Yep.
There is nothing more to say.
Nope.
This clip was sent to you by Tucker Carlson.
And if that's true, that tells us all we need to know about Tucker Carlson.
I'd love to get a comment from Tucker on that.
Absolutely.
Because I would imagine he would not admit to sending information to Alex.
I don't think he would like it.
On account of fight club being ruled as don't talk about fight club.
Yeah.
And so, I mean, I would imagine that he would say, no, I didn't.
And then Alex would have to wrestle with why no one will be publicly associated with him.
But they'll have his employees on their shows.
Yeah.
Anyway, at this point, we've now decided that the Boogaloo boys are going to be blamed for
anybody who appears to be right wing.
So we got Antifa for people who don't feel right wing and we got Boogaloo for people
who are wrong.
And QAnon for people who are weird.
Right.
Even though...
Sure.
Yeah.
Fine.
So now that that's settled, it's time to go back to familiar territory.
Let's play this next.
Over 7,000 strong migrant caravan inches closer to the US border as Biden vows to end Trump
asylum.
And this will be hundreds of thousands if not millions like hit Europe.
It's the UN plan.
As soon as they knew Biden would let him in, they began the march out of a UN camp in Honduras
into Guatemala.
Here it is.
So, yeah, the migrant caravan narratives are back.
Just, just, just do it.
Take four years off and run reruns where you just edit in Biden over Obama.
It's going to be the same thing.
There'll be a lot of similarities.
Think about how much time you can take off if you're just going to recycle the same shows.
Let's run reruns.
Yeah.
I really, I hope that you have drafts of all of your articles from the Obama days.
Save those Google docs.
Yeah.
So, yeah, man, migrants are coming to America and it's a UN plan that is war.
Why not?
War doesn't look like it did in Vietnam or Korea or the Gulf war.
This is modern war.
This is globalist war against the nation state.
So wear your mask and take your vaccines and roll over and die.
Remember this submission only makes it worse.
This is the end of America.
In the next two years, the country will not exist.
Guaranteed.
I mean, almost kind of feels like you're saying a good answer would be to storm the Capitol.
Yeah.
It does sound like we are at war.
And the enemy is demons trying to bring in immigrants.
That sounds some suspiciously like white nationalists talking.
Oh, big time.
It really feels like that's white nationalists.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Just part of the great replacement, the great migration, the UN uses people as a weapon.
They turn their food off.
They turn their jobs off.
You just think you're staying home for a few months and okay, it's a vacation.
No, it's collapsing the border.
When you become poor, the third world starves to death.
When the first world collapses, the third world dies.
How many times did I drill that into your head?
And now in Europe and now in the US everywhere, the borders are collapsing and giant third
world populations that don't have jobs and don't have infrastructures are coming here
to do what?
Collapse the infrastructure.
First they get you to not go to work.
Next they get you to say you're not essential.
Next they shut down main street.
Next they shut down the side streets.
Then they come in and tell you that you've got to open your borders up because the third
world starving to death and mass and then they get here and they're organized into political
weapons and political groups that from the beginning were trained for up to a year in
a UN refugee camp in Marxist, Leninist ideology projected by Mark Zuckerberg, projected by
Jeff Bezos, projected by all them on record commanding it.
That's quite a sentence.
Uh, yeah.
You know, you had any concerns that it might not be a white nationalist thing.
Yeah, I wasn't.
Certainly.
Really made it pretty clear there.
Let's put it bad.
Now I would say that, I mean, we've been over this territory so many times in the past when
he's gotten into the, the past caravan narratives.
Now this is, is very much based on a white identity fear.
Totally.
Now I would say that the behavior that he's engaging in and the way that he's framing
a lot of these ideas are very dangerous.
They are the sort of things that I do think sound a lot like incitement towards violence
of people that you suspect might be immigrants.
This is the takeover.
This is modern warfare using giant third world starving hordes that have been put in the
position of starvation or invasion and the UN is going to manage with the left every
damn bit of it and they're going to swamp your red city.
They're going to swamp your red town and they're going to take your ass over cause you're under
military attack.
I don't know what you would expect the outcome of that to be other than like rank xenophobia
and the possibility of violence directed towards people that are determined to be immigrants
whether or not they actually are.
Followed by a sign at every border that says whites only.
Yeah, it's, it's pretty bad.
It's not unfamiliar territory for Alex certainly, but I just constantly end up getting in a
position where like the world is really like serious.
You know, like I, I just don't understand how Alex can not be living in a world of reflection
about how serious things are and how unhinged people are and how, how dangerous we are in
a mis, like a misinformed populace.
People are living outside the prism of reality and I don't believe that he is a committed
believer of the things that are distorted reality.
Absolutely not.
He's, he's, he's monetized it.
He's exploiting the fact that other people are living in the fake reality that he preaches.
Yeah, I was going to say.
So he wouldn't be able to operate if he actually believed the things that he's saying.
Of course not.
He wouldn't be able to work.
He wouldn't be able to do any of this shit.
He would be dead by now because he would have stormed the Austin Capitol 10 years ago.
Totally.
It's not, it's, it's nonsense.
And I, I, I just constantly think like, well now we'll take it seriously.
And he just never does.
He never does.
No, it's, I mean, yeah, it's, it's hard to say any of that.
You know, when you ask like, how do these people not take it more seriously?
And it's just like scream.
I just, MONEY!
It's MONEY!
It can't matter that much though.
It does!
I guess.
It matters so fucking much.
Anyway, Alex gets to talking about how his enemies are ugly and they want to kill you
and he rambles a bit about this and then he's just, I don't know.
I would say that this is an incitement towards violence too.
And it's all weird, disreputable creatures because that's all they can get because there's
such virtue in humanity that no good looking, no well-spoken, no honorable man will even
serve this.
But it still doesn't matter because just because honorable men don't take the field and don't
join the enemy, the enemy goes great because you didn't join the fight.
And the fight is informational, it's cultural, it's spiritual, and it's about boycotting and
it's about information war and it is about noncompliance.
It is about civil disobedience and it won't matter.
They're going to hurt you so bad because they have a nature, like a child molester has got
to rape a child or a murderer has got to kill.
They just have this drive and this desire and they've got to have power over you and
they got to inject you and they got to shut your farm down and they got to shut your business
down and they got to see their stock go up at Amazon and they just got to do it and they
just got to put you down, they can't help it.
And they're going to go and go and go and go and go, they can't ever stop until you
stop them.
They can't stop until you stop them.
Wild.
Yeah.
It's not a good look overall.
You know what I've always thought?
I've always thought that the Democrats secret weapon could be governing the country well
and they refuse to do that for the same reason Alex refuses to take the six seriously.
Money!
If you material improved the lives of the, I just, I'm just running my, I'm losing my
mind.
Um, and if you think that Alex is solely driven by money, um, then I would suggest that this
must be what everyone keeps telling him to do more of.
Humpty Dumpty, Brian Stelter, we're like a hundred thousand viewers.
He led her bitches.
No one watches me.
Well, no kidding, dude.
You look like a child molester.
I'm not saying you are one, but I mean, I'm not letting you babysit my kids, bro.
You molest the truth.
I'm sorry.
Let's go back to them.
Both are happening.
Both are from the same platforms and the same pro-Trump media outlets.
Both are problematic.
Um, Chris, what do you say to the following?
We have to be clear eyed about what is a domestic terror threat, but also very careful not to
exaggerate it.
Not to overstate it.
We're on this again.
We're on it in 10 seconds.
There's a domestic terror threat.
It's called your speech.
Oh, they killed four Americans at the Capitol.
There was a riot, a small riot.
It's the worst thing since Pearl Harbor.
You're a child.
Well, we gotta be careful not to exaggerate it.
He plays all these games.
Let's go back to this shack of puss.
It's interesting because it was supposed to be his fake last show again, and it is fitting
that he would do an entire segment complaining about a Brian Stelter piece on his fake last
show because that should go in the time capsule.
Totally.
100%.
It has been a while since he's done one of these where he just plays a Brian Stelter
interview that's just uncontroversial.
Just a completely normal...
Yeah, I was listening to it and I was like, first of all, he's not saying the things that
Alex is responding to.
Second, it is not a hot take.
It is a pretty soft conversation about misinformation online.
You would take Brian Stelter to just a regular old like, hey, how have you been?
And turn it into a 10 minute long, this is why he's a demon who mouths the truth.
Look at his eyes.
Oh, God.
So anyway, for old time's sake, here's a minute 40 of Alex just getting really mad at Stelter.
We have to be clear eyed about what is a domestic terror threat, but also very careful not to
exaggerate it, not to overstate it, not to create undue fear in this country right now.
I think that's absolutely right.
We've got to be very careful here.
Just because someone may believe that the president did not win the election or the
president elect Biden did not win or that someone believes in QAnon doesn't mean that
they're going to go pick up arms and pause again.
It's like we're outlawing him questioning the election, but we don't put them in the
FEMA camp right away.
Did he say that?
Did anybody say that?
No.
What are we talking about here?
Oh, we don't.
We just shut them down.
And then, oh, we kill them.
This is all psychological scripts they're reading.
Super predatory, super dangerous, super evil.
Continue.
Is that possible, Alex?
Will there ever be a solution, a real clear, full solution to this information crisis that
has been perpetuated in my view by platforms like the one you're used to work face?
Is there a final solution, he's asking?
Like, how do we deal with these people that, like, you know, saw them with suitcases in
Georgia, pulling them out and closing things and saying the water main broke and then all
these Biden votes come in and it happened and all, you know, Biden can't get 20 people
that Trump gets a million.
But, you know, what do we do?
What's the solution?
We're going to come back.
I'm going to be nice.
I'm going to play the clip unedited because by edited, I'm jumping in.
I'm talking over.
It's just it's hard to look at someone with no viewers, but it doesn't matter.
It's what the banks.
They know that the globalist word is through Stelter.
That's Jeff Zucker.
And so here is this, this, this, this Hitler, this Stalin, this Mao.
I mean, they call us that he's the one trying to stealth everybody.
It's Brian Stelter.
He's Hitler.
I'm not.
Look, I'm not saying he's not a public figure or he hasn't accomplished anything.
I'm just saying he's Brian Stelter.
Yeah, he's Hitler.
He's Brian Stelter is the voice of the globalists.
Really?
The voice of the globalists, Brian Stelter.
I hate how small potatoes everybody who's a big deal is to these people.
I think it's fascinating because, you know, like if this is the pretend last show, it
makes sense.
I mean, like all day, Alex hates Brian Stelter for reasons that I can't quite figure out,
except that Brian Stelter has mentioned Alex a couple of times and he comes off as a less
than Alex's definition of masculine man.
Sure.
And I think that that bothers Alex on some level.
Right.
It feels like he's been emasculated by a less masculine man in Alex's eyes.
And just saying that Alex is a dumb-dumb.
And because I don't think that Brian Stelter lets Alex live in his mind, whereas Alex is
clearly thinking about Brian Stelter all the time.
All the time.
He's curious about him.
Yeah, he hate watches Brian Stelter so much.
He has to.
And you see this, like, just to come out on the show, these outbursts, it's amazing.
I'm so glad that I've passed my Friedersdorf stage.
Yeah, well, you had to get it out of your system.
I had my time and now it's over.
You processed it.
Yeah.
Unhealthy, healthy.
Yeah, yeah, I got through it.
Yeah.
Yes.
So Alex comes back from break and he promises, I'm not going to interrupt now.
And they're just, I mean, this is so textbook 1984 and you're just watching these criminals
talk about it, but I'm not going to interrupt them.
Just go ahead and play it unedited.
Just play a few minutes of this.
I'm going to try to shut up.
Go ahead.
Five.
We have to work on the broader disinformation problem to try to turn down the anger that
you see from that huge percentage of Republicans who believe that the election was stolen.
It's yeah.
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
Ooh.
I was really close.
It was 10 seconds.
I should have done the countdown.
So he's unsuccessful.
He just, oh God, is so much Stelter.
So he's talking about, uh, how like we're at war to not be enslaved.
Jesus.
There comes a point when powerful organizations and groups decide to make their move, no matter
what happens, they're committed to the fight.
It has a name.
It's called war.
We are now under open globalist attack.
The United States did not see the sneak attack.
I tried to warm people for decades.
People going back to Barry Goldwater, Cleon scouts, and some of the others warned before
I was even born, but Americans were arrogant.
They believed that we were so strong, we could not fall.
We had major rot from within, and now we face the prospect of slavery and massive persecution
and the full thrust of the globalist attack at levels never before seen.
That's why tomorrow I'm going to do a special transmission.
Don't you fucking dare.
Is this Alex Jones' last broadcast?
Because every day now is precious.
Go fuck yourself, man.
I'm not doing this.
I'm not going to be strong along by the likes of you.
I want to start fires.
I don't want to start building fires.
I want to start large brush fires just in the street, just to let everyone know what
is happening.
Yeah.
Alex is doing another viral broadcast.
Like I'm sending smoke signals up.
There's too many people who are unaware that he is doing this again.
It's so annoying.
I need someone to know that he is doing this again.
It's so annoying, too, because he did nothing but waste time on this Sunday show.
There's so much just like, it's the Boogaloo Boys.
That's who we don't like now.
Tucker Carlson's my source.
Whoops, Fight Club.
Yeah.
And then yelling about Stelter.
Stelter.
Helter Stelter hate.
I got blisters on my fingers.
Oh my god.
Yep.
I'm so tired, dude.
There's this last clip here from Sunday is fitting.
This is kind of how Alex wraps up the show.
And I will say that it is exciting for me because now on Friday, on our show, we will
finally get his actual- Sure, sure we will.
Of course.
Last episode.
Yeah.
But here's how Alex goes out on the seventh.
Just perfect.
But I'll just recap what we started the show with before I have this important information.
We know the Boogaloo's left this group with a few hundred people, staged the attack.
Only the Q folks were dumb enough to go in to get media attention.
And your employees.
It was Q people that went in non-violently to be set up and arrested.
They didn't arrest the Boogaloo's.
When they've arrested Antifa, they're released later.
They did their job well.
They set up America.
Trump knew his supporters were patriotic and non-violent.
He said be non-violent.
He didn't incite anything.
They went down there to say, we see the election fraud.
We have the numbers to show it.
Trump fought back.
He did the right thing.
He didn't roll over.
He didn't submit.
If you want to keep us on air, go to mfoarstore.com and get t-shirts, books, films, got a bunch
of supplements that are about to sell out that are great for your immune system and
your body.
X2, X3, super male vitality, DNA force plus.
They're all there at mfoarstore.com.
But separately, this is new world order.
This is 2020.
I remember reading when I was 21 years old, 2020 in congressional record, I was into that
stuff back then.
It was so interesting.
So again, here we are.
Every generation goes through something.
Every third generation goes into something really big.
We're going through it right now.
So I want to thank the crew for their great job.
There is this amazingly important report from a major pop artist exposing chemtrails and
country clubs.
Don't do it.
I hope that you will share.
Chemtrails over the country club video.
Just don't do it.
It's posted to band.video.
Here it is.
That's amazing.
He introduces Glennon Del Rey's video for chemtrails at the country club as a report.
That's a very important report, this music video.
He used a lot of words to say that the Patriot movement is filled with stupid gullible cowards,
but I understand why he tells his version of the story.
It's far more exciting than saying that the Patriot movement is a bunch of stupid gullible
cowards.
Well, that's what Pete Santilli would say.
Yeah.
Man.
I love, I want to see what the most trivial thing Alex would call an important report
is.
We are fighting demons who are overthrowing the United States Republic, destroying the
constitution.
We need upwards of two amendments now, and I will tell you this right now.
We're going to go out to our special report.
That's right.
It is a Looney Tunes cartoon.
Here we go.
From our new reporter here at Infowars, Lana Del Rey.
Jesus.
God, what a ride.
What is happening?
I don't know.
Are we, are we fake or is he fake?
I can't tell anymore.
I just don't know.
Yeah.
I don't feel like I learned much from this.
I learned a lot about history.
Yeah.
I learned a lot about World War II, Dan.
I mean, I'm glad, I'm glad I got the benefit of his thousands of books.
Totally.
It's nice to see multiple instances of him just reading Wikipedia pages poorly.
Yeah.
God, this is dumb.
This show is so dumb.
I'm really excited for Friday, though, because I do think...
Well, it's his last broadcast.
Well, I mean, can't wait for the second last broadcast.
Can't wait for the second last broadcast.
But it'll be better than the November 24th, for sure.
Well, I would hope so.
Can't be worse than that.
He's had time to think about it.
Yeah.
And multiple false starts.
Yes.
Yeah.
And I just think there will be something interesting on the day of the inauguration.
Like I hope that everything goes smoothly in the world.
You know, we're recording this on Tuesday, it comes out on Wednesday.
I hope it's an uneventful day by and large.
But I also hope that Alex cries or something.
Sure.
I hope he throws a hatchet or something.
Yeah.
Like, I hope there's something interesting and it's not just mopey Alex.
Yeah, he's gotta bring something.
There's potential for, like, some real performance.
And I hope we see something as opposed to nothing.
But I hope that the something that we see isn't this, like...
That Sunday show, the hard shift into immigrant bashing is really not good.
I know that that's a normal thing for Alex, but it had been absent for a little while.
Or at least on the back burner.
Really don't like to see it coming forward again.
It's really annoying.
Yeah, the full, let's direct our attention away from all Democrats directly towards minorities
of any shape, specifically ones that aren't white, is normal.
But it was nice whenever they just wanted to kill us all equally, you know?
There was a feeling of, yeah, I don't know.
Camaraderie?
Yeah, I guess.
I don't know.
Anyway, Jordan, we will be back.
But until then, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
You bet.
We're on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at Knowledge Fight and I go to bed Jordan.
We're also on Facebook.
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work right now.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZXClark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I'm telling Mike Adams to grow the fuck up.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.