["Radio, Radio, Radio, Radio, Radio, Radio, Radio"]
N-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-knowledge fight.
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com. It's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying we are the bad guys.
Dan and Jordan, Knowledgefight.
Riddle, riddle, riddle, riddle.
I need, I need money.
Andy and Kansas, riddle, riddle.
Andy you're, stop it.
Andy and Kansas.
Riddle, riddle, riddle.
It's time to pray.
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air. Thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a true Simpler, I'm a huge fan.
I love your world.
Knowledgefight.
N-n-n-n-n-n-n-knowledgefight.com.
I love you. Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fat, I'm Dan. I'm Jordan. We're a couple dudes, I like to sit around and drink novelty beverages and talk just a touch about Alex Jones. Just like a sprinkling to taste.
I would say a smidge even. I would go so far as to say a smidge. Like pepper in a recipe. Yeah, yeah, yeah. A sprinkle or perhaps a toss. A dusting of Alex. Indeed, just a hair. How are you doing Jordan?
I'm subverting the form. I like it, I like it. How are you doing? Good. I have a question for you. What's that? What is your bright spot today? My bright spot today Jordan is I, first of all, I accept this already, don't fucking, I don't care, don't point a finger at me.
This is preemptive defensiveness Dan, we've talked about this. It is. I'm a sucker for like Lovecraft themed horror video games. Of course. Like storytelling, that sort of thing. Eternal Darkness is one of my favorite video games of all time. Of course. It's great.
Whenever we played Mansions of Madness together you get really into it. It's fantastic. I insist on holding the iPad so I can read the story. You love reading it to us? Yeah, you've got the whole thing. Doing the voice of the Lovecraftian narrator. Of course.
I love it and so I was looking around for a cheap game. Bright Spots have just become video game reviews. At this point. I was looking for something in the five dollar range as I was trying to expand my horizons and I saw one called Lovecraft's Untold Stories.
And I'm like, well, I'm a mark. I'm buying this. So I bought it. I'll send you a thousand dollars in the hopes of getting five thousand in return. If the letter is not from a Nigerian prince but it's from someone in Innsmouth then maybe, maybe I'm writing back. Miskatonic University would like a donation of your generous service. No, I'm an alum.
I got it and I was really enjoying it and like the first level of it was pretty fun and then it got absurdly hard in the second level. Oh no. It got like unfair levels of heart. Okay. And I actually looked into it because I was like, this can't be right. Something's wrong. Right, right, right. And a bunch of the reviews online were all just like, this game is. This game gets unfairly hard at the second level.
It's just like, this is not balanced. And it's true. Yeah. But it was also like not impossible. Sure. It was just really hard. Right, right, right, right. And I kind of, I was playing around with it a little bit and here's the bright spot was that I didn't back down to the difficulty. Nice.
I kept trying and I learned and I realized like this is kind of how it used to be with video games. Oh totally. Like if you were playing Mega Man 2 that was fucking hard. It was impossible to do. It was so hard. Yeah. It has that sort of difficulty. Yeah. It's just like, it's really, it's, it's, it's fun. I enjoy it. Anyway. That's awesome. I did beat the second level. Love it. Love it. Congratulations. I felt like it was an actual achievement. Just something that I have not felt a ton in video games. Yeah. It's been a while.
Yeah. A lot of these open world games that I enjoy are like, yeah, you get things done and maybe you beat a castle in a, or a, you know, a monastery in Assassin's Creed. And it's difficult. It can be. Yeah. But it's not hard. Yeah. It doesn't, it doesn't feel like, wow, I did that. Yeah. That second level. I fucking did that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And it feels, yeah, achievement. That's so cool. Yeah. How about you?
Uh, my bright spot, Dan, may sound counterintuitive, but I mean this wholeheartedly as a bright spot. Okay. My bright spot is failure. Oh. Uh, I, as you know. In a certain way, so was mine. Yeah. Well, I think that is kind of the, no, I think we share this. Uh, as you know, I started trying to stream a little bit of video games on Twitch. Yeah. And, uh, it has gone disastrous. People had asked what your channel is. I don't know if you gave the address. Oh, I haven't. It's, uh, it's Twitch TV, JB Holmes 3209.
Okay. Yeah. That was the important thing. You get to find it. Sure. Well, there's that. I appreciate that not many people have found it because it has gone disastrously every time. Uh, the audio issues. It's a learning thing. Yeah. And it's, it's really, it's really fascinating cause it's fun to teach myself new stuff at 33. Like I've never touched the software on this before. I've never done all that stuff. It's fun to learn all the things that I'm terrible at and require new equipment for and all that stuff.
And it reminded me of when I started doing standup of just like I failed for two years straight and as I'm doing this, I was so frustrated because I couldn't figure it out properly and I felt like I was disappointing the people who actually came to see it and I was really grateful to them and I wanted to do a good job for them and I failed miserably.
And then I remembered I can fail so hard for so long and then eventually I got good at it to the point where I think I can do the same thing here. I mean, we failed quite a while doing this podcast. Totally, totally. Our streams did not always go.
And now I think maybe you're getting a greater appreciation for why I have such a difficult time with being like, yeah, let's get back to doing live stream. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I don't want, I have so many headaches. I get it. But I wish you luck with that. I know you'll get it figured out and it'll be great and people will have fun watching the streams.
I'm just excited because it also means that I'm trying new things, you know, and you can't expect to just be good out of the gate at new things. No, that's true. Yeah, it's been really good and humbling and I've appreciated it a lot.
This is your second level of Lovecraft's Untold Stories. Exactly what it is. Challenging, maybe unfair. That's a little unfairly hard. 33 year old people anymore aren't supposed to be able to use computers. I think that's the rule.
So Jordan, today we have an unexpected twist. Oh no. Alex is out of studio. No. On our last episode on Wednesday, I had said that today we were going to be listening to the end of Trump's presidency and inauguration day on Alex's show and I cannot deliver that.
And I'll explain why. First reason. Alex's fake last episode thing carried over into this episode. Oh no. No, because you knew that. Oh, of course. On our last episode, when we talked about the 17th, Alex was saying tomorrow will be my fake last episode. No, of course.
And so that was something that I couldn't not follow the thread of. Naturally. Then it turned out that on inauguration day, it was an all day affair. Right. So that's going to have to be on Monday. Okay. We're going to be covering January 20th on Monday. Today we're going to be talking about the 18th and the 19th, 2021. Blackjack. Blackjack, baby!
No. End of show. No, baby. All right. And yeah, so we'll get to the inauguration on Monday. I just need a bit more time to prepare that because it's a lot of stuff to go through. A lot of disappointment. You don't have to listen to 12 hours. Well, I don't have to listen to all of it. Harrison Smith's hosting, I'm sure, a good bit of it. The Capitol has unfallen. Oh no. The Capitol is back in the arms of the globalists. Shit.
So before we get down to business on today's episode, though, where we witnessed the last proper shows of the Trump time. Yes, even though there's two of them. Yeah, the 18th and the 19th. Yes. The last days when Trump could do something weird while Alex is on air. Before we get down to that, though, let's take a moment to say thank you to some folks who have signed up and are supporting the show. Oh, that's a great idea.
So first, Nathan S. Thank you so much. You're now Policy Wonk. I'm a policy wonk. Thank you, Nathan. Next, Disgruntled Honey Bee. Thank you so much. You are now Policy Wonk. I'm a policy wonk. Thank you very much. Disgruntled Honey Bee. Thank you. Next, Dave Endor's Donation Drive. Thank you so much. You are now a policy wonk. I'm a policy wonk. Oh, that's a reference to my book, Dave Endor's Donation Drive. Oh, that's cute. Thank you. Thank you. Next, Nicholas L. and that's N-I-K-O-L-A-U-S. For my money, probably the best one.
Nicholas. Nicholas. Nicholas. Nicholas. Thank you so much. You are now policy wonk. I'm a policy wonk. Thank you very much, Nicholas. Thank you next, Lee Green. Thank you so much. You are now a policy wonk. I'm a policy wonk. Thanks, Lee Green.
They go. Next, Kate K. Thank you so much. You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, Kate.
They go. Next, Thomas B. Thank you so much. You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Tommy B.
And 1-800-NW-HOGS. Thank you so much. You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, 1-800-NW-HOGS.
And finally, I'd like to say thank you to a couple of people who donated on Elevated Love and we appreciate that very much.
So first, Derek and that's spelled D-A-R-R-I-C-K. It's my money, the second best way to spell Derek.
That's pretty great.
It's up there. Maybe it's the best. I don't know.
It's pretty up there.
Thank you so much. You are now a technocrat.
And the Waffle Witch. Thank you so much. You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate. That's fantastic. Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
We gotta go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, alright?
Let's just get down to business. We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much, Derek, and thank you so much to the Waffle Witch.
Yes, thank you very much to the both of you.
You know, a way you can blow people's minds is waffles.
Yes, that's true.
People don't realize how easy they are to make.
They're delicious, too.
And they're so cheap. Like, make a waffle iron.
Yeah.
Five bucks, probably.
Also, Waffle Witch should be in a Miyazaki movie, if not already.
And I would pay a lot to see it.
I might have to fight the Waffle Witch and love her kinds of untold stories.
That's level four. Super unfair.
So, Jordan, here's an out of context drop from today's show.
I'm at war with these people, not just on air.
I'm constantly fighting them, and I'm not special.
I'm just not dead inside.
I will never let you eat Satan get me.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
He always sounds exactly like the people that he says are demons.
Yeah, yeah.
I just, you know, I don't know.
It's hard to take someone seriously when they're like,
I'm fighting the demons all the time.
Yes, all the time.
Yeah.
All the time.
Nonstop.
A little silly.
My wife gets to go play tennis with her instructor,
and I'm out here fighting demons all the time.
Yeah.
It's brutal.
It's not fair.
Yeah.
So we start on the 18th, and of course, on the 17th,
Alex had decided he was going to do his last show.
Sure.
Which he, again, already did last November.
Right.
This is between his third and fifth last show.
Somewhere in that range.
He decided on Saturday that he was going to do the last broadcast
as he was in the middle of a show.
So him and Mike Adams did a very dramatic show.
Oh, yeah.
I assume Mike Adams can never come back on.
He was on the last broadcast.
I mean, for good taste's sake, he can't.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He already gave his farewell address.
So on that Saturday, Alex got distracted by Robert Barnes,
the lawyer extraordinaire, coming in to yell about QAnon.
Sure.
And then Alex realized, like,
ah, I can't do it today.
I'm going to do it tomorrow.
So on Sunday, he came in, did not do it.
Went hot for it.
Decided to point the finger at the Boogaloo Boys.
Right.
For the Capitol storming.
Well, you got to do something.
And then he's like, ah, I can't handle it.
I'll do it tomorrow.
So the 18th, Monday, is in theory supposed to be the last show.
The last show ever.
Right.
The final broadcast.
Great.
Yeah.
We're doing it.
Here's where we start.
New Jersey, where they tried to bankrupt that big successful gym,
and they were starting to win in court.
So the state just seized $150,000 every dime the company had to pay payroll
and to pay for the bill on the building and to pay for the insurance.
They barely had enough money to stay open,
and now they're going to have to close.
But they're starting to get cash donations.
And all they got to do is call themselves a church or BLM,
then they'll be protected under the First Amendment.
And all of us should say, we're part of the Church of Freedom.
In fact, I really think I'm going to incorporate a church.
All I got to do is believe in freedom and a pro-human future,
and you can be part of it.
Okay.
That was inevitable.
Yeah.
It was about time.
Honestly, this has taken too long to go full cult.
Basically.
Yeah.
This is a church.
Why not?
Yeah.
No, I've literally shit all over the Satanists for not having a church,
and they shouldn't have the protections of the First Amendment.
But...
He really screwed up not doing this when Trump was in office.
Totally.
Because Trump wasn't going to prosecute churches for 501c3 violations,
but that might change.
That might go back now to where you can't do political organizing
in the guise of a church.
I very much doubt it.
So yeah, Alex doesn't want to pay taxes.
No.
That's basically the game here.
Yeah.
And yeah, finally getting around to it.
I'm going to make a church.
You're already a church.
I don't know why Wesley Snipes never did the Church of Blade,
because I would have joined the Church of Blade.
Sure.
I don't know how Alex isn't already a church.
That's a good point.
He constantly talks about God,
and this show is a deeply religious thing where he thinks he's fighting demons all day.
I don't know.
It's either science fiction or religion, one of the two.
Both of which could be a church.
Because it ain't news and it ain't politics.
Hey, if Elrond can do it.
So Jordan, I don't know if you know this, but America is dead.
Fair.
It didn't die on the inauguration.
Oh, that's good.
And that's only because Alex misspeaks.
Okay.
You can definitely put on the tombstone,
the United States of America,
born July 4th, 1776.
Not true.
Died of treason.
Died of infiltration.
Died of Satanism.
January 21st.
The year 2020.
Whoops.
Still writing July on my checks.
Wow, still writing July on those checks.
Man.
So I guess America's been dead for a year.
And see, this is why you gotta double check before you put the death date on the tombstone.
Yeah, of course.
Because that's in rock.
Yeah.
America died before Bernie had to drop out of the race.
We couldn't even get a real socialist to kill America.
I know that you were taking issue with him saying, you know, America was born July 4th, 1776.
Sure.
And I don't want to parse that right now.
I have no interest in parsing that ever.
What I do want to talk about is that this seems to imply that Alex doesn't believe that life begins at conception.
It seems to me that this is an indication that birth is when life begins.
If you're pro-nation, you're pro-choice.
I think that's the reality.
Or else you have to celebrate the Independence Day, the day when someone came up with the idea to have a country.
Yeah.
1617, somebody was like, man, I think we can do it.
Or maybe a thousand years before that, Eric the Red is out here.
Man, I think these states should be united.
Or just even the day that the beginning of the protesting against the crown began in the colonies.
Then, I don't know.
Anyway, I just thought that was kind of funny.
America wasn't born when it became a twinkle in the eye of some revolutionary.
I might have been fairly bored by Alex at the beginning of this episode.
Sure, sure.
And so I was having thoughts like that.
Sure, you're having fun thoughts.
Yeah.
So Alex decides to talk about the One Ring.
That's good.
Sure.
Yeah.
The globalists, apparently they all want power in the rings that Sauron makes.
Naturally.
Give power to the ten kings with the ten rings.
Nine rings.
Whatever.
But there's one to rule them.
So that's the ten.
Well, yes.
But there's three for the elven lords.
Right.
Seven for the dwarf lords.
I understand.
Okay.
Alex gives himself chills talking about this.
Okay, okay.
And so the globalist AI system is the enemy that is parasitically sucking the U.S. dry.
And there's only a competition with globalists about who gets the AI takeover.
It'll be China's AI or the U.S. AI, but it's Satan's plan that it's really all the same
AI.
The Lord of the Rings allegory.
Ten rings given to ten kings of the earth who above all seek power.
It's a Christian allegory.
Tolkien said this about what he experienced.
He specifically said it was not.
A professor at the highest levels of the insider knowledge.
Went out of his way.
And so ten rings are given to ten kings for power.
But when they take the power, they actually become enslaved.
And there's one secret ring that controls them all.
That's Satan.
Not secret.
That's a spiritual element.
So, he's got chills.
I believe it's nine rings given to mortal men.
Doomed to die.
Literally in the poem.
Yeah.
You make a good point about Tolkien really resisting allegory as well.
Went hard on it.
People were like, it's about the nuclear bomb, right?
And he was like, oh, that's interesting.
No.
Yeah.
He did say that it was a religious story.
You know, it was a Christian story.
Sure.
Unintentionally at first and then intentionally upon reflection.
Who's Jesus' hobbit friends?
Who's Jesus' pippin?
Pippin?
That would be Bartholomew.
I think that's a good answer.
Yeah.
I just love it anytime Alex is talking and he impresses himself or he freaks himself
out.
Ooh, got chills.
Oh, man.
Ooh.
I nailed that.
I absolutely got that one perfect.
One ring?
Satan.
Yeah.
Solved that problem.
And there's still going on about how there's in the riot at the Capitol before the storming
of January 6th, there were agents.
Sure.
Right?
Everybody who might be inconvenient for him.
Right.
Probably an agent.
That's Aragorn.
But he can tell.
Alex can tell.
Sure.
He has a special sense for this.
I mean, you've got FBI agents in there running this damn thing.
God, we're in so much trouble.
And again, I'm not saying those guys, the agents, the guys with the Black Lives Matter
and the Antifa shirts, it's the video you showed later of the people in full camo and
full mask that are definitely got squared away there.
And I can just tell you learn things, just look at them instantly.
You know what's going on.
This just makes me think of the time that we spent listening to the immediate aftermath
of the Boston bombing.
Yeah, totally.
Whenever Alex was like, I can tell who everybody is just by looking at them.
Yeah.
Just by looking at the way they're standing and I know this guy's hostage rescue team
all over.
Yeah.
You don't know shit.
Here's my...
I think Alex proves that the blood of Numenor has grown thin.
Come on, man.
All right.
How many more do I got?
I think you got way more, but I don't know how much patience I got.
You don't want any more?
No.
Blackjack.
Oh boy.
Okay.
So yeah, I mean, the people that he's talking about, I think, I don't know what the video
he's referring to, but I assume based on the descriptions, probably the Oathkeeper folks
who were there.
Yeah, it has to.
Yeah.
But now it would be as good a time as any to talk about how Joe Biggs, former Infor's
employee, Rambo Joe Biggs, he going to prison.
Yeah.
Hilarious.
He's going to prison hard.
For a while.
Yeah.
Unless he flips on a lot of more important people.
And I don't even know.
I don't even know if that's going to do much.
I doubt it.
Who's more important than him?
He's like second in command of the Proud Boys.
Yeah, that one's pretty easy to pick out.
I don't know.
What if he, I mean, I assume he can flip on some congressmen on account of them committing
the crimes.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I don't know what he knows or what he's up to, but it's interesting to see this path
that he's gone from.
Ding dong working at Infowars trying to get Pizzagate going to the guy who gets Ted Cruz
to finally go to prison.
It's an interesting path.
Also just before we got on air here today, on air, what the fuck am I talking about?
No idea.
Before we got on these mics, there was a news story that was breaking about William Watson,
who's a guy who had a big beard, was pictured at the Capitol with, along with Q shaman.
And a lot of the headlines were really stressing that he went to the Capitol because Alex told
him to.
Sure.
Because people are making more out of that than they should.
I don't think you can do much with that.
No.
I mean like, but I saw some people tweeting things to the effect of like, Alex ordered
him to go.
Sure.
And even the Raw Story article about it, the phrasing of it was a little bit iffy.
Yeah.
Because as far as I can tell from the actual information, he just said that he knew that
there was a rally at the Capitol because Alex had said, meet there at one, which you got
to assume is Alex wanting people to go to the stage that he was conceivably going to
be having a rally at.
It would be nice, and we've referenced this before, it would be nice if before people
ran with stories, they would at least like send you an email.
But I mean, I imagine that the reason they don't is because you would be like, hey, could
you add more nuance?
And they'd be like, more nuance means fewer clicks, so we're not going to talk to Dan.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know if I could even be of much help with this, but I wish people would
recognize that like the more you put Alex in the crosshairs for this, when it's something
like what you see in those stories about this guy, the more it works in Alex's favor.
They're trying to set me up for this.
And yeah, you shouldn't do things like that.
They play into his- No, you wind up not just letting him off
the hook, but doing a, I would call it pulling a Rogan, where you accidentally give him more
credibility than he by any means deserves.
You also write him a new narrative.
Yeah.
I mean, really, this is like a Son of Sam kind of stuff where it's like, oh, you can't
blame the dog.
You know what I'm saying?
Or was that him?
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure the dog who was in, yeah, Satan and stuff.
Alex is just Satan for this guy.
No.
The ring is Satan.
Ah, that's fair.
So I hated the beginning of this show.
It was very boring.
There was nothing going on.
And thankfully, about an hour in, hour and 10, and Alex condenses what he's been talking
about for the last hour.
Okay, good.
The whole last hour could have been condensed into two minutes.
It's confirmed- The Alex Jones story.
The deep state ran the Boogaloo boys via the Southern Poverty Law Center, ADL and the FBI.
No.
You're back.
To protect the Capitol.
They've all bragged about it with Antifa.
They've been protected.
When they were arrested, they were released.
It's been confirmed, apparently.
That is a fair condensing of most of what he spent all of his time talking about.
But he didn't prove any of this.
He hasn't confirmed any of it.
He just believes that saying something repeatedly is the same thing as confirming it.
Hey, how about this?
How about fuck your William Watson article, and instead, here's your article.
Alex doesn't get to do this.
And all you do is go through what he did on the sixth, and how he lied about it immediately,
and how he's lying about it now, and how we don't get to let this go.
He doesn't get to go on and talk about how there's going to be problems, and everybody's
going to have their balls caught off.
He has to say, I lied to you, and I was full of shit, and everybody should write an article
about that.
And also, there's a written article that in the lead mentions that he believes he's constantly
fighting demons.
And he believes he's constantly fighting demons.
Yes.
So he had the FBI, and through the Southern Poverty Law Center and the ADL, they were
running the Boogaloo Boys to do all this and get the storming going.
Weird, they were buddies.
And then you had QAnon people who were patsies, apparently.
They were just there to be a spectacle.
And we walked right into a trap.
They did stand down.
They ushered the Q people, who were not violent, in to be killed and in to be arrested as sacrificial
dummies, just like in Spies Like Us, a great comedy, but very accurate.
You're like, oh, we're going to accelerate you guys to be frontline spies.
You did that.
With like two weeks training, yeah.
And they put them in as decoys.
Of course, they ended up doing a better job than the actual spies, which is how it actually
works.
Because real people get real stuff done, not you mentally ill sicko freaks that have Asperger's
or whatever.
Satanic Asperger's.
I don't mean Asperger's or Satanic.
I mean a form of it that's like Satanic.
Disgusting.
That was weird.
So then you're saying that they did it.
I don't know.
He's saying that the real people at the Patriots did everything.
I think he watched Spies Like Us recently.
I think maybe his kids are coming to such an age that you've got to get into some of
those classic comedies.
That's fair.
Yeah.
So I think one of the things that I'm noticing about Alex around this time is that it's pretty
much just, it's very Doom filled.
It's very much the country is no more.
Well, I mean, in his cosmology, the devil has taken over the United States.
So you would expect that kind of thing.
Yeah.
But you would expect it to be in that language.
The devil is in charge.
Well, yeah.
He's been yelling about it for a long time.
Yeah.
But instead it kind of comes in this form and it's like, this is just going to incite
people to impotent violence.
We're going to come back and talk more about what you're witnessing there in our former
Capitol now under globalist control.
We are now officially occupied.
Joe Biden will be installed in about 46 hours as the first dictator of the United States.
Okay.
And then we'll all be shut down after that.
Shouldn't he think FDR was the first dictator of the United States?
I managed to avoid a spit take.
Yeah.
I appreciate that.
That was going to go straight at you.
Yeah.
That doesn't even fit with his own ideas.
No, no.
But DC is the former Capitol.
We're now under complete occupation.
Biden is a dictator.
Naturally.
It's all like, okay, well, what has your show for 25 fucking years suggested people do when
those circumstances are achieved?
Yeah.
Well, I think you know.
So there's a couple of days left for Trump to be in office.
Sure.
He's got criminals to say you can go free.
Well, actually, Alex has a prediction about that.
Oh, strange.
And I think with this type of action, Trump is going to pardon Julian Assange tomorrow.
I'm predicting that right now.
My gut tells me that Trump's good and the Trump at the final crucible do the right thing.
Ooh, snake eyes came up just short on my prediction note.
Headline, you don't get to do this.
Alex, probably very disappointed about that.
Yeah.
Why did he think that would happen?
I don't know.
Probably because it's what his audience wants to hear.
Well, that's fair.
So Alex is getting, we heard on that Sunday show, he's getting back into the migrant caravan
fear based narratives.
Naturally.
And one of the things that I've noticed about him is he has an absolute inability to estimate
sizes of groups.
Yeah.
He will say like 100,000 people is 10 million.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You ever do those, how many gumballs in this jar?
He guesses a million every time.
Or seven.
Yeah.
He's not good at estimating.
No, no, no.
He's saying, he's looking at a picture of like a caravan of migrants and he's just like,
oh, that's so many more people.
And if you don't admit it's the end of America, it will be.
By admitting we're under attack, by admitting this is globalist, by admitting that they've
collapsed the third world with the COVID lockdowns and now the UN has set up giant refugee centers
to make the hundreds of thousands that caravan here a few years ago that Trump stopped look
like insignificant.
Let's go ahead for radio listeners, any viewers can see this, roll that little newscast about
the 7,000 folks that is the 7,000.
Let me give you a newsflash.
It's 50,000.
I've seen the footage and that's just the first group, the UN trains, they've got debit
cards paid for by the state department.
Trump cut off the money, but now they do it directly from Soros and I'm gonna go to your
phone calls, but that's what's happening.
Prove it.
Prove any of that shit.
Anyway, look, I noticed this and I hate it.
It sucks, but I think that these sorts of stories really get under Alex's skin more
than a lot of other ones because he gets really mad for a large chunk of this episode.
Al, the border's close to his home and he's a racist.
The end.
He's really, really like just down and like he freaks out quite a bit.
And that does get- Might have to see two more Muslims than I'm
used to.
At the pool supply shop.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
So he addresses the idea that this was gonna be his last show and then he just goes downhill
from there.
Okay.
All right.
I'm gonna go to break and I promise for at least four segments, three segments, I'm gonna
go write the calls.
I'm gonna go to Michael, Steve, John, Christian, Houston, Scott, Preston, Izzy, Richard and
others.
And listen, I want to explain something here to everybody.
Okay?
It might seem really irritable and mad it's not with the crew.
I'm just done with all this.
And I meant to come here today and say this is my last broadcast.
And by that, I'm gonna keep doing shows.
But I mean, you understand folks, I believe they're gonna shut everything down the next
few months.
They're gonna blow up federal buildings.
They're gonna put poison in water supplies.
I mean, it's over.
You understand?
Your only shot you've got is realizing that we're screwed.
Your candy ass church isn't gonna do it.
Your candy ass boss isn't gonna do it.
We're a trained group of monkeys in this country.
We're not what Americans used to be.
We're not rugged individualists.
We don't stand up for the Bill of Rights and Constitution.
We're a joke, okay?
So he's in a bad mood.
Yeah.
That bad mood has started after covering this story about the migrants.
And it turns pretty fucking extreme.
I mean, he's talking about blowing up federal buildings, poisoning the water supply and
like...
I don't think even Stone Cold called churches candy asses.
No, and it was The Rock who called people candy asses.
Oh, I apologize.
I apologize for not getting famous Republican The Rock.
You did speak at the RNC.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, so Alex goes from there, how they're gonna do all this shit.
Yeah, we're all just gonna let The Rock get away with that, right?
Everybody's just agreed, like, eh, don't worry about it.
Sure, The Rock endorsed all of the horrifying things, but we'll still let him be a movie
star.
I mean, sure, I don't know what his politics are anymore.
Sure.
And I don't know what...
I don't know how...
Look, Vince McMahon is a lunatic.
Yeah, that's true.
That is true.
That's all...
I don't know.
I'm not gonna sit here and defend The Rock, but I'm also not gonna say that I know.
I'm not gonna?
He did speak at the RNC, but that was also 20 years ago?
Eh, that's fair.
Anyway, Alex gets deeper into Doom fantasies.
I mean, if we ever beat this thing, it'll be in the history of, like, these people were
Hitler.
I mean, this is unbelievable.
It's not like, oh, we're getting there, it's bad, things are out of control.
It's...
They've just begun.
They're gonna take your pension funds.
They're gonna bankrupt.
They're gonna cut the power off, the oil off.
They're gonna open the borders.
It's over, man.
It's over.
It's all gone.
It's all over.
They're gonna activate the Boogaloos, FBI, ADL, terror forces.
They're gonna start blowing everything up.
Then they're gonna come arrest all the patriots.
The idiots will cheer it.
Then they're gonna shut your power off.
They want you starving in the street.
They wanna rape your wife.
They're Bolsheviks.
They're Jacobins.
You're...
I wish.
It's all over, man.
All over.
Enjoy.
All your games.
In fact, America is rotting and deserves it.
Now, the Satanists aren't good.
They're not God.
God just lets them have their way now.
So all your games are over.
All the TV watching, all the laziness, all the slack-jawing's over.
It's over.
You're gonna be just like a baby at six months being chopped up in its mother's womb.
You're not a human.
You're not essential.
You're dead.
They're gonna kill you, because you don't care.
There's so much hand sanitizer on the market, but beware.
So...
Yeah, that was a jarring shift into that commercial.
Never not fun.
Yeah, so I guess we should not storm capital buildings then if we're all, you know...
I don't understand.
If I recall correctly, I do believe that Alex said God appointed him to defeat Satan.
And he was the only person that Satan was worried about.
Yeah, and that's why Satan tried to recruit him when he was younger with all the hot cheerleaders.
So I mean, now that he's done, I assume Satan's like, whew, dodged a bullet on that one.
I guess God isn't that powerful now, is he?
Well, look, don't blame God for Alex's failures.
I'm pretty sure that that's the only person you can blame.
This is an HR issue.
His prophecies are shit.
I don't believe God at all anymore, Dan.
I do think that if you take everything Alex says seriously, then yes, he has been defeated
by the devil at this point.
And by extension, so has God.
Yeah, but also I could see a world where God is sitting off at the side, he's like, I didn't
tell you to do that.
Nah, I can see that world too.
Hey, Alex, don't keep my name out of your mouth.
I didn't tell you to do anything.
Hey, buddy, pssst, guess who you've been working for the whole time, you idiot?
Yeah, yeah.
You're controlled opposition for the devil.
Alex Jones is a devil of false flag.
Yeah, that does sound right.
So Alex believes that everyone in the news, like all over MSM, sure.
Everyone's calling for Trump people to be thrown in camps, Trump fans, just people who
like him.
What kind of people who bad ones like, like offsite FEMA, FEMA, all right.
Five years ago, if we had one club of national TV saying, let's put people in reeducation
camps, we'd be airing in every segment, I probably saw five clips this morning of national
news saying, when you do arrest all supporters and reeducate them right now for no reason.
You said if you had one clip, we need emergency legislation, we need the States lining up
against this.
We need all the big churches coming out against it.
We need all the men that I see on the golf courses are polishing their Porsches or their
jet boats to spend some time caring about this.
Don't you have boats?
All the successful men keep their heads down and it makes me sick because you're not successful.
You're the ones that took our birthright and crapped it away.
That's why I'm pissed, man.
I'm really pissed off right now.
We got a case of communist cancer.
So again, Alex is furious that rich people aren't doing more to support the info war
or something.
I think you can read between the lines a little bit on that.
Yeah.
We've heard this chorus before.
I do think that this is him trying to do like a posterity last broadcast, like the fake
last broadcast thing.
He's getting really mad.
He's trying to get his Howard Beale moment.
Mad as hell, not going to take it anymore.
Never.
Kind of thing.
And it's really funny because he starts time traveling.
His mind starts traveling through time.
He brings out a story from 2008 and pretends it's current.
I'm excited.
I mean, this is it, folks.
I start thinking about all the things I want to say and all the things I want to do and
it just makes me mad that our precious country is being literally sucked into a black hole
of world government.
Literally.
God.
You understand they are announcing shock collars and shock bracelets and bracelets and dog
collars for everyone to wear, OK?
I mean, I have the newscast from 2008.
The plan is they're going to be shocking callers, but it was, oh, you're wearing a collar now
to show your COVID thing and attracts you and social businesses.
No, no, no.
The actual meetings are about having a shocker in it and the public's like, I love my shocker.
I'm not joking.
No, but you're talking about a 13 year old news story about something that the DHS was
considering and didn't implement.
There is that.
This is so sad.
Yeah.
That might be an issue.
And I actually know that that's exactly what he's talking about, because we heard him talk
about that in the past episodes.
And...
No, the problem is, Dan, liberals don't have any memories.
Right.
But I also heard him bring it up on this episode.
Sure.
This same episode, he talks about how they were going to do that for anti-terrorism in
2008.
I hate it.
And he remembers it and then he incorporates it into the present narrative.
I hate him so much.
Yeah, he's the worst.
Yeah.
And there's some content warning, I guess, about this.
This next clip is pretty gross, but it's Alex freaking out.
He's now super mad.
He's losing his mind, starts complaining more about shock collars.
Are they shock collars like what we're used to, or are they collars that just explain
what is happening with climate change?
They're shocking collars in the sense that they are, like, garish.
They're collars that are just...
They're bedazzled.
Yes.
They're like, ooh, you can't wear that.
They're like slap bracelets and people are shocked you're still wearing them.
Yeah.
Gotcha.
So, there's more talk about shock collars here, and then Alex brings in a little bit
of his fears and disgusting stuff about drag queen story time.
Oh, God.
Which is...
You don't get to do this!
It's been a while, and this ends predictably.
Not communist China, Homeland Security is having meetings about shockers you wear around
your neck.
13 years ago.
I mean, hell, you let convicted pedophiles go to elementary schools and have your six-year-old
daughters and sons bounce up and down on their erections.
I mean, literally, I watch these videos.
We can't even air these on air.
I can't even look at them of some fat pot-bellied dude with a little six-year-old girl on him
riding his crotch, and he's got an erection.
This is what they do on TV.
And then they cut to the local newscaster and he goes, well, got to get them when they're
young.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
See, he's the leader.
He just goes along with it.
Got to get the children when they're young, huh?
Do you think you're safe in a world where they got kids with pedophiles on TV?
Do you think you're safe, you dumb son of a bitch?
Hmm, maybe.
You think they're safe when they're...
Now we know the COVID vaccine kills old people at a very high percentage rate.
You think we're safe when they're killing all the old people?
And do you think God likes us when we do that?
It's all going to burn.
All of you that think you're smart and you're part of the system is you can manipulate those
under you.
It's all going to come back on you a trillion fold.
And I'm just saying right now, I will not be part of this.
I will not submit to it.
You know, simply safe sells a social distancing sweater.
All right, I said I'd go to your calls.
Show them the Homeland Security video where you wear taser bracelets.
I'm not making this up, folks.
I know I'm saying this stuff.
It just sounds fantastic.
I'm not lying.
Is there a solution to hijacking?
Yes, everyone will wear a shocking bracelet, Homeland Security says.
It's okay.
Only if you're bad will the stir to shock you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
The flight attendant, don't put me in a reeducation center.
Put them in a reeducation center.
Okay.
I'm going to just say this and go to a call.
It could be your last chance to get an Infowars t-shirt, a Trader Joe's t-shirt, shows his
countries he's sold out to, to be your last chance to get X2, X3.
Wow, that really just really drives home the sincerity of that entire rant, like really
feels genuine and organic and real.
You don't get to do this!
It doesn't feel like a performance at all meant to heighten people's emotions, put them
in a suggestible state, wherein they might be like, oh no, I got to buy this t-shirt.
You know, I think this is why I really don't care.
Like I've seen a lot of like, a lot of those takes where it's like, no, you need to feel
for the Q people.
They really believe this is real and that, and that's why, you know, I know you don't
think that they should, and it's like, man, I get it.
I get it.
I care because a child believes that the boogeyman is under the bed.
I care.
If I'm going to be held as a child, I'm going to do, I'm going to be like, hey, no, there's
no boogeyman under the bed.
Let's do this.
You're an adult.
I don't care.
I don't care if you believe that the boogeyman is under the bed.
I just don't care.
You're an adult.
Many of you people are middle-aged or older.
Stop believing that there's a boogeyman under the bed.
Yeah, but you're not taking into account nearly enough how belief that there's a boogeyman
under your bed gives you security and fills an emotional hole that you need filled.
And you don't realize that it's being filled by something as false and nonsensical as a
boogeyman under your bed.
I realize that.
You may, but I don't feel like you're empathizing to that.
I'm not.
I'm thoroughly not because they're not children.
That's okay, and that's your right.
I disagree with you.
I understand that.
So if we're pretending that this is Alex's last show, one of the things that he would
obviously do in this last show is put off going to calls and not really get around to
them.
Oh yeah, of course.
And so he does successfully do that by screaming about all sorts of stuff.
And then he finally does get to calls, and in normal caller fashion, they're kind of
a bummer.
This one guy who calls in has been in the capital, in DC, since the 6th.
Not the building.
Okay.
Excuse me.
All right.
Okay.
So he's really struggling to understand why Trump would go away.
Why would he get on an airplane and give up on being president if we know the election
was stolen?
Right.
If we know these people are demons.
Why would he do that?
It's tough.
Yeah.
So I got the call from the president to be here on January 6th, and I'm still here.
Well, God bless you, brother.
What do you see there?
What's unfolded?
I see a lot of buses.
A lot of buses with the tinted windows.
And I'm hoping that there are troops, real troops, US soldiers.
One thing that you're not mentioning at all is where's Trump?
If he doesn't say something and start the insurrection act or something to slow this
down, this will be worse than the Bay of Pigs.
I hear you.
That's what I'm saying is he's surrounded.
No one is supporting him.
The cube movement was to make people think he was invincible.
They set us up on the 6th to demonize us.
You said he was chosen by God.
So Trump's going to have Trump's going to leave.
I mean, that's what's going down here, brother, those troops.
But here's the weird wrinkle.
They're now saying the troops are terrorists.
Fox News is saying and CNN's reporting they don't trust the troops either.
So who knows what's going on up there?
I mean, this is crazy, brother.
We're about to find out, aren't we?
We the people know what the truth is.
We know there was election fraud.
We know COVID is a hoax.
We know there's a rampant pedophilia going on.
We know Epstein didn't kill himself.
We know we didn't send help for the Benghazi soldiers.
We know that Joe Biden sent a senile.
What in the heck?
How can a man get on a plane and fly away from all of this?
He also said he would never surrender.
So I'm here in the belly of the beast waiting for the command.
That's so sad.
That just really bums me out.
That's a guy who's accepted and internalized all of these, these narratives from right
wing media.
And he's really, he has the right thought, but he's not reaching the conclusion.
And that is how could Trump, if he is our hero, how could he know all of these things
and allow it to continue?
Take the next step, buddy.
I would imagine that the next step is making up a reason that makes him still be the hero.
Or just turning it into like, uh, Trump was set up himself or yeah, who knows what Alex
is doing?
He's surrounded.
He can't do anything.
No, he was chosen by God.
He was defeated.
So was God, but that's not his fault or God's fault somehow.
Really no one's no, it's no one's probably the devil.
It's probably the devil.
So another caller calls in and Alex gives him some bad advice that if people are listening
to a show and taking him seriously, Alex could like be costing people thousands and thousands
and thousands of dollars.
Coming from a blue state, you know, in a populated area, we got a thousand people per square
mile.
Easy.
Here is the time to go here.
You know, we, we continue to quest for those who 100% is, is, is, you know, downsize your
life and have, and have cultural goodness with God.
It's worth everything not to be part of the system.
You must flee blue States and blue cities.
They're designed to totally collapse and bring down the entire United States.
God bless your brother.
So I guess, um, this caller, he does mention that he is like, his family has some land
he can go to.
Sure.
But like if you're someone who's listening, uprooting your life, it would be very, very
expensive.
Sure.
Um, and Alex is good thing that his family has land though.
Well, that makes it less, this caller does, but not other people who are listening probably
if they believe what Alex is saying, they're like, they're coming to kill you.
They want to chop you up.
Uh, you know, America's over, it's time to flee the blue cities cause they're death traps
and they're meant to collapse.
Like he could fuck around and ruin people's lives in a way that you'd never hear about.
You'd never hear about these people who would listen to Alex, took him seriously and decided
to go to Idaho.
And I'm sorry to the people of Idaho that that's the example I often come up with.
Sure.
It could be Montana.
Idaho is a great state.
Idaho, could be Oregon, could be any of those.
I mean, but a penny that they're spending on moving to a remote location is a penny
they're not giving to Alex.
That's true.
So except if they need, I think Alex is the one who's the real loser in this scenario.
Not if they need to stock up with survival food.
Ooh, that's fair.
Yeah.
He's got that one.
He's got them coming and going.
He does.
Literally.
And he has those water filters that are the size of a school bus and the only, he's the
new Amazon for people who flee.
Yeah.
So Alex now has a guest on, it's Jason Jones.
He's a guy who didn't like COVID restrictions and came to Alex's attention through a YouTube
video, I think.
Anyway, he is there because he was at the Capitol on the 6th and he's complaining about
how the media's gaslighting people about what happened.
This is so funny.
Mic down for this.
Okay.
Because this made me laugh so hard.
You know, it's one thing to tell a lie.
It's another to seem like you believe your own lies.
It was all, it was all quite horrifying, Alex, and it just convinced me that we have to double
down on our commitment to freedom of speech, freedom of religion, free and fair elections.
And you know, we're not, we're not going anywhere.
We're going to keep standing up.
Oh, I thought Alex was still here.
I thought, okay, so yeah, I, uh, that, that's what I got.
Out to break.
That's, that's good stuff, man.
I thought eating a sandwich was rude.
Alex just left.
I love it.
That's beautiful.
That is beautiful.
Ah, I don't understand how Trump could just leave, you know, knowing everything he knows.
I don't understand how Trump could just leave.
Alex, I don't know how he could just leave.
It's remarkable.
I mean, Jason was saying like Alex, he was addressing Alex and Alex wasn't there.
That's fantastic.
He later says that he was walking around with a headset mic so he could hear everything
that Jason Jones was saying.
Sure.
Uh, there's man, that is, that is profoundly rude.
That is fantastic.
Yeah.
Love it.
Doesn't matter how much of a dick Alex is.
Doesn't matter.
He has a platform.
Just keep on coming.
Okay.
Um, somebody who used Alex's platform, uh, maybe for nefarious purposes, Steve Pachannik
and uh, Steve might have turned evil according to Alex in this.
Okay.
And he seems to be implying that Steve flipped over and started supporting Q cause he turned
evil.
Okay.
But that introduces a problem and that is that Alex is huge on General Flynn now.
Right.
General Flynn pledged allegiance to Q.
There's that.
So Alex tries to thread this needle here and it does not work.
The movement was exploding, Q came along to take control of it with intelligence ops.
We now know that well-known intelligence ops that I know personally flipped to Q at the
end because they were controlled.
Um, General Flynn's a great guy.
He just wanted to lead an army that was waiting there with Q, but he still didn't control
it.
He's a good guy.
Oh, so he's a good guy.
He's, he just wanted to control an army.
I don't know.
I feel like controlling an army under false pretenses makes you less of a good guy.
Right?
Oh, okay.
Good guy.
He's a good dude.
He's just, uh, you know, lying to all these evil people in order to turn them into an
army that he can use to overthrow the government, Dan.
Yeah.
That's a patriot.
Mm-hmm.
And see, the problem with QAnon, according to Jason Jones, is, uh, you know, they use
vague information from anonymous sources.
Mm-hmm.
While you're listening to this, just remember how many times Alex has referenced vague things
that a Lieutenant Colonel told him.
People have such faith in Q.
I've been startled at people in my life, people I love and know from, I went to high school
with, college with, served in the army.
They're just, I'm getting inundated with these texts and forwards that their source, they
all have these sources and I'll call them and I'll say, listen, you know, put, put that
aside for now.
Please stop sharing this information.
It's from an anonymous source.
It's communicated in a, in a way that's ambiguous and you can't verify what they state.
When you have, uh, um, an ambiguous statement from an anonymous source that cannot be verified,
you can't support it or refute it.
All that can lead to is infighting and mistrust.
And then that's the structure, the very structure.
It doesn't matter even the content of what they say.
It doesn't matter what you say when it's from an anonymous source, said in an ambiguous
way that cannot be verified or refuted.
The only thing you have that is argument.
It is a satanic action.
What?
I mean, Jason might as well be explaining what Alex does and Alex turns in it's a satanic
system.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's very dumb.
I do like whenever a self-awareness of one's evil is allowed to sublimate through blaming
someone else.
That's good.
That's good stuff.
Way to not reflect.
So earlier on this episode we heard Alex pretty bad, you know, freaking out a little bit.
They're going to kill you.
They're going to chop you up.
Sure.
Shit's going down.
Naturally.
Poison in the water.
Uh-huh.
They're going to kill you.
Naturally.
He was also very viscerally responding to things.
He seemed pretty mad.
And that's why this is really, really funny.
You have been probably, you should write a book on maintaining inner peace.
I agree.
I very much agree.
Breathe through the nose.
I very much agree that I have often been lacking a zen and the art of screaming propaganda.
This position's called the sun salutation.
Do it every morning.
Keeps me centered.
Keeps me sane.
And she's going to start some Adderall real quick and then I'm going to yoga.
First Adderall, then incense, we burn incense to keep the vibe real chill in the house.
I always have a glass of tea.
You know what's fun about yoga is whenever your right leg is constantly shaking.
Makes it more difficult.
Yeah, it does stuff.
So anyway, their interview's stupid, don't care.
And that brings us to the 19th.
So now we're on to Tuesday, the day before Communist Joe Biden becomes president.
And since we're recording this on the 21st, we know that it went off without a hitch.
No real trouble at the inauguration.
I'd say 25,000 uniformed troops probably is a pretty good deterrent.
Probably.
He gave his speech and it sort of flew in the face of he's senile, he can't talk for
even a minute kind of stuff.
There was an issue.
So Alex is still living in the before times though.
But he does know that that is what's going to happen, that Biden is going to get in.
Sure.
Unfortunately, almost half of his audience believes Steve.
And I have a lot of people mad at me, but you won't be mad tomorrow when you see that
I told you the truth.
You'll be very, very sad.
We had a poll on infowars.com over the weekend with tens of thousands of people that clicked
on it.
I don't know if we ever had a chance to pull that up, show an article about it where we
can repost it and have people vote again.
And over 45% thought that everyone's being mass arrested and Trump's gonna stay in office.
Absolutely incredible.
Well, maybe part of that is because of the people you talk to.
I don't understand.
Maybe it's because of-
It is absolutely incredible that my audience, after me telling them this, would believe
it.
And me having guests on who I've overinflated their credibility.
Totally.
Saying that they know everything, they overthrow countries.
I mean, you've had somebody who's literally toppled governments before.
I don't understand why we would believe he couldn't once more.
Exactly.
Yeah.
I think that that's indicative of... I mean, I don't know how scientific these polls are
on Infowars, but assuming that a third of his audience even, let's say, believes that
Steve is right and that Trump is gonna somehow magically remain president, if I saw that
number for our audience, I would think I'd failed.
Yeah, I would strongly believe that.
I think that's a big problem with my audience.
Yeah.
I would almost say that would be a reason for us to quit doing the show.
We're bad for people.
Alex doesn't look at it that way.
He's kind of excited for them to be proven wrong and to be proven right.
Just a little shitty.
That'll show the people who give me money.
Yeah.
So there's a loose thread dangling from the sixth, and that is that Alex has said repeatedly,
and on microphones, that Trump personally asked him to lead the march from the speech
to the Capitol building.
Doesn't look good in hindsight.
Does not.
Turns out Alex was set up from the inside.
Okay.
He wanted a million people in DC to peacefully demonstrate so that we would show we had more
numbers than they did and to show that Biden couldn't fill a parking lot and Trump could
get a million people there, that Trump was coming to speak at a stage that was set up
on the other side.
But it was all a setup.
That stage was there the night before.
It was broken down by the time we got there.
Oh, we were totally set up.
We walked completely into a trap with people inside his administration we know now that
set Trump up and told him, uh, that, uh, you know, it's Jones's idea to march the Capitol
and all this stuff.
And it's a great idea.
You should tell him to lead it because they intended for me to go in there and lead that
thing so they could throw my ass in prison.
But of course, by the time I got there, I saw what was happening and tried to stop it.
This is the real world, people who inside the Trump administration was trying to set
you up.
Name names.
If somebody was trying to set you up, I would imagine you would really want to name names.
That'd be big news.
Yeah.
I think everybody would give you a lot of attention if you could name names.
Come on, Alex.
Jesus does not doesn't.
So the globalist plan, um, Oh, also, by the way, I realize now that we've moved on to
the 19th.
He didn't really do a last episode on the 18th, but he also didn't say I'm doing it
tomorrow.
So I assume that was meant to be it.
And it was just that outburst and he just got distracted.
I think he just did an outburst and started yelling and hoped it would be kind of look
like network.
Sure.
That's kind of the feeling that I get.
I think, I think his last broadcast being like 15 minutes long would really be great
for me.
His last broadcast being talking about migrant caravans over, over exaggerating their fear
that you should have for them.
And then that putting him into a mood where he screams about shit and how you're all going
to die.
Right.
And this is over man.
And then puts off going to calls.
I think that's fitting.
I think that's pretty good.
I mean, that's about right.
It's either that or him just being like, and now I'm going to say all the slurs that I've
wanted to since the beginning in alphabetical order.
Hey.
Yeah.
Also, here's what I think about Willy Wonka.
Yes.
Yeah.
I watched it last night and I've got a 20 minute review.
Horrific, horrific racism plus sci-fi reviews.
Yeah.
Um, speaking of sci-fi, did you know that, um, H.G. Wells, formerly was the head of the
bad guys?
I did not know that.
I learned that.
Okay.
And they were planning this takeover for a hundred years, really longer.
You can debate.
I mean, 1850s, they had the basic plan under Galton Wedgwood and Huxley.
Sure.
Those are the grandparents of like Aldous Huxley and Julian Huxley.
And then by 1900, H.G. Wells was the leader of the Illuminati and they had more of the
modern plan all dialed up and ready, but it was all extremely visionary.
Just ultra visionary.
They're always 30, 40 years ahead of everybody, which is why they say they have the right
to do this.
And I understand their perspective.
I mean, I'm not going to join them because I can feel my immortal soul is in danger.
I can feel it.
Uh, but I understand why they're doing it.
It makes a lot of sense.
I mean, the public's so dumb.
They can openly take everything away from you and kill you.
You put up with it.
You deserve to die.
Wow.
Alex.
Strong words.
Yeah.
Strong words immediately following.
I think that the Dead Authors podcast by Paul F. Tompkins is real.
You shouldn't, uh, probably have that position.
It seems, it seems, uh, bad.
I think it goes against everything that he said he wanted in the past for saving people
in the light.
It does feel that way.
Yeah.
Also, if like, uh, the H.G. Wells was the leader of the Illuminati, but this plan only
goes back to the Wedgewoods in 1850, the Illuminati started in 1776.
Sure.
Right?
I mean.
Something along those lines.
Doesn't that go back before 1850?
Who knows?
This is stupid.
They were the new Illuminati.
Like the old Illuminati died, Coke brought it back in new Illuminati, I believe.
That sounds right.
Anyway, H.G. Wells, not just an author.
No.
Head of the Illuminati.
Not just a...
Cool.
Yeah.
Um, Alex doesn't have a meeting with him, but he might have a meeting with another top
Illuminati figure.
Okay.
The difference is I'm not going to join him, though I am going to be meeting with a top
globalist the next month.
Top globalist.
So I will be entertaining, at least what they have to say, because it's important to keep
those dialogues going.
What?
What did you just say?
This is very serious, ladies and gentlemen.
This is your life, your soul, your children's future, and you just have to understand that
I'm not going to sit here and debate and argue with people about this stuff.
It's all out in the open.
So yeah, Alex is going to have a meeting with the top globalists.
So it's got to be what?
Bill Gates?
It has to be something like that.
Although he's a middle man now.
Maybe.
It's possible.
That's Alex's guess to ask.
Yeah.
Could be Klaus Schwab?
It could be.
Could be.
I want to say it's a secret Rothschild.
I think it's one of the ones that we've never heard of.
A mystery Rothschild?
Yeah, that's why they get away with it.
Like that one Jonas brother who's not in the group?
There's another Jonas brother?
There's a bonus Jonas.
There's a secret Jonas?
Yeah.
Who was it?
Was it the Kennedys who supposedly had a relative that they kept in the attic or something like
that?
I think they did.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
Holy shit.
That's real weird that we're just...
Oh, that's crazy.
Yeah.
I was just talking about a Jonas brother who didn't get to be in the fucking group.
You're talking about something really sad.
I thought it was a myth at first.
No.
I don't know who Alex is talking about.
I also don't believe this is true.
But the globalists, they need you to accept their plan in order for them to get away with
what they're doing.
Sure.
Alex expresses this a little bit.
And then I wanted to talk a tiny bit about where this idea comes from.
Humanity is starting to wake up and actually be who they should be and say no to it.
And then the globalists don't get to play the social Darwin game.
But if you don't recognize what they're doing, if you don't have an open dialogue with the
globalist and talk to them person to person and say, I know what you're doing.
You don't have a right.
I'm going to resist you.
Then they have no respect for you and will run over you.
They metaphysically need you to acquiesce and submit.
They always have to leave you an escape valve.
That is a rule of the universe that God has put down and they follow these rules.
He got his ass kicked by Satan.
And if you won't study what they're up to and if you won't study their plan versus God's
plan, and if you won't make a spiritual, cultural, economic and physical decision who you're
with, then you are fair game to them.
So the religious stuff that he adds on to this is whatever, but like the idea that if
you don't know their plan and specifically fight back, like he's just taking that from
that fake document, Silent Weapons for Quiet Wars, which was chapter one of Bill Cooper's
book Behold the Pale Horse.
We covered this in depth in our episode number 381 on this podcast, so I don't want to rehash
all the history of that again.
But if you're interested in how fake that document is, go and listen to that.
On page six of that fake document, there's a particular quote that Bill Cooper would
repeat over and over and over again on his show.
So to the point where like if you were a listener, you would definitely have that implanted in
your mind as a really important point.
Quote, all science is merely a means to an end.
The means is knowledge.
The end is control.
Beyond this remains only one issue.
Who will be the beneficiary?
In 1954, this was the issue of primary concern.
Although the so-called moral issues were raised, in view of the law of natural selection, it
was agreed that a nation or world of people who will not use their intelligence are no
better than animals who do not have intelligence.
Such people are beasts of burden and stakes on the table by choice and consent.
This is where Alex's idea that if you don't directly fight the globalists, that's the
equivalent of you consenting for them to do whatever you want, they want to do to you.
That if you're, if they can get away with taking all your stuff, you know, that's, this
is all just silent weapons for quiet wars.
I've heard Alex reference the document before, I know he was a huge Bill Cooper listener,
like that's all, that's all this like mythology about the globalists needing you to consent
by not fighting them stuff comes from.
It's all just a fake document.
I assume he's apologized for saying that he knows God's plan and he can see it and he's
part of God's plan and that he's, and he's apologized for being wrong and he said that
he can't see God's plan and maybe, you know, all of his ideas of what God can control are
off.
No, not once.
Not once?
This is all still part of God's plan.
God's plan is now for him to fight Joe Biden politically and make a bunch of money telling
people to head to the woods.
See now, I thought he had already told me that God's plan was for him to defeat Joe
Biden and the devil and Trump to take over and create a lasting 1,000 year long reign.
I don't know if he was ever specific about the 1,000 year reign, but it did certainly
have overtones of that.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know.
One of the things about prophets is when they're alive, they're really slippery.
They change their prophecies quite a bit.
Joseph Smith was real good at that.
He had a real talent for that.
Kind of, it's where long form improv comes from.
It might be.
Super long form improv is rearranging prophecies.
Decades long form improv.
So these games that Alex is playing with his predictions and stuff, maybe decades long,
but the globalists, their plan is hundreds of years old.
You can debate it.
Maybe it's 1850.
Maybe it's H.G. Wells.
Maybe it's Mesopotamia.
Maybe it's the pyramids.
That doesn't sound right.
Okay, well that sounds closer.
But anyway, Alex is going to take a meeting with them because he thinks, in his hubris
filled mind, somehow he thinks he's going to talk the globalists out of their plans.
I don't take enjoyment seeing how screwed up and falling apart humanity is.
But the plan is to make humanity so dysfunctional that those of us that aren't part of it are
going to basically have to either commit suicide or join with the globalists and wipe your
asses out.
Because if you won't stand up for yourself, then I can't help you.
And I'm not going to join the globalists, and I've openly had dialogues with some of
their next to top level people, and I've had some dialogue with their top people, and they
want me to stop.
And they are not going to be able to convince me, I'm going to try to convince them.
Yeah, that's going to work.
I don't believe any of this stuff, but let's humor him for a second and imagine that he's
going to go into, I don't know, a meeting with Klaus Schwab and be like, you gotta cut
it out, man.
And they're going to be like, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, I have not heard this information
before.
Are you serious?
This is bad for humanity?
Oh no, I'm talking to the devil?
Fuck!
You know, his horns and the fact that I could never see him through the shadowy fire, that
I agree might have been a sign.
Fuck, I should have figured this out.
Can't believe it took a weird Texan guy yelling at me to help me see the light.
Hold on one second.
Hold on, Alex, just real quick.
Are you telling me that when I sold my soul to the literal devil, he was lying to me?
Alex has also said that these people act compulsively and they can't help themselves.
So I don't know how he's going to talk anybody out of anything.
They're also not human anymore, according to Alex.
I don't know what having a parlay is going to do.
It's all such stupid shit.
Well, I guess in order for him to enact his plans, he also has to get their tacit consent.
Because it's a rule of the universe.
It's God's plan.
No, because he's not doing anything to them.
They only play it's to.
The globalists only need your consent because the things that they're doing affect you,
like chemtrails over the country club.
Sure.
That affects all of us because of our passivity and not fighting them on it.
That's consent to have chemtrails dropped on us.
Well, I mean, if you're going to defeat the globalists, I assume they're going to lose
all of their money and power.
So that's doing something to them.
Yeah, but.
I'm just saying, if it's a universal law, he actually has to get the consent of the
globalists before he can defeat them.
Fine.
Then I guess sports can't exist.
Not in God's plan.
Because then every team has to consent to be beaten.
You have to sign a waiver before you play the game.
Oh, God.
You both consent to.
So Alex has a guest on this episode here on the 19th, and it's not an interview I'm
really interested in all that much.
It is the brother of John Sullivan, the guy who got arrested for videotaping inside the
Capitol building.
And Alex has decided he's the big Antifa leader who caused all the trouble.
We've got Mike Flynn the third, because Mike Flynn and Mike Jr. are not answering my calls
anymore.
So James Sullivan is a guy who has some right wing tendencies and is the brother of John.
I just, I heard this, I was just like, ah.
So James, wow.
Incredible.
Tell us about yourself, about your brother and why you're on air with us and what you've
witnessed.
Because you're very well known in Utah.
You've been in news for a while countering your brother.
I mean, you're not just popping up now after this.
You've been warning folks for a while.
This must be really hard for you to do.
Yeah, yeah, it was.
This interview is deeply irresponsible.
A lot of it ends up just being James talking about John's personal life in ways that I
don't feel like they belong on Info Wars.
And a lot of it kind of left me feeling gross and uncomfortable.
I know that Alex really needs to build up John Sullivan as the big Antifa boogeyman
in order to carry his conspiracy theories about the storming of the Capitol being a
false flag, but this feels super inappropriate.
The whole thing is Alex trying to get James to give some details that Alex can use to
build a deeper narrative.
He's asking these probing questions about like, did someone put him on drugs or do you
know who his handler might be?
It's really gross.
And also, I don't know if James, however much he might disagree with his brother, I don't
know what kind of potential damage he realizes could come to him by virtue of the way this
conversation goes.
If I fumbled in the Super Super Bowl in the one yard line, not understanding I was being
set up in all this, and I did, I don't take blame for it because I'm in the arena and
we were fighting for election integrity and calling for legal and lawful things to happen.
I'm now being accused of trying to foment things, but he didn't fumble at the one yard
line.
He scored and won the game against America in the Super Super Bowl of our Republic.
I mean, if they put a tombstone saying our Republic died in the future, if we don't come
back from this, it will be your brother and people like him that day that helped kill
the country.
Yeah.
Oh, that's not good.
I don't know if he realizes like the kind of conversation that they're having here is
like, it's really the kind of thing that could potentially put a target on.
Mr. Sullivan, Mr. Sullivan, real quick, do you want our listeners to kill your brother?
I just want you to, I just want you to agree with me that all of this is your brother's
fault.
He has killed the country and he of course deserves, I'm not going to, politically.
Right.
Yeah.
And at the same time too, this dude is saying that there was somebody who was along filming
John because they're making a documentary about him and his brother.
Like the two of them are both like on opposite sides of the political aisle.
Sure.
And so I'm like, I don't know what's going on here.
I don't trust any of this.
I don't care about any of this.
Yeah.
I, yeah, I really don't care.
It's just really, really, really uncomfortable, but I will say that James doesn't realize
what Alex's narrative is clearly because he counters it.
Seeing him wasn't really that much of a surprise.
After he was removed from Utah, he traveled to Kenosha, to California, to Portland, trying
to get into these Antifa communities and they would kick him out.
So seeing him here wasn't really that big of a surprise.
Huh.
Well, his brother's saying that he keeps getting kicked out of Antifa groups, anti-fascist
groups.
So it's kind of tough for Alex to then argue that he is an Antifa leader.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Seems like they're both running a game.
That's what I, I'm not saying that they're running a game, but it does seem like they're
running a game.
I think that a lot of, there have been some people who have reached out with like their
comments about Jon and from the sense that I get, there is sort of an attention seeking
behavior pattern and kind of disregard for what other people are doing that are productive
things.
Maybe, maybe I'm just so conditioned to believe anybody in that sphere is running a game of
some kind.
Well, the thing that I think is the most worrying is the idea that someone was making a documentary
about the two of them.
Like that to me is like, okay, if one of you, one of these brothers is someone who seems
to have a clear pattern of attention seeking behavior and the other brothers happens to
be directly on the other side of the political aisle and is doing a documentary with, it
seems like this is all attention seeking behavior.
It really does.
And the fact that you would go and talk about your brother in such a weird way on Infowars
of all places.
Yeah.
It just, it grosses me out.
There's too many human elements to it that just like, I wouldn't, I wouldn't like this,
this kind of conversation to be had about anybody really.
I don't see, I don't see any like either they're like the, okay, so they could be running a
game and this is fucked up or they're not running a game and this is fucked up.
Yeah.
You know, like this is fucked up.
We have not interviewed people who know Alex for a reason because it's uncomfortable and
fucking weird.
Totally.
I wish Alex would do the same because this is weird.
This is weird.
It's very, very unpleasant to listen to it and so we won't listen to any more of it.
Alex does though on this episode, get to sit talking about how he doesn't want Biden dead,
but he is going to put them in his death pool.
Okay.
That's not great.
So I don't want anything bad to happen by they'll turn them into a martyr, but I do
put a death pool on him, a dead pool.
I don't think he's going to be dead in the next year, but I, I bet Biden, he likes power
though, but they put him in there cause he's so weak and so addled.
He's talked about stepping down, fainting an illness as a reason to go.
When?
I don't know.
We should have a whole show in debate once we have our installed president, our first
dictator.
So first dictator again.
Yeah.
He was talking about stepping down and faking an illness when he was vice president.
If he had a fundamental difference with Obama.
Yeah.
Um, there's a very different situation than, uh, than the current, but whatever.
I don't know.
I know that, you know, he's trying to say he's putting him in the death pool, but I
don't know what it'd be.
He's saying I put a death pool on him.
Like it's a hex.
Yeah.
He did say that.
It's very weird.
I put a death pool on you.
Yeah.
So we have another guest here before we wrap up the 19th.
This episode was not good.
This was a slog to get through.
Um, Alex has Nick Fuentes on and uh, it's interesting because they have slightly different
viewpoints about the storming of the Capitol.
Unsurprising.
Alex is all false flag.
This was bad.
Totally.
Nick has been pretty in favor.
But they're calling it the great insurrection.
They're calling it into the world.
They're calling for Nick Fuentes to be arrested because he was seen outside.
They're calling for me to be arrested.
I think it was great to see people say, we know this was a fraudulent election, but I
think it was terrible that some people gave the system what they wanted when they broke
in.
So Nick Fuentes has been quoted in the media as liking what happened.
I imagine that's probably out of context.
We appreciate him coming on to tell us what he really thinks.
So the founder of the groipers, a former Trump volunteer and popular talk show host, Nick
Fuentes.
Nick.
Thanks for coming on.
Thanks for having me.
I want to play one thing here that's sort of out of order because I think it, uh, it
uh, is our rights context.
It's our responsibility.
Okay.
Later people falsely claimed that I breached the Capitol, which wasn't true.
Uh, but I stood outside the Capitol.
I watched, I gave a little speech and then we packed up and left.
There were people who were claiming that Nick Fuentes was, uh, along with like baked Alaska
in the Capitol.
And there was a picture that definitely looked a ton like Nick Fuentes.
Yeah.
It was quite believable.
And I, uh, took that as proof that he was there cause I looked a lot like him and uh,
it appears that that's not accurate.
Okay.
It appears that he was outside.
He did not go inside.
He claims that is the case and I can't find solid evidence outside of that picture.
Yeah.
And I'm willing to believe, uh, his, uh, his statement that I was wrong when I repeated
that he was in, uh, in the Capitol.
So yeah, totally.
Um, anyway, he still thinks it was great though.
Yeah, of course.
Which almost is more evidence I think that he didn't go inside.
Yeah.
I, I imagine if he were under arrest right now, he would think less of how great it was.
A lot of people who are getting arrested probably are not like, that was awesome.
I'm a, I'm a big fan of the, Joe Biggs is not, uh, pumped right now.
I'm a big fan.
I'm a big fan of the, uh, we got carried up in the moment argument.
Hey man, it's a crime of passion, Dan.
Those don't count.
Well, some people would look at it as a crime of passion and some people would think of
what happened that day, the entirety of it as the culmination of the stop the steal thing
that Alex was a big part of.
You could say that.
And when we got there, the entire Capitol building was surrounded.
You know, I have to say it was a pretty awesome site because I had been, and I know that you
were there as well.
We were traveling the country in Phoenix, Atlanta, all over the place doing stop the
steal protest, raising awareness about the voter fraud and everything.
And so to finally see hundreds of thousands of Trump supporters surrounding the U S Capitol
building demanding that Mike Pence or the Republican senators take action on the voter
fraud.
And to me, that was kind of like the fulfillment of the past two or three months of stop the
steal protest.
And to me, it looked like the American people were waking up, rising up and all of that.
Everything else was a fulfillment of it too.
Yeah.
Everything else was the logical extension of the movement that you all have been pushing
down the road.
Yep.
Anyway, Nick has a little bit of a softer view on QAnon than Alex.
Alex is pretty mad.
And of course a large portion of it always comes down to he wants credit.
Right.
And that is also where this clip is going to go.
But Nick kind of has a position more like, eh, it woke people up.
The normie types, the suburban moms, you know, they, they now know about how all of the people
I don't like are Dracula's.
Yeah.
Now that we've got the suburban moms terrified, we're on our way to victory.
He sees the utility in that and thinks that there's probably still some ability to get
those people back into a profitable revenue stream.
The good thing about QAnon, I always thought was that it got a lot of regular people to
believe the right things, even if they were believing them for the wrong reasons.
You know, it took a lot of maybe mainstream conservative Republican types who believe
this usual stuff about small government and free trade and mass immigration and low taxes.
And I think it woke them up about the power of the elites and the evil and the corruption
of the elites and kind of this international thing that's going on with all the work that
I did and countless others did and you've been around a while, did, and it became Q
like, Oh, Q knows about this and then it, but don't worry, everything's fine.
But, but, but I mean, I agree.
It was kind of a pop way for the general public.
It was just now waking up to get into it.
See, the thing that I liked about that is that Alex is, is pissed off that he's not
getting credit.
Once again, I want credit for, and in order to not sound like a super petty asshole, he's
like, you've been around a while and it's like 22 years old.
He's a vet now.
He's a veteran.
He was there at the storm in the Capitol.
There's no rookies anymore, Dan.
He was in high school at the 2016 election.
I know I heard him debate.
It was garbage.
Yeah.
Granted.
He was at the unite the right rally and the storming of the Capitol.
He's seen some shit, but he's not been around a while in the way that Alex is pretending.
You were a big fan of bill Cooper back in the day.
You're nine.
Oh, I'm in trouble.
Let me tell you about scousing.
So it's our last clip here.
Nick is just talking about how the globalists fear Alex because he has an audience.
He can reach people, but what they feared about you and what they feared about Joe Rogan
and a lot of these people is that you have your own totally independent infrastructure
broadcasting to millions and millions of people you still do, and they don't control you and
they don't control what you say.
They want to control everything that people hear.
They want to control what's on their phones, want to control what's on their TV, on their
radio.
They're freaking out that I'm pointing out that the boogaloo's are still on Twitter and
you and I aren't.
Nick is still verified on Twitter.
Oh yeah.
It's still there.
Yeah.
So that kind of punctures that.
I don't know.
I think it's less that everybody wants to control how everybody speaks and all that
and more, you know, there's certain platforms that just don't put up with certain behaviors
and you guys have crossed those lines to the point where people are going to take it seriously.
And I would assume that if those boogaloo accounts, you know, you can show that they
were involved in X, Y, or Z and report them, they will be banned.
They will be kicked off, I would assume.
And I don't know who he's talking about, so I can't even fact check it.
I can't go look for every account that has hashtag boogaloo in it and that's not even
going to help.
Then I have to go through hashtag big igloo, all the weird fun ways everybody spells things.
I can't do that.
Yeah.
You're making a nonsense statement.
It's almost like vague information from an unknown source.
It's satanic.
It's hard not to hear them saying like, okay, well we used to never have to think about
how people feel.
Then they started asking us to think about how we feel and we stormed the Capitol and
now they're demanding that we think about how other people feel and they're giving us
consequences when we don't.
That sounds like exactly what they're saying, right?
There's some overlap.
Yeah.
I find this to be sad.
This was not a good couple of days for Alex.
It wasn't even like, maybe he's holding back for the, you know, the long-
For the marathon.
The inauguration day, but like, I don't know, it's the last two days and like he mustered
up his fake last show on the 19th, or I'm sorry, on the 18th and it was just sort of
like, it wasn't anything, it was a, it was a real disappointing crescendo.
I just got nothing.
Yeah.
I mean, that's not terrible.
You know, you've had that day where you know that at the, at the end of the week, you're
going to have the worst, like longest day and the day before that, the day before that,
you're like, you know what, I'm going to take it easy today.
I'm just going to do my job, but I'm not really going to, you know, go hard.
I'm going to yell a little bit and then I'm going to-
I got, I got a lot of things to scream about.
I'm going to lie, but then I'm just going to take it easy, man.
I imagine maybe he's been too busy writing that book about inner peace.
I do think, even if everything sucks and nothing is really going on here, I would have done
this episode just for that clip where Alex is gone.
When Jason Jones-
That's so good.
I just want that there.
I will say this, I will make this pledge.
If Alex does write that book, I will edit it for free, 100% for free.
I will do an audio book of it in my Alex impression.
That will be-
Absolutely.
That is the one thing we will do for Alex in our career.
Breathe.
We will be back, Jordan, with the inauguration spectacular 2020.
Indeed.
And I said 2020 because Alex, that's what's on the tombstone.
Yes, I see that.
We'll do that on Monday and I'm excited for that, but until then we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yes.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledgefight.net.
Go to bed, Jordan.
You're also on Facebook.
And if you could, please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work.
Yeah, we'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZXClark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I am constantly fighting the devil.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.