N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying we are the bad guys.
Knowledgefight.
Dan and Jordan, Knowledgefight.
Want to learn?
Need, need Money.
G dispensaries labor.
TSD Community Veterans Office.
Stop it, Andy Tian MP and the looped up to the rollins.
Boston color
with your band and love your world Sit sculpture.
I love you.
Hey everybody!
Welcome back to Knowledge Fat, I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes that like to sit around and drink novelty beverages and talk a little
bit about Alex Jones.
Oh indeed we are Dan.
Jordan.
Dan!
Jordan!
I have a quick question for you.
What up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today Jordan is actually a little bit of something that we need to play
catch up on.
Okay.
Alright.
A little bit back we got something in the mail bags, yep, from Hannah out in Erie, Pennsylvania.
And I need to make good on this.
How are our sisters doing?
Ah they're great.
Okay good.
Hannah sent us some chocolates.
Okay.
From Erie, Pennsylvania.
The Pride of Erie.
Yes.
Some sponge candy from two different brands.
Okay.
Romolo.
Uh huh.
And what is this other one?
It's Stefa something or other.
Stefa something or other.
Stefanelli's!
I like it.
Hannah asked us to, how did Hannah put it, there is a rivalry between two families in
Erie that are chocolatiers.
One makes a chocolate that is deemed quote better than the other.
I want you two to do a blindish taste test between the two milk chocolate sponge candies
and so we did that before the show because chewing into the mic does disgust some people.
Many people find it horrific.
We don't want to set anyone off.
So I, we've tried these and Hannah would like us to guess which one is the classier one
or just considered the classier one and I say it's Stefanelli's.
And I say it is Gondola's, nope what is it?
Romolo.
Yeah Gondola.
Gondola.
Yeah.
I got Gondor on the brain so, no I say it's the reverse.
My bright spot is that I think I'm pretty sure I'm right in advance.
I'm not saying that you're not, I'm just, I'm playing the game.
Exactly, we were talking about this before we started recording as we were eating the
chocolates and your reason for choosing Romolo is almost oppositional defiance.
No it's not!
Why would you ask the question?
We both agree which one tastes better.
Because it's a local thing.
It's something that people outside of Erie probably don't know too much about these rival
chocolatiers.
Hatfields and McCoys of chocolate.
Sure, sure, I just assumed that one of them, if it's better it's the less, or if the one
that people assume is better is the one that we're supposed to say is not as good.
I don't think that either of them were bad.
No, no, they're both delicious.
They were both fine.
Love it.
I just think the Romolo was a little bit, the chocolate was a little too dry.
A little thicker?
Yes.
Doesn't melt in your mouth.
No.
No, absolutely not.
Anyway, that's my bright spot.
Indeed.
Sponge candy.
It's delicious.
Absolutely.
Jordan?
Dan, I have the rare triple bright spot.
The rare triple bright spot.
He's batting for the cycle.
Absolutely.
Wait, you need quadruple for that.
First things first, somebody reached out to me, sent me an email, and they had done a
better job of converting my terrible PDF into an EPUB and a MOBI than I could ever do.
Oh, that's awesome.
Yeah, huge shout out to Old Man Sitko, as he would like to be named.
All right.
Yeah, the formatting of your book left something to be desired.
It was awful.
I tried everything 30 different times.
It's hard.
It's just like, I can't, yeah.
He did an amazing job.
Second, I was going back through my... I've been writing about music for a while now.
So I've been-
Mostly Taylor Swift.
Digging, almost entirely Taylor Swift.
But I've been digging through all my old crates and stuff like that, and I finally re-listened
to the Feist version of Lover's Spit by The Broken Social Scene.
I think it was off Beehives or something like that.
So good.
Feist manages to be both sonorous and breathy at the same time, and it's incredible.
Okay.
It's beautiful.
And then the third is something that you just gave to me-
Yeah.
Well, I didn't give it to you.
No, no, no.
You did not.
You handed it to me.
Yes.
Physically.
That comes from the... What was mine again?
What?
I had a mail bin.
What did I have?
I don't know.
A box?
It's not my job to remember your passive aggressive kits.
I think I remember there was a... Wow.
That's not my job.
I just thought you would be offended enough by them that you... Anyways, I was sent by-
Yeah, from Amy.
From Amy.
Raptor Princess Amy.
Raptor Princess Amy, a signed copy of, I believe, the first American edition of The Long Dark
Tea Time of the Soul by Douglas Adams.
It was your favorite book of Doug's.
It is maybe my favorite book.
This one and So Long and Thanks for All the Fish are my two favorites.
That's really awesome.
Yeah.
That's amazing.
No, it's incredible.
Actually, in that package, I also got a survival heirloom seed vault.
Yes, gorgeous.
And some awesome socks.
A little known fact about Dan, I'm a man who likes funny socks.
He's a man who likes funny socks.
One of them says crazy cat dude and has some cats on it, and the other one is a pro wrestling
themed socks.
I'm very excited.
Fantastic.
Thank you, Amy.
Yes, thank you very much.
That's very nice of you.
I was going to get to that on our next mini episode.
Sure.
I can't.
I mean, you handed it to me, and I need to tell the world because it's incredible for
me.
It's a huge moment.
Yeah.
I'm very excited.
We might have to stop the show.
Yeah.
I'm a little overstimulated right now, but it's incredible.
Take some breaths.
I will.
Because we got some stuff to go over today.
Let's do it.
Today, Jordan, we're going to be going over Inauguration 2021, Black Jack.
Black Jack.
Now you're so fast.
But I'm trying to beat you to it.
Yeah, no, I got to race you.
This is going to get weird.
Yeah, it is.
The rule is you can't start saying Black Jack until one gets out of my mouth.
No, it's traditional Jeopardy rules.
You have to buzz in.
Oh.
So on Jeopardy, you have to wait until the sentence, the question is finished, and then
you have like 0.001 second to buzz in, and whoever does it fastest.
But if you click it too soon...
Do I have to buzz?
No, you don't have to buzz.
Okay.
It's just a game.
We'll figure it out as we go along.
Anyway, we're talking about Inauguration Day.
And Alex set out to do a marathon all day.
And part of the reason for this is that he was expecting a false flag terrorist attack
to happen.
Totally.
It did not happen.
And so it kind of falls apart, the idea of it being a marathon.
Naturally.
Pretty quick.
So today what we're going to be doing is we're going to be going over the American Journal,
hosted by Harrison Smith.
Okay.
Some other issues about Harrison Smith.
Right.
Then Alex Jones' show, Until John Rappaport Takes Over the Fourth Hour.
Sure.
He's going to also do the War Room.
But by that point, this thing had ground to a halt to such an extent that I just was like,
I got no interest in this.
And the American Journal I honestly think was a bit more interesting than I expected
it to be.
And there's some issues that we really need to talk about.
All right.
Let's do it.
About this fucking ding-dong named Harrison.
Also I'd like to say, what could have been one of my bright spots is all of the stories
that are coming out about Alex losing his appeal in the Texas Supreme Court.
Oh yeah.
We are aware of that, but inauguration must be taken care of before we jump down that
road.
So we'll deal with that later in the week.
Absolutely.
For all those who were champing at the bit for us to get to that.
Yeah.
Before we get down to inauguration though, we've got to thank some Joe Biden donors.
Oh, that's a good idea.
I don't know that to be the case at all.
I don't know if any.
Some people who have supported our show had signed up in our policy wonks.
Yeah.
So first, Elliott Morgan, thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, Elliott.
Thank you.
Next.
Don DeGran Prix's ghost.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Don DeGran.
How's he doing in heaven?
Bad news.
No.
Well, he's doing good in heaven, actually.
Is he doing good in heaven?
I don't think he made it.
Grifter heaven.
Yeah.
Next, Andrew Kemp.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, Andrew.
Thank you.
Next, Corey, and actually Corey made an interesting request, and that is that he'd like to be
known as a policy wonk, so congratulations, Corey.
You're a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Policy wonk, Corey.
I said Corey's a dog.
Could be.
Yeah.
Next, I'm a doctor, and my time is precious.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, and we agree.
Yeah.
Next, Mr. Muscarello, a very fine fellow.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
Why not Mr. Toad's Wild Ride?
Let's just roll with it.
Gregorium's Wonder Emporium.
Then finally, I'd like to say thank you to a couple folks who signed up on an elevated
level.
I appreciate that very much.
So, Jodie C., not the band Jodeci.
Jodie C.
Yes.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
Lord Subwalled.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
But it was the band Lord Subwalled.
Yes, it was.
Yes.
And Dan didn't read my joke name when I became a policy wonk.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate.
That's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right.
We got to go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why are you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much, all.
Yes.
And there's a certain irony to this, too, and that is that I still didn't say whatever
the joke name is.
Well, I was thinking about it, and I was like, our inability to get to your joke name immediately
is in some ways a passive extortion.
You got to get up to technocrat if you want to jump to the line.
That's not the joke name.
No, of course not.
I don't know what the joke name was.
I don't know.
I lose track.
I can't keep track of this stuff.
Anyway, Jordan, we're going to jump in here at the beginning, where it all started.
In the beginning, there was the word.
I was going to say, we're going all the way back, huh?
No, let's skip back a little bit.
Little bit.
Okay, move forward.
The beginning of the day.
Abraham baguette, and then, okay.
Eventually you get down the line and you find Harrison Smith, and he's sitting at a desk
and America has fallen.
Okay.
You're watching American Journal.
This is a dirge of sorts, a funeral song for the United States, for the Republic as we
know it.
This is now a wartime broadcast.
America, the Republic has fallen.
Again.
With Donald Trump vacating the office, leaving the White House, and taking Air Force One
while he still can to Florida.
These people are intensely dramatic.
I know.
This is so...
Yeah.
All right.
I think I start to realize when I look through the prism of people similar to Harrison or
to Mike Adams and their just overly dramatic tendencies, I kind of realize that Alex is
the same, except the way it manifests isn't like this weird over the top modeling America
has fallen.
It's kind of sci-fi and a little horror-y.
Yeah.
I think that's why it's a little bit less like obviously like really dramatic.
It is a little bit like what's going on is these are all the theater kids who are so
into masculinity they couldn't join the theater program, and so they're trying to get all
this theater kid stuff out.
I would have been a theater kid, but they were too inclusive.
Exactly.
Totally.
100 percent.
Yeah.
I tried debate.
I had to play football because I was too manly.
Harrison did not play football.
No.
Well, that's probably true.
He's too much of a theater kid.
Too much.
Yeah.
So there's an interesting dynamic that's going on throughout most of the coverage here on
the 20th, and that is wrestling with Trump's legacy in the last hour of his presidency.
Okay.
Harrison comes solidly down on the side of that dude done fucked up.
And I got to be honest, Donald Trump completely failed, utterly, totally failed.
I was having this debate with my dad yesterday, and he was saying, you know, Trump was probably
the greatest president in my lifetime.
I said, it doesn't matter.
He failed.
He left us not with any lasting triumph, but with ash.
You got some ash.
I mean, I think a lot of people probably predicted this.
Who?
How?
Why?
When?
Everyone.
What kind of person would possibly have predicted this?
Remember when he was elected president, Dan?
We were meant to give him a chance.
Yeah.
You know?
It's tough, I guess, to hear aspiring authoritarian dictator servers sad that they don't get to,
you know, that their guy wasn't strong enough to get them to the point where they could
be his servants.
I was hoping that the boot I was licking was strong and powerful, and it turns out it was
weak, ineffectual, and a grifter just like my boot.
I can't believe that my tongue made it all the way through that boot.
So quickly, too.
How many licks does it take to get to the center of Trump's boot?
I will say this about Harrison, though.
What's that?
Um, for all the, like, hey, Trump has failed kind of talk, he's a big man.
He's a big man.
He's big enough to admit that he was wrong.
Okay.
Although this clip is only 34 seconds long, and it ends with him saying, I wasn't actually
wrong.
Okay, well.
We thought he had what it took to do what was necessary to save this country.
And it would, I guess it would feel embarrassing if I cared about that sort of thing.
I'm not too big to admit that we were wrong.
We weren't wrong, really.
He could have.
He could have done it.
He just didn't.
He just didn't do it.
He didn't do it.
He didn't have what it takes.
Wow.
I'm big enough to admit we were wrong.
Actually, nevermind.
I am not.
Nevermind.
We weren't wrong.
Indeed.
I am not big enough to admit we were wrong.
Hold on.
Late breaking news.
We weren't wrong.
Excuse me, sir.
Denial can only get to you in the cliff.
It cannot get you to jump over it.
Yeah.
That's pretty amazing.
That's.
I'm a big enough man to admit I was wrong.
Actually, I was right.
Trump fucked up.
I do like that he's completely missing the point of being a big enough man is the sense
of like, I am an adult by immediately undercutting it.
Well, and I think also, it's my experience that when you talk about like being big enough
to admit you're wrong, that's usually the byproduct of like introspection and it's clear
that this isn't something that has been wrestled with or like, huh, what was it that led us
down the road to thinking that Trump was going to be our king?
No, it's almost like he'd heard other people say I'm a big enough man to admit when I'm
wrong a lot.
Maybe his dad, who is debating.
Yeah, yeah, this is supposed to be the thing that I say and then he walks it back because
he doesn't understand it whatsoever.
Yeah.
So there's another thing that's going on in Info Wars right now, of course.
Anybody who's listened to our shows aware of this, they're really mad at Q and QAnon.
And so Harrison is also there and he has this expression that he keeps using and that is
politics is war deferred, but that deferment no longer exists.
Okay.
We've never lied to you folks.
We have never put a friendly face on something that was horrific.
We have never told you to trust the plan that people were working behind the scenes that
you needed to do nothing.
Oh, really?
We've always shot straight here at Info Wars, so that's what I'm going to try to do today.
Really?
I'm going to try to do it in a way that doesn't get me on a list of some sort because this
is a brave new world.
Yuck.
This is a new situation that we are in.
We've been discussing it this entire week, really ever since the sixth.
Drink some coffee.
Yeah.
It is no longer safe to...
Hurry it up.
... express yourself believing that the First Amendment will protect you.
He says, broadcasting lies.
It's not the case anymore and we'll go through some major stories that show you that.
I don't want to show this video, this is a rant Alex Jones went on yesterday that I
think lays it out fairly well because this is a war now.
If politics is war deferred, if politics is a replacement for war where people we elect
do our fighting for us in the halls of government rather than us brawling it out in the streets,
that is no longer the case.
All right, so I guess it's time to brawl in the streets, Harrison.
I don't like his understanding of politics very much.
It can't be war deferred and also a replacement for war.
It's a delaying tactic.
If that's your description of democracy, we have a real problem.
It's troubling.
I think, again, this is just like him repeating things he's heard that do sound pretty good
if you're not paying attention.
Yeah, they do sound good.
Yeah, they roll off you pretty okay.
Politics is war deferred sounds like something someone strong would say.
Now here's the thing that's really funny.
He's introducing a report from Alex because Alex went on that rant about migrants and
so he's going to play that, but what's really funny is that at the end of that rant that
Alex did, he throws it to a Harrison Smith piece and so at the end of the video that
Harrison plays, Alex references a Harrison Smith video and then there's a long silence
or Harrison's like, oh God.
Okay, so it's like an ouroboros of bullshit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, for sure.
But this gets Harrison into thinking about how like, hey, if you're white and you're
young, shit's going to be bad.
If you're...
Yeah, yeah.
Calm down.
This is going to get really bad.
Okay.
But if you're like 50, you could just go out to the woods and wait it out.
You'll be fine.
All right.
But your children.
Okay.
Oh, think of the children.
Oh boy.
If you're over 50 or whatever, you might be able to live the rest of your life off your
meager retirement, enjoy it, have a nice little place in the mountains, watch the sunset,
drink your wine, listen to your old music, but your children and your children's children
are going to be a despised minority with no rights, no future, no ability to make anything
of themselves robbed constantly and the money given to people who hate them in order to
replace them.
Okay.
So you can't just ignore this anymore.
And if you do, you're part of the problem.
You need to be involved.
You need to be aware and we need to fight.
Not politically, literally.
I'm not calling for violence.
I'm letting you know violence is upon us implemented through the state.
So you're surgically.
So there seems to me to be very little difference between that mentality that Harrison is expressing
and the tiki torch wielding Nazis at the unite the right rally chanting Jews will not replace
us.
Yeah.
I'm going to go with zero difference.
I listened to info Wars a lot.
In my perspective, that was a very explicit overt plea to white nationalism to the point
where I was shocked by how blunt it was.
I was wondering what was up here.
So I went to the American journal page on band.video and there's some pretty mask off
stuff going on over there.
That doesn't surprise me.
Perhaps the most telling video title you'll immediately be confronted by is from January
21st titled quote, stop white genocide.
That is an intensely direct title for a video and the description really says it all quote
Harrison Smith explains why migration is the choice weapon of the elite when trying to
dominate and destroy a population.
Okay.
Oh boy.
It's tough to be more clear than this.
Harrison Smith is explicitly disseminating white nationalist narratives on the info Wars
morning show, which I recall, if I recall correctly, is supposed to be almost entirely
phone calls.
Yeah, I do remember that being the plan.
This is not something that's just like tacitly supported by Alex by virtue of the fact that
it's on his network.
It's just a more explicit recitation of the talking points that Alex himself spouts constantly.
Yeah.
It's almost like Alex hired Steve Doocy.
I didn't want to just point out that Harrison put out a video decrying his fears about white
genocide and then say that the work was done.
There are far too many lazy commentators who will react to titles of things without looking
at the body of the piece and I strive not to fall into that trap.
So I watched the video.
The structure that Harrison is going for is to make the argument that the treatment of
white Europeans in the United States is the same as the treatment of the Uyghur people
by the Chinese government, and if people are comfortable with saying that the treatment
of the Uyghurs could be called genocide, then Harrison's well within his rights to claim
that white people are the target of a genocide here and in Europe.
Uh.
Right.
In order to bolster this claim, Harrison does some pretty predictable false equivalencies.
For instance, he mentions that the Chinese government is accused of forcing Uyghurs to
be sterilized or be required to take birth control.
Harrison then claims that this is the same as the U.S. offering people birth control
and that somehow decades of propaganda are responsible for people making family planning
choices.
Yeah, that sounds right.
This is a completely insane false equivalence and I don't see a good way for Harrison to
defend that flimsy ass plank in his argument.
So he doesn't.
He just says it.
No, I don't think there's any way not to hear him say this and think what you're saying
is white men are going to be treated like white men have treated everybody else in this
country and that's worthy of killing everyone.
Hmm?
Maybe?
Yeah.
So then, Harrison gets to the point in the video where the argument pivots to immigration
because at this point, you know, at the beginning he's laying out this groundwork and he's saying
that it's the same as the treatment of the Uyghurs.
Sure.
Nonsense.
Naturally.
Harrison's primary source that he's reading from is a July 4th article that was posted
on NPR.
Here Harrison discusses his contention that white people are being the subject of genocide.
As the government, and get this, and if this isn't genocide, I don't know what is.
The government has brought millions of Han Chinese settlers into the region with promises
of high salary, jobs, and free housing.
My God, ethnic migrants, economic migrants coming into a region for high paying jobs?
That's genocide, obviously, when it's in China.
What about here?
It's diversity here.
You have to understand the distinction, folks.
Do you support giving First Nations land back?
When happening to you, it's a good thing.
It's diversity.
It's our strength.
It's what we need.
When it's happening to Uyghur Muslims in China, it's genocide, by God.
What about white people?
This is what people...
I don't know.
I mean...
Hello.
Come on.
Wake up, dammit.
So a couple of important points here.
The first is that the guy who was interviewed by NPR does not say that the form of immigration
that Harrison is discussing is genocide.
He says that it's a part of a, quote, policy of ethno-racial domination, which is still
bad, but it's not the same thing.
Harrison stops reading right before the guy says, quote, the reason why this has changed,
we do need to probably call it a genocide, is quite simply because the evidence now for
the first time very specifically meets one of the five criteria set forth by the UN Convention
for the Punishment and Prevention of the Crime of Genocide from 1948, which specifically
says the suppression of birth.
This guy is clearly expressing that bringing the Han Chinese to replace Uyghur workers
doesn't meet the definition of genocide.
But now that there's evidence of birth suppression, that does meet the definition according to
this guy.
Yeah.
Harrison is completely misrepresenting this researcher's words because his agenda is to
yell about immigration to the United States and stress white aggrievement, not to cover
any of these issues in a meaningful way that helps the audience better understand the world
and hopefully pushes public opinion towards better policy preferences.
He's trying to make white people scared of non-white people, and he's trying to use the
prop of the Chinese state oppression in order to justify his shoddy arguments.
None of the complaints that Harrison brings up here rise to the level of meeting the UN
definition of genocide, which is the standard of the conversation as presented in his primary
source.
Article 2 of the UN Convention lays out the five acts that constitute genocide, and what
makes it an even more difficult argument for Harrison to make is that it says, quote, genocide
means any of the following acts committed with intent to destroy, in whole or in part,
a national, ethnical, racial, or religious group.
The word intent is going to be a really serious problem for Harrison.
The argument he's setting out to make requires that he somehow demonstrate that immigration
of non-white people into the United States is being done with the intention of destroying
in whole or in part white people.
That's going to be really impossible for him to do without slipping into explicit white
supremacist or neo-Nazi conspiracy theories.
I mean, I would just have to say, manifest destiny, and if you want to start pulling
some shit, then fine, start giving land back to the First Nations.
Otherwise shut the fuck up, because these are the people who celebrate manifest destiny
as the greatest thing that's ever happened.
Well, it had something to do with God telling.
So Harrison goes on to complain some more in this piece.
We're taking a little side tour into his Stop White Genocide video, so this isn't from the
inauguration day, but I got really sort of curious when he was talking about your ancestors
being a hated minority, and all of that, it was like, this seems like code, and I wanted
to understand a little better, and then I found this Stop White Genocide piece, and
I was like, holy shit.
The United Nations Convention for the Punishment and Prevention of the Crime of Genocide from
1948 specifies the suppression of birth as one of the primary attributes of a genocide.
Now, if I was some sort of insane conspiracy theorist, I might point to the ongoing attempt
by many, many mainstream outlets to suppress the birth rate of white Americans.
Say white people don't have children.
You shouldn't have children, white people.
It goes on and on and on.
We've seen this headline over and over again, but that's not genocide.
That's a good thing, because remember, white people bad.
I don't think that makes Harrison sound like a conspiracy theorist.
I think it makes him sound like a flagrant racist.
That's exactly what it makes him sound like.
Harrison Smith isn't seeing the media constantly saying that white people shouldn't have kids
because they're not.
He's seeing things like interracial couples represented in commercials and sitcoms, and
he's experiencing that as an attempt to say that white people shouldn't just reproduce
with each other.
I decided to check out what happens when you Google white people shouldn't have kids.
Looking for some headlines, looking for some digging around.
Can I guess, just real quick, you are going to find roughly 10,000 reactionary right-wing
articles about this, and very few, if any.
Not so much.
I found the first eight results are just about raising children who are capable of talking
about race issues.
Oh, that's nice.
I don't say that white people shouldn't have kids.
The ninth result is a 2017 article out of The Independent titled, quote, seven reasons
people shouldn't have children according to science.
That has nothing to do with white people not having kids.
It's more of an exploration of the research into things like changing friendships after
one person has a kid and the other doesn't, or how according to one poll, quote, non-parents
tend to lead healthier lifestyles than parents.
Was that the one, okay, that was 2017, right?
Yeah.
I was interviewed for that one, and they rejected mine, which was white people don't have kids.
Oh.
Yeah.
Maybe Harrison got the early version.
Maybe Harrison accidentally talked to that one.
Then the results go back to being about, you know, people being able to talk about race
with children.
The closest thing that gets really, like, the closest to really complex racial issues
that you find is that there's a couple articles about, like, the dynamics of adoption.
Yeah, trans adoption is a real huge, yeah.
You see some articles discussing that, but that's not what Harrison's talking about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can't tell page seven of the search results to actually even find an article that's actually
about people advocating that people not have children, and again, it's not race-based.
It's a 2019 editorial piece on the BBC about a group called the Antinatalists, who just
want no one to have kids.
Yeah, well.
And there's also the Voluntary Human Extinction Movement there, but that's not racially based
either.
I assume Harrison also looked up a lot of New York Times articles and the like from
anywhere between 1878 and 1939, whenever everyone was advocating for black people to voluntarily
not have children ever again?
Nah.
Oh, okay.
I don't know.
I would like some citations.
I don't think that Harrison's making a serious point here.
I think this is just a white identity talking point being presented as if it represents
reality.
Totally.
And that's fucking gross.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I would like more ideas, I would like concrete examples of what white men are going
to face, young white men are going to face, and I would like him to put those up on a
wall somewhere, just so we can refer back to them every time one of them occurs, I imagine.
I also just resent when people like this present this idea, like, we've seen all the hundred
articles telling white people not to have kids.
I haven't.
Name one.
Yeah.
Pick one.
And also, it can't be something that's clearly satire.
Yeah.
And it can't be something that you said.
Okay, if it's McSweeney's or me, then you don't get to reference it.
So like I said, this entire argument really just hinges on Harrison trying to make the
treatment of white people be equivalent to the Uyghur and other minority treatment in
China.
Sure.
I want to continue to lay out the case for white genocide, I guess, is what I'm doing
here, because after all, I'm one of these crazy conspiracy theorists that thinks genocide
is bad.
I agree.
I know.
It's just, it's just nutty.
I have this weird consistency where I think the genocide of the Uyghur people in China
is bad, and I think the genocide of European people in Europe is also bad.
I don't understand the complex geography that goes into determining whether one is
bad or not.
I just, I'm just such a simple guy.
To me, genocide equals bad, and I just don't have the college thinking, the university
brain that's necessary to understand why it's good when it's against white people and bad
when it's against the Uyghur minority.
I just, I just am too dumb, I guess.
I don't know.
I don't think Harrison is too stupid.
His problem isn't stupidity or not understanding, it's that he's outrageously racist, and he's
also unfortunately smart enough to know that it's bad for business to just admit that and
live openly.
That's why he has to make these strained comparisons and false equivalencies to try
to pretend that the experience of being white in the United States or in Europe is in any
way comparable to being Uyghur in China.
That's a ludicrous proposition, and it's why he has to pretend that allegations of
forced sterilization in China are the same as the availability of birth control here.
Any right thinking person would hear that argument and recognize pretty quickly how
stupid it is, but that's because it's a crypto argument.
The argument or the false equivalence doesn't actually exist to be taken seriously.
It's only there because Harrison knows he can't come out and express his true white
nationalist positions without consequences.
I wouldn't say that genocide against Uyghurs is bad and genocide against white people is
good.
I would contest Harrison's point that the situations each group are facing are in any
way comparable, and that's where Harrison's argument would completely fall apart.
I know that because I was listening to a twenty minute video where he's trying to defend
that premise and he's failing embarrassingly and really letting his racism show.
But that said, the Lonely Shepherd by Zamfir slaps.
Okay.
All right.
The king of the pan flute.
Oh.
Harrison does have a couple of decent music choices.
Okay.
He has some good cues that I haven't heard from other Infowars shows, including the Lonely
Shepherd.
Yeah.
I mean I would-
I guess it's the morning show.
You gotta be a little chiller.
Yeah.
That pan flute really does-
That wakes you up.
That Zamfir branded himself the king of the pan flute as if it was a crowded space.
Pop culture pan flutist.
I think that's why you have to brand yourself as a bombastic something, otherwise people
aren't gonna be like, oh this guy's really good at the pan flute.
He's the king of the pan flute.
It's like Chuck Mangione, the king of the flugelhorn.
He is the king of the flugelhorn, that's true.
No one's gonna fuck with his title.
He's not wrong.
No.
The Children of Sanchez, such a good song.
Good soundtrack.
Alright.
Anyway.
Harrison gets to going about, eh, he just keeps going.
Yeah.
The 1948 Convention on the Prevention and Punishment of the Crime of Genocide, which
has been ratified by at least 149 countries, including China, defines genocide as any of
these acts committed with the intent to destroy a national, ethnic, racial, or religious group.
Killing its members, causing them seriously bodily or mental harm.
By the way, vast, vast majority of suicides, vast majority of medication for depression,
is all on white people.
But that's a good thing because white people are evil.
So even assuming that everything Harrison just said is true from a statistical perspective,
it's still meaningless in terms of his argument that there's a white genocide going on.
Again, he's using this 1948 UN definition of genocide that includes the word intent
as a really important element of the definition.
I mean, Harrison works for Infowars, so he probably shouldn't even care what the UN thinks
about the subject, but he's operating off that definition, so that's the conversation
that's being had.
In order for his argument to carry any weight, Harrison is going to have to demonstrate and
prove the following.
One, that there are in fact disproportionate medication and suicide rates between races
that cannot be explained by other factors, like income inequality or access to healthcare.
Two, that this is the result of a concerted plan by some group as an attempt to destroy
white people.
Harrison can't even come close to either of these.
The best he can do is suggest that mental health practices like psychiatric medication
are an attempt to kill off white people, and suggest that that's the way it is because
someone's out to get white people.
That's all he can do, because there is no argument here.
There's only an appeal to emotion, only an appeal to fear.
This is an attempt to give racist people listening a way to express their racism without sounding
racist.
It's honestly pretty pathetic.
Yeah.
Also, a recent paper from the Division of Vital Statistics out of the CDC reflects that
in 2017, once you adjust for population, the group with by far the highest rate of suicide
is non-Hispanic American Indian or Alaska Native women.
I eagerly await Harrison's coverage of that.
Yeah, I would be interested to hear that.
Oh, I know, I wouldn't be interested to hear that.
So in order to bolster his claims that there's a white genocide going on, Harrison brings
up the case of Ireland.
He seems to think that their entire population is going to be replaced with immigrants because
of a need to do so in order to make their pension system work.
Here's the profoundly racist and idiotic way that his segment on white genocide ends, and
I will explain to you on the other side why this is very dumb.
I don't like what's happening to the Uyghurs in China.
We should be defending these people who are being systematically eradicated by their governmental
organizations.
And on the other hand, I don't want the people of Ireland to be systematically eliminated
by their super state governmental organization.
I don't think the pension system is worth replacing every single person in your country
with a foreigner.
There's plenty to go around.
Hell, there's more, there's more Bangladeshis in a single district of a single city of that
country than there are in the entire nation of Ireland.
So maybe we can help out Ireland, maybe we can help increase the birth rates, maybe we
can stop this genocide, at least in Ireland, and then maybe we can expand that to the rest
of the world and recognize that white people are a global minority, the least population
out of any racial division, if you want to take the big ones, Asian, black, whatever.
Whites are the smallest, and they're being genocided, and that's the headline.
Stop white genocide.
So Harrison is working off a primary source that's an article in the Independent out of
Ireland.
The headline of the article is, quote, Ireland needs four million migrants to sustain state
pension system.
Harrison takes that information and combines it with the fact that Ireland's population
is only like five million, so that must mean that they want to replace everyone with immigrants
to save the pension system.
Yeah, that sounds like the Irish.
The problem is that Harrison didn't do any work, like even reading the article.
The first thing that jumps out at you if you do read the article is that the idea that
the country needed four million migrants to make the pension system work was something
that was used as an illustration of the problem the country was facing regarding having an
aging population and meeting the pensions, in a meeting of the Pensions Committee.
It wasn't being suggested as the plan to fix the pension system.
They were saying that by 2051 they would need four million new people paying into the system
to balance out all the people over 65 drawing from it.
If Harrison wasn't such a dopey racist fuck, he would have kept reading to the part of
the article where it says, quote, but the statistician and commission members say it's
unlikely that net inward migration will reverse the current trends, and some migrants would
become pensioners themselves.
This article is about a discussion of why this wouldn't be a solid plan to fix the
pension system, because if that were the only approach taken, you'd end up creating more
net problems for the pension system than you fix.
The article goes on to say, quote, Irish fiscal advisory council chair Sebastian Barnes said
tax and spending would have to adjust to fund pensions while pension age would need to rise.
Social protection minister Heather Humphreys spoke at the first meeting and made it clear
that a reduction in the amount of state pension was not to be considered.
This article is not about Ireland bringing in four million migrants to fix the pension
system, but the headline is written in such a way that it's easy to use it that way.
The four million number is used as an illustration of the imbalance that will exist between those
paying into the system and those drawing from it, but because the headline is poorly written
and because Harrison's a lazy craven racist, this article can be used to justify an argument
that Ireland is engaging in white genocide in order to save its pension system.
Harrison knows what he's doing.
He knows that this article isn't about bringing in four million migrants to Ireland, but he
also knows that because it looks like it is, he can mislead his audience into thinking
that it is and hide his racist agenda behind that misrepresentation.
Anyway, that's the end of our side tour through Harrison Smith's piece on white genocide.
I can say with a fair amount of confidence that this special report was quite possibly
the most transparent and most poorly argued racism I've ever seen on Infowars.
It's the racism equivalent of Harrison saying that the capital had fallen and patriots were
in charge on January 6th.
He's not hiding what he is.
Yeah.
He is a fucking...
Yeah, this is...
Because what is he saying whenever he says we can stop the genocide of Ireland is just
we can make sure that Ireland remains a white nation, and then we can save everybody else.
So Europeans for European nations, Africans for African nations, Chinese people for China,
and no mixing at all.
And the primary source that he's working off of for this article is a headline that he's
misrepresenting in a way to use as a racist cudgel.
Totally.
Like, it's outrageous.
Yeah.
I mean, it's to be expected on some level, but it's pretty...
It's like using story math problems as like, okay, if the migrant caravan is racing towards
the border at 60 miles an hour, but the white nationalists are going towards the border
from the opposite direction at 50 miles an hour, then the white people will be exterminated.
I don't like this quiz.
Bad quiz.
Yeah, it is a bad quiz.
I started to wonder about this, and one of the things that I think is interesting is
that like, yeah, I mean, a lot of the same themes are exactly the same as what Alex talks
about, but just more crypto.
Like Alex is way, way less close to the edge, let's say, than Harrison, because he knows
that there's consequences for being too overtly racist.
People will treat you in a certain way.
He'll lose his ability to argue, oh, everyone says I'm a racist, they all lie about me,
that kind of shit.
I just wonder, you know, it makes me feel like there's two possible dynamics, and one
is that like Alex is thinking, fuck it, let Harrison do a show that's extreme as hell.
Test the white nationalist water.
Yeah, let's see if that's a tap market that we can tap.
Is anybody going to punish us for this?
Or is it the case that Alex has run out of fucking steam to the point where a bigot like
Harrison is taking over, or not taking over the whole thing, but like he has his own show
and he's like, I'm going to speak to you fucking freely, I don't care, who else are you going
to get to host a show?
You need to sell your dumb pills.
That's fair.
I don't know, it's outrageous though, like I think that Harrison might be a much bigger
problem than he appears.
I mean, Harrison isn't even smart enough to do the dumbest, easiest thing that you can
possibly do, which is immediately do what Alex does after saying something that's explicitly
white nationalist and say, now you know me, I don't care about white, black, Hispanic
or whatever.
He doesn't even bother to do that cop out.
No.
What an asshole.
Because I think he's speaking.
He's just a white nationalist, yeah.
Speaking freely.
Yeah.
So anyway, now we jump back to inauguration day.
Sure.
Sorry to take that side tour, but I felt like it was important.
It was a good detour.
Does that...
You got to know when the whites are coming.
Well, I mean, I really felt like that was something...
That's my argument for white genocide.
You got to know when they're coming.
I felt like that was something that was behind the clip of him talking about your children
will be hated minorities.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Look how that is.
I was not wrong to suspect that this is the kind of thing you talk about.
Yeah.
And now we get back to the 20th and this is a scary thought.
So we know how fake the news is.
Imagine how fake history is.
You see this play out in real time.
We see the truth with our own eyes and then we hear the lies about it.
We see the truth of the past.
Head back to us.
Imagine how false history is.
That is so scary.
That mentality is so scary, especially considering a week ago we had Alex presenting a completely
false version of Hitler's rise to power.
InfoWars does so much historical revisionism surrounding very serious issues.
You know, hey, we've created an alternative reality for us to live in and we say that
everybody else is lying.
Can you imagine how much more lies are going on with history?
Yeah.
It's fucked up.
You're, you're basically, yeah, you're, you're absolutely right.
Like, hey, we've defeated reality in the present.
Our only way to go now is the past unless somebody invents a time machine.
Well, I think, I think that that's been the project of a lot of fascist types for a long
time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, neo-Nazis have revisionist ideas about what happened in Germany.
Well, I mean, when you allow the Texas board to have any influence over textbooks whatsoever,
you're not going to get a real history.
Alex has revisionist ideas about the Confederacy.
It's not, it's not too surprising.
How many people learned that it was about states' rights in school?
How many people?
Probably Alex.
Millions, millions, maybe the entire country in our elementary school system that is designed
to teach you history and for you to take into the world, they lied straight to your face
when you were seven.
What are you going to do?
So Harrison is, is going on here on inauguration day and he's talking about how the, the mainstream
media, the MSM, the globalists, they've taken the people who believe that Trump won and
they've turned the idea that Trump won into the big lie that they're being misrepresented.
This is just nonsense.
This they're calling the big lie and they're saying, even pointing this out or people trying
to represent their constituents who are all calling out saying, this was fake, please,
for the love of God, you're supposed to be our representative.
Please say something, please stop this deal from going forward.
They are now being portrayed as racist, fascist, implementing a new Jim Crow.
I mean, this is absurd.
This is beyond anything we've ever experienced before and at the heart of it.
This is a war against white people.
That's what you have to realize.
They are making a concerted effort now.
They're out in the open.
They're not hiding it.
They're not couching it in any friendly phrases.
They're saying white people are bad, must be destroyed, must be rooted out, must be
ripped out by the roots, must be eliminated from this country.
So at this point I got a little bit worried.
I was like, I'm listening to, I was just checking in on inauguration day.
I got a little sniff of something that I thought maybe Harrison was a bigot.
I went and watched his stop white genocide video.
Now I come back to the inauguration, he's talking about the war on whites.
The war on white people.
Oh no.
I was like, what did I get into?
They've declared war on the whites.
It wasn't that white nationalists literally tried to overthrow the country.
They've declared war on all white people.
I was like, okay, when I sat down to prepare this episode, I was thinking, all right, I'll
breeze through Harrison's dumb ass and then we'll get to Alex and that'll be when the
episode really begins.
No, this is going to be half the episode probably talking about Harrison Smith.
Brutal.
Yeah.
Terrible.
He is real biggity.
Let's just stop for one second and remember that the evil globalists are now declaring
war on white people.
According to Harrison.
Even though last year, only a few months ago, their plan B was murdering everyone.
Sure.
Well, plan B is not to be remembered now because it's not the profitable angle.
Well, that's fair.
Yeah.
We have, uh, we've gotten a new sales flow chart.
Now it's white.
Whiteness only.
Certainly for Harrison's show.
Yeah.
So he also wishes that Trump was a little bit more authoritarian and he's talking about
this in the framework of sort of optics differences between Trump's inauguration and Biden's.
Um, he's being really dumb here.
When Donald Trump won duly elected, nobody expected it, but he did it.
He pulled it out.
He pulled, he pulled through.
He got elected president of the United States and everybody was very, very concerned about
authoritarianism.
I'll tell you if in 2016, before the Trump inauguration, DC was filled with 65,000 troops
and there were people going on TV who were heads of the army saying, we need to have
purity tests and we need to kick out anybody that doesn't adhere to our view of what it
is to be an American and reality entire national mall was covered in flags because they weren't
letting any people come.
And the entire city of Washington, DC was locked down like the green zone in Iraq.
You tried to throw a little freaked out.
I would have thought, Oh God, maybe this is the authoritarianism they're warning about.
Of course that didn't happen.
None of that happened.
Nothing.
Just authoritarian in the slightest.
I wish it had been more so.
I wish he had been more like the, the monster that they portrayed him as.
Maybe we wouldn't be in the situation we're in now if he'd actually used an iron fist.
Ah, what a shock.
Someone who works at info wars revealing that they wish Trump was a dictator.
If they think history is a lie, these motherfuckers can't remember two weeks ago clearly.
No, I know.
That was the thing that really bothered me about that, like, uh, that description of
the inauguration.
It was like, you're pretending there's no cause to these effects.
Did, did I, Dan, now I could be wrong, but I don't remember in January of 2017, uh, liberals
overthrowing the Capitol.
No, that didn't happen.
That didn't happen?
And that kind of affects this inauguration.
Also, the smaller crowds pandemic, the flags also about a memorial to those lost.
Representative to the pandemic.
They keep bringing up the flags as if it's just like a way to fill space because people
couldn't be there.
It's like, no, there was a symbolic meaning to that.
Yeah, it wasn't that we committed, uh, oh, well, I mean, some could argue even a genocide
with intent to kill the poor.
If you go back and look at Kushner's fucking statements.
And then, uh, in terms of like, uh, the screening of service members, that is also because some
were involved in storming the Capitol.
There was that.
Um, yeah.
So I mean, like, I think that when you have a situation like that, um, it's important
not to allow yourself to give in to the impulse to go on a McCarthy-esque witch hunt.
But at the same time, the conversation about extremism and extremists infiltrating law
enforcement and, uh, uh, the, the services like that is something that is long overdue.
Uh, but you have to retain your, your, uh, sensibility about it.
You can't just be like, oh, this guy donates to the Heritage Foundation.
Yeah.
Therefore he's an extremist.
No.
You can't go that far.
You need to be careful.
But that's a conversation that you should never pretend you can have with someone like
Harrison Smith.
Yeah, no, it wasn't like in 1863 Lincoln was like, well, of course I need to have a confederate
in my secret service detail.
Why wouldn't I have a confederate soldier in my secret service team?
It would be discrimination for me to get rid of this literal enemy of the United States
from my secret service detail.
And then I would also like to say, um, just in the same way that like the screening of
things is like a very sensible, reasonable thing.
You can understand why it would happen, but you have to resist going too far with it.
Of course.
I would say that the, like the presence of security forces in, uh, and around the inauguration
is something that I don't like to see.
It's not good.
No, it's fucked up.
Yeah.
I can be against that.
And at the same time, be enough of an adult to understand why it's happening.
Yeah.
I don't have to, I can, I can be against the militarization of the police and still
recognize, hey, some people fucking stormed the Capitol a week, two weeks ago.
And I understand that you're like, oh no, there were so many troops there.
I understand that.
But you need to understand there were so many there because they're worried.
There are a lot of you wanting to overthrow the United States government.
And there were people online, uh, impotently or sincerely discussing plans for other, uh,
things.
You know, and I do think that probably if it was less or if it was more than two weeks
in between, there might've been a better solution that would have been available.
But it's a really, it's a really time crunch kind of situation.
Well, you know, America, we never overreact to situations.
Sure.
Yeah.
And again, like what I'm saying is those things are valid concerns to have.
Yeah, absolutely.
Just not something that you should ever find common cause or ally ship with info warriors
about because they're not sincere.
And it's your fault that those things happened.
Well, anyway.
You are the one who literally said the Capitol has fallen to the Patriots.
He did, but he pretends that he didn't because he's against it now.
Sure.
Fuck off.
No, you don't get to do this.
He shouldn't.
So, um, you may recall that Alex has said that, uh, if the host of the American journal
doesn't take calls, they will not be hosting it any longer.
That is true.
Harrison doesn't take calls immediately, but he does get to some calls and these calls
are not good.
Filled with happy people.
Oh boy.
Greetings Harrison.
This is the Renegade Patriot in Ohio.
I use this calling in because, uh, I've been listening for 11 years in silence, but I prompted
me to make my own YouTube channel that was inspired partly by info wars and by a political
prisoner named Charles Dyer, Sergeant Charles Dyer, known as July four Patriot on YouTube.
In case you're curious, Charles Dyer is not a political prisoner in 2012, he was convicted
of sexually abusing his six year old daughter and sentenced to 30 years in jail.
He's been turned into the hero of the extreme right wing who curiously call everyone they
don't like pedophiles because he was a member of the oath keepers and was the type of extreme
right wing militia guy that when his house was searched, they found a fucking grenade
launcher.
Anyway, it says a whole lot about a fellow when they call into Harrison's show and say
they were inspired to start a YouTube channel because of info wars and Charles Dyer.
Yeah, that one, that one solves most problems.
Now that caller was bad.
Yeah.
Not great.
Nothing compared to this next caller.
Oh, that's not good.
This caller is...
It can't escalate.
Oh boy.
After analyzing the top 10 high rank picks for Biden, all 10 of them have a dual citizenship
in the state of Israel.
So you know, Trump tried his best to get that support from the Israeli lobby and really
he was basically the best president for Israel ever.
I mean, that's actually true, yet it didn't even work.
They don't support him now and they're all, Biden's their man.
So we've been over this before, but when you hear a right wing dumb dumb like this caller
bring up someone having dual citizenship with Israel, it's an expression of deep antisemitism.
It goes hand in hand with the Holocaust didn't happen.
This guy wants to complain that Biden has Jewish people in his cabinet, but he knows
that that looks bad.
So he tries to couch things, tries to couch that hatred of Jews and language that has
to do with concerns about dual citizenship.
This is a classic neo-Nazi talking point that the Jewish criminals who they believe run
the world, they don't care that what they're doing is illegal because their Jewish heritage
gives them right of return citizenship in Israel.
So they can just flee there and avoid being held accountable.
Uh, Dan, I saw Die Hard 2.
Diplomatic immunity.
This is what's at the core of this caller and what he's expressing here.
And it's been an insidious antisemitic trope for decades.
Since Die Hard 2.
This caller, incidentally, is just responding to a meme that went around on Twitter from
an account called Syndrome of a Down, which claimed, quote, all 10 of Biden's high profile
appointees are Jews.
That's right, every single one.
This is accompanied by a screenshot depicting 10 Biden appointees next to Israeli flags,
which is unsettling.
This is a really simple game this Nazi is playing where they just cherry pick Jewish
people Biden has appointed to various offices, then assert baselessly that these 10 are the
most high profile appointees, whatever that means, and that it's suspicious that these
people are Jewish.
Of course.
This is transparent.
And anyone who's calling in to enforce to repeat this talking point is absolutely an
antisemite until proven otherwise.
Totally.
Quite a show Harrison is hosting here, just full of white identity based fear, callers
inspired by patriot pedophiles and potential neo-Nazis.
Yep.
Now, Harrison tries to fact check this guy.
Oh yeah?
And he finds the meme.
Oh my God.
And so he just reads the meme.
Is Joe Rogan fact checking here?
Yeah.
Hell, you're making a lot of good points.
You have, uh, the, the image here that's been going around all 10 of Biden's high profile
appointees are Jews and dual citizens with Israel.
You have secretary of the treasury, Janet Yellen, attorney general, Merrick Garland,
secretary of home real quick there.
The meme that he's reading off of doesn't say and dual citizens of Israel.
It just says Jews.
Yeah.
Harrison has added that because he realizes don't want to do it.
Oh boy.
I'm going to hit that J too hard.
I have to soften this a little bit.
Otherwise, otherwise it looks as antisemitic as it is.
Yeah.
Homeland security, Alejandro Mayorkas, uh, director of national intelligence, Avril Haines,
uh, white house chief of staff, Ron Klain, secretary of state, Anthony Blinken, deputy
secretary of state, Wendy Sherman, secretary of state for political affairs, Victoria Newland,
the office of science and technology policy, Eric Lander, director of the central intelligence
agency, David S. Cohen.
Now call me crazy.
I think the people serving in our government serving in the American government should
not be dual citizens with another country.
Am I crazy for thinking, am I an anti-Semite?
Yes.
You are super antisemitic.
That is exactly what you are.
That's really, really bad when you traffic in dual loyalty tropes about Jewish Americans.
It's super basic stuff in terms of antisemitism and I can explain one of the reasons why it's
really obvious.
Harrison's complaint is that these people are dual citizens in the United States and
Israel.
Having dual citizenship in this case is defined, defined solely as these people being Jewish.
Insisting the people who have dual citizenship being in government is suspicious or wrong
is really just a way for these people to say that they think Jewish people shouldn't be
in government without having to say something so obviously antisemitic.
Harrison isn't an idiot.
He understands this dynamic fully well.
He's a flagrant bigot who knows that daddy Alex will fire him if he speaks too freely,
I suspect.
And so you do stuff like this.
This is outrageous.
This can't be like, I was aghast at this.
This is not what I expected on inauguration day.
Out and out white supremacy?
And yeah, yeah.
Honestly I kind of was expecting this on inauguration day because you can't say that they're going
to kill everybody now.
I expected it before.
Well we've seen plenty of it before.
But this is- Not quite.
Not quite.
No Jews should be in the government.
And maybe it's a function of Harrison Smith being like not a great broadcaster.
That he's being this- Yeah, yeah.
This transparent about it.
He doesn't have the chops to be less racist.
Man, and this caller keeps going.
Oh.
Why?
Well remember there was this nice sweet little Jewish lady who came onto Oprah and said that
within the Jewish community there are people who are not Jewish.
They're hiding under Judaism but they're not Jews.
They don't follow Moses, they don't follow the Torah, they don't follow the Ten Commandments
so if you're a Jew and you actually follow the Ten Commandments, you know, you're not
the problem.
We're not talking about you.
But there are people who hide behind this Judaism and she openly admitted they are breeding
babies with really obese people who you can't even tell they're pregnant.
And then they do satanic rituals and when Oprah asked her, why are you doing this?
She goes, for power.
Like it was an obvious thing, like you should know.
So I don't think these people are actually Jews.
I think they're part of an organization that is satanic that is hiding behind Judaism.
Wow.
I was listening to this caller go hard on the antisemitism and listening to Harrison
be completely open to it and not shut it down at all and I was thinking, I wonder how long
it's going to be until we get into blood libel.
Yeah.
Turns out not too long.
Not long at all.
This Oprah segment that the caller is bringing up is from May 1989 and it was a huge embarrassment
for Oprah.
What happened is that there was that whole satanic panic going on in America.
The McMartin preschool trial was in its like sixth year and lurid stories of ritualistic
satanic abuse were widespread, the idea that they were widespread in every neighborhood,
that was drawing ratings.
Oprah tried to do an episode of her talk show about ritualistic satanic abuse cases and
one of her guests was a Jewish woman who told all sorts of insane stories about her family
performing ritual murders since the 1700s, that it was prevalent in Jewish families and
the police knew about it and didn't do anything.
Huh.
Oprah had attempted to frame the conversation by introducing the guest as someone who is
quote mentally disturbed and under psychiatric care, but I think that's not good enough.
A better move would not be doing this kind of interview with someone you have to preemptively
introduce as an unreliable source of information.
Just so everyone knows, I want you to say that this person is not fit to be on TV.
Good.
And now we're going to exploit her!
Exactly!
In the past it's putting a mentally unstable person in a position where they're being exploited
for ratings and at worst it was allowing a mentally unstable person to spread deeply
dangerous accusations about a religious community.
Either way, if this had happened nowadays, Oprah's career would have been over.
No, we would have fucked everybody up.
Somehow in 1989.
Ellen was just a dick!
In 1989, you can have this kind of a scandal and granted, you know, I was able to find
a bunch of articles about Oprah meeting with leaders in the Jewish community and apologizing
and responding to criticism, but like, this should never have happened to begin with.
No, no, no, no, no.
So producers better have been fired.
Yeah, it's a good thing that 30 years later we're still hearing about it.
That's how good it was.
Well, from Nazi callers on Harrison's Nazi show.
Yeah, there's that.
This show is absolutely mind-blowing and how offensive it is, this American Journal.
Harrison Smith seems way, way more committed to or just willing to broadcast explicit racism
and anti-semitism to the audience.
Yeah.
I was taken aback by how horrible this is.
I would say, I think, I mean, maybe there's just a simple explanation, which is that Harrison
isn't rich enough to want to protect money more than anybody who's not white.
I can't imagine that he has a more lucrative offer than what he's doing at Infowars.
Absolutely.
And I can't imagine Alex pays him anywhere near what David Knight got.
That's true.
And I also, I would imagine that if Alex wanted him to curb these behaviors, he would.
Maybe.
And then he would get an alias and write a blog.
Well, that's probably true.
Start a YouTube channel where he wears a mask and bores everyone with racism.
That would be linked back to Infowars.com too, yeah.
Undoubtedly.
Yeah.
So Harrison takes another call and apparently what needs to happen is, you know how Infowars
is obsessed with the idea that there are no-go zones all over Europe, where the Muslims won't
let people in?
Absolutely.
Well, Harrison believes that they need to make some no-go zones in America, basically.
Okay.
Well, we're going to move into a very new dynamic.
And I've said it before, I think geographic approximation will suddenly become very important.
I think you need to find like-minded people that you can be near, that you can protect
each other, that you can actually put up a substantial force in order to prevent the
American forces from coming in and robbing you of the rights that you have as a sovereign
individual.
I think, you know, personally, maybe I'm a little biased because I'm from Texas, but
I can't think of a better place to gather patriots and say, everybody who's out there
in America, I know it would suck to have to leave your home and go to a different place,
but if we stay de-separated, if we stay sort of in these small pockets around and around,
they'll come one by one and scoop us all up.
You have to, we have to gather in a single place.
We have to defend that place.
We have to create areas of land that the powers that be cannot break into, cannot get into.
We need to have our own autonomous zones around the country.
Okay.
All I heard was, I thought sundown towns were a great idea and I don't understand why we
ever stopped that.
Was there something wrong with sundown towns, Dan?
It's strange.
Yeah.
This show gets really weird and I lost my taste for it at a certain point.
I have very much.
I had a lot of conversation about getting people to move to Texas to secede.
He has a South African caller lady who seems to think that apartheid didn't happen, but
I couldn't make sense of what she was saying and so I don't have any clips of it.
It was just, it was kind of all over the place.
And so here is how he goes out to break before Alex joins him for a little guest appearance
on the American Journal.
This is bleak.
Interesting agencies to review their actions and ensure racial equity.
Everything's going to be based off this.
He's talking about like some of Biden's policy initiatives.
Yeah, I'm seeing it.
Racial equity, which basically means robbing white people and rewarding non-white people
in order to basically do a genocide on white people.
I mean, it's not, let's not mince words here.
Everything that the Chinese are doing to the Uyghur Muslims are exactly what the plans
are for the Biden administration for white people.
I mean, when you say it's a good thing and we're making policy in order to decrease the
share of the population that white people hold, that is a genocidal policy.
Let's again, let's not mince words, let's not pretend like this is something that it
isn't.
This is a genocidal policy to essentially eradicate anybody from standing up against
these people.
And it all has to do with the fact that white people historically have been the only civilization
as far as the world is concerned that actually puts in freedom into their governmental organizations.
And that is mostly based on the fact that Christianity is a European religion.
So third hour begins on the other side.
So now we've shifted into white supremacy from white nationalism.
We're straight up there.
No arguing that.
You know, I will say this.
This show is nuts.
I will say this.
I think Harrison has absolutely succeeded.
When he said earlier, he is going to lay out the case for white genocide.
I get what you're saying.
He nailed it.
Calm down.
Oh, he nailed it.
Your satire.
Your joke.
Yeah.
So Alex comes on to stop by the Journal and I was weirded out by this, actually.
You're watching American Journal on Infowars.com, I'm Harrison Smith joined by Alex Jones.
Welcome, Alex.
Yeah, and I'm just popping in for a segment here to invite all your wonderful viewers
to have our live coverage coming up here in just about 39 minutes of the installation
of the inauguration of the communist Chinese spy, Biden.
Why is Alex coming to promote his show on Harrison's show?
Because the white nationalists are tuning in, Dan.
Do get the sense that maybe Alex sees a different audience.
Maybe Harrison is appealing to another audience that might not stick around to watch Alex.
Yes.
He's coming in to promote himself to them, because otherwise the only place you're watching
the American fucking Journal is on Infowars' streams, which would automatically start playing
Alex's show afterwards.
I would like to welcome all the Red Ice listeners to Harrison Smith's show, and I just want
to let you know that the Alex Jones show is up next.
Yeah.
So Alex thinks that people think he's soft, because he accepts that Trump is going to
be leaving office.
Sure.
I've seen him on Infowars.com saying, how dare you say he would leave today.
You're a traitor.
You're agreeing with CNN as if as I magically said he was going to stay.
He was going to stay.
We literally talked to the president.
Okay.
I talked to two of his lawyers.
I talked to somebody else very close to him the last few days, and he was going.
As soon as he capitulated the day after January 6th, it was over.
What happened January 6th?
They sent in provocateurs.
They sabotaged our operation, but that was a last-ditch Hail Mary to begin with.
I was listening to that, and I was like, it's 10 a.m.
You sound fucked up.
He sounds not good.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
But I also was like, he probably just woke up or something.
You know, I wasn't sure, but I was worried.
I was worried.
The way he's talking is not normal Alex Jones.
I would give him a hangover and a hair of the dog.
I think that's what I'm hearing.
That's kind of what I thought, but then he explains what's going on.
OK.
And so they don't want a big mainline debate about this.
They want to have it be esoteric.
They created a secret society to make people think that we're in the inside group with
military intelligence and that everything was going to be fine, so people can be pacified.
I'm going to move on from Q at that point.
We'll talk about what Biden's going to do, how they're going to strangle this country
during inauguration and afterwards.
I do not have COVID or anything.
I had some dental work done and got a little infection back on one of my tonsils have been
to see the doctor.
It's localized.
It's fine.
About a dime size rattle back in my throat, but I'm fine.
I never take painkillers.
I'm actually on painkillers right now.
Oh, OK.
So you're on painkillers.
All right.
Cool.
Good time to be at work.
All right.
I'm just going to go.
I'm just going to get some dental surgery.
I talk for a living, dental surgery, the morning of Biden's inauguration and coming to work
high on painkillers.
That's what I got to do.
That's what you got to do, Dan.
Wow.
Inauguration.
The show must go on.
I will say that I don't think it affects him nearly as much as it could have.
Yeah.
So it's not like he's fucked up.
You could just hear like there's a there's something different in his delivery and that
explains it.
He had some dental work done.
He's on some painkillers.
Yeah.
So I think that they thought that Biden would be giving his getting sworn in on Alex's show.
Right.
But that doesn't work out.
No.
And you know, we get all of that while Harrison is still hosting and Alex has left to prepare
for his show.
Yeah.
And so Harrison tries.
God bless him.
He tries.
Joe Biden probably wondering where the hell he is right now.
Hey, there's a baby that knows what's going on.
Hell yeah.
That's great work, Harrison.
That's great work.
So Harrison just plays Biden's acceptance speech and he interrupts kind of limitedly
because I think that he's just hoping that Biden will make a big flub and then respond
to.
Yeah.
The whole narrative about Biden on Infowars is that he's senile and he can't form sentences.
So honestly, I think this is a bad strategy.
They're literally airing evidence that he can speak and make sentences, essentially
debunking one of their big talking points.
And that is how the journal wraps up.
Yeah.
The book.
I assume he's a big enough man to apologize for saying that Joe Biden is not.
Nope.
He's not?
They just sort of pretend that they never said that.
Much like Harrison pretending that he didn't say the capital's fallen to the Patriots.
Weird.
Yeah.
So Alex comes in and he knows what to do a little bit better than Harrison.
Harrison just lets Biden talk for long stretches.
Sure.
Alex tries to mystery science theater that shit.
Hell yeah.
A few centuries ago, St. Augustine, a saint of my church, wrote that a people was a multitude
defined by the common objects of their love, defined by the common objects of their love.
What are the common objects we as Americans love?
Children, you want to molest.
Define us as Americans.
I think we know opportunity, world government, security, liberty, the population, dignity,
and honor.
And yes, the truth.
So yeah, that's, that's what you come to expect for watching a speech on Infowars.
Yeah.
You know, for somebody who thinks that Biden is senile, he got his speech patterns pretty
well down.
Uh, Alex knows when to jump in real quick about how much time he has.
It seems like he, yeah.
So Biden, in his speech, he proposes that his first act will be a moment of silence
for the Americans lost to COVID.
How does Alex take that?
Well, it's interesting because we know that from listening to his show, he often has long
stretches of dead air.
Yeah.
So a moment of silence should be no big deal.
Takes nothing.
Should be no big deal.
It's a moment.
In my first act as president, I'd like to ask you to join me in a moment of silent prayer.
Remember all those who we lost in this past year to the pandemic, those 400,000.
Most of which died of something else, husband's wife, son's daughters that came out of the
Wuhan lab that your buddies, Obama and Fauci and Gates cooked up for becoming the people
and the Democrat States.
When you ship COVID patients into the nursing homes and kill people, I ask you, let's have
a moment of silence for by the Democrats in the UN and the shy comms murdered.
And my most silencer.
We can't do that on our radio stations have silence once and it'll send everybody into
a panic.
Having a moment of silence.
Alex pretends that he can't accept this moment of silence because of radio restrictions.
That's such nonsense.
He just has to interrupt the moment of silence to like not allow it to air.
I would bet that he has like some spiritual explanation for it in his head.
Like he, I can't allow, I can't allow Biden to have a spiritual moment on info war.
Absolutely not.
Yeah.
That's really weird.
He has to, he can't, he can't let it happen.
So this next clip is maybe the only, uh, real moment where, uh, on Alex's show itself where
I was like, Oh, those pills might be affecting you.
Pass along a new and better world to our children.
I believe we must, I'm sure you do as well.
I believe we will.
And when we do, we'll write the next great chapter in the history of the United States
of America.
A story.
It might sound something like a song that means a lot to me.
It's called American anthem.
And there there's one verse that stands out, at least for me, like this work and prayers
of century have brought us to this day.
What shall be our legacy?
What will our children say?
Let me know in my heart, when my days are through America, America, I gave my best to
you.
Let's add, let's us add our own work and prayers.
So this is the front man, all they dismantle the country.
All they teach America shouldn't exist while they pull down our statues.
Then when our days are through while they burn down cities and our children's children
will save us.
He says that he loves America and he's here to bring us unity.
They healed all their pundits say they want to put us in reeducation camps.
Yikes.
Um, the part where at the beginning where it just seemed like he wasn't making a lot
of sense, the interjections he was making were like, he lost the, he lost the thread.
But he picked it up together to like at least make sense, I guess by the end, although still
messed up.
Yeah.
So Alex had been talking about how they were going to be commercial free because there's
a lot to cover at the inauguration.
Fourteen minutes into his show, this is what happens.
But now that's my next question.
I thought this would go for hours.
Well, it isn't.
So we are not going to be commercial free, I guess until six o'clock tonight when we
take calls up until 10 PM and have a whole raft of special guests here.
So Alex had expected this inauguration to go all day.
He didn't realize it was going to be a ceremony.
It's real quick.
Yeah.
He didn't realize that maybe Trump's rambling speeches aren't normal.
The wedding ceremony part of the wedding is usually pretty quick.
Yeah.
The reception is what goes on.
It's the reception that takes a while.
Yeah.
A party.
Unless you have maybe someone who's officiating the wedding because of Blowhard.
Sure.
That can happen.
Yes.
Bet you might be there a while.
Could be.
And I think Alex expected a Blowhard as a president because of last time.
And 14 minutes in he realizes, uh-oh.
Oh no.
Oh this isn't going to be a rambling nonsense speech that I can...
I have got.
I have no commercial breaks.
Not good.
Let's get those commercial breaks back.
Guys, I don't have anything to say.
I am not doing this commercial free.
Yeah.
When he gave me 14 minutes of content that even listening to it I had a hard time riffing
over.
Yeah.
Jesus.
Not good.
So here's a commercial that Alex goes to.
Sure.
And I listen to his commercials on Infowars itself for a while because I generally listen
through the feeds that have Genesis Communications commercials on them.
So here's one of Alex's commercials.
This blew my mind.
The pope came out yesterday and announced a global government corporate alliance to
redistribute wealth and create a planetary universal income, which of course the United
Nations and global corporations will control through the apps on your phone and finally
a chip under your skin.
It's all now completely official, part of the UN Great Reset of the Davos Group and
Klaus Schwab, all officially written about in hundreds of books by Schwab and Rockefeller
Foundation, all the rest of them, agenda 21, agenda 2030.
It's here.
And only gets worse like being fed into a wood chipper or a meat grinder until you reject
it all.
And the rejection starts with realizing it's spiritual battle, good versus evil, and stopping
abortion.
What?
What's going on here?
What is happening?
This is a commercial?
Am I supposed to watch this show or?
The musical cues are sophomoric, they're amateurish.
Love it.
Yeah, I don't know what's going on here.
Also, I don't know what he's talking about.
I think this is old because the pope, in his Easter letter last year, discussed UBI.
And maybe the world is approaching a point where universal basic income is something
we should be considering.
I couldn't find, I don't know if he's doubled down on that, but that was like a big story
in April.
Sure.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I just thought that like, I thought the music, it's all like really dark and like music and
then at the end like.
Is that a commercial so much or just an interstitial?
Do you think there's a product that he's selling?
That's what I'm confused about.
Am I just supposed to listen to more Info Wars because UBI might be coming?
I don't know.
I can't actually remember.
I was so caught off guard by that left turn to like, you have to stop abortion.
Yeah, that one threw me.
I was like.
I forgot the previous part of the commercial.
It might have ended up in like a bodies commercial or something, but I don't know.
Anyway, we get back to Alex's coverage of the inauguration, which is now over 15 minutes
into a show.
Yeah.
Trouble.
And so he's got to do what he does.
I assume he didn't listen to the poets.
No.
He didn't do anything else except for.
Yeah.
I mean, maybe in the evening coverage, they went over the party aspect, but oh, no, they
also they complained about Lady Gaga a little bit.
Who cares?
Yeah.
Why not?
Anyway, Alex has a guest on who we've been curious about his whereabouts the FBI might
be as well.
Okay, story.
I know you're on the road.
I appreciate you popping on on short notice.
Obviously, I want to get your take on what's happened.
How people that were delusional about Trump being invincible, how they're going to handle
it.
But the big issue, they're clearly saying domestic terrorism is here.
They're clearly preparing to wind up for rock and tour groups.
You're a domestic terrorist.
You are for the American people.
Stuart Rhodes, founder of the Oath Keepers.
They're saying.
Been wondering what he's up to.
Yeah.
What's his lie going to be?
Ha ha.
Interesting.
Alex doesn't start with, Hey, I haven't seen you since the six.
How was the six?
Yeah.
Do you have a good time?
What happened?
Hey, Stuart Rhodes.
You're on the road.
I am definitely not saying you're on the run.
Yeah, definitely.
Wouldn't say that.
I'm not.
I'm not saying that he's wanted or anything, but he's a fucked up dude.
Anyway, he is disappointed in Trump in very similar ways that Harrison was.
Everybody sees right through it.
These are not the president and vice president.
These are Chai Comm agents, Stuart Rhodes of OathKeepers.org.
Your view on all this.
Well, I think what we have to realize is that, you know, Trump actually failed.
He, um, this is unpopular, but I consider it a dereliction of duty and frankly, cowards
in the face of the enemy.
I'll be blunt.
You know, we were calling for him to use the insurrection act all through the summer.
Um, he did not do it and he brought him to the last moment.
He could have done it.
Yeah.
You sound, I mean, I, I, his, his response is like as expected as it, you could, it could
be for someone like Stuart Rhodes.
He's disappointed.
Yeah.
Cause he has been very clearly calling for Trump.
We wanted to overthrow the government and institute a theocracy.
He's straight up been on Info Wars talking about how Trump needs to deputize him and
all of his buddies, the militias, call them up to restore order in the country.
Yeah.
He, of course he's disappointed.
He was really excited.
This was as close as he was probably ever going to get to a president being like, yep,
you guys are my army now.
Yup.
That's about as a, yeah, he wanted a new Confederacy and he almost got it and now he's sad and
I assume Alex texted him being like, Hey, the line is it wasn't you guys on purpose.
And he was like, but I want to tell people that we should do it again.
Well he does have, he has an interesting take on what happened on the six and we'll get
to that in a little bit, but Alex certainly doesn't want to start with, yeah, he wants
to start with Biden is a fake leader and because he's a fake leader, Stuart knows cause he's
a constitutional scholar.
He went to Yale.
Can you imagine how many lies are in history Dan?
Many.
So Stuart, based on the constitution, he's just like, fuck it, we don't have to follow
laws now.
I'll get plenty of hate mail for saying that and all kinds of people saying, you know,
all the same excuses we've always heard, but he was surrounded by bad people.
Whose fault was that?
It's his own fault.
And he's still a commander in chief or he was the commander in chief.
He had a duty and responsibility to step up, but he failed to do that.
He allowed a Chi-Con puppet into the White House and I think we now need to just declare
that to be illegitimate and refuse to comply with anything that comes out of his mouth.
Anything he signs, anything passed as so-called legislation, label it pretend legislation
like the founding fathers did.
Ha ha, rules are pretend now.
Sweet.
Okay.
All right.
I got three Supreme Court justices who don't count anymore.
That's how we're going to do this.
That's how this rule works.
This is not functional.
I get to choose who I think is the government.
Yeah.
This is not a way for a cohesive society to work.
And I mean, it makes sense because that's not their goal.
Their goal is not to have a coherent and cohesive society.
It's time to declare independence.
Great.
But he was not duly elected.
It's just amazing that Trump will let the election be stolen out from under him and
then let our country be stolen like this, our government.
So we have to now prepare to walk the path of the founding fathers, where your independence
from that illegitimate regime.
We still defend the constitution, but they're the ones that are the Ursipers and the violators.
And you-
I'm sorry.
And then get strong in your communities.
You need to be raising local militias in your towns and counties.
And like the founders did, you need to then nullify, refuse to comply, and when they come
for you, you defend yourselves.
But you got to do it together.
Okay.
So commit crimes and kill cops when they try and arrest you.
I guess.
I think they're pretend laws.
I...
Man.
Oh boy.
I'm gonna-
What?
What pretend laws?
By this point, I'm-
I would like to know specifically which ones are pretend and which ones are not pretend.
Anything that has Biden's signature on it, his Hancock on it.
Okay.
That's fake.
All right.
Look.
Sure.
I can't say enough how stressed out I was when I was listening to this because I got
really caught with a left hook out of nowhere by Harrison's overt racism and anti-Semitism.
I was surprised by the white nationalism, yeah.
That made going through his shit much more of a slog than I expected, and it made it
like...
It was taxing.
And then at the same time, it filled me with all kinds of thoughts about like, all right,
I guess the morning show on Info Wars now is just like...
White nationalist happy hour.
Speak freely.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Speak freely big at time.
Yeah.
And that seemed like a bad direction for things to be going.
Then you get into Info Wars itself, like Alex's show, and you got Stuart Rhodes coming in
and it's just like frank discussion about like, the government isn't real.
We need to secede.
Yeah.
And this is doubling into the talk on Harrison's show about creating these enclaves where you
can protect yourself from the America.
Sundown towns are great.
It's fucked up.
Don't they already have white nationalist compounds in the Pacific Northwest?
Like entire cities that are like, no, it's whites only here.
And everybody's just like, it's the Pacific Northwest.
I guess you guys do that.
I don't know enough to know for sure, but I believe I've heard, at least unofficially
there are some places that have that character.
So one thing that Stuart is clear on is that he's gotten the memo.
Sure.
We got a shit on Q people.
Right.
But the Q people, I mean, only silver lining in all this is maybe the Q people will finally
shut up because all they did the entire time, even up until last night, because, Oh no,
the trips were there to arrest the bad guys.
That's delusional nonsense.
Q was an absolute psyop and well done one, what they call a lullaby to get you all to
be lulled into a false sense of security and, and just be asleep.
That's what happened for four years.
You had people sitting on their hands, doing nothing, waiting, saying, trust the plan,
waiting for this miraculous day that never came.
It was a masterful, uh, sign up, but now you're going to wake up, smell the coffee and realize
now you got to do it the hard way.
You got to do it the same way.
The founding fathers did, you know, who else was sitting on their hands, doing nothing
for a long time, who people like Alex and Stuart Rhodes, like, you know, these people
who thought that they had something that they could gain from Q Anon until it got to a point
where they realized, Nope, I can't gain anything from this.
And now they sound like people, uh, who we are associated with.
Like all of a sudden they're pretending that people who have maybe more left politics,
uh, people like the guys at Q Anon Anonymous haven't been like banging the drum for a long
time talking about the dangers and the misleading nature of Q Anon.
Like I have no patience for this.
You guys have all just jumped onto this now because you realize, well, that's our stick
to beat.
That's our scapegoat.
And there's a good chance that we can bring in some of the people, uh, anyone who hasn't
already decided that Alex Jones is controlled opposition because of Q Anon, maybe we can
get them into our revenue streams.
Isn't the implication of his argument though, that he wanted more people there on the 6th
to overthrow the government?
No, because then Biden hadn't been inaugurated.
Well you got me.
No, Stuart doesn't want the overthrow of the government to have happened on the 6th.
What he's saying is that Q people, because they were lulled into a false sense of security,
did not show up on the 6th in order to overthrow the government like he wanted.
I mean, I think that you could read his comments and maybe some of even like Alex's comments
that way, but I don't think that that's a totally fair reading.
I think it's a possible reading, but I think it's more like the way that they intend it
is more like there's organizing that you could do.
There's information warfare you could engage in that you were lulled into a false sense
of security about.
You thought Trump was bulletproof, but there's other things you could, you could have been
banging on doors in Georgia.
I think that that's what they want you to hear.
Yeah.
Dan, you are fair.
I am very much unfair and I'm telling you right now, he wished there were more people
on the 6th.
Look, that's the dynamic of the show.
Anyway, speaking of the 6th, Alex finally gets around to asking about that and oh boy.
Give me your take on what happened to the Capitol.
I mean, we got set up there bad.
Well, sure, but I think it's, I think it's, I see it like this.
Yes, there were provocateurs that made sure the doors were wide open, but I think it's
important for all of us not to use the rhetoric of the left, condemn everyone that walked
in the Capitol as you know, storming the castle or storming the Capitol and, and, and engaging
the insurrection.
We should just say, look at the most they were trespassing.
Stuart Rhodes has a lot riding on people believing that people who were at the Capitol were just
trespassing at worst.
You see, unlike Antifa, the Oath Keepers are a group that exists and Stuart Rhodes is the
head of it.
They have a website where you can donate to them and everything and they have an online
store where you can buy official merch.
It's an actual group and it kind of looks bad when three members of the group get arrested
after storming the Capitol and their charging document lays out how they planned for weeks
in advance in order to, in theory, kill members of Congress.
It took a lot of planning to trespass, it looks like.
Yeah.
Thomas Caldwell, Jessica Watkins and Donovan Kroll are all Oath Keepers from Ohio and they're
going to prison for a long time.
According to an article in the Daily Beast, Caldwell stands accused of organizing a group
of eight people to aggressively disrupt the certification of the Electoral College vote.
The group used Facebook and the walkie-talkie Abzello to communicate, which is really fucking
stupid because now the FBI has all that shit, including them messaging with someone on Facebook
who is apparently encouraging them to kill members of Congress, saying, quote, all members
are in the tunnels under the Capitol.
Seal them in.
Turn on gas.
Bill Gates is going to inject us all with computer chips to know where we are at all
times so we need to protect ourselves by using unencrypted apps while in the Capitol.
After leaving the Capitol, Caldwell posted on Facebook, quote, Proud Boys scuffled with
cops and drove them inside to hide, breached the doors.
One guy made it all the way to the House floor, another to Pelosi's office.
A good time.
We need to do this on the local level.
Let's storm the Capitol in Ohio.
Tell me when.
In this individual case, Stewart's personal hands may be clean.
One of the messages that the FBI had in the charging document was Caldwell saying, quote,
I don't know if Stewie has even gotten out his call to arms, but it's a little frickin'
late.
This one we're doing on our own.
We'll link up with a North Carolina crew.
Oh, man.
Stewart read that and was like, boom!
I'm free!
Yeah.
I get...
Thank God they said that shit.
Whee!
I guess you could say that the best case scenario for Stewart Rhodes is to say that he's responsible
for starting a decentralized right-wing extremist militia organization that he has so little
control over that now it's being used by members to plan militaristic takeovers of state and
federal capitol buildings.
Also, he might be in hot water, because the charging document for those Oath Keepers does
include a charge of conspiracy, and it explicitly alleges that they, quote, conspired together
and with others whose identities are known and unknown to law enforcement at this time.
Oh, boy.
That's not a great sentence to see when you're the head of an organization that these people
who were going to jail for a very long time were conspiring in.
What I'm saying is, I would still be worried if I were Stewart, even though that, you know,
the Stewie thing is pretty good for him.
Hey, Don, a lot of our generals flipped, and you're in the RICO case.
Is this good?
Is this good or bad?
Yeah.
He has stuff to be concerned about, and it's probably his best play to pretend that people
are just trespassing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's probably his best interests.
And they were just trespassing.
Hey, it's no big deal.
I mean, sure, they had to push through some barricades and kill a girl.
It's no big deal.
Yeah.
So, like, we have a couple of Oath Keepers members that were in there.
When they establish a defense fund, we'll contribute to it.
They did not do that under my orders.
They did that contrary to our plan for the day, which is just to PSD details and protect
events.
That's what we were there to do and protect individual Trump supporters from the radicals
in the streets, like we've always done.
But I'm not going to chuck them under the bus and condemn them as horrible people or
traitors or any kind of nonsense like that.
Too many on the right are adopting the same.
Yeah, no.
The police opened the doors after a few people knocked out some of the windows.
They were ordered to suck in enough people to have a crowd.
Stuart, don't you understand?
We already have the narrative.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
You have your own personal issues, and I understand how you don't want to throw your people under
the bus, but they are going to jail for a long time.
Long time.
And, hey, that's tough.
I feel for you.
Infos has a narrative, and I'm not going to stray from it at all, not for your ass.
Hey, buddy, you can thread the fine needle of it's good that they overthrew the Capitol,
but it's bad that they lost.
You can do that all you want.
I wish you the best.
Yeah, have fun.
Have fun.
You're also probably going to jail.
So Jordan, Stuart Rhodes has some interesting ideas about cancel culture.
I find that hard to believe.
Apparently, I don't know exactly what the root is, how you get there from point A to
point C, but you start with cancel culture, then things get out of control.
Are we going to get back into white genocide?
Mass graves.
Okay.
People dead in ditches.
He'll play the good cop and say, we come in peace, but they really come for war.
Stuart Rhodes, what do you expect from the left now?
Are going to follow through with cancel culture, and it ends in a ditch.
It's where it's going to end if you don't stop it.
It ends in a ditch full of bodies, which is what the communists have done throughout their
history.
I mean, in fact, there's a state rep from New Mexico that's calling for all of us to
be tattooed, if you were a Trump supporter, to be tattooed with a mark that's visible
so they will know who you are.
So we need to understand that it's far worse than the founding fathers faced.
Citation needed on that New Mexico state rep.
So if I understand correctly, if Toobin can't rub one out in a meeting, we're all going
to mass graves.
Yeah, you remember how Mao got rid of his political opponents by bringing up blog posts
they'd written.
Yeah, absolutely.
They'd written.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
That was the main source of issues for the Cultural Revolution, I'm pretty sure, right?
Oh, God.
Okay.
I just can't stand this overly dramatic person making these petty complaints, simultaneously
being the leader of a fucking militia, where people did storm the Capitol and seemed to
have pretty nefarious intent.
I get it.
You know, like when you're so used to having uncontrollable and impenetrable privilege
your entire life and the lives of your forebears, I get that the idea of equality is threatening
to you.
Sure.
But let's just remind ourselves that at best from a Biden presidency, we're going to get
a little bit more equal.
It's not going to change too much for white people.
Yeah.
And I think-
It's just not.
And I think that you'll see more coherent and more sincere aggressive critique and action
from the left.
100%.
I think you will see more organizing against or in order to push policy for Biden from
the left than you will from the right.
You'll see culture war nonsense and just a bunch of aggrievement from the right and you'll
see an attempt to form more coherent social policy on the left.
I find it hard to think that, you know, like watching Portland happen just recently-
Since the inauguration.
Yeah, since the inauguration, watching the way the cops reacted, it struck me that more
likely what we're going to see from the Capitol riot is not that people are going to go back
to DC, but that cops are going to fuck people up at home.
You know, like the DC overthrow is going to everybody's home and it's cops fucking people
up.
Oh, and there's that video out of Tacoma of the police car driving through a bunch of
people.
Yeah.
That's the legacy of the sixth.
I think it's entirely possible and I think that there will also be the other legacy and
that is I think that there will be a lot of people who end up going to prison or who at
least get charged with a bunch of stuff and I think that we may or may not hear follow-ups
on a lot of it, but I think a lot of people are going to be jammed up for that.
And hey, three of them are Stuart Rhodes' militia members at least.
Yeah, it's unfortunate that the people who created the conditions are absolutely not
going to face any...
Rico.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah.
Anyway, Stuart believes that Trump, you know that guy?
Last sitting president who was real.
Okay.
All right.
That said, there is a potential for future elections to...
No!
Yep.
Future elections...
Sorry.
They can go well.
Okay.
But there's something that needs to happen for these elections to go well and that is
paper ballots, but also...
I'm fine with paper.
I'm happy with paper ballots.
Hold on.
I like paper ballots.
That's just the beginning.
That's a good beginning.
There's a second step to this that is ludicrous.
I don't know how I feel about the second step.
Anything else you'd like to add in about 30 seconds we have left?
We no longer have a legitimate president.
This is...
Trump was the last actual sitting legitimate president.
We will see if we can ever have one again that's going to require paper ballots.
At any local elections, you must insist on paper ballots if they won't do it.
You hold your own parallel election using paper ballots to prove that your patriot candidate
did win.
Make sure you have a way to prove that.
And from bottom to top, bottom up is how you take it back.
That's right, Stuart.
How do you do that?
How do you run a second election?
I think the funniest thing about that is that the only people who would be furious at the
results of us going to entirely paper ballots would be these people.
I have zero doubt in my mind that if we were using paper ballots, Stacey Abrams would have
been governor of Georgia.
Zero doubt.
I would...
I don't know.
Maybe.
I don't know what I think entirely would change because I don't believe that there's rank
corruption of electronic voting.
I think that there's problems with gerrymandering and access to polling places.
And I don't know if that would be fully solved by paper ballots.
I would doubt it.
I would say that one thing that would be even more helpful than paper ballots would be having
a holiday for elections, having multiple days that people can vote, which are things that
people are doing, that we're making progress towards, and also expanding access to remote
voting.
Keeping Republicans away from how many polling places are allowed in, let's say, majority
black neighborhoods.
And not letting people like Stuart's friends hang around outside in the fifties.
That's a good one.
I like that one too.
These things would make more progress than paper ballots.
But I will say that one thing that is stupid is the idea that what you should do, if you
can't have paper ballots, is run a second election.
I think a parallel election would teach people a lot about how you would want to steal it.
Here's a really good way that that process could get subverted and you'd never know it.
How?
So you're running a second election.
Sure.
I go ahead and vote differently in those two.
How would you ever know?
Well, because it would also be run by the Georgia election commission.
Why would they ever do that?
Well, because right wing nut jobs want it.
No, he's talking about like the oath keepers running their own election.
So dumb.
I think they should have the UN come in to observe the results of the election.
I think these guys would love that.
They'd love it.
So Stuart leaves and Alex, earlier, Stuart had said that Trump is a disappointment.
He failed.
He didn't step up when Judy called and all these people are going to be going around
and saying that, hey, he was surrounded and making excuses for him.
Like Alex and Roger Stone and Steve Pachannik and Jerome Corsi.
No, no, no.
Alex immediately after Stuart leaves.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
And I respect Stuart Rhodes, the oath keepers.
He was on last segment here on the Alex Jones show last hour.
And he was saying, you think Trump really failed by not declaring the insurrection act.
Well, Bob Barnes was a lawyer for Trump and was in some of the meetings and they were
planning to have the military arrest Trump if he did that, even though it was lawful.
And so Trump was totally surrounded.
Oh, so it sounds like you're the kind of person who Stuart was talking about having no patience
for it.
Yeah.
Yep.
You're being a narcissistic shithead on inauguration day.
I'm just, I've always tried to steer you as accurate as I can with the best info I have
with real research and real historical understanding and quote sources.
But I'll tell you most of the time I know more than my sources, what the Pentagon calls
me up.
The CIA calls me up to ask what I think of things.
Not the other way around.
I'm not trying to brag about that folks, but I have a good political brain.
I've been doing this a long time.
I've been trained in the field, in the school of hard knots as an organic Patriot citizen
who wasn't trained by the system.
Matt is seen by the system as the proof of someone's real gravitas is that they pull
themselves up out of the mud.
And I'm not telling you that to act powerful.
I'm telling you that because that's the reality, ladies and gentlemen, now let's shift gears
into Lady Gaga.
Those pills might be kicking in.
Yeah.
Let's shift gears into Lady Gaga.
I think that's good.
They really do respect people who pull themselves up.
How did Alex get his first show again?
His dad bought an ad.
Oh yeah, that's right.
Yeah.
Radio station.
One of the other things I think is really funny is like just imagining just any other
show where like somebody interviews somebody about like Medicare policy or something like
that.
And then they're like, you know what?
I know way more about Medicare than these assholes that I have on.
Rest in peace to Larry King.
If only he had a few broadcasts where he's just like, man, all these people that I talked
to are fucking stupid.
The government calls me up for what I think about things.
In any context other than Alex Jones, it becomes so clear how rude it is, how unprofessional
it is.
But for Alex, it's just like, yeah, this is the kind of dickhead that he is.
I mean, if you have an M.O. for long enough, people will just be like, fine.
Yeah.
Also, speaking of which, with Larry King, I was reminded on his passing, and a lot of
people posted the clip.
Dick Rubin?
Yes.
Yeah.
I was glad they did.
That's a good one.
And if you haven't seen it, go check that out.
Larry King was on with Dave Rubin.
They were doing a live broadcast, and Larry King answered a call from his son.
It was incredibly rude.
It was beautiful.
It went on forever.
Dave Rubin is so pissed.
Lovely.
One of the best things ever.
I love it.
So Robert Barnes shows up now.
Cool.
We got to have some constitutional law to tell us why.
Well, we already did.
Oh, that's right.
I'm a constitutional expert.
Stuart Rhodes telling me about the Constitution.
That's right.
He's just basically there to shit on Q more.
I think that that's Barnes' new thing.
His new branding is anti-Q guy.
I like it.
That's a good rebrand.
Sure.
Whatever.
But he also has an idea for what Trump needs to do now that he's out of office.
I think Trump's great skill is his marketing, and his great asset is his brand.
And so he should leverage both to look at an independent news media network, independent
information distribution network, independent social media platforms, maybe even look at
independent banks and financial institutions.
The reality is there's there's going to be huge demand for all of those things from people
that are our Trump supporters because of the censorship campaigns and the blacklisting
campaigns by the institutional media, by employment institutions, by financial institutions, by
the social media oligarchs.
The only way to counteract that is to have our own networks to do to replicate and repeat
what Infowars has done.
Build an independent brand that's not dependent at all either on corporate donations or sugar
daddy billionaires, but also isn't dependent on big tech distribution platforms either.
The Infowars is the model and the template for the president to mirror and follow in
a broader context of industry.
I'm not sure that I would want to be involved with a bank that's modeled after Infowars.
I don't think I would feel confident having my money held by people who are constantly
ranting about the devil and how they might be out of business next week.
I don't know.
There are some good financial advisors.
I think that those business models are, especially ones like, you know, banks.
A lot of that has to do with confidence.
That's one of the things that will go a long way in terms of making investors and depositors
not make a rush on their money trying to get it out.
I think that Alex is, uh, maybe...
Here's what I want to do.
I want to put my money in a bank that screams at me about how the government is going to
take my money away from that bank.
Right.
Also, is this independent bank going to be involved in the FDIC?
Also, if you're telling me that you want a social network started by Trump without a
fucking daddy billionaire, you know what?
It's a little incoherent.
You know, um, yeah.
It's all a little incoherent.
They're functionally, like, his plan is functionally, let's secede from reality entirely.
Yes.
We don't have to live in, look, we can't leave the country because it's land, but our brains
can secede.
Yeah.
We will create a media ecosystem, which you've already done a lot of legwork on with InfoWars
and Newsmax and OAN, and Trump has, you know, certainly elevated all these things.
We'll create online spaces for us to interact.
We'll create, um...
You know, this would remind me a lot, and I don't think Barnes would like it too much.
If this were actually enacted, I think it would remind me more of, like, the mining
towns in the 1890s and early 1900s where the guy who owned the mine also printed your money.
Right.
Owned your home.
Ran everything there.
Printed the newspaper.
I'm not positive that Barnes wouldn't like that.
I mean, that's basically libertarian fantasy land.
Yeah, that's true.
Well, I think a lot of people would love it if they were the owner of the mine.
See, that's what they think.
And that is...
I'm gonna get my own mine.
Well, to an extent, I think people like Barnes and Alex are at a level of society where they
view themselves as being okay in a libertarian landscape.
Like that.
Like that mining town, they would either be the person who runs the mine or somebody who's
an associate of the person who runs the mine.
So they're fine.
They're gonna be a monkey, Mike.
They aren't the miners.
You don't want to grow.
You don't want to be a miner.
Right.
So they, you know, obviously that's the society that they would like to see and they would
like to build.
I'm going to tell you right now, a society built around people who don't want to work
in the mine, but all want to own it.
Not a good one.
It's functional.
Hmm.
So Barnes, like I said, most of it is complaining about QAnon, which is just becoming annoying
at this point.
Yeah.
And so he leaves and Alex, he said this and I got pretty excited.
Here's a short compilation.
We've got like a 20 minute one, but here's a minute and a half compilation of them calling
for reprogramming, reeducation camps of the American people.
So Alex is going to play that compilation.
You know, I was curious cause I hadn't heard him play those clips, but he keeps talking
about it.
Yeah.
So I decided that what I was going to do is I was going to look into each clip.
Do it.
Here's the deal.
Okay.
I took this compilation clip by clip and I found the context for each of them and I found
that none of them really had anything to do with putting conservatives in camps or anything
even close.
And I was thinking like, what the fuck is going on?
I spent a long time sorting this out.
And then at the end of the compilation, it didn't matter.
Cause Alex said this, Oh, the enemy is the American people.
So that's another compilation.
Sorry.
We heard the wrong one.
Go fuck yourself.
I wasted so much time.
Sorry.
Yeah.
It turns out the compilation that I was talking about doesn't exist.
That's the equivalent in my world of like me slipping on a banana peel.
Yeah.
That's that's Lucy holding the football.
Alex just pulled it away forever and ever, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but
Charlie Brown, what are we talking about?
Somebody said camps.
All right.
Now, now, now Barnes, we did get one of the clips.
It's not the crew's fault.
There's so many brainwash reeducate kill firing squad, uh, reprogram, but I wanted to just
show one of the clips about reeducation camps because that's where they're going with this.
Here it is.
And Harvard now want to set up kind of a reeducation camps and moral rehabilitation centers and
institutions for vetting people who had the chutzpah to work in the Trump administration.
That's right.
And that's him criticizing.
We've got a bunch of clips that we'll add in post.
We add this to live and where they actually say it.
Yeah.
So I guess Barnes is still around, but who cares?
Alex breaks into the air interview to say that he did find her on the clips, but unfortunately
it's not a leftist saying they want to put conservatives in camps.
It's just another right winger complaining about his fear that leftists are going to
put conservatives in camps.
Yeah.
This is noted Epstein lawyer, Alan Dershowitz complaining about Harvard students starting
a petition to encourage the school to not hire anyone who worked for the Trump administration.
This doesn't help Alex's point and guess what?
That's a clip from November.
How does the Dersh get allowed on TV?
I don't know.
I don't understand.
I don't know, but that's the best.
What's wrong with people?
That's the best they could do.
What's really interesting about that is that Alex is supposedly in possession of hundreds
of these clips.
Yeah.
He breaks in with this clip after playing the wrong compilation.
Yep.
I don't know if he has all these clips.
He does not.
There are not then.
Yeah.
Because they don't exist.
So Alex is kind of bored.
Yeah.
Because...
Inauguration really isn't that big of a deal.
No.
And it also was shorter than he thought it was going to be.
Yeah.
Biden didn't make any real serious gaffes.
And Alex is a little bit disappointed.
Alright.
I think terror attacks should happen any time something happens, turn your phone on, brother.
We're going to be live until 10 o'clock tonight.
Thank you so much.
So yeah, there should have been attacks any time now.
I'm pretty sure he's very disappointed nobody attacked the Capitol.
Yeah.
Or around the country at some other state house or something.
He's pretty much like, that's the whole reason we were going to do an all-day thing.
Because I thought my buddies were going to start fires.
I predicted false flags.
Yeah.
Come on, man.
So it goes on a little bit longer.
Alex is spinning his wheels.
There's nothing really going on.
It's very boring.
I think they...
We haven't had a false flag yet today.
Maybe it's going to happen.
I pray it doesn't.
They were certainly saying what was coming.
I think we put so much attention on this.
Who was?
And told patriots, don't go out and demonstrate on the 20th that we may have dodged a bullet.
That's knock on wood.
Yeah.
So, you know, we stopped it from happening by saying it, but so, so awful.
Alex has Matt Bracken on, noted race war predictor Matt Bracken, noted shoddy Diagram fan Matt
Bracken, noted ebook about race war salesman Matt Bracken.
He's on and the two of them have a largely unproductive conversation.
And I think Alex is so bored that he just leaves, like not in the same way as during
his interview with Jason Jones.
Sure.
But like mentally in his head.
He's just like Bracken, you're doing a half hour.
You take care of this until John Rappaport shows up.
Alex just leaves.
That's great.
Bracken hosts for a little while and I don't give a shit.
And then John Rappaport shows up to host the fourth hour and this is where I turn things
off.
Okay.
Hello everybody.
John here.
I thought I would celebrate the Biden inauguration by, uh, putting myself in a virtual loft as
you can see behind me in a virtual city that is on virtual lockdown.
And my refrigerator is stocked with virtual food because it was of course a virtual inauguration
after a virtual election.
Rappaport got a zoom background.
This is riveting stuff.
I can't believe how boring that is.
That is the most bored I have been so fast in the shortest period of time.
35 seconds for him to explain that he got a zoom background.
That was brutally boring.
Outrageous.
That's terrifying.
Inappropriate.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It makes me, it makes me mad.
Yeah.
Well, I could have probably kept going and listened to The War Room, although that's
not a show that I normally listen to.
True.
Owen Schroyer is basically a less competent, broey version of Alex.
Yeah.
And I just, what I, what I got to by the end of Alex's show was this sort of sense that
they're all disappointed.
There's no real new talking points being developed in terms of like what happened on the sixth.
Yeah.
Biden's a fake president.
Whoop-dee-doo.
This is all exactly the way they've been going.
I didn't, I didn't have any faith that this was going to develop into anything interesting.
Right.
Simultaneously, I didn't think that there was any chance that Owen's show could be any
more offensive than the American Journal.
I don't think that there could be anything that topped that in terms of the dangerousness,
the offensiveness, the bigotedness.
And the banality of it.
True.
And the banality of it was such a terrifying part.
Yeah.
It's always the scariest part where they're just like, we have to kill millions of people.
Like just tossing it off.
Yeah.
And so I kind of felt done with Inauguration Day.
Sure.
We saw some outrageous white nationalist slash supremacist slash neo-Nazi content in the
morning show.
We saw Alex disappointed that his predictions of bombings and false flags didn't come true.
And therefore he had no content on his own show.
I just, oh, and Stuart Rhodes showed up.
So I was done.
Yeah.
I was done.
I think we got what we needed out of it.
Yeah.
I think Alex definitely didn't get what he wanted out of it, which was a lot of terror
attacks.
Yep.
Yeah.
I do think that that was something he was kind of hoping for.
Why else would you say we're going to do, look, if you're Info Wars and you're saying
we're going to do a live 10 hour broadcast, that's not because you think the inauguration
is going to go well.
No, or that you have like something, some analysis or something to say, a breakdown
of policy, a breakdown of like the agenda that Biden is setting out for in his first
hundred days.
You really want to get down into the nitty gritty.
You want to get in the weeds.
You want to be a policy wonk.
He is a policy wonk.
We all know he's a policy wonk.
We all know that.
He says it on our show like five times a show.
All the time.
Yeah.
I don't think he has the ability to, nor the interest in it, and his audience wouldn't
be at all motivated by it.
This is Info Wars.
We want spectacle.
Yes.
And we want explosions.
And apparently we want a dork being a bigot.
Yeah, I guess so.
Anyway, we'll be back probably on Friday, I think, for another episode.
Maybe a bonus little thing on Wednesday.
Let's hope.
But and then we'll discuss the fallout of Alex losing his Supreme Court in Texas appeal,
which I think will be maybe interesting.
Maybe not.
Who knows?
Yeah.
But until then, Jordan, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledgefight.com.
And I go to Betjordan.
We're also on Facebook.
We are Facebook.
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to do God's work.
Yeah.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZXclerk.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I got bad news for you, Harrison Smith.
You have attracted my attention.
Andy in Kansas.
Thanks for being on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.