N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys.
I am sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys saying
we are the bad guys saying we are the bad guys.
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight, I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're couple dudes, like to sit around, drink novelty beverages and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones.
Oh indeed, we are Dan.
Jordan!
Dan!
Quick question for you.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, Jordan, was getting to join you on your debut stream of your video
game channel over on Twitch.
Indeed.
You started playing Final Fantasy VII, it was a lot of fun to sit in and have very little
to say.
You are very offended when you do not have a sincere and large body of research from
which to call upon.
It's a challenge for me to care.
Ah yes, there we go.
And I, look, you know.
I like you judging other people for caring.
I'm not judging you, I'm happy for you and I fully support you in this and all your endeavors.
I know.
I just can't care about watching this stupid video game.
I understand completely.
I also don't like it being exposed that I probably didn't beat the game, though I thought
I did.
You came close enough.
Oh god.
But yeah, it's really fun.
I'm happy for you and congratulate you on the launching of your side project there.
Yeah!
It was very enjoyable and everybody really had a good time and you were absolutely great.
How dare you act like you were, oh I was so terrible.
We had a grand old time.
I wasn't saying I was so terrible, I said I was so bored.
I will keep my mouth shut.
Slight semantic difference.
Retracted.
Retracted, sir.
How about you?
My bright spot, Dan, is today my partner is getting her vaccine.
That's great.
Yeah!
She's a teacher, she didn't even have to try and cheat her way in or lie to anybody.
She's getting her vaccine at the right time and I'm really happy for her.
That's fantastic.
Congratulations.
Yeah, I'm very stoked.
I hope that the roll out continues and intensifies.
In at least May or June I'll be able to get it.
2022.
Yeah, absolutely.
Once they get around to podcasters.
Probably low on the list.
Yeah, she'll gladly watch me slowly fade away, I think that'll be...
Your partner is a teacher, like you said, so obviously there's much need for folks in
that line, much less so podcasters.
Very...
So yeah, Jordan, I'm glad for that, and I wish you the best on your new exploration
of Midgar.
I'm gonna remember the name now.
That's true, you will remember Midgar.
So Jordan, today we got an interesting thing to talk about.
Oh yeah?
Interesting episode.
What's that?
We're gonna be talking about January 27th, 2021, Blackjack.
Ah, shit, you're so good.
So fast.
We're on the 27th, this is Wednesday of this week, and the reason that we are sort of jumping
ahead in time, our last episode was about the inauguration and Harrison Smith being
a...
Blatant bigot.
Yeah.
And the reason is, hey, I'm Alex Jones, I'm sitting around, I'm thinking, the devil just
got into the White House.
Sure.
The Texas Supreme Court has just ruled that I can be sued by the Sandy Hook families.
Problem.
I'm gonna go on vacation, man.
Smart move.
Yeah.
So Alex just leaves for Utah, which is a strange place to go, but whatever.
I like that the only time, every time he threatens a vacation, he never takes it.
The only time he does take a vacation is when his lawyers have clearly said, if you are
on the air, you will say something that hurts our case.
You need to chill.
Yeah, you gotta go away.
You gotta go to fucking Utah.
You gotta be in Utah right now.
Go see the Jazz, Rudy Gobert's having a great season.
Yeah, I don't know what he's doing in Utah, it doesn't seem like, I mean, nothing against
Utah, I've been there.
It's a nice state.
Yeah.
I like the Southwest quite a bit.
Eh, it's pretty.
Yeah.
So, I retract that.
It is a good place to go on vacation.
Yeah, it's a great place.
Whatever.
It just seems strange.
Well, I mean, you know, too many places are dry, I suppose is the only argument I have.
There's a dry Salt Lake.
Oh, you mean too many places in Utah?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, yes, yes.
Are alcohol-free.
Oh, that too.
Yes.
A lot of dry counties.
Yeah, a lot of dry counties.
I thought you meant it's arid there.
No.
No, I did not mean that.
So, yeah, Alex was out of studio and Owen Schroyer was hosting for a number of days
and I just don't care.
And so, I was considering maybe, like, let's check in and just do a Harrison Smith episode.
Sure.
But then, Wednesday, Alex hosted a good bit of his own show with Owen Schroyer riding
shotgun in the studio and something happened that requires our attention.
So we will be talking about that today and honestly, I think that there might be a sequel
to this on Monday's episode of our show because this appears to be something that might...
I am going to fight a bear on Friday this week.
Take away the bear.
We've got a charity boxing challenge?
Take away...
Yep, we do.
We've got a charity boxing challenge.
There will be a bear knuckle boxing match.
Okay, there we go.
Challenged.
How do I just guess these things, Dan?
I don't know.
There will be a bear knuckle boxing match challenged and then retracted at the end of
this episode.
Okay.
Alright, spoiler alert.
That's too soon.
But there is a feeling that I have, I mean, we're recording this on Thursday and I have
some awareness of what happened on his show today, but I think that this is a narrative
that's continuing.
There's something that's going to continue into Monday's show without giving too much
away.
Everybody who's listening already fucking knows what I'm talking about.
Of course.
So let's take a little moment before we get down to business, Jordan, to say thank you
to some folks who signed up and are supporting the show.
Oh, that's a great idea.
So first, Dr. Bingo, like Van Gogh.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you.
Dr. Bingo.
Thank you very much, Dr. Bingo.
Like Van Gogh.
Next, Brunisinde.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you.
Hey, thank you very much.
Next, I love you.
Thank you so much.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I love you.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, Chad Rice.
Thank you.
Next, Leeland.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
My favorite of the Stamper clan.
Ooh.
Yeah.
Next, Davron from Sweden who loves your podcast.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Davron from Sweden.
And then finally, thank you so much, Trump, the tiny hands of fate.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
That's a little Mystery Science Theater reference.
Yes, yes, absolutely.
To go along with your-
Trump, the hands of fate.
The tiny hands of fate.
That's to go along as another plug for your Twitch channel.
Great, great.
Where you have a Mystery Science Theater cut out.
I'm already embarrassed.
That's the goal.
Doing something is a terrible idea, Dan, that's the lesson.
I'm trying to smother you with embarrassment.
So Jordan, we started off today on the 27th.
Like I said, this is all going to be on the 27th.
Yes.
And Alex opens up the show and he teases
what will end up being the reason
we need to do this episode.
Gotcha.
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for joining us on this January 27th,
2021 Wednesday broadcast.
Blackjack.
I am your host, Alex Jones,
and we are going to have the founder of the Boogaloo Boys
joining us. Interesting.
Coming up on the broadcast today.
That is in the second hour.
I appreciate Mr. Dunn coming on after I've said
some critical things of his group.
He says to set the record straight.
So I look forward to that because who's going to know more
about the Boogaloo's than the founder of the Boogaloo's.
He is not the founder or the leader of the first thing that
Mike Dunn does when he gets on the show is correct Alex
about this.
Alex is trying to present him as like the head of these,
the Boogaloo's.
And I wrote down founder of the Boogaloo boys and then put
giant scare quotes around founder.
Yeah.
This is something that's a little bit murky.
I don't think this is a good idea for Alex.
You'll see why.
Cause he agrees with them on everything exactly like he did
with David Duke.
And this guy is a 20 year old who is really,
I would say he is more consistent than Alex.
Oh, that's not good.
And that makes it really tough to argue when you're Alex.
And that ends up becoming very embarrassing.
I would say that we have not talked as much about the
Boogaloo boys on this podcast because it doesn't intersect
with Alex as much as one might think.
Alex leaves them alone for the most part,
except a couple of times he's tried to use them to scapegoat
things that right wing militias have done.
And the situation with the Capitol on the 6th,
January 6th is so large and so important that it's led to a
critical mass of throwing them under the bus and blaming
them.
So his beloved oath keepers and such don't come under
attention.
Right.
Yeah.
He wouldn't do too much to, I guess,
point out the people who are basically he's running
stochastic terrorism for, you know, like he's,
he's the one who's both giving them that cover of like,
these guys aren't part of what we believe in while at the
same time, stoking their rage.
So you don't want to be also like Boogaloo boys,
let's pay attention to them.
Sure. It would be unwise.
And it's complicated for him too,
because there is a lack of uniformity with a lot of the
Boogaloo communities.
Right.
There is an embracing of Antifa sometimes even,
and black lives matter, or at least a loose accelerationism
being the goal, regardless of ideology behind it.
Yes. Perhaps some would say a potentially performative
collaboration and an acceptance of those left wing sort of
groups.
And that would be really difficult for Alex to explain to
his audience.
He's made such a sort of market off of globalist,
devil bad, Alex, Patriot, God, good.
Yeah. You know?
And I don't think that he'd be able to have his audience
understand the idea.
They're like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
They're going there because they want to antagonize.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But also that they're trying to bring some people in there.
I know I've called them all demons,
but they're trying to bring in the accelerationists who I
guess are good now.
I don't know.
I've gotten some messages in the past from folks who,
or into boogaloo stuff.
And they implore me to understand that, you know,
it's about guns and gun rights.
Sure.
And the feeling that I have that I come around on it is I'm
not going to judge any individual based on their liking to
wear Hawaiian shirts and protest for the second amendment.
Sure.
But I'm also not going to trust them.
Yes.
If they associate themselves with a group like this.
And part of the reason for that is there have been enough
instances in the past of people who associate with boogaloo,
iconography, ideas, the movement,
doing things that are meant to accelerationist protests.
You know, make, who was that guy,
that sergeant who shot a cop and then wrote
a book and blood on his car.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He was talking prior to this about using left-wing protests,
using the energy of it in their anger for their purposes.
There's been enough instances of that.
There's been all that discussion.
And then let's just deal with the fact that boogaloo is a
reference to electric boogaloo break into,
which is like,
it was a meme back in 2012 about a second civil war.
Right.
The whole organizing central thing is a joke,
quote unquote joke about,
all right, we're going to have to have a second civil war.
Right.
Boogaloo is from electric boogaloo,
civil war to electric boogaloo.
If you are someone who just cares about people's liberty and
rights and second amendment,
and you also like to be goofy and wear a Hawaiian shirt,
I would implore you to not be associated with the group
that's name is derived from a joke about how we need a
second civil war.
That would be wise.
And has spawned a bunch of incredibly malevolent actors.
There's nothing about this Hawaiian shirt that's intrinsic
to the thing that they seem to want to push for.
Yeah.
There's nothing, it just, I don't know.
It seems like a bridge too far.
I just can't imagine being in 2021 and taking anybody at
face value who says anything similar to that.
It's 2021 guys.
We don't take them at face value anymore.
Maybe you're a good person.
I know plenty of good people who are second amendment
people, tons of them.
But if I took any of them at face value,
I would be an insane person.
That's simply not a thing that we get to do anymore with
second amendment people.
I would bet that there are many individuals who consider
themselves part of the oath keepers that are decent,
family, caring, considerate people that aren't the type
that would have a napalm bomb.
Right. Right.
But. Napalm bombs, still rare.
True.
That said, even if that individual I could see as possibly
a decent person and I could probably get along with.
Sure.
I would not align myself with them politically.
Right.
Were I to know that they were associated
with the oath keepers.
Totally.
Because that's a deal breaker.
And I feel the same way largely about the Boogaloo stuff.
Yeah.
No, I just background check everybody I meet anymore now.
Just go back through their Twitter feed.
Just going back through the ah, ah, ah.
Nah, nah, nah.
You're not a face value second amendment guy.
Ah, I caught ya.
I don't believe anything.
So Alex does not want a violent revolution.
Sure.
But he is against the Boogaloo folks, which makes sense.
I mean, they kind of are gearing towards
like the inevitability of a second.
But it's kind of what Alex said.
He's, he's makes no sense.
Okay.
Those of you out there that are like,
oh, let's just have a violent revolution.
You're always the ones that are asking somebody else to do it.
You're always the ones asking somebody else to do it.
You know, take the Boogaloos.
They've said, and I'm gonna ask them about this,
that they want to have an armed march
the weekend after the sixth.
But if you have an armed march in DC,
they'll arrest you for that.
You can say, well, it's my second amendment.
They'll still arrest you.
And so then we didn't see the Boogaloos show up armed.
Were they hoping other people would?
I don't know.
I just don't like this thing
of let's have violent revolution.
And then people say, okay, well you go first.
Well, I'm not going first and.
There's so much in that clip there
that just contradicts Alex's entire branding.
Yeah.
He's saying that he isn't gonna go first,
but he also spent so much of his time on his show
yelling about how he's the tip of the spear.
The spear.
And Infowars is the thing that it's at the front.
It hits the barbed wire to make sure
it's safe for everyone else to charge.
Absolutely.
If you listened to Alex's show
and believed a word of what he said,
you might be surprised to hear him say
he doesn't want to be at the front.
Also, Alex's opposition to the Boogaloo idea
of having armed marches makes no sense.
None.
Alex is a gun rights absolutist.
And in the past, he's been pretty clear
that every American has the right to carry arms
peacefully and responsibly at protests.
The idea that a certain group is being told
that they'll be arrested if they march armed
should be a huge violation of his concept
of the Second Amendment,
and yet here he is saying that the Boogaloo type
shouldn't march armed because the state told them not to?
This is where it's important to recognize
that Alex has no real concrete principles
that he's working off of,
or else his position here would have to be different.
He doesn't have a principled belief
in the right to gun ownership.
He just likes shooting guns a lot,
and he found that it was a really marketable niche
to be a guy who yells vague threats
towards anyone who indicates support for gun regulation.
True.
At the moment, business requires that he actually
be in favor of people he would normally call gun grabbers,
and somehow this doesn't seem weird
to a large portion of his audience.
Yeah, I mean, when your ideology is,
er, money, and your strategy is scramble
every time something weird happens,
then yeah, you're gonna get into
some real uncomfortable situations.
It does appear that way.
Yeah.
Someone else who's in an uncomfortable situation
is old Donald J. Trump.
Oh.
He's got his impeachment trial coming up.
Sure.
And Alex has a pretty good idea.
I believe.
Of what he needs to do.
Okay.
He's lost over 60 other platforms,
so he can be silenced, listen to this,
silenced ahead of and during his trial.
And it guarantees they're saying,
oh, let the president's lawyers put on the defense.
No.
Put Trump in there.
Put Trump in there on the witness seat
and let them attack him and lie about him,
and all he's gotta do is have a hit list of exhibits
after they attack him that he puts on,
and it will destroy them right out of a Perry Mason movie.
Yeah, that's right.
Get Trump up there.
Just putting the whole system on trial.
Yes, please.
I would like that.
Please take that advice.
That is something that I would,
that would be the first time
that I have ever watched an entire speaking,
yeah, yeah, I would be riveted.
Yes, keep on going, man.
It's, I think it's sound advice to be like,
let your lawyers represent you in a trial.
A man who takes himself as a client has a fool for a lawyer.
Yeah.
So Alex is really getting into this idea
that Trump needs to get up there
and lambast the entire Congress.
Yeah, I think that'd work.
And then he pulls out a really weird quote.
Right out of the real footage
of the famous House Committee on Un-American Activities,
and then the Senate Committee on Un-American Activities,
and the lawyer says, have you no decency?
You know, just that point.
And I mean, I could go into that trial
and annihilate them, annihilate them.
This is their Waterloo.
But of course, they're always the aggressive globalist.
We always cower to them.
We always act like we're the bad guys
and we're on the defense.
So that'd be great.
The idea of Trump like having Alex
as his sort of representative in court.
I thought it was going to be the best it could be
with Trump representing himself.
But now the idea of Trump represented by Alex Jones
has one upped it again.
God damn.
It would be a zoo.
It would just, I don't even, I couldn't even imagine it.
I would love it.
It would be perfect.
Now that famous quote that have you no sense of decency,
that's an interesting thing for Alex to pull out.
That line was spoken by Joseph Welch,
a lawyer who's representing the army
in a case against Joseph McCarthy.
McCarthy had accused one of the young attorneys
working with Welch of being connected to the communists.
And that is what prompted Welch
to question McCarthy's decency.
The beginning of the quote is actually quote,
and tell this moment, Senator,
I think I never really gauged your cruelty
or your recklessness.
This hearing was being broadcast on television
and most essentially it destroyed Joseph McCarthy's career.
At least in part because it clearly exposed
how much of a witch hunt McCarthy was engaging in.
Alex loves Joseph McCarthy
and thinks that the House Un-American Activities Committee
was absolutely legitimate
and they were doing the essential work
of rooting out commies.
Alex shouldn't celebrate the line have you no decency.
I was really confused by that
because it was directed towards the guy.
That's what threw me for a loop.
No.
Okay, so he's saying he really could have taken it
to Joseph McCarthy if he had.
He's saying that he could be that lawyer
saying it to like Nancy Pelosi.
Right.
Or I guess Chuck Schumer
because it would be in the Senate.
He doesn't understand how things work.
Nope.
He's evoking something that should be like a deep wound
in his anti-communist psyche.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you destroyed the guy
who I think or I think could have solved
all of our non-white problems, yeah.
So in this next clip,
we get one of the more unsettling ideas
that Alex has about the Boogaloo types.
And this is something that we've heard him express before
and it's a revelation that he kinda can tell
whether or not a group is real or not by who they target.
Okay, that's great.
They wanna accelerate us into a physical conflict
because they believe they can kill our free society
and submit their takeover that way.
That's why they're gonna lead paramilitary groups
that are either knowingly controlled or unknowingly controlled
because of their low IQs
into hitting targets that are not good targets.
I mean, let me tell you, I'm not saying kill anybody, okay?
But you know, the globalists coming at us
with these deadly vaccines
that they know are meant to be populated,
the super unpopular top globalists, Klaus Schwab,
Bill Gates, notice you never see anybody
actually going after the people above Biden, above Trump.
There's all the secret service from the president
to make you think they actually run things.
Seem disappointed that people aren't making runs
at Bill Gates and Klaus Schwab.
All right, I wrote this down as a quote.
I'm not saying kill anybody.
But you know.
You know.
That's words that mean kill people.
No, that's me.
Yeah.
No, that's kill people.
Yeah, I think that the message is astoundingly clear.
Absolutely clear.
I'm not saying kill anybody, but that's what.
See now, if I'm not saying kill anybody,
I'm going to say, I'm not saying kill anybody, period.
Period.
Period in that sentence.
Not comma, because nothing that comes after that comma
is gonna be anything other than, but we should kill people.
You know, the next clause is generally gonna be like.
Negates the first clause.
Yeah, or at least delineates like circumstances
where the first clause doesn't apply.
By the rules of grammar,
Alex has called for violent revolution.
Does feel that way.
Yeah.
So, but the thing that he's calling for even more
is that Trump needs to turn this damn impeachment trial
into a circus.
I love it.
And we need to get that message to Trump
and we are getting that message to him
that he needs to go on the offense.
He needs to demand to face his accusers.
He needs to demand to be in that Senate trial.
He needs to make it three weeks long, a month long.
Suck all the oxygen out of Biden.
And I hate to even say all this on air,
but this is the advice I've actually gotten to the president.
I'll leave it at that.
He needs to just demand, because I mean, in a real trial,
he could have a two month trial.
And Trump just needs to dominate,
suck all the air out of Biden.
And he can literally turn this whole thing around
against him if he doesn't abide that he's been defeated.
I can tell you, he doesn't feel defeated,
but he just feels totally sick of it and pissed off
that this was allowed to happen.
And I'm telling you, Trump needs to go on the offense.
They're telling him behind the scenes just on record
that if he shuts up and goes along and rolls over,
they're gonna leave him alone.
No, they're not.
The only way they leave him alone
is when they're defeated.
This is like the same shit he was saying four years ago.
Yeah.
Yep.
They're saying like, oh, just leave this alone
and we'll leave you alone.
Like, no, these globalists, they're making these deals.
It's just, this is so boring.
Yeah.
He's talking about his own feelings.
I know, I'm disappointed to be in reruns
of reality right now.
This is really a bummer.
You can almost feel it, the way he's,
the manner of speech, he's just coming up with things
that he, Alex personally feels and applying them to Trump.
Yep, yep.
It's ridiculous.
I would like to yell at Nancy Pelosi.
So strangely enough, my advice to Trump is to yell at,
he should do what I wish I could do, is all he's saying.
Yeah.
So there's big Proud Boy news.
Sure.
Also, it should be pointed out
that Alex was jumped into the Proud Boys
by Gavin McGinnis on air on Infowars.
That's true.
So he is technically a Proud Boy.
That is true.
He aimed cereals.
While Gavin was giving him little silly punches.
Yeah, I think that should be actionable.
Rufio Panman.
Yes.
Based stick man.
Right.
Gavin McGinnis, Alex Jones, Rambo Joe Biggs.
What a murderer's row of shit bags.
But there's news about one of the other members.
Okay.
All right, we've got some really big Proud Boy news
that's gonna be breaking next segment.
I wish I never had to hear that sentence.
I wanna cover this very important topic right now.
The Left is not created.
Okay.
What?
Big Proud Boy news.
The Left doesn't know how to make memes as well as I do.
Yeah, I'm the meme machine.
That's what they call me.
Yeah.
Yeah, all right, great.
So yeah, there was news that came out
that in the past, Enrique Tarrio.
Yeah, he was an informant, right?
Yes.
I've read these stories and I'm not sure
that I see concrete indications that he still is.
Right.
And I can see that going either way.
And so I am gonna withhold any kind of judgment
or any declaration on what his current behaviors are.
Right, right, right.
Because I'm not involved and I've never met the guy
and I don't give a shit.
Now, I would say if I were Alex, I might be worried.
Because Enrique Tarrio's been on Alex's show
a bunch of times.
He was really good friends with Joe Biggs
who just got arrested.
Well, there's that.
I would say that Alex might have,
or Joe Biggs might have, said some things
that you wouldn't want to say to an informant.
Well, I bet they probably didn't text it
to each other though, Dan.
I don't know if that's the case.
And like I said, I still need to see further indications
to feel at least, you know, like convinced
that he was like snitching on the Proud Boys or whatever.
See now, this is a problem for me.
It is kind of funny.
This is a problem for me.
This is what I'm talking about
with higher class of criminal, all right?
The Proud Boys are also really bad at being a gang.
Like in Chicago, if you get taken up by the cops
and you're in a gang, man, they just assume you talk.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter if you talked or not.
You can't take that risk.
Sure.
So they can.
Of course you say Enrique Tarrio is an informant,
whether he is or not.
You gotta get him out of there.
I think if you're doing like security for the Proud Boys,
yes.
I understand making that like sort of safety decision.
Right.
I understand that.
This is a gang that punches you
and makes you name cereals to get in.
I understand that.
They should get into meth is what I'm trying to say.
Isn't that what I'm saying?
Maybe our expectations for how tight a ship they run
should be adjusted.
They're also-
They do not have a string or bell.
No. That is for sure.
No.
They laugh at Gavin McGinnis' jokes.
It's not a good group.
No, that's not good.
So Alex has some vaccine news.
Also, you have some vaccine news,
like you mentioned up top.
I have good news.
Yep, Alex has some other news.
Oh.
Hey, did you hear?
Merck has pulled its two vaccines
because of major health problems and bad reactions,
both their mRNA vaccine and their regular vaccine
that had a bizarre measles delivery system.
Those have been pulled and they say it doesn't work
and it's dangerous and you shouldn't take a vaccine
because they know the house of cards is coming down.
Alex isn't wrong about the underlying story here.
And that is that Merck did in fact abandon its attempts
to create two experimental coronavirus vaccines this week.
However, the message of this story
is completely misrepresented by Alex into being anti-vax.
In reality, a story like this
should give people even more confidence
about the vaccines that are widely available
because this clearly demonstrates
that there are some vaccines that don't make the cut.
These two that were developed by Merck
are not the same ones that were made by Pfizer or Moderna.
So pointing at this story
as a way to make those vaccines look bad makes no sense,
but that's exactly what Alex is doing.
Alex is also just lying when he says
that Merck decided to stop pursuing these vaccines
because of bad reactions.
From NPR, quote, Merck is halting development
of its two COVID-19 vaccine candidates
saying that while the drugs seem to be safe,
they didn't generate enough of an immune response
to effectively protect people against the coronavirus.
So they just didn't work.
Yeah, Merck spent a ton of money
on developing these potential vaccines
and ultimately it didn't work.
The fact that this happens pretty regularly
is actually an indictment of Alex's fictional worldview.
And it's really interesting
to see him reporting on a story
that's a huge problem for his narratives
as if it somehow validates them.
It's very weird.
Yeah, but the narrative for them is
if the system isn't working, the system isn't working.
And the system is, if it is working,
then the system isn't working
because if it's working, it's trying to kill you.
Maybe.
And that idea of like-
I think in this case,
it's more just like a sleight of hand thing
where it's like these vaccines got recalled.
Now, how can you trust this completely separate vaccine?
And then also just making shit up.
Yeah, I mean, the obvious thing for him,
the obvious problem there is that this in many ways
is essentially the free market
working the way it's supposed to.
They don't have a product they can sell
so they can't sell it.
Yeah.
It's very simple.
But Alex would believe that even if they did have a product
that was ineffective because everything is about money,
just 100%, they would still sell it
even though it wasn't effective
because they'd sunk so much money into it.
Of course.
He just doesn't, he has an incoherent worldview.
Doesn't care.
Anyway, Alex is gonna get to interviewing this Boogaloo
gentleman and it's interesting
because he can't quite figure out where to place himself
because he's like,
you do have a responsibility to overthrow a government.
Well, he already said earlier,
I'm not saying kill anybody, but you know.
And that theme may develop later.
I believe that.
This just is really, this makes no sense to me.
I believe the Declaration of Independence.
I believe that when we have a destructive government
that has come after our freedoms and our rights
and that has proven itself to be an authoritarian force
that isn't going away, it's not just our right,
it's our duty to throw off such a force.
But I don't wanna stupidly do it.
I don't wanna be led by the ADL,
the Southern Poverty Law Center.
I don't wanna be led by idiots.
I don't want to go with the wrong targets
and I wanna exhaust every form of unofficial warfare
because war is just politics by other means,
as Von Bismarck said.
The pen is my iron sword.
And so I'm not very good at war if I can't win with the pen.
And so I'm really trying to do that.
You're not gonna win with the pen or a sword.
But I just, I don't understand what he's saying
other than kill my enemies.
Yes.
Because he's saying that these,
like I don't wanna be led
by the Southern Poverty Law Center or the ADL.
That's meaningless.
That's just nonsense.
But the problem that he seems to have
is that these groups aren't doing what he wants.
Yes.
Yes, that's a real issue.
Because he says that you have a responsibility
to throw off this government
once it reaches X, Y, and Z point.
Right.
His show is essentially all about
how we've reached X, Y, and Z point.
99% of it, yes.
Yeah.
Also the left is uncreative.
That's true.
Those are basically the two themes.
Yeah, so he makes a career out of arguing
that we have reached the point
where it's essential to throw off the government
and then you have these people who are like,
well, eh?
Well, he made a career out of it.
If he hadn't made a career out of it,
he would be more interested in people actually doing it.
Yeah, probably.
Because there's not a money in that.
Exactly.
Yeah.
So now we get to the point where Mike Dunn,
Boogaloo Boy extraordinaire comes on for the interview.
And this note that I have right here on this clip is just,
this is a bad idea.
Oh.
Now, Mike Dunn, I appreciate him coming on.
Usually people we disagree with are cowards.
They don't come on.
So he gets landmarks coming on.
And Mike Dunn is a well-known Boogaloo Boy.
They call him the leader, the founder,
constitutional adherent, 20-year-old,
former Trump supporter, turned libertarian.
I guess he was in the Marines too as well.
And so I'm going to try to give him
the floor of the rest of this segment.
We've got about seven minutes left.
Then I've got my questions and my comments.
So he wants to set us straight.
We're all about folks that want to set us straight.
And if I'm wrong, I will apologize.
So Mike, thanks for coming on.
None of that is accurate.
Mm.
Yeah.
It's funny too, whenever Owen Schroyer, who's also there,
chiming in periodically, he is complaining
about these other people who are too cowardly to come on.
It's like, Brian Stelter, Rachel Maddow.
Yeah, they're not going to come on.
No.
No, no, they're not going to come on.
Also, maybe the reason that he's coming on
is because he's not your, he doesn't disagree with you.
Yeah.
I'm not saying that you guys are wrong.
Maybe he recognizes that you are very usable.
Yeah.
You are a platform that is exploitable for his purposes.
Which he could have learned is a lot easier
than he might think if he had listened to our show.
Sure.
I mean, Steve Pajanik laid it out.
Exactly.
That's all you got to do.
Alex, you are fucking so easy.
So easy.
Yeah.
So Mike starts off, like I said, the first thing he does
is correct Alex about the leadership.
Right.
First things first, I'm not the leader of the Boogaloo.
I'm not the founder.
It's an autonomous movement.
I'm just someone who's in the movement who
helped make it big in the media limelight and public face.
And I happen to control a large portion of the movement.
So I just wanted to get that straight.
The movement was not founded by me,
and I'm not the leader of it.
Simply a prominent figure in it.
I control a large portion of it is an interesting.
That's a strange.
Yeah.
I control a large, how large a portion?
I don't know.
But he is a guy who there was a Vice article and video
about him done, I believe, last year.
And it sort of traces some of his roots
from being a Virginia gun rights militia type, which
if you recall a year ago, Alex was super into.
Loved it.
And then through that, he fell in with Boogaloo communities
and what have you.
I assume the article started with Mike Dunn dot dot dot
or Mike Fun question mark.
And then just a Hawaiian shirt emoji.
Yeah.
Yeah, so he was involved prior to getting
into the Boogaloo stuff in just a lot of stuff
that Alex is super, super into and capitalized
on the gun rights rally in Virginia
that Alex talks about all the time.
Some of the malicious stuff that Mike was involved in
was involved in that.
No, it's almost like a lot of these far right guys
are almost giving these exit interviews with these people
like, hey, you did a great job, but we got to cut you loose.
And by cut you loose, I mean blame you for everything
that we've done.
And the flip side of it is kind of a don't meet your heroes.
Yeah.
Kind of lesson for all these people who
are coming on to Alex's show.
Wait a second, I thought you liked us.
I thought you were great, Alex, but unfortunately, oh
boy, Mike.
Mike is, I think that he can tell that Alex
is trying to set him up.
Yeah.
Because Alex is trying to be a dick to him.
And I think that Mike knows that,
and he's a millennial Gen Z kind of guy.
Gen Z, I guess.
But, or Zoom?
What's it called?
Don't even worry about it.
I don't know the name of Generations.
Don't worry about it.
But he's a youth, and he's equipped
to handle Alex's bullshit.
Trouble.
To start with, Alex, you started with a quote.
I want to address that as well, from yourself.
Here's some other quotes from you.
1776 is the answer to 1984.
You also said if just 5% of people
got motivated in some direction, and it doesn't
have to be what I believe in, but if they got motivated
and stopped getting their political ideologies
from the media, they would go and figure out what they want.
And we're literally doing that.
We have been motivated.
We figured out what we wanted, which is freedom from tyranny.
And we're willing to stand against that.
When you say 1776 is the answer to 1984 and your involvement
in the Capitol incidents, I know you can put up
an article from the Gateway Pundit
accusing me of inciting the violence and blah, blah, blah.
Feeding into the media narrative like you
don't want others to do.
Hold on a second.
I don't mean to interrupt you.
I don't see what they're putting up.
Let's not put the articles up right now.
I'll get to my questions coming up.
I want him to have the floor uninterrupted.
Please continue.
Alex is giving him a lot of space, and I think it's very
weird.
Oh, you weren't supposed to listen to me when I talked.
You're definitely not supposed to come back at me with things
that I've said before.
You're definitely not supposed to use my words and ideas
to justify your beliefs and your actions
that I'm supposed to be condemning.
Yeah, because they are my words, and boy, they sound
exactly like what you're doing.
Oh, boy.
I'm in trouble now.
Whoops.
I imagine that's his thought process is just like, oh, no,
he used words.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Again, I wouldn't have done this interview if I were Alex.
I think this is a bad idea.
I think that he thinks that he can do these gotcha moments,
like the Bill Ayers interview or David Rothschild.
And it just, he's so bad at this.
He's really good at steamrolling con men.
He's not good at talking to people
who have actual beliefs.
Yeah, it's trouble.
I don't agree with Mike, and I don't trust him.
I don't think he's being necessarily above board
and fully honest, even in this interview,
that I do believe that he has beliefs more
than Alex, and that's a problem.
Alex can't handle it.
And beliefs that are almost certainly inspired by Alex.
Yes, and he is aware enough to recognize that Alex doesn't
actually have those beliefs, and that's not good.
Uh-oh.
But 1776 is the answer to 1984.
I want to paint you a picture from 1776.
January 18th, Major Habersheen arrests a royal governor,
James Wright.
March 2nd, Americans begin shelling Boston, March 4th.
We captured Dorchester Heights after a bloody battle.
April 7th, we had a bloody major sea battle.
August 27th, we had the Battle of Long Island.
September 15th, we had another bloody battle.
September 21st, New York City, a quarter of it was burned.
October 11th, we had another bloody battle.
That's just one of the many instances of 1776.
So when you call for 1776, I almost
feel like you're doing it just for the merch and not
for the actual fact.
We understand that our laws, our avenues
that we should go through, have been clogged up
by old men in politics.
Politicians who were there for the money,
they've been clogged up.
They blocked us from actually having access to our rights.
They've infringed upon constitutional rights,
whether it be the First Amendment, the Second
Amendment, the Fourth Amendment, it doesn't matter.
They've infringed on those rights,
and we realize that those avenues are no longer open to
us.
And so the only answer to that is
to try to win the hearts and the minds of the people.
And ultimately, there is going to be a revolution.
Even you know this, and I know this.
Even you.
This is fucked for Alex.
Wow.
This is not good.
No.
This is a terrible situation for him
to be in because he's being rightly
confronted about his using Americana for merch and shit.
That is a valid criticism for it to be levied against Alex.
But he's also being scolded by somebody
who stands to deeper radicalize, perhaps, his audience.
Yeah, I'm interested in that push and pull
because it does seem like there are twisted motivations here
for Alex.
Like one, of course, he has to be top dog.
But two, he does want to give these exact ideas a platform.
True.
So that, to me, is part of why he's not interrupting so much.
Yeah.
It's hard for me to tell if it's like a way of painting
this person as the fall guy, but also at the same time.
Spreading his message.
There is a part of me that feels like maybe that's
what's going on.
But I've seen enough interviews on Alex's show
that are just like, he does not prepare at all.
That he probably thought this was going to be a 20-year-old
idiot who didn't know anything, who
didn't have an awareness of Alex's career,
didn't have an ability to stand up for himself.
I would bet that he's just like, I'm going to talk to a tween?
All right.
I'm a man.
Yeah, it is fascinating.
I've been on there 27 years, man.
It's really funny how completely clueless old people are,
considering the fact that I believe
that 90% of 16-year-olds are savvier and probably have
a better education than I do.
If you're under 23, I'm terrified, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You have powers.
You guys don't even know what kind of fucking powers
you have yet.
And you're not going to lose an argument to Alex fucking Jones.
No, that's pretty clear.
I think there are probably some 20-year-olds who would,
but this guy is not what Alex expected, I don't believe.
Now, the thing that I take issue with,
or the thing that I'm worried about, is that this is a guy
who stands to be a negative influence on Alex's audience,
insomuch as there are people who are like Gavin McInnes,
or Nick Fuentes, or E. Michael Jones, who
come on Alex's show and stand to take audiences
on a different path.
Take them from this, I mean, it's bad,
but there's kind of an exploitative, vampiric nature
to Alex's just keeping people scared
and then selling them dumb pills they don't need.
Like, I hate it.
It's an awful thing, but it's kind of,
Alex has a vested interest in them not going too far.
He's doing it for the merch.
Yes.
And falling into overtly anti-Semitic communities,
starting to watch the American Journal.
These kinds of things are dangerous,
and I don't think that he is the right person, this Mike,
to be making these critiques of Alex that
are justified and fair.
And one of the reasons is, I mean,
Mike believes a lot of the same stuff
that Alex does, like that the election was a fraudulent one.
We all saw widespread voter fraud.
We all understand what happened in the election.
We're not Trump fans.
We're not Biden fans.
We understand that.
But a lot of you hold on to the hope of voting your way out
of voter fraud, which is an impossibility.
We see it as there has to be a revolution.
There has to be a result. And it's going to come to that.
We preach unity, bottom scale unity,
against the elitist, the globalist, the people
who control our country, the people who
control our presidents, which you talked about previously.
We see that as a way to say, hey, we're a dumb attorney,
and we're going to stand against it.
We're part of those 3% that have stood up, or in your case,
from your quote, it's just 5% of people.
We're part of that.
We're the ones who have stood up.
And that's pretty much all I had to say concerning the boogaloo
and what we're about.
We're about freedom and liberty for all people,
non-discrimination, and the Constitution
being applicable to those who disagree with you.
So this is a chance to launder and sell this group as,
but I honestly don't even understand
why he would say that as if it's a good thing on Info Wars.
Like, we don't discriminate.
This whole thing is about discriminating, man.
Yeah, all I hear is, we're looking for the right boot
to lick.
We ran out of boots.
Now we are hoping somebody will come up
who will help us oppress the people we want to oppress.
I don't know if I would agree that that's
the vibe I get off Mike.
Sure.
Alex, perhaps.
No, I don't get that.
Well, I mean, I guess it's that kind of always getting
to that conversation of like, you guys just
don't realize because you think you're
going to be the mine owner.
You don't think that you're going
to be under a different boot.
You think it's going to be some sort of utopia
where you get to do whatever you want to do,
and all you're doing is establishing someone else
to fuck you over, probably worse.
Yeah, and it's also, there were logistical reasons
in a disconnected world why the Civil War in the United
States in the 1860s didn't really
lead to the complete destruction of America.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're another Civil War to break out today.
It's not like what this fantasy is, where it's like,
one side will fight the other, and then someone will win,
and then America.
There are no battlefields anymore in the States.
No, but were there to be an actual Civil War,
do you think that that would work
for the other global powers that are tied up in our economy?
Well.
It wouldn't work.
I imagine that China and Europe now,
naturally they do have a massive investment in the United States
continuing to function the same way.
I imagine they would stand on the sidelines
if all of the sudden the global economy were to crash.
Let's see who wins.
Because two groups of morons were dressed in red and blue
on fucking a plane running at each other with knives.
Oh, no.
We need the economy and the entire world
to get back online.
We better pull for the boogaloos.
Yeah, no chance.
There's far ranging consequences from this sort
of fantastical idea that they have.
It was one of the reasons why I have
a real lack of interest in accelerationist ideas
is like, anyway, I really don't care.
I don't care for this guy's kind of ideology.
And I also don't take him at face value
about the non-discrimination.
Maybe him personally, I don't know.
I don't know anything about him as an individual
except for what he's put out on Vice and shit.
But I don't know.
Yeah, I find it hard to believe how many people still believe
that a civil war in the United States
would have two armies opposed to each other with two generals
all choosing which troops to put where,
as opposed to either being like, there's
no middle ground in a war in the United States.
It's either street battles in every United States city
or explosions everywhere.
There's no just, we're going to go fight.
And you know the quickest way to get the UN here too
is probably that.
Yes.
Get the UN involved.
Oh, man.
I'm sure Alex would love that.
Yeah, it'd be great.
So Mike and Alex get to talking about how Alex's ideas are
kind of behind what Mike is doing.
And Alex has a really tough time with this.
I'm just trying to figure out, are these,
because you mentioned this.
And you respond to the 1776 thing
because I'm somebody that's very clear that I believe
in civil disobedience.
I believe in defensive defense and violence.
I really want to fix this peacefully.
In fact, let's just go there first.
You're saying listening to my work, my energy,
you're taking from that the idea of revolution or armed
conflict?
Yeah, no shit.
I definitely wouldn't say that I took it directly from you.
I'm just saying that the idea that you portray
and the message that you carry sometimes
tend to look like you're just there to create merch
and not actually stand for an actual revolution.
You talk about peaceful protesting.
And I always thought, the Alex Jones I listened to growing up
was someone who wanted the government to fear the people.
And so I'm not saying that you incited it or you directed it.
But I am saying that if you continue to preach a 1776
revolution or the type of message that you preach,
you're going to have to figure out whether you're just
going to bend the knee and continue
to make your talk show or if you're actually
going to stand against the tyranny that is present in the US.
Well, Mike, let's be 100% clear.
You better believe I sell t-shirts and I sell product.
That gets the word out, that's dedication.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
They want to shut us down.
They want to kill our speech.
They want us to exercise our speech online.
You guys wear your shirts that are Hawaiian shirts,
to see them being owned.
We're info wars.
And damn right, I've got the globalists
trying to shut me down.
I am a capitalist.
I didn't get $10.6 billion from Democrat donors
and George Soros like Black Lives Matter.
So I don't get any funding like Antifa or a BLM.
I don't have people volunteering to do my security.
I pay my security.
I don't have the Boogaloo boys volunteering for my security.
I pay for my security.
So I mean, I'm a capitalist.
I am not ashamed of selling products.
But to be clear, if we get to a point
where I think I've got to be violent,
then I'll do what I have to do.
That's why I'm fighting so hard.
Because I'm not going to stand around in capitals with guns
if I get violent.
Yeah, if Alex gets violent, he's going to have suction cups
on his hands, skiggling up the side of a building.
Alex Jones is going to be a commando,
breaking into Soros's house with piano wire.
Now, we all know Alex is a paratrooper.
He's going to get in that parachute,
and he's going to land directly on top of the catapult
building, repel his way down.
I know one thing about Alex Jones,
and that is he is a man who is not unfamiliar with stealth.
Yeah.
Hey, hey, hey, where's my enemies?
I'm a little drunk.
Yeah, that's a little silly.
I do think that Mike has a decent point,
though, that Alex, the way he engages with his rhetoric
and the way he behaves on air, does lead to a point
where he has to be honest with himself.
Am I just being a talk show host,
or am I actually trying to rile people up to 1776?
And we've heard Alex, when shit gets too hot, he's like,
I'm just a talk show host, man.
Right.
You know, Shadow Gate comes out, he's like,
I don't do any of this shit.
Yeah, when the country is stable,
or at least more stable than it is now,
you can get away with the answer to 1984 is 1776.
Everybody gets that it's a metaphor.
Now, it's not a metaphor.
It's not.
You can't say it without meaning it, because it's happening.
Yeah, and your use of it as a metaphor
is part of what normalizes the state that we're in now,
in the same way that Mimi jokes about civil war
to electric boogaloo leads to people actually wanting
to engage in ways that could set off a second civil war.
Like, jokes can lead to action.
And hey, maybe jokes were fine then, but not now.
We can't do this like, no, no, no, what I really meant was,
no, be specific, be careful in your language,
and make sure that everybody is fucking trying, at least.
It would be helpful.
And instead, it's just like, oh, no, no, I didn't mean that.
Well, guess what?
Hundreds of thousands of people are ready for 1776,
maybe millions.
And they're surprised that you're not.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
So now, this is the point in the interview
where I think Alex realizes, uh-oh, I
better be mean to this guy.
I've got to condescend to him.
How do you see this thing unfold?
And tell me, General George Washington 2.0,
how we're going to do this revolution.
I don't know.
I thought you were the General George Washington 2.0.
And, of course.
No, no, no, I'm not the guy out there
saying we're going to have a revolution.
So tell me.
We need a declaration of independence by the states.
We need a coalition of leaders ready
with a bill of particulars of what we want.
And then we go to war.
Not a bunch of people taking selfies in the Capitol.
That's the opposite of what we need.
We need George Washington.
He hadn't shown up yet.
So I'm telling you, tell me what we do, General Dunn.
What do we do right now?
Go for it.
Get those papers in order.
Get the plan of government for after in order.
And actually get it done and start building forces
like you're supposed to, like all of us had done.
I think that Alex thought he'd be cowed by that yelling.
I think that he thought he'd be intimidated by Alex
doing a little outburst.
See, look at how stupid this is.
You don't have a plan in place.
OK, well, let's get a plan in place
and take over the government.
Oh, no.
Oh, I thought you were just going to be stupid.
Mike is saying, essentially, my part in this
is rising up people.
And that is what I have been doing.
Great.
We need those bills of particulars.
Why the fuck isn't anyone doing it?
Why are you doing it?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
No, he was like, I guess.
Alex is in a bad place.
I guess Alex was expecting him to reveal himself as stupid
and reveal that, look at all your stupid ideas that
don't make any sense.
And then when he didn't reveal himself as stupid,
he has to try and portray him as stupid.
And now he realizes that it's impenetrable.
You know, like, this is a generation
that's been raised on my generation's irony.
They're indestructible.
Well, it's impenetrable for Alex also,
because the only way to penetrate it
is to sort of also puncture your own mythology
and your own worldview.
Were you to say, like, well, all this stuff that we complain
about is bullshit.
So the reason that you want the bill of particulars
and a new government and all this is nonsense.
It's all lies that we've been spouting for years on the radio.
Now, you could do that, and then it
would devolve into a completely different conversation.
But Alex can't do that.
Mike is essentially bulletproof on a lot of points,
because he's talking to Alex, who he clearly
knows profits from putting on a certain presentation.
And he would stand to lose those profits
if he were to do the thing that would
deflate this conversation.
Yeah, I don't know why people who
are going to absolutely beat the shit out of Alex
in an interview do not bring a hype man.
So many different lines in there,
he said, where somebody should be on the call
to just be like, what?
I cannot believe you just did that.
Yeah.
And this would be a good place for it,
actually, because in this next clip,
Mike kind of chews Alex out a little bit.
We go to our capitals on where they say,
you know, in Richmond, Virginia, Owen Troyer drove there.
He saw some of my guys there on.
They said, hey, you can't open carry here anymore.
It's illegal now.
We went and we disobeyed it.
If they had tried to arrest us, we
would have used the Second Amendment the way
that it was intended, which is to limit government.
Hold on.
Say that again.
Where did you do this?
Because this is you putting your money where your mouth is.
Caravan.
This is in Richmond, Virginia.
It's illegal to open carry any protest or event armed.
So we go there for Owen Troyer's thing
when he came through with the Stop the Steal.
We've been at every protest, whether it
be MAGA, Black Lives Matter, anything,
to make sure that things are peaceful and respectful.
And we go there armed.
We disobeyed the law.
We stand against the tyranny.
And what we see, people like you, Alex,
who used to be my hero as a young man,
we see young men in the need to it repeatedly.
You have your talk shows.
You give your speeches.
But y'all don't actually stand against tyranny.
And that's disheartening as a young man, a young American,
and someone involved in the liberty movement
and constitutionalism.
Personally, I'm not speaking for the young man.
Wait a minute.
How am I not standing against tyranny,
fighting evil legislation, marching, going out
and having events?
Sorry?
Because you talk.
We go out there.
We actually disobey.
We stand there armed.
We're not willing to.
We don't boot lick like a lot of you and Republicans do.
We actually stand up against the tyranny that is prevalent.
That's what I want to see y'all do.
When you ask, well, what's the revolution look like?
Well, there you go.
It's us engaging in civil disobedience.
And if they decide to do something,
then we'll stand against that.
You're not going out there where they say, hey,
you can't open carry here.
You can't exercise a constitutional right.
You're not going out there and disobey it.
Y'all want to do everything by the law
because you're the party of law and order.
Well, no, I have supported open carry.
And I've supported the lawsuits and all the rest of it.
So that's not a fair statement.
Oh, you lost.
Listen to the sound of his voice.
Listen to the defeat.
That was so weak.
Alex cannot rebut.
I went outside one time.
You can honestly imagine somebody
who likes Alex hearing this and it
shattering some of the illusion that you have about Alex
as him being a competent, confident, strong force.
This guy is mirroring back a lot of Alex's rhetoric.
He's pointing out the places where
it's clear that Alex is in contradiction with himself.
And it's, uh.
And he's hammering the fact that he's in it for the merch.
You talk.
You talk for money.
That's what you do.
Yeah, you talk.
We act.
And that's why, you know, if there is tyranny, then.
I'm halfway waiting for this to end like a Molyneux declaring
himself a white nationalist where Alex is just like, well,
I guess I'm a boogaloo boy, too.
I didn't know it, but here we are.
We'll see how it ends.
Oh, god.
So Alex, like you said, I mean, you could tell there was
a little bit of submission there around showed ass.
That like, oh, no, I've supported open carry.
And so Alex has to retreat to trying to have gotcha moments.
So he brings up the Capitol.
The strategic blunder of rushing into the Capitol,
the strategic blunder of the selfies and the cute art stuff
and all the rest of it is not what Trump wanted.
It's not what I wanted.
That was our rally to try to put pressure on them to have
a 10 day investigation of election fraud.
So wait, do you think what happened to the Capitol
was a victory or a fiasco?
I definitely think it was the right thing
for the wrong reasons.
I think it was a good way to make government
for the people again.
It was nice to see members of Congress on their knees
fearing the people.
I think it was the right thing for the wrong reasons.
So you now wish that people wouldn't have knocked down
the doors and gone in there?
I wish 100% that people would do it more all over this country
and make government for the people.
So that's a little bit fucked up.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, there is nothing quite so terrifying as a zealot.
Especially a 20 year old.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But also I can think of a lot of historical problems
that come from 20 year old zealots.
He is also limiting his own personal involvement
with the Capitol and the storming of it.
There's an article in Reuters from January 8th
that says that Mike Dunn, quote, who lives in Virginia
said three or four groups of loyalists under his command
helped storm the Capitol this week amid a motley mix
of rioters who supported President Donald Trump's
attempt to overturn the results of the November
presidential election.
While most boogaloos are libertarians
who largely oppose Trump, Dunn said
the group embraced the moment to strike against the government.
So I don't know.
Like, if this Reuters article is wrong?
Right.
But he downplays his own involvement.
And it seems like there might be some disingenuousness
on his part in terms of his exact actions.
I just don't think that you can get away with commanding people
to overthrow the Capitol.
It seems like this Reuters article, if true,
is a problem.
Yeah, yeah.
That said, I don't know.
Yeah, that's fair.
I do know that that is a point that Alex really hoped
would show some sort of weakness on Mike's part.
But no, he stands firm to what he has a consistency.
And I'm not saying that as a positive thing.
No, no, no.
I believe I just pointed out, zealotry, terrifying.
Yeah, yeah.
So Owen Troyer is there, like I said.
And he pops his little head in to say, hey, how's it going?
And then he indicates that, hey, I'm into this stuff.
I like it.
We got to do it later.
OK, all right, great.
And then Alex, you could tell, is getting a little heated.
There's no doubt that we have encroaching global government.
There's no doubt that the government's out of control.
There's no doubt that the biggest crooks in America
are in Washington, DC.
I think 90% of Americans would agree to that.
Here's the problem, though.
And Mike, I'd like to get your response to this.
We're not in a 1776 colonists versus the British government
time, where we're hiding in the woods.
And we've got the local communities.
And they don't have a world technocracy set up against us,
or a federal government set up against us.
I mean, I've been to jail multiple times
for my free speech.
You know that.
So I mean, to sit here and say.
Oh, you've done nothing because you didn't stand around
in a Hawaiian shirt with a gun.
Whoa.
All right, Alex.
All right, I'm not going to just let these two young dick
wads talk around me without me asserting some dominance.
And Alex is being a real dick.
I mean, like.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Absolutely.
I'm not going to sit here and like feel bad, too bad for Mike.
But like, you know, I can tell he's being rude.
Alex is being rude.
I am not winning the war of ideas somehow.
Alex invited this guy to be on his show.
And now he's just being a dick to him because he's
failed to take the upper ground in this argument.
As usual, he's pouting and he's throwing a fit.
Yeah.
And in this next clip, again, we return to this theme.
It's like, if you were real, you would kill my enemies.
But I'm telling you that the target, if Boogaloo's are real.
I'm not saying do this.
But if you really want a violent revolution,
you should be calling for the Council on Foreign Relations.
Every member should be in a deck of cards,
the whole leadership, Richard and Haas, all the rest of them.
And the last thing I want is anything
to happen to Bill Gates or Richard and Haas or any of them.
I'm just saying, if you really want to do this,
Klaus Schwab should be the ace of spades.
And then Bill Gates is, you know, right after that.
OK, I'm just telling you, man, you're hitting the wrong target.
Oh, boy.
So you are not endorsing him.
But you are saying, if you take out my targets, I like you.
I will consider you real.
You'll be real.
Yeah, you wouldn't be you wouldn't be suspected
of being SPLC, ADL-run false flaggers
if only you did kill Richard and Haas.
Listen, I'm not telling you that I want anything bad
to happen to Bill Gates.
But, you know.
But I am going to use the same sort of visual metaphor
that was used in the War on Terror, Saddam Hussein.
Hey, hey, you know, you said, I asked you
what the plan was.
And you came back with, it should be my idea.
And my idea is that you should take out these targets.
Oh, shit, I'm in it, aren't I?
Oh, no.
Fuck.
So Alex comes back from break.
They're talking.
And now the Proud Boys, under the bus,
does not look like they're going to be heroes.
Oh, god.
Although Alex is walking a little bit of a fine line
with this.
Because he's not.
He's saying that he still supports the Proud Boys
and what have you.
He is a Proud Boy.
He's now lumping them in with forces
that might have acted no good.
Sure.
I'm not an informant like Enrique Tarrio.
But at the same time, I want to expose the federal forces that
are involved in this.
We identified Boogaloos.
And we identified Proud Boys leading the attack
on the capital of Antifa.
And I'm now bringing all this out today.
I was already intending to before this broke about Tarrio.
Sure.
So.
And we have the footage.
So no Boogaloos win the capital.
Put it up of a Boogaloo boy walking into the capital.
And I will.
Hold on, they have their faces covered.
But I mean, well, we got you saying
you have fire teams inside the capital.
But I'm going to ask you right now.
Building.
You said we're inside the capital.
You said that doesn't mean what you said.
DC is the capital, not the capital building.
Capital building.
Oh, DC is the capital.
Oh, OK.
Oops.
Alex's big gotcha is a tweet.
Or maybe it was a post on Parler.
I'm not sure.
But it's Mike saying that they have four fire
teams at the capital.
Right.
With an A.
Well, I don't know.
I didn't actually see the tweet.
But it makes sense that his explanation
is we met the country's capital, not the building.
Sir, sir, there are two words.
I know they are homophones.
They sound the same.
Yeah, so Alex thinks that's a big gotcha
because you have four teams inside the building.
We were talking about Bain Capital.
We went to the wrong building.
I am really sorry about that.
You see how quickly that gets resolved.
He's like, I was talking about the city.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
And he was curt about it, too.
He didn't try and dissemble.
He was just like, there's a difference!
Yeah.
And so this isn't going well.
But Alex has blamed the Boogaloos
as being the people who were the ones who had the zip ties.
And they were the ones who were the actual really scary folks
in the storming of the capital.
They weren't the patriots.
And Alex has said that he's proved these things.
Yes, he has.
He's not just saying, I think it's them.
Pictures of you.
Now, because this interview isn't going well,
Alex kind of reveals that I'm just
looking for someone to blame.
And I decided it was you.
Here's the deal.
We're going to find out who these guys were
in camo that had masks on.
And we think they work for the FBI, OK?
Because our president that really got elected
is on trial in a week and a half.
And we're pissed off about it, OK?
And we wanted to put peaceful pressure on them
to show our numbers.
And we got screwed over by some people.
We're going to find out who they are.
You hear the headlines.
Oh, boy.
Oh, great.
Yeah.
That is not what someone would say
if they've proved something.
No, no.
Nope.
I have proven it's the Bugalo Boys.
And we are going to find out who did it.
And I think they work for the FBI.
I'm pretty sure it was the FBI.
We don't know who these people are, but we think they're FBI.
We're going to find out.
We're going to get to the bottom of this.
Hey, Mike, have I ever told you about how I'm a psychic based
on people's posture?
It's like a body language expert,
but I can tell from still photographs.
Also, by the way, God gave me a vision
30 years ago that laid all of this out for me.
Mike, you're not really fitting into this vision.
I'm confused.
Mike, I think you might be working for the devil, Mike.
You're the devil, Mike.
Mike.
See, now, I don't understand why he
doesn't end every interview that doesn't go well with like,
well, obviously, you're working for the devil, sir.
And I must have you off my show.
Obviously, this is a challenge that the devil
has thrown my way.
And I decide to rise above it.
Click.
Pass.
The devil took Jesus into the desert for 40 days and 40
nights, and on night one, Jesus said, nah, I'm out.
Did you know that the devil is actually a booger boy?
I did not know that.
Alex proved that.
That's fair.
So like I said, Alex has claimed that he's
proved all these things.
When he's talking about it on his show,
it's not like spitballing ideas.
It's talking about we have definitive proof,
sources have confirmed.
We have the documents.
Everything that it was, Antifa and Boogaloo Boys.
It's all there.
And some Q folks got tricked into going and taking selfies.
And the Patriots were doing the right thing.
They were fighting off Antifa.
But they didn't actually go into the, yeah.
They were trying to fight off Antifa.
Oh, that's right.
They're fighting off Antifa.
But they got overwhelmed.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
So when you hear a clip like this,
it's just like, this is not, this is incongruous.
We're trying to find out who the bravacaturgrips are.
And I'll just say it.
And I've said this.
I'm not against the Proud Boys.
They've been lied about.
I don't think they're racist, all the other stuff.
We know Proud Boys not wearing their outfits,
not wearing their uniforms, that were
part of the Capitol breach.
We have tweets by you and by other people
saying they supported the Capitol attack
and that it was a great thing.
Now you're kind of halfway backing off of that.
What?
I'm not here trying to get you arrested.
Like who?
My big question is, I see this Dr. Gold lady just
going in being arrested.
I see Brandon Straka, or Strak, being arrested when he
was just there doing nothing.
And then it freaks me out.
Interesting way of putting that.
Like who are the men in uniforms with masks
handing out clubs saying, attack, attack, attack.
That's my big question.
So Alex, if he knew what was going on
and he had the information that he claims to,
he would not be trying to figure out
who the provacaturgrips are.
He would not be having the alleged leader
of the Boogaloo's on and being like, well,
we're just trying to spitball and figure out who did what.
Also, there's video of Brandon Straka
citing a crowd to steal a cop's shield.
All he was doing was nothing.
He's just not, he wasn't doing anything.
He posted a video of himself yelling, take his shield.
That's barely anything.
What if, look, if he was in my hometown, Princeton, Illinois,
nobody would be bothered by it.
Right, but then they did take a guy's shield.
OK, well, now there is that.
There is that.
That's hard to, I understand cause and effect.
Brandon Straka's going to prison.
I'm telling you, you know, cause and effect
is really just the way we perceive
entropy in the universe.
So this has already happened.
Yeah.
And I think that at this point in the interview,
you can really tell that Alex is done.
He's been defeated.
He doesn't have the energy.
It's just no good.
Too young.
You can see, Mike Dunn, where I'm a little concerned
and I see this going on.
I'm worried about the idea of your movement
that anybody can say they're a Boogaloo.
It's like, are you for anonymous?
Well, anybody can be anonymous.
Are you for Q?
Anybody can be for Q. I mean, don't you worry that.
For Infowars.
Are you for Antifa?
But explain to me Boogaloo, where it came from.
Are you worried about being taken over?
I mean, what do you think's really happening here?
Since Boogaloo is an ideology, it's
not necessarily a worry of being taken over
because if somebody doesn't embody the ideology,
then they're not Boogaloo.
Boogaloo started as a meme, a joke back in like 2012.
It was just an online joke.
And then in 2019, several people started
making it a little more public and actually turned it
to an ideology or belief that liberty is for all
and we're done being tread on.
Yeah, and it's a joke meme that turned it
to an ideology about the need for a second Civil War.
So I don't think we can sort of eliminate that and pretend
that that's not a piece of this.
I think that's fairly important.
But Alex signaling defeat there and just being like,
well, you know, look, I'm just trying to tell you
that your group can be co-opted.
That is an attempt at a trick.
That is a false move backwards into a pose of submission.
It's a sidestep, more like.
Yes, because then Alex tries to get him to sort of what's
it called?
What's the pleading the fifth?
Incriminate.
Yes, self-incriminate.
Alex is trying to get him to self-incriminate.
Great.
Yeah, look, look, here's my issue.
Are you guys putting on a manifesto of targets
because, you know, random police, capitals, that's
I mean, that's just a seat of what the people should
be in control of.
I mean, I'm not calling for targets, God forbid.
I don't want any violence.
What about Bill Gates?
What about Ted Turner?
What people trying to put poison vaccines in us?
What about the UN?
So tell me, tell me in a deck of cards
like Saddam Hussein was the top target, 2003.
Like, who's the ace of spades for you guys?
It would be ignorant to sit here and release a manifesto
or say this is a target.
Yeah, so let's not mention any real evil kingpins, right?
I'm not going to allow you to be in the same,
something like that.
Say that again?
I'm not going to allow you to go be in the same,
something like that.
That would be ridiculous.
Oh, like the Southern Poverty Law Center
does posing as malicious, goading people into stuff?
Maybe you're Scott Hill.
Oh, maybe.
Oh, maybe I am.
Oh, shit.
Listen, what I'm telling you is I'm going to save this country.
OK.
This is the Spider-Man meme.
This is.
It's just what this is.
Oh, I'm the bad guy.
No, you're the bad guy.
All right, this isn't going well for me.
So tell me who you want to kill on there.
Yeah, exactly.
Alex, that's a stupid idea.
I'm not going to do that.
Oh, look at you.
Look at you.
Oh, you're SPL.
That's what you are.
Oh, my God.
That is so funny.
Yeah, but I mean, like, God bless.
I mean, like, God bless.
I don't know how I would phrase it.
It shows some wherewithal for Mike
to recognize, like, I'm not going to talk like this on air.
Yeah, no, I think it's a good.
I would say nice move.
If this was Bobby Fischer versus Kasparov,
it would be like, nice move, sir.
It would be an unnecessary error to make.
It would be a blunder, in fact, to continue the chess metaphor.
So Alex, I think he also makes it a little too
obvious in this conversation that this is personal.
Like, this really feels personal.
And in this clip, Alex is going to express
that by way of being like, hey, I'm the real person fighting
for liberty, and you can prove that because a bunch of people
are suing me.
Is anyone suing you, Mike?
That's fair.
I want to save this country, and running around storming
capitals is not the way to do it.
Either the courts or not, Alex, the country is not safe.
Let me ask you a question.
Do you have 50 Democratic lawsuits against you?
What to say again?
Do you have the Democratic Party financing your destruction
like I do?
I don't know, nor do I care.
I'm going to stand by what I do.
No, I'm asking you, see, why am I under so much attack?
Because I know nothing.
I'm this coward.
I thought it was because you were a piece of shit.
I've never done anything.
And you're this, because you walk around with a gun,
it's like, oh my god, I'm supposed
to fall down on my knees.
And like, holy hell, this is my leader.
I mean, seriously, you keep telling me that I stood down.
You said, my generation stood down.
Bull.
My generation didn't stand down.
It's the fact that you're doing the same thing
that's been done for years, and it's not
accomplishing anything.
The only thing that's going to accomplish
is forcing a revolution.
I am not doing the same thing.
I'm not Democrat, Republican.
I'm exposing the globalist program.
Do you understand that information is powerful?
They're scared of it?
You're talking.
That's all you're doing.
You're doing the same thing that's been done for years.
So now you are admitting you told people
to storm the Capitol.
Because you're not like me, a coward.
You're a big man.
You are a woman.
I have not told anybody to storm the Capitol.
I've preached revolution, and I always will.
So Alex is trying to, again, incriminate him.
He's trying to get him in this thing where it's like, oh, you
told people to storm the Capitol.
Because then, like, afterwards, Alex
can still use that for his narratives
if he gets him into that box.
Right.
And not least of which, he wants this guy emotional.
Yes.
He wants this guy to be like, no, I did tell
people to storm the Capitol.
Yeah, whereas there's a poise to it just being like,
no, you guys, you are engaging in the same sort of shit
that doesn't achieve any of the goals you profess to have,
and we're going to force a revolution.
Now, that idea there is the accelerationist idea.
The force of revolution is not something that is,
it's not what goes well with the public-facing idea
of the Boogaloo types that want you to think like, oh, we're
just here standing around making sure nothing gets out of control.
Right.
It's like, no, you're there because you
want to force a revolution.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And you want something to go bad,
and people start shooting each other.
Right.
And I think one of the most difficult things for Alex
is he doesn't understand that their agenda begins
with revolution.
There's no, like, I don't think they
care what strikes it either.
If it was a left-wing cause, they would be like,
yeah, let's go and the revolution
is what their goal is.
Yeah, yeah.
So you can't really be like, oh, see, you're so stupid.
And it's like, no, we just didn't succeed yet.
The goal is still a revolution.
We're not changing our goal because we lose.
Yeah, and I would say that based on this reporting in Reuters,
if accurate, is counter to what Mike
is presenting here on the show.
And I have some question about that.
I don't know what the reality is.
I wasn't there.
But it does seem to be like, at least a reason to be like,
I don't think that you're above board.
I don't think that you're being honest here.
Now, here's where things turn a little bit more hostile.
Alex brings up that the Boogaloo types
were trying to get a second march going
after January 6, an armed march in DC.
Alex conflates Boogaloo types and Mike personally
and is accusing Mike of trying to get people
to do an armed march while they sit back and watch
the chaos happen.
And Mike.
Mike, you're pulling a me, right?
And Mike calls Alex a liar.
The Boogaloo supreme leadership, whoever they are,
said, go to DC the weekend after the 6 and have armed marches.
But you guys didn't show up.
So you were trying to get other people to come into DC.
And she could sit back and eat popcorn and watch that.
Or was that not the Boogaloo that said that?
It's the word you like, Alex.
It's called a psyop, brother.
Oh, a psyop.
So you're not going to respond to the stack of tweets
I've got and messages from you saying,
we're going to have an armed march three days after the 6.
Yeah, Alex, you're a liar.
Show the tweet where I said we're going to have an armed march.
Oh, shit.
Show the tweet where I said.
So the Boogaloo's did not call.
They didn't say, armed march is still on for DC.
We're going to have it.
Show the tweet where I said there's going to be an armed march.
I'm at the Boogaloo lordship.
Well, you said you're not the lordship.
I said I'm not the leader, correct.
Oh, so you don't have any problems or anything.
Have you ever been to the ADL or Southern Poverty Law Center
headquarters?
I don't care to go to any of those places
because I can care less about them.
So Alex is now just like, this is falling apart.
Yeah.
Alex was conflating other Boogaloo people
and this guy personally.
And this guy calls it out that you're saying that I did this.
I didn't do that.
And Alex realizes like, ah, shit.
I did just get called out on that sleight of hand.
Hey, have you ever been to the SPLC Center?
To tangentially imply that you're an agent provocateur,
I'm not even going to say it.
I'm going to be like, hey, you ever been to these places?
Yeah, this is soft.
Weak tea.
So Alex now goes out to break and he thinks
he's won a little bit.
I think he thinks he's got some win back.
He's saved face.
Because he's made some suggestion.
And then he also got Mike to say that an armed march on DC
a week after the storming of the Capitol
would be an unwise strategic move.
And somehow this is hypocritical,
although I think Alex agrees.
I don't know what's going on anymore.
I have said that no armed march in DC.
And armed march in DC would be unwise.
I said that repeatedly.
Well, good.
Good for you.
I remember the Boogaloo said that.
So wait, I thought you were a man of action, though.
You just said that I'm the coward.
You're the man of action.
Wise action.
I go to Capitol so we can punk the police department,
punk City Council.
You told me earlier that we should not follow the law.
You said I'm a coward.
I follow the law.
You don't follow the law because you're for revolution.
Correct.
I am for revolution.
But I am for a wise revolution, which
is where we go to these capitals, we punk the PDs,
we punk the City Councils that want to make unlawful cops.
We punk the PDs.
Yeah, because the local cops are our issue.
All right, all right.
Hey, you are the Boogaloo, lordship.
We're going to come right back if you're still here with us.
You hear that laughing because Alex
thinks like he's got a dog.
Got him.
I finally got him.
Don't think so.
Don't think you got anything there.
No, I'm very bored with this conversation.
I'm annoyed by it.
It sounds way too much like a fucking Philosophy 101
course where they're like, well, I'm for platonic ideals
and I'm for existentialism.
And it's like you're both stupid.
I don't appreciate this.
And this is even worse because you guys are not
arguing about philosophy.
You're like, how do we kill all these people?
I think that I can relate to what you're talking about
in that I think it's very stupid and it's a frustrating
conversation to listen to.
But I do still think that there's an importance to it.
Oh, no, that's what I'm saying.
OK, well, we're talking about how to kill everyone.
Right.
And you're also seeing just yet another example
of how the ecosystems that have been spawned
by people like Alex have now outgrown them
to a point where they are able to embarrass him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The young eat the old, Dan.
It's how it's always going to go.
It does feel a bit like that.
There is a theme of that.
So they come back as Mike did not
leave after Alex routinely insulted him and suggested
that he went to the SPLC.
Sure.
And Mike repays the favor by blowing up
one of Alex's narratives and makes it clear that Antifa
was not at the Capitol.
Uh-oh.
What I said was I would not encourage an open arm march
on DC, which is what I've said repeatedly, because I find it
a poor tactical plan, a poor strategy.
So I know you like blowing things out of proportion
and trying to pay me as the bad guy or pay me as illogical.
But I've been consistent with what I'm saying.
You just keep trying to twist out, man.
No, Mike.
I'm trying to find out who the guys in camo
are that lead the attack with Antifa
and then get a few, maybe 100 idiots to go in with them
so that they can destroy the peaceful movement.
Look, I've been around quite a few Antifa.
There are some Antifa that are good.
The majority we've not had good interactions with,
we do not support.
But there are some that are good.
But I've interacted with a lot of Antifa.
And I can assure you that they were not
Antifa that were on that front line in that Capitol riot.
So trying to find somebody to point fingers at,
you're failing when you're pointing at Antifa.
They were not there.
Oh, I'm failing.
Even though they arrested an Antifa leader that
said he brought 100 there, I saw a bunch of skinny jean guys
helping do it.
Oh, so this was all Trump people.
Yeah, it's called an op, Alex, the same thing
that you preached about.
What's an op?
It's not.
It's simply not true.
Oh, so OK.
So should Trump be arrested for inciting this?
Probably.
I think there are a lot of other problems
that Trump should be arrested for.
I don't believe he incited the insurrection at the Capitol.
No, but I believe there's a lot of other crimes
he should be arrested for.
So have you ever met?
Have you ever talked to Southern Poverty Law Center?
I don't believe so.
Maybe I talk to a lot of people.
A lot of people call me, ask questions, reporters, agencies.
I have no clue.
Oh, and you want to put any bookends on this?
I mean, this is just a mess.
That's just a dude giving up.
He asks him a second time, have you been to the SPLC?
Brutal.
Talk to them.
And now he's just like, Owen, you got anything?
See, now that's the problem with getting
that brief moment of victory.
It makes the gut punch loss all the worse.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And Owen doesn't do much better.
He starts talking about now that Trump is out,
maybe there's some stuff we can do.
Now we can argue about it.
Maybe there's some stuff we can do, now we
can organize against war.
Sure, sure.
Thanks, Owen.
And this actually brings up Mike having a decent point.
And that is like, you could have done that before.
We have to become unified.
So we can organize against the wars,
against the surveillance, against the mask,
against the forced inoculation.
I think that's a positive thing.
Let me ask Lord Boogaloo, do you agree with that, Lord Boogaloo?
So I'm 100% clear.
You're cool with the tyranny.
It's the tyranny that you like, which would be Donald Trump.
I just want to make sure I'm tracking on that.
So you're not actually against tyranny.
You're not actually for revolution.
You're only for doing it when somebody is in office
that you don't agree with.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
I just talked about all of us unifying
against forced inoculations of Joe Biden.
Trump's gone.
You wouldn't do it like Trump was in office
because you didn't stand against Trump.
You stood for the very time.
Well, I didn't stand around.
I didn't stand around with a gun in front of stuff and say,
hold on now.
That's another cheap shot, Mr. Fireteam.
We have fire teams in the Capitol.
We have taken the Capitol.
We are commando based Delta.
Come on, don't get mad, Mr. Dumb.
We're back in 60 seconds.
Alex is complaining about cheap shots
and he keeps calling him Lord Boogaloo and like the high master.
Mr. Dumb?
Mr. Dumb.
Oh, Mr. Dumb.
I thought he said Mr. Dumb.
No, that would have been too far.
I was like, wow, you ended with Mr. Dumb, huh?
OK.
But yeah, so they're talking about unity and unifying.
And it's like, we can now get together with folks
and fight against the war and all this.
And Mike's point is pretty fair that it's like, well,
you had no interest in reaching out to any other groups
when Trump was in office.
You weren't concerned with what inroads
you could make with cooperation because that's
the tyranny that you enjoy.
Yep.
Yeah.
Which again, is a good point.
I don't want it coming from him.
No, no, no.
He's essentially saying your belief system is incoherent
and Alex is proving it.
And Alex is trying to say his belief system is incoherent
and he's proving that it's not.
They're awful.
All of them are awful.
But when you have a coherent belief system
and you are in an interview with someone who doesn't,
they're going to be like a wave on the mountain.
So you've got nothing.
Yeah.
And Alex totally misses the point
that Mike was trying to make about how like, oh, yeah,
all this stuff, these real problems
that you could have found common cause with some other group
that maybe you politically disagree with.
He had no interest in any kind of unity before,
but now you do because Trump is not in office anymore.
He completely misses that point.
So the problem is, oh, and it's the same thing
I've seen with Republicans across the border,
people who identify as conservative or white.
Is that you're all for unity when it fits your idea.
You're all for, oh, let's ally with Black Lives Matter
or let's be friends with Black Lives Matter
because we got a stand against the government
because Joe Biden's in office
and his administration controls.
Where was that unity when Trump infringed
upon the Second Amendment?
But that's not fair, though.
That's not fair.
I didn't work with Black Lives Matter.
You did, Boogie Lou.
That's exactly the point that Mike is making.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah.
How can you both call for unity now
and then proudly say,
I would never work with Black Lives Matter.
And I didn't before.
Exactly.
Because I have, wait, what was I saying?
And then he calls him Boogie Lou.
More pejorative.
So we've already seen a couple of instances
of Alex trying to paint Mike
as a Southern Poverty Law Center collaborator.
And now Alex pulls out, he will talk to the FBI.
Okay.
Let's ask this question of the Grand Boogaloo.
What comes next in the Boogaloo universe?
Or is there no, it's an ideology.
Who creates, who's the high priest?
Who creates the ideology?
Or does it just flow forth from where?
It's autonomous.
And the next thing is unity.
Unifying the lower bodies,
the people that were subject to this globalism
that you speak of and this elitist mentality
that is running the US through our governmental officials.
It's unifying those people
and getting ready to stand physically
to defend our rights, our life,
liberty, and the pursuit of happiness.
Well, I mean, I think people have a right to stand up
and I think they should.
Let me ask you this.
Have you been contacted by the FBI?
Yes, I have.
You're not, you're not,
there's a joke in the Boogaloo that you're not Boogaloo.
You know, you haven't been questioned.
So the FBI has been all over us.
So what'd the FBI say?
What'd they come to you about?
They like asking questions, that's all.
And I don't like giving them answers.
So if that paints a good picture for you, I hope it does.
Well, I just think what happened at the Capitol
was called screwing the pooch
and it ruined the great thing we had set up
and it gave the left a major victory.
I was really hoping to blame you for it.
I was really hoping this interview would end up
with me being able to blame you for it,
but you have been going circles around me.
I guess you're an FBI informant
or maybe you're working for the FBI.
I don't know.
You mean, just go away.
I think Alex expected some caginess or some non-answer
when he asked if you've talked to the FBI.
Of course I have.
Yeah, the FBI is coming for me.
Duh, I'm voluntarily and loudly calling for a revolution.
Of course the FBI is coming for me.
I've talked to them and I stonewall them.
The only reason I've been murdered is because I'm white.
So Mike at this point has to clarify to Alex
because Alex is trying to pretend
that they aren't anti-globalist
because they don't target the same people
that Alex does and they haven't killed Bill Gates yet.
And so Mike has to clarify
that they're opposed to the New World Order
and then this goes way off the rails.
The Capitol is a symbol of us voting.
Just because it's been captured
doesn't mean we attack that.
The New World Order,
I'm not trying to get you to go attack people.
I'm just saying, if I saw a movement saying
we're going after Bill Gates and Klaus Schwab
and the Rothschilds, the New World Order
and the CFR building in New York,
I'd say those guys are real.
They're about to get a fight.
Because about 10 minutes after you said that,
they would be having the HRT SWAT teams
will be coming after your ass.
Within a day, you're going to get a SWAT team.
Alex, what have I said repeatedly?
I have said repeatedly that we stand against
the globalist and the elites
that continue to control this country.
So when you're saying,
oh, if I saw people that run after that,
we'd literally stand against it.
We stand against the pedophilia that's prevalent in Hollywood.
We stand against media controlling people.
We stand against the elitists that run our government.
We stand against the money that run our government.
It's just that we're going in a slightly different way
than what you agree with.
All I wanted to come on here and say, Alex,
if you'll allow me to finish real quick,
all I wanted to come on here and say, man,
is these people out there putting in the work,
you know, you called them CIA ops,
you said release the boogaloo.
You know, you like to make your jokes,
but these people are legitimate people
who are putting in the work
and believing in what they stand for.
There are people in the boogaloo movement
who don't agree with me.
who are different than me,
but these people put in works.
They're not CIA ops.
They don't work for the CIA.
They're not unwiddling CIA sources.
And they're not controlled opposition.
Like sometimes you appear to be.
We are legitimate people who believe
in what we stand for.
That's all I want to say.
Oh, I'm controlled opposition.
There you are, Alex.
I'm controlled.
Who gives me my orders?
Please tell me.
I do believe you're 100% controlled opposition, Alex.
That's why you'll never preach anything
besides peaceful and legal, lawful,
wonderful hunky dory ways of protest.
Okay, so I'm not the one saying
we got fire teams in the Capitol
and then you guys haven't been indicted
and then they're trying to indict me
and then you're sitting there
literally saying I'm getting orders
from a higher level group,
which is not the case.
Look at my eyes.
I take orders from God.
That's it.
You understand that?
You fired the one good man you had
and that was David Knight.
I do believe you were controlled opposition, Alex.
Oh no.
Once again, bad HR decisions
come back to haunt Alex.
Ah, I never thought I'd hear that said in seriousness.
20-year-old Boogaloo boy coming in like,
you're controlled opposition
because you fired David Knight.
Oh boy, oh boy.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Oh man, if only, if only.
This is the one time where if he had just listened
to that Stevie P's broadcast,
he could have just been like,
Steve literally said he's been manipulating you
this entire time.
Yeah.
You're so easy.
Of course you're controlled opposition.
Well, I mean, I don't know.
I think that the term is loaded.
Oh yeah, yeah, totally.
I wouldn't say that.
I'm saying from his point.
Yeah, yeah.
I think the term controlled opposition is so loaded
because it implies like state control or something.
And I don't know.
I don't see compelling evidence
that Alex is like working for the feds
or something like that.
But he is unreliable opposition.
Yeah.
Maybe not controlled opposition,
but he is a persuadable opposition.
Sure.
He's influenceable by people who play games
with his ego in particular,
his sense of self-importance.
Those are things that are real soft spots for him.
And Steve's such a good example of that.
Yeah.
I would be interested to know if we discover a new thing
that he's so weak to,
which is being belittled,
being forced to like,
do you think this is going to make him have to be like,
well, fine, I will act more aggressively
in order to look cool to these idiots?
I don't know.
I mean, you would think that our show
would be a part of his psychosis.
Yeah, that's true.
If that were the case.
That's true.
So I've made a career out of belittling him.
He's not trying to impress us.
That's something I was thinking about.
Yeah.
One of the things that's particularly dangerous about this
or something that makes it more difficult for Alex
is that if he had somebody who was like an Antifa person on,
he could berate them and humiliate them,
hit the pause button.
He can't really do that to somebody who has credibility
in the right-wing world, in quotes.
Somebody who might have access to an audience
of right-wing people that could like Alex.
Yeah, I mean, it's a weird thing to pop up into my brain,
but I was just thinking about how in World War II,
one of the big issues with the Japanese command
was that the higher-ups didn't want to lose face
in front of their subordinates.
So the subordinates were driving overall policy
by having this hardcore stance that was imparted upon them
by the leadership.
And then the leadership realizing that they were fucked
couldn't then say like, okay, we're fucked
because the subordinates would be like,
you guys are a bunch of cowards.
So it created this kind of feedback loop
where the more extreme elements were,
even though ostensibly they were under the command
of someone else,
they were the force that was driving policy at that time.
That sounds like the right win.
Yeah, exactly.
So Alex has been called controlled opposition
and he did not take kindly to that.
And this is Owen's cue to step in and cool things down.
Sure.
And so he tries to, hey guys.
Hey, we're all friends here.
We all want to end up-
We all want a violent revolution.
We all want to kill all of our enemies.
Look, we want this, but we got to do it later.
Exactly.
That's his whole thing.
I've been arrested for my peaceful protest.
I'm calling for, we have to awaken 50 million,
a hundred million, 200 million Americans
before you can ever even think about doing
a finger lick of violence in this country
and have a chance at victory.
That's all I'm saying.
Well, it doesn't matter.
We've done some good radio here
and had some thought provoking things.
What?
And I'm not going to do cheap-
Of all the things you've done.
You're a well-spoken person and you have,
I mean, I think you believe what you're saying.
And so we'll continue to watch the situation
as it unfolds.
And I appreciate you coming up here
and defending your ideas.
That's all I can say.
But yeah, it's pretty hilarious.
So I built this whole thing myself.
I did it with our listeners and I'm so proud
of the fact that I'm independent
and I don't trust people that aren't independent.
And that's what we're all about.
You're mad.
Also, I like the idea that he's saying,
I'm not going to take cheap shots
after an hour of cheap shots.
Totally.
I'm personally offended by him saying
that they did great radio.
Oh, great radio.
Personally offended.
Solid radio.
Absolutely.
That is the least true thing either of them
have said this entire time.
Well, I will say that as somebody
who listens to a ton of Infowars,
I think it was at least more interesting than usual.
Okay.
I don't think it's good.
And I think it's actually really dangerous.
And I think it's a negative thing.
But in terms of actual content,
looking at it as somebody who's external
and recognizes nefarious motives on both sides,
it is interesting to see the clash of agendas.
Oh, well, listen, Mr. Dunn,
we've done D minus radio today,
which is way above what we're used to.
So I think we're going to call this one an interview.
I think that there's a decent chance
you've humiliated me like crazy in front of my audience.
Yeah.
I don't feel confident at the end of this.
And I probably extended it too long
because I thought I could win in the end.
And boy, do I hope it drives traffic
because then maybe I'll sell some pills.
Yeah.
So now Mike leaves and Alex,
I guess now is aware of other things
that he should have brought up.
They talked for an hour.
And he didn't deny that's his.
So he lied in front of everyone.
He's a disgusting little rat.
What?
And I challenged him to come back on the show tomorrow.
Oh, my God.
Because I meant to get to this
and I forgot about it while it was on.
Yeah. Okay.
So Alex now has other posts and stuff.
I should have brought this up.
You had a fucking hour.
I forgot to get to it.
I asked him twice if he's talked to the SPLC.
I had printed out a stack of 30 tweets,
single tweet per page.
And I just forgot to get to all of them.
I frequently brought up
how he should be killing Bill Gates if he's real.
But I forgot to have my evidence
that he's a dirty little rat.
And now I don't know exactly
what Alex is even bringing up in that context,
nor do I particularly care.
No.
But I don't necessarily think that Alex is wrong
that he wasn't a totally good faith actor
in his interview.
Totally.
Like, I do think that Mike was being
a little bit disingenuous now.
Alex is being full disingenuous.
Well, I mean, you can't trust a zealot.
A zealot has every justification
for lying in service of zealotry.
Yeah, absolutely.
Well, there's one thing you can do with a zealot.
In fact, I challenge Mike Dunn
to a bare knuckles boxing match in a ring.
I'm 47.
He's 27.
I mean, he thinks he's so freaking tough all day long.
Let's do it.
Give the money to charity.
I am so sick of all these wannabe tough guys
running their fat mouths all day
about how badass they are.
Boy, look, I don't care one way or the other,
but Alex, that dude will murder you.
That dude will absolutely fucking murder you.
All it would take is a little bit of ducking and dodging.
Alex would burn out his cardio so fast
to the point where he couldn't even keep his hands up.
It's hard to fight for a long time.
And by a long time, I mean 30 seconds.
If you're 20 years old and you're boxing
a very much out of shape Alex Jones,
like 47-year-old dude.
With sleep apnea.
Yeah, allegedly.
Maybe not.
Maybe not. Apologies.
Apologies.
But he does have a thick neck.
Yes.
Like, yeah, okay.
You don't want him to connect on the first shot.
No.
But if you duck that, if you dodge the first couple swings he takes,
he's done.
Yeah.
This isn't a four minute 40 situation
where you can still go 10 rounds.
This is a dude who will absolutely destroy you.
It would be satisfying to watch in a perverse way.
Yeah.
So Alex talks to Pete Santilli, who is the guy who got arrested after the
Malheur standoff.
Because he's apparently now an expert on FBI infiltration on stuff.
And so Alex needs to sort of feel better about himself
after getting clowned by this Boogaloo dude.
And afterwards, Alex realizes like,
ah, right, fine, I don't want to box you.
You know, I think Owen's been right since the first hour.
Trying to guide me back to not fight with the Boogaloos and not fight with the Proud
Boys, which I'm not fighting with any of those groups.
I love the Proud Boys.
I agree with a lot of stuff the Boogaloos say.
I just see a fertile ground for the feds to set us up.
And you know what?
Fine, everybody wants a revolution.
You're trying to set him up.
It was all a joke about Mike Dunn in the boxing match.
I saw that stuff with, what's his name?
I've been on the show.
What's it called?
Logan Paul.
Logan Paul and the other Paul guy.
Logan Paul and I forget the other guys.
That's like the biggest news in the country
because they do the boxing matches.
It was a joke.
OK, I don't really want to fight you.
You'd you'd definitely be really embarrassing.
Awful.
I'd be humiliated in front of my heart.
Yeah, probably.
I'd have at least a black eye.
There's no doubt you'd knock out all of the teeth I've been grinding.
Yeah, yeah, I could use some new teeth.
Uh, hey, look, here's the deal.
Yeah.
Oh, and Owen's right.
Cooler heads should prevail.
I do think that I see the Boogaloo's as a way for the FBI and the man to set us up.
Now, granted, I've been spending weeks on my show using them as a fall guy
for the storming of the Capitol, which is kind of the same thing.
I literally tried to get one to commit to a target on my air.
I tried to make him incriminate himself.
I implied heavily and repeatedly that he works for the globalist secretly.
Yeah.
I failed.
And I guess we'll be friends now.
So embarrassing.
What an, like, just ineffective, bad, like, there's nothing good that can come of this.
I don't even know what Alex expected in terms of, like, a positive outcome from this.
Although I do think it's really, really funny that Alex is doing this like,
eh, I guess calmer heads got to prevail and we got to be friends with these people
that I have already said are awful.
And, wow, the intro music that's playing is The Doors.
Don't play with me because you're playing with fire.
I hate everyone.
There's an intern.
There's an intern who knows what's up.
Oh, it's got to be.
For sure.
Thematically, that is really funny.
Too on the nose.
Yeah.
So, like I said, this is sort of going to be a two-parter into Monday.
Right.
And one of the reasons is because I do know that at least someone from The Boogaloo Folk
was on the show on Thursday.
All right.
I did not have enough time before we needed to record in order to get that already for
Friday's episode, but that will be on Monday.
So, we'll be back on Monday for part two of this.
I haven't come up with a good pun, like the Caravanity Project.
That's trouble.
But trust me, by Monday, I will have a great pun.
Was there a Breakin' Three?
Let's find out.
Yeah, that's a good question.
I don't know.
Breakin' Three.
Rubber Boogaloo.
I don't know.
Breaking Bad season three.
All right.
I like that one.
Monday.
Breaking Bad season three.
We're having a great time.
Yeah, I'll come up with a better pun.
Nope.
Blackjack.
There was no date.
Ah, shit.
Yeah, you're gonna get this game one of these days.
Someday.
So, I think that there's some fun to be had by listening to this in terms of seeing somebody
mirror a lot of Alex's shit back to him in a way that Alex can't really deal with,
can't really respond to.
It's funny to hear him say, hey, you're probably controlled opposition, which also
implies that he thought that at the beginning of the interview, which is weird.
Why even go if you think he's controlled opposition?
I don't know.
Or why not make that the thing you bring up first?
I think because if he brought that up first, he wouldn't get the chance to defend Boogalooing.
It would immediately become like, I'm not controlled opposition, here's all the blah, blah, blah.
That's probably true.
And it does give a bit of a coloring to the beginning of the interview.
Totally.
Where the poise that he's showing or the kind of lack of concern with the way Alex is portraying
him may come from a place of like, I don't even believe you're real.
Yeah, I mean, it could also definitely come from a place where, I mean, obviously he had
quotes from Alex.
It could come from a place of preparation.
If you believe that you're going on a show that's controlled opposition, I imagine you'd
be like, okay, then I have to find a way to defeat that.
Otherwise there's no point in going on the show.
Or failing defeating that.
Yeah, exploiting it.
Existing that place in a way that I can achieve my goals while not falling into the traps
that will be set for me.
Like, hey, do you work for the SPLC?
Absolutely.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I think that he did that.
And I actually think that that's why this is dangerous.
Because I think that Mike successfully navigated the terrain of Alex Jones' shitty interview
style and was given a place where he could appear to be the person who lives Alex Jones'
ideals.
And I would not be surprised if that was not an effective recruitment tool to anybody listening
to Alex's show.
And that's bad.
And Alex should recognize, intentional or not, that is the effect that this sort of
thing has.
Thanks, okay.
The Boogaloo's should pay Alex for this, quite frankly.
Well, and then there's just that known psychological exploit in humanity where he sounds so confident.
He sounds like a true believer.
And he's laying out stuff in a way where you're like, I guess revolution has to happen somewhere.
And Alex can't refute that.
Exactly.
He can't disagree with it.
Owen's best thing is like, well, later.
Later, yeah, great.
That's a dumb argument.
Yep.
Yeah.
And you have it in opposition to or in juxtaposition with this guy who he's saying, I used to look
up to you.
You were my hero.
The Alex Jones that I grew up listening to, creating that differentiation between the
Alex Jones I grew up listening to and this person I'm talking to, who is Alex Jones in
the present, is damning.
Like, it's...
No, it's hard to...
He got clowned.
It's hard not to look at that like 23 and under generation and not see people who were
birthed in the misinformation age.
You know, like we lived through it.
They were born of it, you know?
So that ability to have that...
High speed misinformation.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
His misinformation was still going around in newsletters when we were kids.
Totally, but like the information era we live in, like they're not going to be cowed by
old media.
It's just not going to happen.
And Alex's old media.
Exactly.
Anyway, we'll see what happens on the Thursday show.
Will the bare knuckle boxing match that has been canceled happen?
Wait for Breaking Bad season three to find out.
Yes, we'll be back.
But until then, Jordan, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledgefight.com.
Now go to Betjordan.
Or Facebook.
We are on Facebook.
And if you could, please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work.
Yeah, we'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
Daryl Rundis.
I sometimes forget that I'm Daryl Rundis.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.