N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledgefight, knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying we are the bad guys.
Knowledge Fight.
Dan and Jordan, Knowledge Fight.
I need money.
Andy and Kansas, Andy and Kansas, Andy and...
Stop it, Andy and, Andy and Kansas.
It's time to pray.
Andy and Kansas you're on the air, thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a 50-cent color, I'm a huge fan.
I love your room.
Knowledgefight.com.
Knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody
Welcome back to Knowledgefight, I'm Dan. I'm Jordan
We're a couple dudes, like to sit around, drink novelty beverages
and talk a little bit about Alex
Ooooh
This is what happens when we record in the morning
Alex Jones talk
Hey Dan!
Dan, I have a quick question for you. What's up?
What's your bright spot this morning?
Well, this morning my bright spot, Jordan, is
we're recording this
and it's delayed and I appreciate everybody's
understanding. The weather in Chicago was
such that recording last night would have been
a disaster
unnecessary
risk in terms of
transportation
and my bright spot, I guess, is
that because of that
little scheduling
mix-up, shake-up, I was able to
watch a little bit of the Royal Rumble last night
Oh, okay
I love a Royal Rumble
Royal Rumble's the one where thirty people
run in every five minutes
I think it's every two or three minutes
but the time is fake
It's all fake
Who is the person this time who ran in
and within less than five seconds is gone?
I don't know if it was less than five seconds
but the sort of joke
elimination person was
The Hurricane
is a character who's a superhero
Wait, a guy named The Hurricane
was tossed out quickly?
Carter
There's a guy named Hurricane
and he's a sort of
goof character who is a superhero
and he got
eliminated pretty fast
That'll happen
I love a Royal Rumble
I do enjoy the pace of it
I like the idea of
people just keep coming
Theme songs kick in
which is one of my favorite things
There's exciting returns
and you know
there's a lot of potential for good storytelling
in that structure
and yeah
I enjoyed it
A lot of people are probably asking if I have
thoughts about it
I don't have thoughts about it
It just was
Hurricane was my favorite character
For sure
It was fun though
It was nice. How about you?
My Bright Spot Dan is a movie
called PG colon
Psycho Gorman
and it is
You guys listening cannot tell
that Jordan just leaned in very hard
Serious
It's one of those movies
that was made by just
somebody for
50 bucks or whatever
It is a live action cartoon
that is very occasionally
incredibly funny
in a dry deadpan
way and also incredibly terrible
but it's one of those movies that I'm not
going to recommend anybody watch
but I'm so happy it exists
What year are we talking about?
Immediately
This is recent?
Yeah
It's just wild and out there
It's one of those things where you're just
happy that something like that is real
If it didn't exist
I've thought about willing something like
that into existence before
Do you think that this has a possibility
of becoming a cult classic?
I do not
Aggressive head shaking
It's not good and people aren't going to watch it
or enjoy it but it's there
Wow high praise
It's important to be there
It's important for it to exist
I don't know how to describe something more
aptly than that
I feel like I understand exactly what you're talking about
and I have no idea what this thing is
Yeah exactly
We're going to be talking about the time span
between January 28th and
31st 2021 Blackjack
Yeah dammit I was actually
my plan on the way here
when he starts I'm going to go
Blehhhh
And then when you're done I'll go
Backfired
Failed miserably
We're not actually going to be talking about
the 29th on Friday because that was a
travel day for Alex coming back from Utah
vacation
I'm not going to be talking about the 30th
because that was Saturday
although I do have a little bit of something to say
Alex did a special
report with
Stuart Rhodes of the Oathkeepers
in studio
where they did running commentary
over a documentary
about the lockdown
or something
I was watching it and I was thinking
maybe we'll cover this but it's
just the two of them having kind of a casual
conversation about secession
and it's not really
Beyond
just saying that they did that and that
Stuart Rhodes is standing by
the Oathkeepers who got arrested
Of course
That's all they really need to know
I imagine he wakes up every morning and he's like
Hey they didn't get me yet
That's it. That's his life now
Oh the other thing that was worth
pointing out is that Stuart Rhodes
was saying that what you should do
is throw a big rave
and then when the police come to shut it down
shoot at them
Basically it was his
They're encroaching
on your right to live freely
and then you know
start it off
So here's what we do
We set a trap for the law
That's basically his version of
civil disobedience
Do something that will
attract the police and when they try to arrest you
start fighting
Okay so here's what we do
We hold a big rave but before that
we dig some trenches right
outside the rave and then put some
wooden spikes in there
and then cover it with leaves and when the cops come
they'll all fall and impale themselves
It's a pretty good plan Now Stuart I like your plan
Have you considered quicksand?
Instead of
spikes I find that quicksand works better
destroys the evidence
Derek actually came up with
moat and but
it's just too much I love moats
Now have you considered this
I know a guy
who likes to hoist safes
Get a pulley system going
Have a safe hanging way up in the air
I'm liking it I'm liking it Sometimes people use
pianos Sometimes people use pianos
I love pianos That is a possibility as well
When the cops come
drop the piano or safe
Also we need to have
two people walking by holding a very
pain of glass
I do like the idea
that it just turns into
Looney Tunes There's a watermelon
cart The whole thing
Someone walks through with a bunch of pies
Yeah
It's not a good
special report by any means
It's not interesting and it's very
long and we'll not be covering
it So Jordan
this episode we'll get down to business on it
So first let's take a little moment to say thank you
to some folks that have signed up or are supporting the show
That's a good idea So first the Bashki
thank you so much You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk Thank you
Thank you So much Then you're now
a policy wonk I'm a policy wonk
Thanks Aaron! Thank you
Next the Watson Alex had to go full
till boogie on thank you so much You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you, the Watson that has to go
full till boogie on Wil Huang
Zach the Axe thank you so much You are now
I'm a policy wonk
Thank You Zach and also
Someone who donated on an elevated level actually bequeathed their their shout-out
In a way that I think is really cool, so I'm still gonna give them a shout-out Tom
You're you're a technocrat Tom, but Tom wanted to give a shout-out to Chicago bond org
Which is the Chicago community bail fund and I know that we've brought up. You know like if
You know donate to a local charity bail fund in your area
But you know that's a specific one here in the city of Chicago, and yeah, I don't know that one
Then it's something that you know pointing pointing out a specific may be helpful in terms of like you know
Recognizing people in your area there is an analogous version of this so please
If you feel so inclined check out the local bail fund in your area
Please do and I guess Chicago bail fund you're a technocrat ah sure I'm a policy wonk crikey mate
That's fantastic. Have yourself a brew. How's your 401k doing, bro. We got to go full tilt boogie on this Watson alright
Let's just get down to business. We ain't making that money off that heroin
Why you pimps so good my neck is freakishly large. I declare info war on you
Thank you so much Tom and the Chicago bail fund yes
Thank you very much to the community bail fund community bail fund and then another thing
We should take care of here up top Jordan is we've got a couple of
Wonks out there who are celebrating the rotation around the Sun indeed
First Matthias got in touch with us and wanted us to give a shout out to Anna who had a birthday actually Sunday yesterday
Yeah, as we're recording. We would have recorded it on the day of your birth. Yes, so happy birthday
Either way yeah, absolutely. I hope you have better 20 21 than 20 20 black check agreed
Don't you dare?
Kevin Kneeland me with
Black jacks
Maria reached out and wanted us to wish a happy birthday to Eric and that's Eric with an a
It was a birthday is actually tomorrow February 2nd, and I got to say Eric if you're listening
Get fucking work on your thesis work on your history thesis
It's like enough too long. Yeah, what are we gonna be positive get to fucking work?
Ask that we wish him luck yep
I've decided to school. Yeah get that thesis. How we do it absolutely also good luck on that thesis for sure
Happy birthday to you
And also to Anna and everybody else who's celebrating a birthday here in 2121 blackjack
There's one god damn it Dan. There's one birthday wish from
David O'Daugherty
Who says that every song should have a recognition of death as well?
And his song for happy birthday is happy birthday to you. Happy birthday to you
Did you know that the rate of prostate cancer in men over the age of 85 is 100% so there you go?
Happy birthday put a downer
Here's an out-of-context drop from today's show
Burn in hell Frederick Nietzsche and Joe Biden and the rest of you Satanist Wow
Quite a quite a Nietzsche and Biden mm-hmm quite a group. That's a that's a list of
the two luminaries of
Philosophical thought I think when I think of Nietzsche I think of Biden when I think of Biden
I think of Nietzsche of course. Yeah, what is Biden, but the ubermensch indeed yeah, so here we start on the 28th
Alex has
Kind of figured out that at this point that oh boy some oath keepers got arrested
Yeah, because they stormed the Capitol yeah, I gotta figure out how this boys not
boogaloo
Straight up both keepers and and with a lot of these other groups
He's sort of been able to figure out how to thread the needle with Q anon. It's like okay
Yeah, it was all a setup mm-hmm with the the proud boys ah Enrique Tarrio
He is a fed totally totally absolutely easy stuff. Yeah with Antifa obviously. I hate them already
Yeah
Both keepers are a little bit more difficult because Alex is
Long time friends with Stuart Rhodes, but he's been a huge promoter of them
And so he kind of has got to be like hey somebody infiltrated
them
The old keepers have had three of their group
indicted
For going in to the Capitol and of course they have informants of people claiming that they were training
Months before there's some type of capital incursion who knows if any of that's true
But the point is is that they are sending infiltrators into every major organization. Yeah, who knows could be anybody yeah
Yeah, right. We're always we're always infiltrating wrong somebody strong take now now
So I was I was kind of confused when I launched into this episode because the day before this Alex had interviewed the
Boogaloo boy Mike Dunn mm-hmm
As I was listening back as I doing the episode. I realized that we missed a real
Great opportunity for a Mike Dunn Mike down
Oh
Did we miss a great opportunity or did we just miss a an okay opportunity yeah
I might have just been okay, but it was there on the table and we missed it
Alex had been humiliated and brow beaten by this guy. I was like okay
I know that he's gonna interview another Boogaloo dude on this 28th January 28th episode
It's like okay
Let's get to it, and he does not get to it instead this kind of seems to be where his head's at
And for me, let me just lay out what I think's biggest and first and foremost
Trump if he gets off the defense could be the president of the world as Chris ready
Said in a very important interview. That's gone viral last night. We should grab that
Chris ruddy interview it's on Newsmax. It's got about a million views as of this morning when I watch it 5 a.m.
And he says Trump can now be president of the world. That's actually a true statement
What the fuck are you talking all right, okay?
So if I understand correctly Trump can become president of the world
power and
Popularity yeah, so Xi Jinping is just gonna be like hey, man
I got you're just got to be the president of the world you got it. Yeah, yeah, absolutely
Absolutely, they're all gonna jump on board listen. I get it listen. I'm
Aggressively against your policies, and I think you're a toxic influence, but
Is he the president of Burma now is that how this goes Myanmar I know
Whenever it's taken over by a Junta
You make an interesting point yeah um I would say that first of all president of the world doesn't exist fair president of the
World being a position implies world government
I would say that would be him being a globalist if if anyone could be a globalist it would be president of the world
I don't want like Obama to be the president of the world
I don't want Hillary to be the president absolutely not
But I do remember a lot of time spent on
Infowars where Alex was talking about how Hillary was gonna be the president sure and then bill was going to become the secretary general
Of the UN yeah, and then they would be together the president of the world you got this was evil
Yeah, now Alex is I guess excited about Trump being the president of the world which sure again doesn't exist no
Whoa oh boy very dumb, which is is he going to get the whole world on board?
Or like what is he gonna do with the holdouts? I guess conquer them. Yeah, he would have to
I mean, it's yeah. Yeah, there's a lot of there's a lot of stuff that goes unspoken
There's one thing I know about Eritrea. They're not backing down
Switzerland gonna try to stay neutral
so
High minded concerns Trump in the possibility of being the president of the world sure certainly very serious mm-hmm
Also, Alex is a little bit petty
Mmm. I'm told by sources close to Biden that he has to read a teleprompter speech up to five times before he can give one
That's half-decent like he gave that very short
Shortest really ever inaugural speech I've heard of I mean Trump's over an hour long Biden's was less than ten minutes
Yeah, and that's because he had to rehearse that at least five times when he's not rehearsed folks
He doesn't know what planet he is on is it possible that Trump's was too long. Why is
His preparation the worst thing a human can do in our world yeah that that is so bizarre like yeah
Oh, he took it seriously
You know what I'm gonna. Go. I'm gonna go crazy on Alex. Let me tell you this
I've got maybe 45 minutes of material
It took me 10 years to write that and I practiced it way more than five times. Yeah, one of the things about performance
Is oftentimes you prepare to?
to
Appear unprepared yes or to prepare like you you want to feel natural. Yeah, I don't understand
You have to say something a million times to make it sound like you're saying it the first time there's a very big difference between
somebody who is
Desperately unprepared and off the cuff and somebody who is able to
Do things off the cuff yeah, I I don't I don't like
This particular instance too is very bizarre to me because it's the inauguration speech. Yeah, that's
Probably one of the most important
biggest sort of
highest respect
Speeches it's kind of a big deal that you're going to give especially in the early times of your presidency
You're gonna set the course maybe give a thesis for like what you want
To achieve in your time in office
I set the tone. I don't want somebody just being like ah fuck it. I'm gonna
I
Think that what Alex is saying is a bad thing about Biden is a actually a really good
I would argue that someone who gives a 10-minute speech over someone who gives an hour speech is always better and
Maybe the preparation allowed him to parse it down to 10 minutes. Maybe trim the fat
Editing is about getting rid of stuff. Yeah
so
Now that Alex knows that the Oath Keepers were there and arrested and that's gonna be infiltrators
maybe
I'll see how Stewart Alex has got a kind of adjust the narrative a little bit and what I think is really funny about this
Is that Alex has to keep changing the narrative?
Whenever new groups of right-wing people are proven to have been there and arrested. There's an issue there
So here's the newest version if we just don't let them use this capital event that they clearly infiltrated Patriot groups
They used Antifa to lead the chance
They got two or three people from each large Patriot group Boogaloo's
Quasi-patriot Oh and Troy are people there but I think overall it's being controlled
The the the Oath Keepers who've been a great organization. They really do remember
Still being set up. I've done a great job right here led by Stuart Rhodes. And then of course, you've got the proud boys that
Good people overall, but it's perfect to be set up at infiltrated and I've reviewed all the footage
There were Boogaloo's there were proud boys and there were
Three Oath Keepers out of the organization tens of thousands
It's true though that that that did lead the break into the capital and I've spent hours again last night this morning
And now that it's all codified now that it's all come out
I actually got tears in my eyes this morning having to watch a Wall Street Journal report
That shows the three proud boys being instrumental breaking into the capital
And they can say oh we showed them and all this stuff
They're not all fed. Some of them are just useful idiots. They got caught up in the mob psychology
But we're not gonna be like the media and lie
You know about things and just you know, say it was all provocateur. It was all staged
If some of it was people being foolish, so what he's trying to imply and he does on this episode
Is that like the people who are leading the charge?
There's a couple people from each group that they had got set up right to
Make everyone in those groups look guilty, correct? This is complicated. So
Every single right-wing group was infiltrated. Uh-huh, and then led to the capital to
Overthrow the government right now. Let me ask you this question Dan
Yeah, why was it so easy to lead them to the capital? Hmm? Is it maybe because they wanted to do it?
I mean, obviously, yes, it's not entrapment even if Alex is
A complete nonsensical conspiracy is true. Yeah, but also none of that is true. It just
Did it know you you guys tried and you failed that's it
You tried to overthrow a country, but you're not a unita. So you failed
The end yeah, and also I don't feel like Joe Biggs would like this kind of tone from Alex
Mm-hmm, because it implies that at best he's a useful idiot. Yeah. Yeah, he's calling everybody
What it this is almost like the revenge of stevie peas like now you're all useful idiots
I'm still the smart one. Damn it. I'm still standing. Yeah
Joe Biggs has got a like I
I got to imagine he's gonna have some complicated therapy in prison about his relationship with Alex
Mm-hmm, because he gets fired from it for wars because of Pizzagate star or he leaves
He tries to start his own news operation Alex kind of is associated with but it's like I don't know keep it an arm's distance
Yeah, the proud boys show up. He decides I'm jumping in both feet
Why not he rises through the ranks of the proud boys becomes like
Really high up in the proud boys makes a name for himself in the in the aggressive dangerous right-wing community
And then storms the capital and goes to prison. Wow. It's so crazy that when it becomes convenient, they just cut loose
Yeah, isn't it? So weird. They don't have that loyalty or anything like that
Who would have guessed man who could have seen that coming? We've seen it happen with all of these groups as Alex
So someone who is loyal to a fault someone who is just just
You know true true as the day is long. I don't know why not Roger Stone is back. Okay, and
He kind of wants to imply that everybody who's into history is a secret leftist
Okay, they want to erase this record in one word impeachment Nixon impeachment Trump
Impeachment it's not right and it's not fair and we know that history is written by the left the historians are
leftists some of some authors like Rick Perlstein pose as
Historians they're not historians. They're
Propagandists, we can't let this happen. You see I think this last final battle for the president is crucial for his legacy
There is this battle of a historical
Pushing yeah that you see that is that is a really it's an interesting thing
That seems to be at least subtly behind a lot of these these right-wing figures
That I find this very interesting the way like sort of Alex believes in lore
As being real. Yeah, and just completely false versions of history
Roger is attacking historians as the left. Yeah. Yeah. I mean the problem is history
Is left-leaning?
The more you read about history the more you're like, oh those fascists are bad and the more you see the fascists
You're like, oh in the modern times the people who are doing the fascism are
Roger Stone and his ilk so it kind of does seem like it's in their interest to portray all of history as
evil, yeah, I mean history is unkind to those who want to cling to
Biases and bigotries of the past totally and I mean pretty clear anyway
Alex is wants to talk to Roger about the impeachment trial. Yeah, the impeachment trial is foremost in his mind and
He really wants this fucking thing to be a circus. Mm-hmm
He really wants Trump to go I don't want it to be you're out of order. I want it to be a circus, too
I don't I I wonder what would be the most sort of politically useful thing
For the sort of policies that we would like sure sure
Would it be more effective for it just to be sort of quiet and go through like the process or would it be effective?
I think if it's a circus, it's probably more effective in splintering the the GOP. Yeah
Yeah, I think that it would lead to
such a
Embarrassing showcase that you know people in the Senate would have much more
baggage
For not voting to convict. Oh, yeah, absolutely
And I think that maybe that would be politically useful, but I'm not positive
It would also be a pretty embarrassing thing just to watch. I mean for the concept of justice
which if you don't have a kind of shared element of
Justice a society can't function. Mm-hmm
So the idea of holding like a two-day little like hey Trump, you're evil
5545 you're acquitted is so offensive to the concept of justice that it's like why?
Why believe that any punishment will ever come to these evil fries?
I'm I'm I'm not even trying to predict or talk about like conviction or acquittal
I'm talking about the strategy of Trump. No totally there. That's what I'm saying about a two-day trial or something like that
that's so offensive to me of like we have
Evidence that is
Controvertible, I guess I guess what you're saying makes sense like a two-day trial with an acquittal or whatever is kind of
Yeah, it's whereas a week two-week trial where Trump is going crazy
Yeah screaming nonsense conspiracy theories and then an acquittal could be toxic to the people who voted for acquittal
Here's the biggest reason. Here's the biggest reason. I don't know how long Trump can be quiet for his lawyers true
So the shorter lawyers wow, he's got two and Barnes is coming baby. I think they all quit
Well, I think the five quit and now he got to like yesterday or something like that, but probably great lawyer. Yeah
Yeah, oh, yeah
God was who but like the longer it goes on the more likely Trump is to be like
I've got something to say and once we get there then the fireworks start happening left and right it is gonna be Barnes, isn't it?
It's totally gonna be Barnes. I feel it in my bones. Yeah, I can't wait to say good job Barnes or good work
It's gonna be so good and I think Trump needs to go in there swinging and saying I'm the guy that's pro law and order
I'm the guy that was you know, trying to expose this election fraud
I'm the he can use that as a place to put on the evidence of election fraud as well
They're not gonna be able to tell him to shut up. This would be spectacular
This would be the ultimate reality TV show and according to many scholars
He could get up to two months of the time to put on his evidence properly hell
Yeah, doesn't agree up front to just let a few lawyers represent him if he does that they're gonna hang him out to dry
What do you think? I think that they can tell him to shut up. Yes, they can
Like if someone is being completely uncooperative
I'm just being like out of order. You could try him in absentia. No, haven't you seen a
Like haven't you ever been to a court, you know
One of those quick traffic courts where they go all day
You're allowed to just scream for as long as you want up to two months and they can't do anything to this thing
It's contempt of course. Nope, not at all
Especially not in the Senate. It's a crucial loophole that we refuse to close never but if you just misbehave in court
Yep, you get off you wait him out. Yeah
Yeah, some people say tubal cane. Some people just wait him out. Yeah, some people go
Yeah, I
Don't think this is a good idea
I do. I think this is dumb in terms of the goals that Alex has I think it's in the real world
It would probably be unproductive and I think that there's another idea that's going around that also would be
Unproductive to the goals that Alex has although because I'm against those goals. I think that maybe they should do it
Yeah, I'm not entirely sure. I'm egging you on I have bad. I haven't fully
thought about or considered the
Logistics or the possibilities of this idea of the Patriot Party right a Trump party splitting
But just from sort of a basic view. I think what you would end up doing is completely
Fracturing the right-wing vote. Yeah, the conservative vote would not be unified and Democrats would probably run
Roughshod have a great almost every election. They might even get DC into statehood
It seems like that would be a really bad decision in terms of the right
Electorally if they had a two-month trial for Trump to present his evidence, uh-huh. They would have to talk real slow. I
Think Rudy could handle it
But the
Roger is against this idea of the the Patriot Party, which I think is probably good political instincts on his part
I think I think that there's a lot of dangers in terms of like were that party to get rolling and have
any kind of
Actual foothold in power. Yeah, I think you could end up with a pretty
Terrifying Overton window kind of situation, but in terms of fracturing electoral power on the right
I think that there's I think it would be dangerous for them. Yeah, and and Roger realizes that
Soros and the globalists don't fund third parties because they don't work
They might be a one-issue, you know deal to stop fracking or this or that
So they'll fund it just to give it legitimacy to shut off our energy supplies like the Green Party
But when you pull back from this, it's taking over parties you want to do
It's Soros and the globalists have taken over the Democrats that the communist Chinese are taking them over
They're putting in their DA's they're putting in their attorney generals. It's a nightmare
We need as American people to control at least one party. We almost got there with Trump. I agree
That's why they fear him so much. He wanted a landslide. They're absolutely right. We do not need this third party
That is a nuclear option down the road, you know just for him to run for president or something if he had to
But he's not gonna be barred from that. He's gonna defeat this trial in the Senate and I really think that
He should run for governor or senator or maybe he should run against Rubio
I mean, I really think we need to get President Trump back in back in DC
That is what we need to be the real leader
I don't fucking understand why you think he has any interest in running against Marco Rubio
I mean maybe for the the campaign he'd have fun with that. Sure. She doesn't want to be in the fucking Senate. Good. God. No
Imagine imagine. Oh god, that'd be terrible. Yeah, what a nightmare that be
He doesn't want to do like that would be so much work. Mm-hmm. It's not all about Trump. No, no
You have to cooperate. There's a there's a minority whip who tells you what to do
Yeah, you're on the phone all the time trying to get donations and shit. Imagine that. Yeah. Oh
Can you imagine what kind of bills he would write?
Cran yeah
brutal absolutely brutal
bill to
Provide senators in Florida with free fast food. No, and it's so right. It's so right to be like no
No, we need to maintain the two-party system because as long as both parties are awful
they can keep passing the ball back and forth, you know, so that means that they can still be owned by
Billionaires if any party governed effectively the other party would be destroyed, you know
Like the Democrats already are like, whoa
Well, I know we promised 2000 but let's do 1400 and you're like guys
Really? Are we doing this? Mm-hmm. Okay, we'll see the Republicans in two years. Thanks, buddy. Good work. Good work you morons
Yeah
Stupid it's a bummer. Yep, but Trump will not be a senator. Absolutely not. Why would he run against DeSantis?
If he runs for governor, there's no way the state remains in the Union the end if Trump is the governor of Florida
He is the president of the United Florida moving Mar-a-Lago to Texas. Yeah, exactly there. We will take our stand
I'm moving to the Alamo, Texas. Yeah, that's not the Alamo shit too close to the border
so Roger is
Weird because he doesn't want a third party like this Patriot Party is a bad idea
But at the same time don't give any fucking money to the RNC. No, fuck them evil. Trump should be president of the world
Look, I would not donate a penny to the Republican National Committee and I would urge those out there in the info Wars audience to
Follow in suit there. There is no chance that money is being spent effectively. Mm-hmm. Okay
amazing points, but please go back to
What ruddy said about Trump could be really the president of the world?
For nationalism for patriotism for populism for better trade deals. How would you be the president of the world for nationalism?
Very weird very very weird
As president of the world, no one can move. I think it's probably a politically
I don't know
counterproductive
To say hey, we shouldn't have a third party. We got to take over the Republican Party
But also don't give the Republican Party any money. No. No, let's make sure we don't support them
But also we had to take them over. Yeah, we all got to give money to the right scam. Not the wrong way man
Exactly. Yeah, so
Alex it gets mad here. He's Roger takes off because he's he's just at his piece and
Alex gets mad about Nancy Pelosi because she is not thrilled with there being members of the house who's murderers
Seem to have hostile intentions
It's murdering attentions
Marjorie Greene
Certainly has said some things that would make me feel unsafe in a work environment. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
She's not Nancy Pelosi is not happy about that and good for her because I don't think she should have to put up with that
Right, right. Then you have the the Lauren Boebert's of the world also not making you feel super safe
And so she in an interview said that the enemy is inside. Yeah
You know Alex is not thrilled about that wrong not thrilled wrong Alex is pretty mad about that
That's a pretty astounding clip of Pelosi saying that the they need more security because of Republican Congress people
Hey lady
It was your supporter went and shot Scalise and tried to kill 18 others you lying sack of garbage
Burning hell Pelosi and by that I mean we're not judgment on you. I think God's sending you to hell
That's what I mean by that
okay, the thing that I think is interesting about that clip is it's one of a number of times Alex has to
over-clarify stuff
All right, so
Everybody is getting caught for doing the thing. I told them to do I better be real safe
I better better be real safe Nancy Pelosi. You're gonna burn it out and by that I mean
I believe that God has it out for you and once you die your soul is gonna have trouble and in this circumstance
I'm gonna point you to Romans 12 16 because nobody gets mad at the Bible
Yeah, so Owen Schroyer has been sitting alongside
He's theoretically hosting the show and Alex is co-hosting
But Alex is just doing the everything sure sure and Owen has some ideas that he wants to introduce to the proceedings about how unpopular
Joe Biden is mm-hmm. He has some primary evidence that I think is stupid
But you know getting back to the Biden issue here Alex. I was looking at this today
And I just have one little printout here. It doesn't really work for the printout, but I was looking at
Google search trends and if the crew wants to do this they can do this I was looking at Google search trends
Biden as a Google search trend was almost
Non-existent in the year 2020 almost non-existent Trump on the Google search trend is like number one
Oh, but Biden had the most votes ever and then the other thing I noticed Alex
two of the top three word associations with Biden on a search trend is this what we're doing pedophilia and
dementia
So the world under why to this guy is and and guys by the way lay that paper back down
I know they consume in more lay it back down where you had it
They should just do this because it doesn't really look good on the printout the
The things I don't care that you but I mean still zoom in on it
No, they can do it. They can zoom in that camera's got like five times more zoom
Just zoom in on that guys because this is huge. Yeah, absolutely. Oh, this is huge huge
Yeah, Google Trends Trump put out an online poll where he
98% of people said they want him to be president. I don't understand how Biden won. Yeah, it's impossible. It's impossible
98% of Americans want Trump to be president. That's the only polls that I listen to this
Yeah, this is this is an instance of taking something that on its on the surface
Appears to be making an argument that Trump is far more popular than Biden
Yeah, but also has no relevance not to the larger issue that they're talking about. Nope. This is very dumb
Yeah, so we got some guests coming up after Roger. Yeah, we got a couple of big big hitters
But I want to let listeners also know Stuart Rhodes founder row keepers will be joining us the last 30 minutes the next hour
We have another one of the boogaloo leaders
Joining us to talk about what really happened at the Capitol
You know, I have to say that the boogaloo guy we had on your state
It's some cheap shot saying, you know that I might be in the CIA or a fed, but I get from his perspective
I'm saying that to him, but only because you can't swing a stick in any of these groups and not hit a Fed
I mean look at the Enrique Tarrio thing coming out. He's been a federal informant for many many years
Is he a bad guy? No, no, I can what but and that just goes with the territory ladies and gentlemen
What it's the same thing with the boogaloo is the same thing with any of this Wow, that's weird
he is if he is a fat informant a
Literal demon servant. Uh-huh. I like that guy. Hey, he's a good guy
Look, I don't I don't know what Tarrio was up to like. I don't know now me
I haven't I still haven't seen concrete evidence that he was informing on the Proud Boys still don't care either
I'm Alex's perspective. He has to think that he was and that's the way that Alex is presenting this
Yeah, it makes no sense to be like, yeah, this guy was a snitch
He was infiltrating groups in order to make them look bad. Maybe even was instrumental in planning false flags
Demon servant good, dude
That makes no sense no also is
Jarring to hear Alex be like look I talked to this boogaloo guy
He said I was a fucking inside dude, like I was false controlled opposition. You know what? Hey, I understand
I'm saying the same thing about him and hey, maybe he's cool. Yeah, you guys are doing great work together
You guys are doing great work together. What man? That's some that's some
Softened really fast. Yeah on this whole thing
Yeah, the boogaloo boys were supposed to be his ticket out of this and now he's like like these guys. Oh
We're all yeah
we're all in trouble and I think one of the issues is sort of distorted views of what unity is possible or is
Pursuable right and Owen Schroyer seems to be really on the unity kick right now
That seems to be his big project
Mm-hmm. He's talking about like reaching out to Black Lives Matter and and like and folks on the left so certain
I saw I heard him screaming fuck BLM. Oh, yeah, and antifa
I'm just positive that there was a flag involved. They burned it. I think they burned a flag
Oh, yeah, and now they're gonna you want to reach out? Okay good and Alex is kind of like yeah
Shit, I'm supposed to be above partisan politics
That was to be my whole thing. What happened? I mean, I want unity. I don't want to fight with the average Democrat
We need a populist movement that is for common sense in this country all team
We're bringing that up because we get so part of described them especially under the last few years with Trump that that's something that actually
Energize the worst elements of the Soros left to kind of take over the populist
Liberals and who are who are on average not bad people and I think could be reached out to what do you think?
I think that the reality of what Alex is talking about is I miss when
Some people on the left were tricked by my opposition to the Iraq war
I miss back when I could yell about George Bush and I could be deemed not an
Incredibly insane extreme right-wing zealot. Yeah, there was a time there where I wasn't in the pocket of somebody whose mood
I was looking I miss having the facade of
Rationality because I was to the right of George W Bush. Yep
Yeah, this is this is silly yeah, I will I will accept it a
unity from these people when I they apologize publicly and make amends for it and
Correct their mistakes. Yeah, then we can be unified again until then go fuck yourselves. So speaking of unity
Owen
Believes that he sees opportunity in the GameStop and Robin Hood
situation in order to bring people into the fold this disillusionment right with the perceived fairness of
the stock market is something that he believes that they can use to bring people into the ranks of the
Info wars universe and and I believe that that is false unity
I believe that's you know
The the kind of thing that you see constantly with anything that galvanizes people particularly online
You'll see an attempt at infiltration of it by the right-wing
Demagogue totally and I can see a bit of Owen
Seeing an opportunity there. Although I don't think
That it's gonna be effective and I also don't think it's gonna be something that's gonna be even discussed on info whores
In within a week. Yeah, I would agree with so I don't care to talk about it too much
because it's not really a big issue and it also is something that I
Just see it as being like this might be a wedge. This might be something we can use and oh and just doesn't have the chops
So we get to the the next book boogaloo boy. Mm-hmm who comes in he's guy named Magnus Panvidya
He's a guy fine. Yeah
he is the boogaloo boy who was recently interviewed on the Jimmy Dore show and it seems to be somebody who's making the
Rounds a bit in terms of like being someone who people will interview sure and I can understand
Why because he doesn't sound crazy
which is
I mean a plus
For a public face
If I was going to be the public face of a group whose main goal was a second Civil War
Mm-hmm. It would be wise to be like, hey, come on. I'm a good dude. I'm smart. I'm
Conversational you guys can I like all sorts of people. Yeah, I seem rational as shit. Yeah, and
He has a different approach
Sort of a good cop bad cop kind of thing with Mike Dunn where Mike Dunn when he was on the day before
Was kind of being a brusque Alex. You're kind of a shitbag. Yeah
Next hey, Alex, we're the ones who are doing the shit that you pretend you do
Yeah, now that Alex has taken that lashing and also now has softened so much
Yeah, now comes the balm the sound sure to make those those wounds feel better
Magnus give us your view on what the boogaloo's really are and what you guys just did and what just unfolded
activate the boogaloo's
Uh-huh. Yeah, we're just kind of a libertarian
Anarchist coalition kind of a militia more of a movement
We started off in the lockdowns
Then we expanded throughout the whole George George Floyd and all the BLM events and look
You just continue to be operating on the ground is kind of a more
Unifying not right or left armed movement. Fuck you
Well, I kind of like that actually I want to get the left involved in liberals deprogramming and into owning guns of self-defense
This isn't the way
no, no, no, I
Think that you already see a contradiction between and what Mike Dunn was saying and what Magnus is saying
He's saying we got started in the lockdown. Yeah, this is this grew out of
Absolutely with jokes about a second Civil War
I am NOT going to be told lies about your own history by a fucking accountant. That's what this dude sounds like
He sounds like a fucking accountant Dan
You're just saying that cuz the release the boogaloo is a real dorky joke to start off
Yeah
So Alex, you know
He's really making
Detente here sure and in a lot of ways he talks about he's talking about how like I had this bad feeling about Mike Dunn
But I was wrong
Well, I had Mike on yesterday and I got to say I thought he was probably a fed or some every law center
I didn't approve of that
I just a lot of these groups get led by those but I I didn't get that sense actually having him on I got the
sense he really believes in what he's doing and maybe I've been I'm not saying boogaloo's are perfect as any big organization can get
Infiltrated but that maybe you maybe you guys overall do have a good goal. My concern is are you guys acceleration is do you want a
revolution I
Mean we we have you not only that a revolution is inevitable. But yes, we want a revolution
It just depends on what form that takes we want it to be the most peaceful
People's revolution is humanly possible, but we're also not ignorant to the idea that the establishment's gonna go after that
They're gonna try to destroy it and they'll probably go on the offensive against us. So I just think that he's steamrolling Alex
Alex is just letting this guy
have a have a very friendly platform to
present this exactly how he wants to and it's it is
unacceptable
dissembling to be like we want a peaceful revolution but but no
No
That sentence ends with a period now if you want to continue that thought and say we want a peaceful revolution
Period we believe that there is going to be resistance to that. We will fight that
Peacefully, yeah, then that's cool. Yeah, there's there's two kinds of
approaches that I see being
Possible when you have something like this group that is really interested in
Gun concerns and what have you second amendment stuff? Yeah, you could have somebody who's like, okay
I disagree with open carry restrictions. So we're gonna get people together and we're gonna have an open carry March right, right
There's two things that can do two approaches
you can take one is that we expect we're gonna get arrested and then that arrest we will accept and we will use that to
try and
Change laws right change public opinion by virtue of our arrest seeming unfair to most people
Or you could take the approach of we're gonna do this and we're gonna threaten people with these cut
That would be the way to do it. And if people try and arrest us someone might get shot
Yeah, like I think the first
Might be productive right? The first one is something that even if I disagree with your position on the open carry laws
I don't see a problem with someone doing a demonstration and a protest like that. Yeah when it comes to like
Someone might get shot. That's that's when we're we're in dangerous territory. I mean, you know like
They're they're bullshit about unity and all that stuff
I I think immediately to of Fred Hampton like Fred Hampton
Was a person who went into these Second Amendment groups these fucking militia groups and was like hey
This is a class struggle. This is about us and convinced them and they joined him
Mm-hmm, and then they acted peacefully and that's why Fred Hampton was murdered
Because it was them moving to the left. Mm-hmm. If it's the other way around
Yeah, we're in trouble there. So Magnus believes and expresses that
Hey, the man is trying to get everyone to fight with each other, right?
Sure. Sure
Alex is like, yeah, okay, cool. Cool. Cool. Cool
But antifa they hate the cops, right? What about you guys? Okay
He does not get the answer. He wants I imagine so the
Establishment right now is trying to get everyone to fight and kill each other instead of coming together against them
They want all of these groups. They want antifa. They want three percenters
They want all of these groups to think the other side is the most evil thing in the world and it's you know
Secretly attempting to destroy them so they can laugh all the way to the bank while we fight and kill each other
Huh, and that's what we don't want. Well, there's no doubt that's going on
But I mean by you if it says the local police of the enemy. I mean, do you think that?
At this point. I find it hard to believe that the local police aren't the enemy like when when you look at gun confiscation
A lot of local police are just going along with that and not saying anything when you look at
Lockdowns when you look at arresting people over pot when you look at
Busting protests whether they be right-wing or left-wing protests very aggressively and laughing about it
I've you know, obviously I'm not saying that officer friendly in a small town
That's never done anything wrong is some horrible individual
But when you look at the institution of policing across the entire country, they've forsaken liberty in all directions
See what's interesting here is that Magnus is coming in with a complex thought
Yeah
That Alex can't really deal with well
He started with people are trying to divide the left and right and saying both sides are the most evil people on the planet
So they can never communicate with each other and while they're doing that they're laughing all the way to the bank
Right that reminds you of anyone did one thick-necked individual comes to mind
The exact person that he's talking to has spent all of his time talking about how antifa are
Meth-head demon spawn. Yeah, whatever. Yeah, the leaving that aside like yeah, I
Don't agree and I'm not gonna side with
Magnus but issues with
Policing are issues with police
absolutely, and Alex can try and deny that kind of stuff as much as he wants but you know
Magnus has a has a more interesting perspective on on
The police then Alex I I would counsel very hard to remember this motherfucker is lying
Yeah, he is. He's he's saying he's making well points. He's making good points
Maybe in the service of lies, maybe not lying because I do believe that he does have problems with police sure
It's disingenuous. Yeah, that's more I think
Lying about what his his his intentions. Yeah. Yeah. No, this is this is absolutely a fucking a
Bullshit way of being like see I listen to the problems on the left and we're gonna pay attention to them when they join us
we're gonna team up and solve those problems and
I don't know Dan. Have we seen what happens when?
Let's say right-wing grifters find something no longer useful a toss-it-aside
Yeah, I would suggest that if you were thinking about
Them having good points maybe remember what they do whenever you're no longer useful
Yeah
And I mean not for nothing in the wake of this dude being on Jimmy doors show
Some people did look through his Twitter and found him supporting Kyle Rittenhouse. Sure
It's like I don't know man. No, I don't know. Nah, it's unity. Yeah, we're all about unity
I don't know about this
So for Alex though, the question comes back to pretty constantly as it did with Mike. Who are you targeting?
I want to ask you about in a revolution and what your goals would be of that revolution or that new declaration of independence
And my concern is I never see people protesting big tech or I mean Apple runs
No factories in China, and I'm not saying Apple
I don't want that but but but I mean if Uyghurs bombed Apple, they would have a real argument Apple runs the main slave camps
So if Uyghurs attacked Apple, they would have a legitimate argument at the UN Hague that we're under attack
We were attacking who's attacking us. I'm not saying do that. I'm just saying all the time
I heard the local police that sounds like a communist takeover of local government. I'm not saying you're doing that
That's what I'm concerned about. Stay right there, sir. We'll come right back to you
No time for him to respond to that diatribe. Nope
and again, it just comes down to Alex like his his his two issues seem to be like
This isn't being directed by me and you're not targeting the people that I want you to target. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, my biggest issue
Is why isn't everybody doing what I say? Yeah, they can be as
Explicitly anti globalist like Mike Dunn was very clearly like I am against these global
global ists
And it doesn't matter because Alex doesn't see them blowing up
My stuff yeah, can you imagine that's what Trump in the Senate would be like, he's like why isn't everybody doing what I want to do
Mm-hmm. That's the whole thing. What's a quorum? I am a narcissist. I can't spell quorum
Yeah, so again announced quorum quokka. Yeah, Alex
You know, he his problem seems to be that like they have a revolution in mind
Revolution is probably good. You should do it. Yeah, but it's not my
Revolution and kind of as a problem. Yeah, and then he makes an insane analogy. We had
Mr. Dunn on yesterday and I really thought about it after the interview. I thought I don't think that guy's a fed
I think he's really pissed off about what's happening in the world and trying to unify everybody
around
One message and if they can successfully do that, that'd be great. I'm just really concerned about
The goals of a revolution and and and who leads it. I mean, it'd be great if we had a bunch of state governors
And respected generals and respected lawyers and the Confederacy you're literally describing the Confederacy formed a new Declaration of Independence
That's 100% the Confederacy over. It's what are we doing over? It's illegitimate the great resets illegal
And so we you know reform our new Union and we have that right. I just see what happened at the Capitol
Which the Boogaloo's bragged about being part of people can try to walk that back whatever it was idiocy
I wouldn't call it an assault. I would call it a a pissing contest. I would call it me like a
Yeah, it was a little bit more intense than kind of that's what you call it
Other than them killing four citizens a cop have an heart attack Wow more intense
Than what you see in movies like Animal House
I mean, you know Animal House pranks are now like terrorism walking off of lecterns one cop got squashed in the door
There was some nasty to some fights. It was wrong, but not a new Pearl Harbor. So so so Magnus see
What you don't understand Jordan your mouth is open as if in surprise
But what you don't understand is that the storming of the Capitol was basically like, you know
How like in an old TV show, you know, like a panty raid sure. It's
Prank, so so what Alex also is quite inappropriate in hindsight
Is that the Patriots jumped the general Lee over the Capitol building? Mm-hmm. That's what we're describing here. Yeah
Yeah, I mean basically it's like teepeeing
Yeah, a lot of cops die when teepeeing. Yeah, basically
The the right-winger is just egged
Hey, what are you gonna do? We were throwing a little prank. Come on
Basically, they waited until the Capitol passed out and then they put the capital's hand in some warm water Wow Wow
Just while they waited until the capital passed out and then they put shaving cream on its hand and then tickled the capital with a
Feather I just don't know what to do when someone would try and say that
Like I just there's what just I want to get a white glove and challenge him to a duel
I don't know what to do about that. Yeah, I would say that if this is just the like slightly above frat pranks
Why are you talking about it so much? Oh, that's a good point
Also, I don't remember
Spending days and days trying to scapegoat a frat prank
Anyway, Alex has seen the interview with Jimmy Dore that this guy did and he loves it
And even before I even went on Jimmy Dore the only podcast I could even get on was a podcast called Liberty Lockdown
Which was a small decentralized podcast that they didn't have the ability to censor. Yeah, let's talk about that
That was a great interview you did with Jimmy Dore
yeah, and I'm so happy for him to have me come on because what has given me the ability to do is to break through all
the mainstream media lies about us because there's
extremist experts and journalists that have covered us all year long and have buck or a heels of video and text evidence showing what
our movements about and it doesn't line up with what the mainstream media has all and they'll they'll directly quote these
Extremist experts that work for DC and quote them on certain parts, but when those same extremist experts say no, we're not white supremacists
Yes, we work with BLM
They'll take those parts of their report and hide it and run us all rough shot across the media and I feel the same
Thing's been done to Antifa. I still feel the same thing's been done to three percenters
I feel like the same thing's been done to BLM. Fuck you. Yeah
Fuck you. Yeah
Now if the criticism is that the mainstream media lacks some sort of nuance in reporting on groups
Particularly like the bugs. Mmm. Yeah, sure fine. Great
I
Don't know if you've broken through that by being on Jimmy doors. I would say no. No, I would argue
No, but then you know, this is gonna wind up with this dumbass being all over the place
I imagine a bunch of easily taken advantage of morons like Jimmy door. Yeah, and maybe maybe the
Sort of high point of it will be him going on Tucker. Yeah, yeah
But I don't I don't know if I don't know if he has the escape trajectory to get out of that bubble very much
But that is interesting. I mean like it does it does indicate like the kind of places that he has access to
Includes infowars. Yeah, Jimmy door. Yeah
Yeah, that should that should put pause in a lot of people's minds. It's not a good sign. No, no
Also, hey, buddy
I'm gonna go out on a limb and say that most white supremacists would deny it
Yeah, and the the issue comes down to the the group is care
the character of the group itself is not white supremacist and a lot of I mean
Obviously there probably are a fair number of white supremacists who fall under the boogaloo
Oh, yeah category and that is fair enough
But the group itself is not white nationalist white
Supremacist in character right and that is something that's the nuance that is kind of difficult for people who aren't
Engaged in these things to really to really
Deliney and and that's where clunky conversations come in and you say like the white supremacist boogaloo group and then you
kind of look
Like you don't know what you're talking about
It's difficult even for me to fully understand where exactly a lot of the lines are
so Alex tries to have this conversation that is
far nicer than the one with Mike and
It's weird because the territory that Magnus is getting into should be really hostile stuff for Alex
Mm-hmm, like Magnus is
Defending antifa sure to Alex Jones indeed, and that's weird. This is a huge problem
Well, you believe in free speech antifa doesn't it's funded by Soros on record
I mean
That's the thing is like yeah that there might be infiltrated parts of it but you but that's the same for everything
That's something you talked about and like when I go back to like your early works about the WTO riots and how the police
Infiltrated the WTO riots to cause chaos and false flag
some of those same people that were at those WTO riots in Seattle are the same people that I talked to today that are part of
Antifa and they get really disillusioned when they hear things about like all of antifa's Soros funded a lot of them talk
Just like you they hate the Fed. They hate global, you know corporations
They stand for free speech
But Fox News or something will put the camera on one guy that has a stupid opinion and be like
Oh, they speak for all of antifa when it's when it's a global
I will invite any of those antiphon that'll actually talk to us. I'd love to actually hear that if that exists
This is a problem for Alex because he has contracts
No one is supposed to remember the things I say
Well, that's a problem
But also if Alex actually believed that the quote-unquote Soros
Antifa contracts the Harrison Smith found on 4chan were real right this argument should not be compelling to him
Yeah, this argument should be like no do you understand?
I have contracts between Alexander Soros
Excuse George Soros and their foundations and antifa in order to try and start martial law in America
You sir, don't know you're being tricked by the people on the ground who are who are old-time commies
Yeah
That's that's how you should be behaving
He shouldn't be he shouldn't be persuadable by stuff like this if anything that he believes means anything
Listen up Magnus Ver Magnusson or whatever your name is. Let me tell you this right now
Everyone in antifa had to sign a contract. I've got the document for you right here
Go ahead and read through that. Oh, no, I'm an idiot aren't I? Oh, no that guy remembered something
I said, I think that Alex probably doesn't bring that stuff up because Magnus would laugh in his face
I don't think that it would be embarrassing. That's why Alex's narratives fall apart
Yeah, like because they're built on nothing. Yeah, Alex himself doesn't believe them and
When presented with somebody who probably isn't gonna play along. This is what I keep coming into. Is that like Alex?
should not
Engage with zealots. Yeah, he's a pretend zealot
Yes, and he's going to get found out when you go up against a real one
Yeah
The end and that's why he can't bring out his real
Narratives that uses all the time on his show because they'd be punctured so fast
He's at an instant disadvantage and somehow he still believes when he has these people on that. He's like nah, I got him
I can take care of it. Well stupid
so anyway, the great reset is the problem or something sure there needs to be a revolution probably and Magnus wants Alex to
Work with Antifa, of course
We should be able to unify everybody against the great reset is literally a corporate takeover to consolidate power under the name of environmentalism
To literally bankrupt everyone and and have a universal income so they can dictate the terms of our surrender
We have got to get everybody mobilized against the great reset. What is your view Magnus about the great reset? Oh, yeah
And I agree and it's funny enough because I had this conversation with an Antifa member. They agree, too
It's not that they're against the idea of like oh, let's reset the system everywhere
But they are perfectly aware of the people that are pushing that idea of how all these multinational billion-dollar banks and everything
It's not a great. Yeah, I love a reset exactly. We need a reset. We need a reset exactly
I'm gonna hold you over but we need a reset but it's not this reset. This is a horrible reset. Sorry go ahead
there's a difference between a reset that involves rethinking our approach to climate issues rethinking our
approach to what
people need to live
That kind of thing and a reset that involves a civil war. Yeah
Yeah, those are very different and if you talk about them being like, oh well
Hey, these people are interested in a revolution just like us
You're muddying the waters in a way that is incredibly unfair
Yeah
and that is like when you engage in that kind of a disingenuous sleight of hand it leads me to
Suspect that maybe a lot of the stuff that you're saying is not sincere
Yeah, not genuine and that's one of the problems that I run into with Magnus and in this next clip
I think we really get to see this pretty clearly
Actually, I was just on the phone with the woman that was at the WTO riots
And she said she would would be willing to come on and talk to you
So if you want to talk to an Antifa member, you can talk to an Antifa member, please
And definitely like obviously the
Dictionary definition of acceleration nascent ism might be correct
But what everyone is calling us if by if by the criteria that you think everything is
Fundamentally flawed and it will not change without radical change then literally everyone is accelerationist
Joe Biden is an accelerationist AOC is an accelerationist Rand Paul's an accelerationist
Like if you look at the world through that view everyone acknowledges that things are totally
Destroyed across the board when it comes to civil liberties, when it comes to our economics, everything
Exactly. So like a lot of people say like, oh you want a revolution? You're an accelerationist
I'm like everyone wants a revolution right now. Everyone's talking about it. It trends on Twitter constantly. So this is
another
Manipulative sleight of hand. Oh, yeah, the accelerationism that people are talking about when they talk about fringe right-wing groups and militias
And and and that type is an accelerationism towards shooting violence
it's an accelerationism that's rooted in heightening tensions and highly tense situations and
protests that have the potential to spin out of hand and prove to be an inciting event in a
conflict between a
Supposed
Sides of a civil war we see the water boiling and we want to push it over the edge. That's the
accelerationism that he's trying to make the same as
Accelerationism where you have people who are saying climate change is a problem that cannot be ignored any longer. Yep
we need to
elect leaders who are willing to
Explore ideas about regulation. Yes. Okay. It's not the same
Recognizing that a system is flawed in many ways and we're past the point possibly even past the point where we can
totally fix all of the issues sure is not the same as thinking everything is fucked and we should hope for a civil war because
It's gonna happen eventually. So why not do it now? I
That's dishonest
100% I I mean, yeah, I I understand this guy and you're you're 100% right good cop bad cop
Bullshit with these two but God I prefer the asshole from the other day
It's funnier cuz he and also he's just gonna be like, yeah, fuck. Yeah, let's blow it up
You know, like I don't like this lying piece of shit coming at me with his accountant
But I think that Mike was still lying too. Oh, he was still trying to put on a
Shiny or facade Oh 100 to what he actually is believing and promoting
but yeah, this this is
Just intrinsically on like unfair. Yeah. Yeah, like what he's what he's presenting and it's it's intentional
Because he kind of understands that there's a lot of Alex's audience. That's probably poachable
No, and it's hard to it's like bring up AOC and all I think of is
Ted Cruz being like yeah agree and AOC being like hey you tried to murder me go fuck yourself
Well, guess what? I get it
You can bring up how antifa and BLM are also against the Fed or whatever it is you want
But you tried to murder all of us. So go fuck yourself
well, but the and the other problem too is that I do I I do think that there probably are some
accelerationist types on the left sure you can rationalize I'm sure way to that like if you take the issue of like
Climate change you can find eco-fascists. You can find eco-terrorists. Yeah
that's not the mainstream of
And and you know
I would say that probably the boogaloo boys are a little bit outside of the strict mainstream of the right
But they're closer than eco-terrorists are to the mainstream of the left. Yes, I would agree a great deal and and and comparing
You know, I don't know. I don't know if he would do this but
Comparing like I don't know
gun wielding
Accelerationists to protests to Greta Thunberg. I think it's a
Little bit different. Yeah a little bit different. I remember Greta
bringing in her AR to the
UN I remember that didn't she do that when she gave that speech? Yeah, I recall so Magnus wants peaceful
options sure now again
Did you leave a public representative of a group that is entirely based around the fantasy of a second Civil War?
to the point where
This listener pointed this out to me and I knew this but I failed to bring it up on our last episode
You know, even the wearing Hawaiian shirts is about Civil War
It's they had to get around social media bands. And so they had big luau instead of boogaloo. Yep
Like everything is about every day. Yeah, but he wants peaceful options
Okay
And I think that he is one Alex over to an embarrassing extent and we need to keep trying to push peaceful options
We need to keep finding cracks in the armor to be peaceful
But they continue to shut those avenues down one after another another if they keep doing that and that was my warning to them
In that speech if they keep denying people
Redress keep denying people the ability to change things
Then you're going to have civil conflict and it's going to be really bad for them for us and for everyone involved
Come back on cuz I'm really impressed and I'm glad that you actually came on
I'd love to have you on with the antifa lady
We want to have them on we want to actually reach out to these folks as I understand that we can all drink the mainstream
Media kool-aid at a certain point need to actually hear what these groups actually stand for
You're not drinking the mainstream media kool-aid. It's your kool-aid. Yeah
Magnus has got Alex so on the ropes that he's willing to work with antifa. Yeah
Doesn't China run antifa? It's just it's hard not to see that like oh well
You're just nicer to Alex, you know, like he of course he agrees with all of this shit
Theoretically in his mind, you know, but this guy's being nicer than Mike Dunn. So well
Yeah, you guys might have a good point. You're being real deferential and I don't see you as a physical threat
So I think we're good to go who knows like how this would have gone if Magnus was the first one
Yeah, talk to Alex
But I I don't think that this interview can be seen outside of the context of the prior one
Yeah
That went very badly for a hundred percent and it's not like I mean you'd have to be delusional to think that Mike
And Magnus don't know each other. Yeah
The night between these two interviews about Alex get him believe you call them a controlled opposition to his face. What a moron
Okay. Now I'm gonna go on and tell him that antifa is cool
I saw I saw one interview he did with Steve pachannik
All you got to do is say that he's a good dude who's super smart and then don't believe anything
yeah, this is embarrassing and
Alex is just stupid. Yeah, so bad. So speaking of
a dangerous bad
Interviews now Stuart Rhodes of the Oath Keepers comes in great
good work Alex is not into this idea that some of them got arrested and
It's just kind of like I don't buy it
shifting gears Stuart Rhodes is a
Retired constitutional lawyer award-winning researcher you name it. What awards do army veteran patriot founder of Oath Keepers?
It's always about non-violent defensive protection of America
Since we've seen the big news three Oath Keepers
Arrested plotted to kill members of Congress. They do a very good job. They're at the Capitol just running around
Whoa, I don't buy any of that. They all went woo. Woo. Woo. They were like Jeffrey Osborn
Can you whoa, whoa, whoa, you know that song it is it's kind of astonishing
do you remember how quickly don't talk about Jeffrey people hand wave a
literal violent coup yeah, it's
astonishing
Well, it's so important for people like Alex and people on the right to do that because it's so indicative of
The sort of danger that they present to a civil insane society. Someone could say that the enemy is with it
It's very important that the hand waving happens. I just don't understand why people who
Are on the other side don't keep stressing this
In in in a really aggressive way cowardice money
I think I think maybe but I think also just kind of like we all are just exhausted
That's part of just fucking tired this goddamn
Pandemic and then these guys took over the country and all I want to do is go to bed
Yeah, a lot of the time whenever I'm you know, getting an episode ready Alex will say something. I'm like
Oh, yeah, yeah, and then I have to like deal with it
Yeah, and I think that sometimes in life you run into walls like that and you just don't want to deal with it
Mm-hmm
I think that maybe some people don't want to deal with that and hand waving is the good way to do it
I mean when you but for Alex, it's it's an existential threat. Yes 100%
Recognizing that his worldview implies this yeah is is really dangerous. This is the logical conclusion of what you say
Mm-hmm the end this is not some like infiltration. This is not some like oops
We were meaning to do this and then this happened
This is what the end goal was and you did it stupid and you lost. Mm-hmm the end
Unlike Jeffrey Osborne who won I was doing so hard
I'm not so hard. I was just zeroed in on not talking about that in terms of awards
Stuart Rhodes, I don't know what the case is here
He when he was at Yale
He apparently won an award for a paper on enemy combatant status that he wrote
I was able to find the paper and it's long
And I didn't read all of it, but I read some of it and I was like, yeah, this seems like a college paper
yeah, and
It would have been I think 2004
and conveniently
Yale
Their records online go back to 2005. Oh
So weird. Yeah, so I was able to find the recipients list of these winners until 2005
That's not to say that Stewart didn't win it. I just know I'd sure sure sure. Yeah, he could have
It reminds me of Mumford the movie Mumford. Oh
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I fakes being a
Psychologist. Yeah conveniently everybody who could verify his time in college died. So weird. Yeah, so weird
Yeah, we've we've met some people like that in the past
so
Stewart is kind of like hey
We're in the situation that our founding fathers were in and so what we need to do is set up autonomous cities
I think okay, make sure you do what the founders did they came together. They were united the town and county level
for mutual defense and also for
Grassroots politics they separated themselves from an illegitimate regime even before they declared independence, you know
They didn't listen to the real governors
They they smuggled and went around all the edicts of the king and they wore a homespun clothing
Stop buying textiles from England. They
That's like moonshine. All of this is pure Americana. I agree everybody. They're trying to drive us underground
Let's jump in that briar patch. Let's just let's just stop supporting them in any way
Alex is currently in a luxury resort in Utah. He has an iPhone in his pocket
This is this is ridiculous God. Yeah, I hate these people so much
It's it's a bit of a mess, but not as much of a mess as Alex's narrative about January 6th
Yes, this is a huge problem for him because as we've seen he's had to gradually expand the narrative
based on
New people who get arrested. Yeah, we're on our seventh or eighth iteration of this narrative
Yeah, and it's falling the fuck apart. Yeah, and one of the reasons for that is
The people that he's tried to blame the boogaloo boys stood up to him
Oh, and he got embarrassed by two of them in two days
Yeah, he can't throw the oath keepers under the bus. He's too connected to them. Stuart Rhodes is his good buddy
Yep, they're they're tight. He can't do it
The proud boys. He also probably can't throw them under the bus completely. Joe Biggs was like the second-in-command
He used to work at Infowars, Enrique Tarrio. Yeah, they were independent contractors. He never met him
He doesn't get into that kind of stuff that those people get in
Enrique Tarrio had been on the show before he spoke at Alex's CPAC event. You can't prove any of this
Alex could be like I was in bed drunk
He probably could. I don't remember Tarrio. I don't remember anything from that night
It's too difficult for him. And so now he has to kind of like do this. Welcome back ladies and gentlemen. Stuart Rhodes founder of the Oath Keepers is here with us and he just learned about this in the last 12 hours or so. Self-styled militia members in three states begin planning in November for recruits, weapons ahead of capital, and
breach US siege. Well, they sure didn't bring the weapons and they sure didn't do all the things they supposedly were planning to do. But it was the Q phenomenon behind the scenes that oh secretly Trump's giving orders to storm DC and all this and then it would piggyback on us having peaceful demonstrations, calling for a Senate investigation that Ted Cruz was calling for. And then you get to demonize the entire Trump system with this badly coordinated few hundred people that wanted to storm the Capitol.
Hell, you get a few Proud Boys, you get a few Boogaloos, you get a few Oath Keepers in the mix. Are they informants? Were they set up? They break in. Okay, four of them get killed. Cop has a heart attack, dies two days later. This is the new Pearl Harbor.
So the narrative now is just so intensely complicated and shifted so far over the course of the last couple weeks that to imagine somebody continuing to go along with this is just embarrassing. Because Alex at every stage has said he's proven all of these things and then everything shifts.
So now Q, the Q movement is the real villain. And there's a couple of people who I guess Alex will probably, I'm gonna guess soon he's gonna say Sheepdipped. He's gonna call these people Sheepdipped. There's gonna be a couple Sheepdipped people in each of these groups that were there as infiltrated provocateurs.
And so all these groups are actually good, just they had a couple people who were bad apples in those groups who were actually globalist plants. This is too complicated.
I guess he has too many Q followers that listen to his show, but if it were me I would just go hard on Q being controlled by the globalists the whole way. Turn all the Q people into globalists.
No, that's kind of where he's at.
Right, but I mean straight up clean break. Everything is their fault because they're the globalists.
Sure. Well, that's interesting. I think it would be difficult to argue that all the people who believe in Q are aware of a globalist plot that they're a part of.
Sure.
And so he's saying that the Q is globalist intelligence and stuff like that.
Right.
But the people who fell for it and were in on it, or the followers, they're just good researchers who got taken down the wrong path.
I know, but you can lump them in with all the people who use it. You know, most rank and file Democrats aren't evil people. They've just been caught up in this whole thing. You just rationalize the Q.
Alex says that everyone on the left is a devil.
Well, sometimes he does and sometimes he doesn't.
Depends on his mood.
Exactly.
Yeah, I don't know. I strain to keep any kind of...
Through line?
Well, yeah, through line or belief that Alex even has a through line.
Yeah, I would agree with that.
I don't think he has a center on this narrative. It's just someone's to blame and it's not us. It's a fake group that's controlled by the globalists.
That's why I'm saying you go with Q and then you go up against a Boogaloo boy and they're like,
you're stupid and you're like, no, no, no, this is all Q shit, man. You are the stupid ones. You are being controlled by the globalists who run Q.
I don't know. I think Alex realizes that the new generation is not going to put up with his bullshit.
No, that doesn't seem like it.
So, Stuart Rhodes is not like Alex in many ways. He's scarier.
Terrifying.
And he also is not somebody who throws people under the bus.
That's true.
Alex is willing to throw anybody under the bus immediately. When it's convenient, bus.
Yeah, I imagine that military service will give you more loyalty to your comrades in arms than
being a radio host.
Yeah, so one of the people that was arrested, Storm in the Capital, one of the three Oathkeepers,
Stuart Rhodes knows for a fact, is an Oathkeeper. And he won't deny that. And he also spent some
time on this show promoting her crowdfunding.
Yeah, I love that. I love it.
Jessica Watkins does have a GoFundMe set up or not a GoFundMe. It's on rally pay,
but a fundraiser for her. We do encourage people to go and defend the actual Oathkeeper member
who was involved in that. So we always stand behind our people. So there you go.
But again, you didn't coordinate. You weren't part of this.
No, absolutely not.
I had nothing to do with it. Now I am going to try and help fund the defense of somebody
who is there because they're my people. That is a kind of loyalty that is foreign to Infowars.
Completely. So wait, wait, wait. Are you saying that she did a thing that you personally think
was a bad idea, but you're still going to defend her? But if you threw her under the bus, then
maybe you wouldn't have to deal with it at all.
Yeah, you could keep that money.
Yeah, it'd be your money. Don't you want that money?
So we are now in a situation that is exactly the same, 100% the same.
Identical to the founders.
Well, the colonies. In the colonies. We're basically in the colonies.
Okay.
Stuart, what do you expect them to do with Biden? He's deteriorating
extremely quickly. I mean, he looks like an Alzheimer's patient now. I mean,
they definitely cranked him up and he practiced that very short inaugural speech, which was okay.
10 bags of blood.
Other than that, he's like, what am I signing?
Blah, blah, blah. I mean, he is like, what the hell's going on here?
Well, like I was saying, he is a Chinese puppet. You should look at this as DC is now the green
zone of an occupying army from communist China using their puppet. And that's why it's a direct
parallel the founders faced. They were dealing with domestic puppets, the royal governors,
who were doing the bidding of a foreign power that was king in parliament that the people had
no control over and no representation in. And we're in the same exact position.
Exact same position.
Exact same position. Explain to me how they're in the exact same position.
Stuart just did, man.
I disagree strongly.
Sure. Me too. So Stuart is, you know, he's not an accelerationist except he is.
Pretty sure he said we're in the colonies and I'm pretty sure that what that required was a
literal revolution.
Yeah, but before that they had people writing pamphlets and stuff.
Oh, so the Oath Keepers are very similar to Thomas Paine.
One might, one were they to be Stuart Rhodes might say yes.
Stuart, he's trying to have this like, you know, like, hey, it's not time for action or whatever
yet, but he does give a little bit of a contradictory message here and it's upsetting.
That shows their weakness because they can't even trust their own troops because they know
that those troops come from us. And so what they do is try to purge the troops and kick
out anybody who's a real American. They really have a skeleton force of no strong military
in the United States that is controlled by them than to have a powerful military they
can't control when they when they try to give orders to violate our rights. So watch for
that. We're going in territory heading towards a sweet spot where we can't wait too much
longer because then they'll have vetted and kicked out all the patriots out of the military.
Confederates.
They have not gotten there yet, but watch for that process to happen. As you get closer
and closer to that point, you have to do something. That's where we're going.
That's right. Let's talk about, both of you stay there, let's talk about the timeline
of tyranny, what the Globals are going to do next, what we've got to do. I mean, folks,
nobody's happy about this. A country has cancer. Again, they're trying to purge the
military now. We told you that was coming next. And now it's here. We got to take the
last three minutes of Stewart, put that on the front of this interview. That was
where he let it out. Literally, DC is now the commonest Chinese green zone. We'll be
right back.
So you have Stewart saying that there's a sweet spot that is, you know, like where you
have to do something before the military is done purging. Also the military has started
purging.
Well, that puts a clock on it.
It does.
It sure does, doesn't it Dan?
This is the revolution QVC.
We're not into acceleration. What we are saying is that it's going to happen shortly.
Anybody, we got about 45, 50 minutes?
Yeah, that's not good.
Yeah.
So the 28th wraps up and...
Blackjack! Shit.
Nope.
You're so good.
You're so good at this.
29th, Alex is, like I said, on the road.
Yeah.
He's coming back for Utah.
Travel day.
30th, sorry, Alex and Stewart Rhodes are in studio and they're talking about this dumb
documentary, talking about how they got us a seed and shit.
Yeah.
Very stupid.
Now we get to the 31st Sunday episode and Alex is basically describing how we're in
Revelation.
Okay.
But it is said in the book of Revelation that John the Revelator in the Isle of Patmos
marveled at the beast, looking forward through an interdimensional wormhole that God opened
up.
That part wasn't in the Bible.
The Antichrist and the world government, what would be happening in the future.
He marveled at the beast.
World government cannot buy nor sell without a mark on the forehead of the hand.
You must turn over your children to the state.
You must destroy your very genetics.
You must kill the earth.
You must worship Satan or you will not be allowed to live.
You'll not be allowed to have a job.
Well, whether you believe John was the greatest science fiction writer ever 2000 years ago.
He was not.
Or whether you believe he was inspired by God.
It's being manifested.
It is not.
It's being set up right now.
So the old Chinese proverb says, may you live in interesting times.
And we certainly are interesting times.
And then you have the battle of Armageddon with the dragon.
All the rest of it now unfolding.
So get your popcorn out because you got front row seats to the big finale.
Is it 10 years, 100 years out or 60 minutes away?
All I know is it's satanic and it's moving quick.
Wait, so it might be in an hour.
The dragon might be here in an hour.
Okay.
Okay, so this is not fair.
I've got a pitch for you.
Actually, I've got a pitch for the devil or the great beast, if you will.
Hold on, hold on.
Let me, let me get into character.
Okay, there you go.
That was scary.
You surprised me.
She popped out of that portal.
Okay.
So you've got the book of revelations.
You've got this whole like head or the hand on the mark of the beast, right?
But you're the devil and you realize everyone has a phone.
Hmm, so do you get around the entire book of revelations?
If you just never attach it to somebody's hand or forehead, do you just win?
Does he win if everybody has the mark of the beast in their pocket?
Well, I mean, it would certainly seem to indicate that the prophecy was a little bit screwy.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
What about like, um, I don't know.
Like there's so much that, uh, aren't in any of those prophecies.
Like, uh, like, uh, custard.
That's true.
Well, I don't know.
Maybe custard existed back then.
What am I trying to think of?
I have no idea.
I don't know where custard came from at all.
French fries?
They did not have those.
Pizza?
That's true.
They didn't even have France back then.
I don't know what I'm trying to get at.
They were called gall fries back then.
There were, there, there were some, some things that were missing, uh, from the,
in terms of it being a wormhole vision of the present.
Uh, but yeah, I don't know.
I just think it's unfair for Alex to be like, it could be a hundred years, could be an hour.
Get your popcorn out.
You might die before it starts, but you'll have the popcorn ready.
The devil's here and it's happening and it's happening fast.
Or in a hundred years.
And who knows?
So, uh, the big news is, uh, vaccine related.
Yes.
On Sunday.
And it's that, uh, Australia has ended, uh, its COVID development program.
So now here's the big announcement.
A month ago, Australia suspends nationwide, their entire vaccine program, because it's
makes people deathly ill, killed a bunch of people and they came up positive for HIV.
Well, we put that on screen place for TV viewers.
Now, now, ladies and gentlemen, last Tuesday seems like a hundred years ago,
Merck, the largest pharma company in the world says we are ending our vaccine program.
It does not work.
We believe you cannot make a vaccine that works to cure the common cold.
And that's what this is, except it's chimera with even more mutations.
So it's even more impossible.
Alex is a sort of editorializing on what these companies have said.
He's adding a little bit there on his own.
Yeah.
I would say, I would say that wasn't a direct quotation.
The other problem too, is that these are all different vaccines.
There is that.
Like the one in Australia was developed by the university of Queensland and a biotech
firm called CSL and the ones that Merck are different, the ones they were working on.
And those are also different than the Pfizer and the Moderna ones.
Nah, they're all fake.
It's all fake vaccines.
Alex is treating them like they're all the same thing.
They're all the same thing.
It's a syringe with some liquid in it, Dan.
It's the same shit.
It's very weird.
Yeah.
It's a weird perspective.
It's kind of like he doesn't understand anything about them.
Yeah.
So I actually lied to you.
That's not the news.
That's the preface for the news.
The big news has to do with Emmanuel Macron.
Okay.
French president has come out and said some things.
Who came out yesterday, Macron, a top globalist.
But he understands that this is such a crime.
He'll be torn limb from limb.
The riots are gigantic.
All their scientists are coming out saying, this is insane.
The top ones.
As opposed to the other ones?
The discoverer of HIV, who's a French scientist and saying, it's man-made in the lab.
It's a power grab.
I told you months ago, I talked to the head of a major biotech company that has real gene
therapy that cures things like colon cancer.
They also sell pillows.
And he said, you're absolutely right.
It's a giant total takeover.
The vaccine will destroy and sterilize women, and it will kill your immune system or turn
it way off the charts and give you cancer.
But they need to want to come on the show.
Oh, too bad.
Yeah.
For somebody with knowledge that could potentially save billions of people, it seems like he
would want to get that information out there.
Yeah.
I guess he's now responsible for...
I'm pretty sure he's killed us all.
So French President Macron said that the Oxford AstraZeneca vaccine appears to be, quote,
quasi-ineffective in people older than 65, which is a claim that scientists have strongly
rebutted.
What about the top ones, though?
I don't know what that means.
Okay.
Macron did not come out against the vaccine or vaccination, nor is he trying to save himself
from being torn limb from limb.
Also, this is not the same vaccine as the ones put out by Pfizer and Moderna, which
are the ones that are currently available in the United States.
The claims that Alex is making are absurd, and it's super convenient that this big time
specialist with magical medical technology won't come on the show.
But honestly, this is just dumb.
One of the things that's the most dumb about this...
Drum roll, please, Jordan.
Okay.
Good enough.
The AstraZeneca vaccine that Macron is talking about isn't an mRNA vaccine.
Well...
But Alex doesn't know that.
If you were a member of the InfoWars audience, you would think that all these vaccines that
were getting developed were all the same thing, as if a ton of companies were just racing
to finish the same recipe.
But that's not the case.
These are different approaches being taken with varying levels of success and setbacks.
Alex doesn't understand the basics of the topics he's covering, and he doesn't care
to, because his work is not meant to reflect reality.
It's meant to push an agenda.
Yeah.
And this is just really sad, because all his ideas are about mRNA vaccines being different
than vaccines.
And that's why this is particularly evil.
And Macron knows that.
And that's why he's getting rid of this Oxford AstraZeneca vaccine that it turns out isn't
an mRNA vaccine.
But Alex doesn't know that.
Macron claims that the vaccine that they were going to use is an mRNA vaccine.
AstraZeneca is almost ineffective in over 65s.
Alex doesn't know shit.
He doesn't know anything.
He's talking out of his ass.
And so this is how arguments get made.
So Australia, Merck, France does not work.
Does not work.
That's it.
That's the level of shit he's bringing to the table.
That's compelling.
Yeah.
That is compelling.
I remember going to my first year.
I didn't originally start out in literature.
I originally started out in audio production.
And I was there, and I was looking at the board, going through all this stuff.
And I remember my teacher screaming at me, it works!
It works!
Yeah.
Yeah, I think that part of the game that's being played here is like, the audience is
obviously humans.
And they think that if someone is yelling this repeatedly, over and over again, so definitively.
He believes it.
He can't possibly be making this up.
How could you be this confident and make something up at the same time?
People can't do that.
It's not possible, Dan.
It's simply inconceivable.
And unfortunately.
Here we are.
Yeah.
So Alex has some staggering statistics about this vaccine that I would beg him to demonstrate.
Guess who the vaccine's killing?
Not just the famous baseball player.
Hank Aaron.
The vaccine killed him?
Local news every day of 20-year-olds, 50-year-olds, 60-year-olds, 30-year-olds.
Take it and die before they even leave the clinic.
They collapse.
And then have a convulsion and bye-bye an hour later.
Bye-bye, Bluebird.
But it gets even more insane.
I mean, this is absolutely the biggest criminal power grab ever.
They are reporting in hospitals and in nursing homes that up to 5% of the patients are dying
within a week when they take the mRNA shot.
Holy shit.
5% fatality rate?
Alex, you need to demonstrate this.
That's an outrageous clinic.
This is an arrestable offense.
That is a legit, like, there should be a legal...
I mean...
That's insane.
You could.
I mean, you'd need to somehow demonstrate that, like, him saying that people believed
it and it led to harm, but I don't think that that...
Like, I don't know how you'd prove it, but I believe it.
Yeah.
Like, I believe that that causes harm.
Absolutely.
Without question.
5% mortality rate?
That's outrageous.
That's fucked up.
So fucked up.
That's a made up number.
That would be the number one story in history.
Culmination of all of humanity's knowledge about infectious disease results in 5% of
people dying immediately.
Yeah, I don't think that you get to make claims like that willy nilly.
And he is.
Yeah, if you can't yell fire in a crowded theater, you can't tell everybody that they're
gonna die.
Yeah.
So the vaccines are a bio weapon, apparently.
And I would like to stress this important point that I've brought up that I don't think
that Alex knows or cares that these vaccines are all different vaccines and some are not
mRNA vaccines like he thinks.
They're closing in to shut everybody down right now.
We have to expose their behind this.
We have to expose the criminal takeover plan and we have to get world leaders, starting
with governors and starting with senators to come out and point this out and it's game
over.
Well, what do you think Merck knows?
What do you think?
Macron knows?
What do you think the Australians know suspending their vaccine programs because it quote does
not work and hurts people.
Quote because it does work.
Macron.
It does work.
Merck.
Australia.
It's a frickin bio weapon.
The mRNA vaccines are gene therapy and they train your body to attack a protein that's
in the placenta.
All four of the damn things are the same thing.
Well, one of them, at least, that you were bringing up isn't an mRNA vaccine.
Well, there's that problem.
And that whole thing about attacking the placenta is nonsense, but-
There is that.
I just, I don't know.
This is desperate.
Yep.
Anyway, we don't have time for us to all wait.
The inevitable thing that's going to happen, as has always happened, is that Alex says
something, it sounds silly, and then 20 years later, what do you know, Alex is right.
Always comes true.
Always.
We're living in exactly what Alex predicted we would be in 1991.
If there's one thing I've learned from doing this podcast, it's don't ever forget
don't ever doubt Alex.
His shit stands up to scrutiny.
True.
He's right almost all the time.
Even when it contradicts other things he's almost always right about?
Yeah, yeah.
Be very facetious.
Never believe Alex.
He's very dumb and mostly is just talking shit.
Half the time, he doesn't even remember the shit he says.
Doesn't care.
But we don't have time to wait for him to be proven right.
We need to act on the things that he's saying now, and just trust that in 20 years
we'll look back and be like, thank god we listened to Alex.
I just don't trust people who make me want, who say I should do that.
No.
Very, very dangerous types.
Yeah.
We don't have time for people to say 20 years later Alex Jones was right again.
Or a year later.
We gotta get that it's not about who's right.
The enemy has written books and laid out their plans.
Of course I know their plans.
It's so easy to beat them.
It's a complete criminal takeover.
They said in Operation Lockstep, 11 years ago, Rockefeller Foundation, which John Hopkins,
the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation, go read it.
It's online.
We do.
They bring in a planetary police state by disease X, something like a weaponized cold
virus, and that there'd be no way to ever defeat it.
We could teach people to be tracked, controlled, and locked down, and that new variants would
show up all the time so that the lockdown would never end.
It's just making that shit up.
Yep.
So yeah, I don't know.
Disease X actually has adamantium claws as well.
True.
Yeah.
In 20 years, we'll look back and be like, wow, I can't believe that this was okay.
This guy got away with this shit.
That's my prediction.
Yeah.
So if you want to look at what he's saying now and sort of think about like, okay, you
think that you're going to be proven right about everything.
Sure.
Here's the kind of shit he's saying.
This is an exact plan.
They teach in elementary school in Germany, we played the actual training videos, that
when you're seven years old, you should be prepared to marry a Muslim by 14.
You should be dating a Muslim by 10, and that Muslims will be the future of Europe and that
Christianity is bad.
I can show you those newscasts if you like.
I would like to see those newscasts.
I would like to see those.
Don't think you can.
That would be a very funny video to share on the internet.
Where the Germans are teaching elementary school kids, hey, you're behind if you're
not dating a Muslim by fourth grade.
Hey, 11 year old, what are you doing single?
You old maid.
You'll never get married at this rate.
You're in sixth grade.
You should just get some cats.
Yeah.
And I see that as somebody who has a cat and I love my cat and there's nothing wrong with
having cats.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is the kind of shit that Alex says, horribly bigoted nonsense.
Anyway, the globalists, as we know, 10 years behind.
Yes, always.
It might just be a few years behind now.
What about plan B?
Plan B, Alex never said that stuff.
Oh, okay.
Didn't happen.
Okay.
They're behind.
Listen to this.
I have a lot of thoughts on the other side of this.
All right.
And here's the deal.
They were supposed to have the whole internet shut down with independent media like us before
they did this.
They weren't planning to launch this for a couple of years.
They launched this early because they're behind schedules.
They thought they'd catch up by launching early.
What?
Some future plans.
But all these different globalists know that everyone hates them now.
I mean, Bill Gates is the most hated man on earth.
Then it's Klaus Schwab.
Then it's Macron.
Then it's the British prime minister that turned out to be a total traitor, Boris Johnson.
Oof.
So he's talking about the releasing of COVID.
Yeah.
Release the COVID.
He actually even says that.
But the idea that he's putting forth is that the globalists were a few years behind.
Right.
And so they had to pick up some time.
Super evil worldwide organization that has orchestrated everything.
Right.
Still a few years behind.
And this is a plan that goes back to the devil.
Yes.
And the beginning of history.
Thousands of years back.
I do appreciate that the devil cannot keep a timetable.
Right.
Just behind a little bit.
Just behind.
He's the devil.
What, is he going to work hard?
I mean, in the song, he's behind.
That's why he got kicked out of heaven.
That's why he went to Georgia.
Too lazy.
They have a real slow pace down there.
He's way behind.
Yeah.
Looking to make a deal.
So this plan that is millennia old and has to do with Trump staying in office or something.
Sure.
They're behind on it.
Yeah.
They're behind on this evil plan.
And so they decide to release COVID a couple of years early.
Sure.
A couple of years early because they got to make up that time.
What's the point of having a plan?
What's the point of a few years?
Honestly, if you have a millennia old plan and you're only a few years off,
6,000 years later or whatever, that's really efficient.
No one's going to remember that.
That's really efficient.
Yeah, a few years in this scale of time is meaningless.
Yeah.
You're at a work project.
It's supposed to last a year and you're three months behind.
People are furious at you.
Right.
Yeah.
So they release COVID a couple of years early to pick up some time.
Sure.
Seems dumb.
Seems stupid.
Hey guys, we're not ready yet for this plan that's going to end the world.
I figure we just go for it.
Yeah, why not?
Yeah, we got a 50-50 shot.
So now the problem is that Alex is still on air.
They were meant to have the internet cracked down by the time that they released this thing.
Right.
So...
So why didn't they?
Yeah!
I didn't get a reason for why they did.
That's my problem.
Why are they behind?
Why didn't they shut down?
Can they not?
So the goal and the motivation is to make up some lost time.
Right.
But the plan that they're engaging in requires that the internet be shut down
to be pulled off successfully.
Correct.
So why would they do this thing to catch up on time
that they don't have one of the essential pieces in place for?
Right.
So dumb.
Okay, so here's our plan.
It can only be stopped if we allow independent media to reveal our plans and stop everything.
Right.
That, by the way, I'm glad we're having this meeting.
Yeah.
That is a crucial first step in terms of us being able to pull off this nefarious plan.
I would argue it's the only step we can take.
If we wanted to go early, it would only be that one.
I'm glad we're all on the same page.
Yes.
Yeah.
So release the COVID.
Alex will destroy our plans.
Yeah.
Certainly.
And we will not only not make up time, we will lose time.
We will be set back.
We'll lose forever.
We'll be set back to devil times.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Our plan will have to go, we're gonna have to do a page one rewrite on this evil plan.
Yeah. John of Patnos is about to marvel at our great beast and then he's just gonna go
back in and the seals are gonna close again.
Cause we forgot to shut down the internet.
Fuck.
Damn it.
You know what?
This is on us.
Yeah.
We can't claim ignorance on this one.
We knew that Alex was gonna fuck us up.
We do like that there are exit interviews for the higher echelons.
Oh shit.
Just like, sorry guys, this one's on me.
Yeah.
This one's my bad.
I'll take credit for it.
So anyway, this is just catalog this in the Alex's plans of the globalists make no sense.
Yeah.
They're real bad at what they do.
They're real bad.
Yeah.
It's almost like he's making it all up.
So, um, one of the things that got everyone really excited over the weekend was there
was a piece in the wall street journal about Alex being involved in the funding of the,
uh,
Stop the steal January 6th.
Yes.
Yeah.
And I read that article and I don't think, uh, that Alex comes off looking that terrible.
I mean, it's just, you know, organizing and fundraising and stuff.
I think Ali Alexander obviously looks like way more of a creep.
That's kind of cause he is.
Yeah.
He's a real dangerous lunatic.
Uh huh.
Um, but
Somebody should give him a radio show and then maybe the profit incentive will keep
him from being too much of an asshole.
Possibly.
Yeah.
Um, Alex responds to this piece on the wall street journal and I think he responds
exactly how I did.
And that is, I said all of that stuff on air.
Yeah.
So there's hundreds of articles, TV shows, all breathlessly.
All breathlessly saying, Oh, January 6th rally funded by top Trump donor helped by
Alex Jones organizers say.
And it's word for word.
What I said, day one, Trump wanted to rally the six.
Nobody would step up with the money.
I stepped up, put 80 something thousand dollars down to try to secure the venues.
Cause you got a park service won't even let you authorize the permit unless you show
you're going to have security and porta potties and all the stuff.
And then a well-known donor heard I was doing it in contact and I was handing them
over to her big Republican fundraisers and to them.
And they tried to turn that into a big conspiracy that I was planning to try to do
all of this so that we could storm the Capitol.
From my perspective, I think Alex is kind of right.
Yeah.
But I think that this reveals a couple of really funny things.
Um, first of all, like just the, the idea that he's like, why are they, I, I said
this and he did.
Yep.
He's constantly said a lot of the stuff that's in that wall street journal article
and the sort of revelations of it are things that you would know if you listen
to info wars.
Yeah.
Now, the thing that I think is really funny is like, let's say January 8th, Alex
has been talking about this and that he had paid for part of this rally.
There's that.
The wall street journal would never report on that cause it's just Alex saying it.
Yeah.
That's fair.
That is fair.
Alex is an unreliable witness.
I can't believe anything this guy says.
Yeah.
Our source is Alex Jones and it's about Alex Jones and I don't believe a word of
it.
Of course.
So there's a story in the wall street journal now cause someone else said it.
I don't know.
I think that would almost be something that Alex should be called as a witness
at Trump's impeachment trial.
He thinks he's going to be.
I mean, he did just say that Trump told him, you know, I didn't have a hard time.
He's putting himself in the center of that impeachment trial too because of this
wall street journal piece.
And, but he's also saying like, they'll never call me as a witness because I
tried to stop the storming.
Oh, I'll call him as a witness.
I'll call you as a witness any day of the week, buddy.
I want to get you in that stand.
Oh, it'd be fun.
Only way to make the impeachment trial more ludicrous would be to invite Alex
Jones.
Alex, can I remind you you're under oath?
I don't even know what that means.
Yeah.
So I think it's really funny that the, like a lot of the underlying information
of this article is stuff that was public prior, but also maybe bullshit.
Not proven, not proven.
Yeah, it's not proven.
And so the second thing that I think is really funny is that the article says,
quote, Mr. Jones personally pledged more than $50,000 in seed money for a planned
January 6th event in exchange for a guaranteed top speaking slot of his
choice according to a funding document outlining a deal between the company,
his company, and an early organizer for the event.
So Alex was doing pay to play.
Of course.
He was putting down money in order to get a speaking slot.
Yep.
That's wild.
That's kind of embarrassing.
That's sad.
In the article, it seems like that's him paying for access.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's clout and there's money and you don't have clout.
And there was no way that Alex was going to get a speaking slot at Trump's
actual event.
No, good God, no.
So, I mean, I figure he did speak the night before.
That might've been what he paid for.
Wow.
Yeah.
Kind of a bummer, but I do think that those two things in the Wall Street
Journal article are pretty funny.
The unreliability of Alex to even speak about his own life and the fact that he
has to pay to get a speaking slot.
It is weird how you can both fall so far and yet at the same time inspire a
literal overthrowing of a country.
It is.
That's an interesting up and down kind of scenario there.
It is interesting.
Yeah.
So we end this episode now, Jordan, with evidence of why Alex should never
have to pay to speak somewhere as long as he's forced to speak over a certain
song.
You can face it.
I understand powerful men.
Most of them never do anything in their lives because they're ashamed of their
power.
They don't want to force their way to the front.
They're humble.
They love their family.
They love their friends.
They love their community.
And so they defer to others.
You can't do that.
You belong in charge.
You belong in charge of your life, your family, your destiny.
And if you don't take control, this evil corrupt system that's laughing at us
will I call on men to start acting like men.
I call on men to follow the basic code God wrote on your soul and to stop
following with fallen men that put out because they're not following God.
They are falling the fallen one.
All right.
You know, I didn't just have all these articles and all these video clips.
Yes, you did.
Yes, you absolutely did.
That's why that's why you would say that.
Of course.
That was not the best work he's done over that song, but pretty okay.
There were moments of the flickering passion.
I would listen to a cover album of him sing talking what he thinks the lyrics
to songs are.
I don't want him to do that.
Although I do think that would be interesting as a side project.
I want an album of just that song, 12 tracks.
Yeah.
Just that song.
But different days, Alex, just Alex's greatest hits, freestyling.
Yes, whatever is on his mind.
This is like a great thesis at the beginning of this.
I know about powerful men.
Go from there.
Go for it.
Just see what happens.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just write it.
You love that goddamn saxophone.
Everybody loves that.
I'm talking about Alex.
He loves that saxophone.
Oh, he does.
It does something to him.
It does something to me.
Yeah.
We were both dancing.
We did, I didn't hear much of what he said.
I was too busy singing along.
That is a sultry ass song.
It is a great track.
It's a banger of a track.
I mean, it's no Zamfir, the lonely shepherd.
But yeah, it clearly puts Alex into some kind of a zone where it's like, it's time to blow
hard.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's time to be...
No narratives right now.
I'm just going with straight, inspirational fucking clear eyes, full hearts, belong to
the city.
I can see the horizon.
Yeah, 100%.
Absolutely.
Alex talks a bunch about being able to kick himself into a psychic state, and I don't
believe that.
But that song kicks him into something.
Something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So we come to the end of this exploration, Jordan, and I'm left with sort of a bad taste
in my mouth for Alex and his January 6th narratives.
I think it'll be interesting to see, as we get closer to the impeachment, how Alex keeps
probably trying to egg Trump into turning it into some kind of a circus.
Yeah.
And what ends up happening with that will be fascinating to watch Alex deal with.
But I do worry about his malleability.
The fact that he can have these people, the Boogaloos, that he decided were a FBI cutout
group, and he said he'd proved all this, and then have two of them on to manipulate him
and embarrass him in different ways.
So easy.
It's just, it's a mess.
Yeah.
Yeah, I imagine that this is...
I think what scares me most about this is how easily they are hand-waving away what
even Alex was like, this is going to fuck everything up.
You know, like, Alex is, I got to back away from this.
This is all, this, I know this is bad for me.
I know that this January 6th takeover of the fucking country is bad for me.
Yeah.
And it takes two weeks for people to convince me that, eh, you guys are great.
Yeah, that's not good.
Well, no, because he's trying to have it both ways too.
He's trying to retain that this was bad, but also like all of the actors who were actually
involved in it aren't bad, there were just a few people in their organizations who were
secret globalists who were trying to make them look bad.
It's too complicated.
No, he's still trying to run interference for people who are going to do what he wants
them to do.
Yeah, in the same way that Stuart Rhodes is gonna still fundraise for his Oathkeeper folks
who stormed the Capitol, Alex is making it very clear that if you kiss the ring, sort
of, or if you'll play ball a little bit, I will pretend that all the members of your
group who do bad things are not really part of your group.
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
And that's stupid.
That's fucked up.
Yep.
But expected.
100%.
Anyway, sorry the episode's late, we'll be back with another episode at the end of the
week.
Indeed.
But until then, Jordan, we have a website.
We do have a website, it's knowledgefight.com.
Yep, we're also on Twitter.
We are also on Twitter, it's at knowledgefight.net, go to bed Jordan.
Yeah, we'll be on Facebook in the future.
We'll be on Facebook someday.
Yeah.
But iTunes, if you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area.
Yeah, we'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo, I'm Leo, I'm DZXClark, I'm Daryl Rundis, I'm the Juiciest Dice
Cube.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan, I love your work.
I love you.