N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Damn, Ed, Jordan, I am sweating
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledgefight, knowledgefight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys
I love your knowledgefight
Dan and Jordan, knowledgefight
Riddle her, riddle her, riddle her
I need, I need money
Andy and Kansas, Andy and Kansas
Stop it, Andy and Kansas, Andy and Kansas
It's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding
Hello Alex, I'm a first-time caller, I'm a huge fan
I love your work
knowledgefight
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to knowledgefight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're a couple dudes, like to sit around, drink novelty beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are Dan
Jordan
Dan
Quick question for you
What's up
What's your bright spot today
My bright spot today, I don't know, this is maybe a little bit of an unconventional bright spot
Cause I don't know if it's bright, but it's been giving me a little bit of mirth
Okay
Um, I noticed that I have, I constantly have this thought
Mhm
But it almost sounds defensive in my head
Or almost apologetic
It's like, I love my cat
You know, it's almost like I'm making excuses within my own head
Sure, sure, sure
For being like, eh, she needs a good cat
No, no, no, you're very open emotionally
Look, I love my cat
I'm sorry everybody, I love my cat
I apologize for sharing my, I'm burdening you with my emotions of love towards my cat
No one has expressed any negative feelings
Ever
But I think it's because she does break a lot of stuff around here
And she makes a lot of messes, she's torn up my couch
Yeah
And so, you know, they're just like, eh, what are you gonna do, I love this cat
Eh, yeah, Jake is a, Jake my dog is an absolute nightmare of a lunatic
So I feel, I understand your feelings there
Yeah, there's a little bit about pet having that requires you to make some apologies every now and again
Even if it's only in your own head
Mine is out loud to a lot of people who are on my street sometimes
Wow, sure
Sorry about that
Little yippy barker
Sorry guys, my bad
What about you, what's your bright spot?
My bright spot day today, Dan, I have a rare double bright spot
Double
Double bright spot
First, Dan, I don't know if you remember this, but a while back
We wished somebody a happy birthday from an Alexis
I believe that was our last episode
I believe that was our last episode, yes
Now, what apparently happened is people have not been taking our advice
Which is, if you are somehow accidentally the person who gave a birthday wish
Let it ride, tell them it was you
We won't snitch
Well, but the problem in this case, I believe, is that the name was wrong
Yes, yeah
So it would have been difficult to pull this subterfuge off
It would have been tough
I think you could have done it with some quick little audio adjustments to the, yeah, you could pull it
Oh, sure
You could pull it off, yeah, yeah
You could take, I mean, think about how many names I've said over the course of this show
Exactly
You could splice in any
Absolutely, absolutely
They, the fact that we have to do this is almost an admission of laziness on their part
I just like that we're becoming Delilah
Yeah
Yay
We're gonna start doing song requests
Yeah, I hope so, I hope so
Hey, where are you coasting tonight, Dan? Where are you coasting?
Anyways, happy birthday
Trying to get you through that long drive
Absolutely
Here's quarter flash
Harden my heart
That's not a good love song
And now here are the Buckinghams
So yeah, happy birthday to Jared
Yeah
From Alexis
Happy birthday, Jared
And if you happen to be a Jared
Just, if your partner's a Jared, absolutely screw up the name
Why not?
And then of course I have to witness, or witness, I witness!
By observing this thing, I make it real
Witness me!
No, there's two people who are watching my Twitch stream
Oh, cool
And it turns out they are having their 18 year anniversary today
Wow
Yeah, I would have appreciated more of an O. Henry kind of
They both discovered our show and they waited until their anniversary to reveal it to each other
And now their 18th anniversary, their marriage can get an apartment
Absolutely
Yeah, hopefully
Anyways, so they have real names, but I refuse to believe it
If you're on Twitch, you are squeakins85 and magnanimousmoose
And you guys are wonderful and a merry anniversary to you
Happy anniversary
Jordan, today
We can't be doing too many more of these requests
I'm so torn, I really like it on the one hand
But yeah, I mean, at a certain point do we give everybody
I don't want to be the one who says, you know what, you're the last one, sorry
That's where I'm at too
I don't want to be that line
The line is the scariest part
I want to break up with birthday requests like a bad relationship we just text every other day
I know our habits and our patterns, we will just be like, yeah, this will resolve itself
Yeah, this will take care of itself
And then
Four years later
Ten birthday shout-outs per show
Yeah
So Jordan, today we have an interesting episode to go over
We're going to be talking about a little bit of action from February 7th 2021 Blackjack
Ah, damn it!
You are so good
Yep
That is really fast
That is Super Bowl Sunday
I was still turning and looking up there having a thought before you had finished a Blackjack
Yeah
This episode may have ended very recently before we started recording
And I gotta be honest
What's up?
Not a lot of content
Ah, not surprising
Not a lot of stuff going on
And I think that one of the things that's, uh, is that like
Well, we've got these, you know, January 6th narratives we're trying to juggle
Sure
Trying to figure that out
And Alex is really confused now that he likes the Boogaloo Boys
And like, well, I can't really pin this on them
Don't really know exactly what to do
Shit
Yeah
And I think he's biding his time a little bit because tomorrow, as we're recording this on Sunday
Monday is the trial in the Senate
Ah, yes
The impeachment trial begins
Yes, yes, yes
And so I think Alex is really getting excited for that
And, uh, so we're gonna do an episode on Wednesday and Friday this week
Yeah
But this episode is still going to be about that Sunday show
Okay
But I have to tell you this
What's this?
Jordan, I found a new genre
A new genre?
A new genre
Yes
Okay
Perhaps my new favorite thing
Alright, refresh the genres so far
Uh-huh
Wait
Classical
Yes, okay
Country
Alright
R&B
Naturally
This new genre is Alex's weird Infowars.com commercial reads
Okay, alright
Because I generally listen to the show on, uh, the GCN feeds or whatever, you know, like
So I will just hear the commercials for, like, Ted Anderson's sponsors
Sure, sure, sure
I haven't listened to the show, like, on Alex's own feeds for a long time
I went back and it's all I want to talk about
Okay
These commercials are fucked up
Okay, alright
They are nonsense
Let's do it
So we're gonna talk about, uh, some of the commercials that played during this, uh, this show
I love it
Before we get down to business on that, Jordan, let's say thank you to a couple folks who
signed up and are supporting the show
Oh, that's a great idea
So first, Dilly Danny, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Dilly Danny
Thank you
Next, Satan's a Little Monkey, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you, Satan's a Little Monkey
Thank you
Next, Lieutenant Colonel Zod, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Kneel before Lieutenant Colonel Zod
Lieutenant Colonel Zod, uh, called me about some info, some intel
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Uh, next, Commie Chimera, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you, Commie Chimera
I'm not sure I like this one, but
The thing people hate the most, commies and chimeras
I'm not sure I'm into this next, uh, name, but
Uh oh
It is what it is
Okay
Thank you so much, Poop Feast 420, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Next, help, I can't stop adopting cats, you are now a policy wonk
Thank you so much
Thank you very much
And finally, I'd like to say thank you to somebody who donated on Elevated Loan, we appreciate that very much
So, Brian W., thank you so much, you are now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
Crikey, mate, that's fantastic, have yourself a brew
How's your 401k doing, bro?
Alright, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, alright?
Let's just get down to business
We ain't making that money off that heroin
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large
I declare info war on you
Thank you so much, Brian
Yes, thank you very much, Brian
I want to say that this episode happened before a lot of stuff during the Super Bowl would have happened
So if anything was particularly Masonic or devilish, Alex didn't have any comments on that during the show
So we're going to have to wait to find out about that stuff
We'll handle what Super Bowl commercials there are people are going to talk about
It's almost kind of fitting that we're talking about Alex's commercials on the day of the Super Bowl
The thing that is known for its commercials
Yeah, I wouldn't say that's almost fitting, I'd say that's exactly fitting
You're just saying it's accidental
Yeah, we backed into something that's actually very fitting
Yeah, it's apropos, 100%
Here's another context drop
People think this is weird, this is normal
He says in a totally normal fashion
Yeah, that's one of my favorite things
People are like, I'm not weird, I'm not bad
People say this is weird, look at me, I'm touching my nose with tweezers, that's normal
It's normal
Sure, it's with my cheeks
So here is just the first taste of one of these commercials that's just
Let me set the scene for you
Alex is sitting there with a bookshelf behind him
He's sitting with a bookshelf behind him
Why?
To the other side there's a map but you can't see much of it
So he's sitting there and he's looking at the camera
So if I have just been injured, my ears have perked up at this visual
Because this is clearly a law commercial, right?
There are visual similarities, yes
Except that law office commercials have very uniform books on the shelf
Alex is lacking that
And then here we go
Look, I've been harping on Q for the last few years
Not because the giant huge Q movement was competition
My goodness, I could have embraced Q and just my show would have been bigger than ever
I gotta pause already
This is a commercial, right?
Yes
And I also gotta say you tried to do the Q thing, it failed
Yes, exactly
You tried to co-opt it
You tried to steal it
You said that
It's literally, but we're verbatim
Yeah
But I can't lie to you
Not consciously, I make mistakes sometimes
And I knew Q was control, I knew it was putting out false info
It was covering real issues but giving fake dates
Telling you we were invincible
And now we're here in 2021
And I just see so many people now that are still believing in some magic trick
And that Trump's still president
He's gonna save us
And that's just not the case
We're gonna have to save ourselves with God's help
There's an old Bedouin saying that trust in God but tie up your camel
Hunter S. Thompson said pray to God but we're away from the rocks
And that's what Info Wars is about
Is admitting the truth
There's a lot of positive things
The world's awakened to the new world order
Q is an attempt to hijack our movement and it's failed now
So now we know the truth and now we're getting ready to take action
Every product you hear me on air advertising
We have in stock in our warehouse
Every product
So if you order it, we've got it shipped out in a couple days
Sometimes the same day
Let's just get confused when they hear me talk about the fact that
The supply chain's breaking down and it's future orders
It's product we're trying to reorder to get back in
That we're having trouble with
I think you might now start to understand why
I'm completely fascinated by this being his commercials
What just happened?
See Jordan, what's amazing is that he doesn't understand
How to keep content and commercial separate
To the extent that during commercial breaks
That's what blew me away
Because I was always like, you know why he does this
Because he can't do it in his own commercials
He's selling other stuff so in his show
He's gonna sell you stuff
But now I realize, this is just how he talks
When he's talking to his kids, he's like
Listen, you need to go to school, you need to get good grades
And the best way to do that is with my suite of products that I have right here
Your grandfather has made some toothpaste
Yeah, exactly!
He can't not!
I think it's a mixture of that and I think it's just habitual
I think he's gotten so used to that being how ads work for him
That when he sits down to cut a commercial
He doesn't just say like, okay this is a commercial spot
I need to talk about the product
This is a commercial to try and get you to buy X
Alrighty
I'm gonna complain about Q, I'm gonna give you a Bedouin thing
Alex, we just want to cut one clean one
Look, you can do that whole thing
We just want to cut one clean one as an alternative
Just in case we need to
I would say
We're gonna stay here for a little while to do that
Chop the first minute off that
Just go ahead and
At least
Let me ask you a question
How does the, you had an argument with Q
Relate to the selling of the product?
Hey, it's what was on his mind
I honestly just think he was fucked up
And they sat him down and he recorded rambling for about
Half an hour
I want him to afford a Super Bowl commercial
I think he just sat there in front of the bookshelf
For like half an hour
And they're like, let's see what we can use
I don't fucking know
Exactly!
No, they did it, they do it like a fucking Christopher Guest movie
They're like, hey listen, we're just gonna roll tape and you just go
So now one of the things that's interesting about that
Is like, okay, so that was weird
That was a minute of nonsense before an ad pivot
Yeah
In a fucking commercial
You don't need to apologize to anybody in a commercial
Nope
You don't need to point out that you never lie
And then equivocate on it
One of the things that I thought was even more bizarre though
Is that some of these commercials aren't commercials
There's no plug in them
Get out
There's no product
There's no plug in the commercials
But I can't watch the show without hearing a plug every five minutes
Listen to this
Imagine a world without free speech
Imagine being buried alive
Scratching at the coffin lid
And no one hears you
You know, that's where the term dead ringer comes from
Going back to ancient England and France
Maybe five percent of people on average
Some of the numbers show even higher
First of all, what numbers show even higher
Second of all, that is not where the term dead ringer comes from
That is not where the term dead ringer comes from
Would look like they were dead
Sound like they were dead
And the primitive daughters of the time couldn't find a heartbeat
So they'd sit there and have a string down
Tied to the finger of the person six feet under
So in case they woke up they wouldn't be buried alive
So what I'm getting at here is this
America is still awake
America still is alive
But we're going to have to realize that we're under attack
And that we've been basically buried alive
If we have any chance to metaphysically with God's help break out of it
We've got to call out to God
To give us discernment and providence to get out of this
And admit the globalists are trying to bury us alive with the lockdowns
If we're ever going to turn this around
There is no product in there
No, the product is God
He's selling God to you
He's given you a good old sales pitch for God
That's why we've got to turn to God
It's so bizarre
That's the weirdest thing
It's unbelievably bizarre
That's weird
I mean, it's not that bizarre that he has this weird fake etymology
This is normal!
He has this fake etymology of dead ringer
No, that makes perfect sense
My dad told me that that's where the term dead ringer comes from
And now I'm going to repeat it to you on it
I mean, that's the level of shit that goes on in Infowars
It's just like, I saw this in a meme once
So someone decided that that was a clip
To air when he's taking an advert
They scored it! They put music under it
Right, right, right, right
But that wasn't a joke
No
Somebody was like, we gotta put that on there
Because it's important to have an interstitial
Can I be honest too?
Like, if you watch the video of it
They have found b-roll of someone scratching at a coffin
Love it
Yes, please
They've even thrown it
They couldn't afford Kill Bill at all
No, no, no, absolutely not
So yeah, they've thrown in b-roll stuff
This is amazing
This is so dumb
How long are the commercial spots?
I mean, it depends
Do they run like four commercials in a row?
It depends
Okay
Most of the time
On how long the commercials are?
So the first break of the hour is from about the five minute to six minute mark
Okay
And so that one's usually just like one
Sure
And then the other commercial breaks, they kind of vary
But they're like maybe three minutes
And it's all just him talking
Wow
But sometimes it's multiple of the commercials
Like, one of them is done and then another will start
It's surreal
I'm just blown away by that
Yeah
That's just really wild
It's indicative of a lack of anyone wanting to give you money to advertise
No
That's for sure
Yeah, no
You don't even want to give you money for advertising
Because you can't afford to pay someone for a good ad
And you don't even want to advertise your own shit
Yeah
You just talk about dead ringers and nuts
I would like more random, not true facts in my commercials
Well, Alex is your guy then
I would like, I'm sick of this Geico gecko nonsense
I want the Geico gecko to tell me that geckos did not evolve
And they were actually from a different planet
And then be like, by the way, we sell great insurance
Sure
That's what I want
So the first hour about of this show, a lot of it is about Alex's disgusting child abuse
stuff
And so we're not going to listen to any of that
Sure
And we will instead get to some of the content in the second hour
Where first of all, got to say, Ali Alexander breaks his silence
Oh
Did not realize he was silent
I didn't know that, I didn't know that
Didn't care
Good for him, I guess
Or bad for him
And then they decide that they have a new patsy for the January 6th storm in the capital
Sure
And we'll get to that in a little bit
And the rest of the 12th iteration of who is responsible for January 6th
Yeah, and then the rest of the time is kind of, a lot of tread and water
By the way, I want to say this, cantcensortruth.com
cantcensortruth.com
Is there an apostrophe?
URL up there, I've seen some of the fancy, bold stuff we've got
Because I was spending a lot of time this weekend doing research on Band.video
Watching some of the other shows, watching interviews, watching censored videos that are posted there
The MyPillowGuys two hour report is pretty good
Pretty good
It is on there, isn't it?
Yeah
So, first order of business, I take great umbrage with someone saying I did research on Band.video
Yeah, that's infuriating
Especially when it's Alex who owns it
Yeah
Gross, that's not research, you are killing time watching your employees
Merriam-Webster can do research into his own book, but beyond that, nobody else
So, Alex did post Mike Lindell from MyPillow, his documentary, Absolute Proof
Yes
Which is hilarious, because it's supposed to be absolute proof of the election being stolen
Right
And Alex says it's pretty good
It's pretty good
The review shouldn't be pretty good
No, no, no, absolute proof, pretty good
Um
It won the Palm, um
Palm de Plumbum
So, the thing is, I got inundated with messages from people asking me to cover this documentary
And we talked about this a little bit earlier, socially
That documentary sucked
Yeah
I was trying to find a way to make an episode out of it, because there was public interest in that
But it just wasn't going to happen
It's so poorly made, there's jump cuts all over the place, there's no new information really that I saw
Yeah
Being brought to the table, it's just not interesting
Well, from the way you described it, I read that he made it in six days working 21 hour days
That's what I read, and my first thought was like, well that's a guy who's clearly pumping himself up
Being like, look at how great I am
Right
As you described it though, I could see a coke-addled man being up for a week making something that bad
He's a former addict
He's, he's, he's, he's uh, that's behind him now
Okay
It's all pillows
Fine
Look, I don't know anything
Is that what makes his pillow so good?
I don't know anything about the guy, and I don't want to ever make fun of someone for having an addiction
No, totally not
And I don't want to drift into that, it's just bad
It's just a bad documentary, it's trash
I just, I don't know, I resented watching it
The only thing that I felt like at all okay about was like, well, this is going to be played in court
Two hours
Yeah
It's two hours long
It's too long
Two hours long
Yeah
Good movies are about an hour and a half
That's what I'll say right now
It was a struggle to get through, I was very bored
Oh
So I'm sorry to anybody who really wanted that, apparently if you want to watch it, it's up on band.video
It's on band.video
Alex might be getting a letter about that soon
But, I don't know
We'll see
So Alex is pumping up this URL that he's got, this youcantcensortruth.com
Sure, sure, sure
And I noticed a lot of comments saying we can't share band.video, man you need to create a new website
I mean I probably saw 20 of those comments in different videos because I care about your comments, I read them
And you know, I actually understand what you're saying
Oh shit, this is bad
They banned the term band.video about a year ago on Twitter, Facebook, Google, all that, just the URL
So we started creating a system where we can create new URLs that actually link to the very database and the very same videos
Like a disease
But then they've banned 2020electioncenter.com and some of the others
They've banned about six or seven
Like they're trying to fight a disease
Yeah, then they ban it tomorrow, it's cantcensortruth.com
This is a loser's strategy that Alex keeps engaging in
He's very open about his ban evasion strategy to the point where anyone paying attention could stifle this very quickly
I think his main strategy is eventually people quit playing whack-a-mole if they never hit the mole enough, you know
So he's gotta be like, listen, you guys know I'm never gonna stop, so just quit
I think that is the implicit threat
Is it?
Or it's like, okay, yeah, I've got cantcensortruth and also four other ones I haven't started promoting yet
You're gonna knock this one out, I'll already
What else do you got?
It seems like a waste of everyone's time
Everyone
So what's not a waste of time is ads
Let's get back to these commercials because they are way more fun
I sell supplements for two reasons
Because they work, they're real, they're powerful, and because it's a giant market
That's four reasons, Alex
That is four reasons
I sell some of those for two reasons
This is four reasons
I love the idea that he didn't even gather his thoughts before this
I have no interest
Nope
Uh-uh, this is pure stream of consciousness
Yeah, yep
Even down to the, like, I don't know if this is an action movie line or what, like, I sell products for two reasons
Because I came here to chew bubblegum and kick ass
No, this is not a they live thing
This is Alex not writing things down
So here's another commercial that's not a commercial
I don't believe there's a plug in this at all
Okay, okay
The world is awakening
The world is beginning to understand the globalist paradigm
They are discovering the globalist, the elites, the manipulation, the CFR
The Trilateral Commission, the Bilderberg Group, the Bohemian Grove, the Club of Rome
And so even though it's like the globalist are winning
The quilted quicker
The truth is they've had to come out in the open to attack human freedom because they're actually losing
We have forced them out in the open
So as bad as these times are, and a lot of negative things are about to happen
Realize humanity is winning
You've got to trust in the plan of God
And trust in the plan of God's justice
That is invincible
That is ethereal, timeless, and unstoppable
So don't trust in man, trust in God to lead God and direct your soul
And then take action against the globalist and realize
You've got my commitment from Alex Jones and my crew to you
We will never back down from the globalist and we will never surrender
Like, this is a wrestling promo
I was gonna say, are you just selling fear?
Are you just selling fear?
Yes, yes
We're not even selling anything this time, just be afraid
I think this is a tacit admission on his part
On some level that like, it's so much more profitable to make the audience feel things
Than to direct them at products
Totally
Make them feel like this visceral fear that's matched with the globalist are secretly losing
Of course, of course
That combination is just like, it must be the most potent marketing tool
Yeah, I mean, you know, get people terrified
Then say that by giving you money they're going to feel better
So you give them money
And then he goes, hey, we're winning
Ah, but you gotta stay terrified because we haven't won yet
Right
So then you give them more money and you feel like you're safe
And so on and so forth until you've forgotten your own name
Uh-huh
Oh boy
The name you'll never forget though
Blackjack
Ali Alexander
Oh, I will forget that name, I promise you
Ali Alexander is on to say that everyone is trying to get him
I don't know
I guess he has
If he doesn't get away and then scream Ali, Ali, Alexander free, I'm going to be pissed
I think he does have actually some valid points about like people posting on Twitter
The video of him, Nick Fuentes, and Alex at the Georgia Capitol
Sure
The Washington Capitol
Sure, sure, sure, sure
Yeah, that's fine
And if those people, you want to complain about them getting that wrong, go for it
Have fun
I also don't care
Not even a little bit
He's also
Oh no, are people lying on the internet?
Hmm, I would say that some people probably are
But I would bet that even more people are just wrong
Sharing it, yeah
Just don't know that they're wrong
Well, eh
Whereas Ali is actually a liar and a shifty grifter
Yeah
But he has some thoughts about why they're coming after the GOP and such
The Christians are all in the Republican Party
And when we get fed up, we control the entire Republican Party
And they can't have that because we're the people who don't believe in a technocracy
We're the people that gave the world federalism
We're the people that gave the world localism that worked
We're the people that stabilized the republic when the pagans and the barbarians
Even if western civilization couldn't
And so they need to mute the Christians first
So that we can't inspire the Republican Party to take meaningful action against this technocracy that they're building
Ali is a wild and sane zealot
Yeah, he just said that genocide is good
But also the notion that all Christians are Republican means that you have a very skewed version of who a Christian is
Yeah
And that tells you a bit
That tells you a bit of what you need to know
Absolutely
I don't care for this guy much
I didn't realize how much I enjoyed him being silent
It is interesting to me the way he puts that, of like, it's good thing that the Christians stabilized us when the pagans were around
I remember something about, what was it that the pagans got done to them?
Oh, that's right, a massive genocide
Wow
A massive genocide, and he's just like, yeah, it's a great idea for Christians to genocide people
Duh
We're doing it now
And this might be one of the reasons why it's tough to get sponsors
Genocide's good
On this show
It's tough
And that leads Alex, he's gotta do all these ads himself
Again, all shot in front of this bookshelf
This is totally, they just let him roll
Some of them are really long
We're gonna bang, listen, we're gonna cut all of our commercials for the next six months
We're gonna do it in a three hour shoot today
Alex, go
Here is a long one
The number one question I get on the street is, Alex, I love your show, but are you for real?
Do you really mean the things you say?
Well, I mean, anybody that's followed the show and written down what I said is gonna happen
knows almost all of it's now unfolded
So it's very, very frustrating
Incidentally, that is kind of what I do for a living
Yes
And I will say that is not the case
No
You do not find that he's right
That is true
You don't need to sit there and put your faith in me
Or your faith in the Dalai Lama
Or your faith in the private Federal Reserve
Or your faith in some televangelist on TV
You just have to have a memory and write down and remember the things I've laid out
You can go research those things for yourself
I have
You can find out is this guy more often than not right
You'll find out about 95% of the time I'm right
Nope
There's nothing more I'd like than to be wrong, but here's the
Congratulations
I am so angry at the Q people
Not because they were awake to the new world order
Not because they were exposing child kidnapping rings
That's all great
But because they had this feeling of invincibility
And this feeling of everything's gonna be handled, everything's taken care of
And this attitude that they didn't have to document anything
Because they were just going off some 8chan board
I can show you DW.EU
Not the address
London Guardian
I can show you thousands of children a month kidnapped, tortured, some killed
I can show you the Catholic Church with nuns delivering little boys to be gang raped by men
That's just this week
My God, there's so many articles and trials and convictions just on that subject
That I can't even look at it all, I don't want to, I'm sick of it
Even though it's my job to expose it, it's a horror to focus on it
So people say, Jones, are you for real?
I mean, I'm as real as a heart attack
I'm as real as getting hit by a bus
I'm as real as a train wreck
Because I'm covering what's really happening in the world
Everybody else just sells out to the system
They go on to get along
But it's been my job to tell the truth
As best I can, I'm not perfect
So if you want to keep us on the air
And you've noticed we've got an incredible track record of being accurate
And you want to keep us in the game for all the crazy things that are about to go down
Then go to Infowarsstore.com
Wild, wild
That is the craziest thing that I've ever heard in my entire life
There's no way that he could have ended that with
Please buy Infowarsstore products
There's no way, and yet he did
And yet he did
You should have just said that at the beginning
I'm great, I'm great, I'm great, I'm great
Go to Infowarsstore
You don't need the two minute ramp up
It's a commercial, people expect it to be a commercial
Short
Also, the only way you can make this more surreal is if you're watching the video
When he says, I'm as serious as a heart attack
I'm as serious as getting hit by a bus
They cut in video of a goat getting hit by a bus
It's that video of like a security camera inside a bus
And the goat going through the windshield
What is happening?
I don't know
I think you could easily drive a human being insane
If for one day, one person YouTube just chose
And they were like, nobody gets to skip ads today
And it's only AJ's ads
They could drive a person insane instantly
I feel like I was losing it a little bit
Yeah, I'm already like, this is not real
And I also was kind of thinking like, I think
I'm coming around to the idea that maybe he's on drugs
Like, it might just be a drug thing
Could be
This is such weird behavior
Yeah, yeah, no, Dan, it's normal
But then
Alright, it's Super Bowl Sunday, I'm Alex Jones, I'm glad you're here
Ollie Alexander's broken his silence
People ask me all the time, they go, Jones, are you
Are you on cocaine, are you on methamphetamine?
The answer is no, I hate stimulants other than like coffee
I get really upset about this
I mean, we led a peaceful demonstration of a million people
They tried to set me up
They're calling for me to be put in prison all over the news
Along with President Trump, who's on trial starting tomorrow
This is serious
Well, I guess that settles it
I mean, he said he's not on coke
Well, that's, yeah
Yep
But I don't have any evidence that he's ever pissed clean
You know what I'm saying?
I ask him so many questions when they immediately come up to him
Yeah, yeah
No one ever seems to say hi
Everybody's like, hey, are you on drugs?
Hey, are you lying?
Hey, Alex, are you for real?
Hey, Alex, are you an actor?
Hey, Alex, how are you taking the deep platform?
Why is everyone asking you so many questions?
Hey, Alex, I'm the devil, blah
But like I said, Alex can say all day long that he's not on drugs
Correct
But I don't know that he's pissed clean
In fact, one time I had a security
A couple of years ago, he goes
He goes, man, you were totally down, tired
He goes, you just came right back on back on break and exploded
Are you on drugs?
And I said, here, let me do a drug test
Called a portable drug test here
Pissed in a cup
No drugs
I said, you see that?
He said, yeah, I see that
People think this is weird
This is normal
That's normal?
When you're under attack
I feel like this sounds like someone on drugs
Hey, Alex, your energy switch is just really off the charts
I was just wondering, do you take any drugs in the bathroom?
I'd be pissing that cup
No, I didn't say that
You give me a portable drug test immediately
I don't need to give you a portable drug test
This wasn't even in a professional capacity
I was just asking you a question
Who?
Professional courtesy
I just want to know if the man I'm protecting is on drugs
I will say I'm suspicious
Yeah
So Alex and Ali get to talking about the 6th, January 6th
The day of the storming of the Capitol
Yes
And there's two interesting takes here
The first is that Alex seems to think that they were right on the cusp
Of getting that 10-day investigation that Rudy Giuliani wanted
So close
And Ali seems to think that all things considered
It was a pretty peaceful rally
Well why the hell would we have the motive to
When Trump had them about to do a 10-day investigation
And we were just showing our numbers
Why would we screw ourselves?
Where's the motive?
We were on the eve of history
And quite frankly we still made history
Because January 6th was peaceful
99.9% of a million people being totally peaceful
When we feel that our election has been stolen
Is a first in human history, God bless us, okay?
Wow
That is a big sell
Yeah
That's a big sell
That is an interesting angle, Ali
Listen, listen, listen
I'll tell you this right now
Real estate, 10 years?
Nagasaki's gonna be huge
That's all I'm saying
I'm saying people aren't thinking about the good things that happened on the 6th
Sure, sure
Yeah, it's an interesting prism to see things through
Yeah
And I do like Alex's attempt at making it like
We were right there, we were about to get those hearings that we wanted
Because that's a good way to really make it like
Ah, we couldn't have possibly wanted anything like this to happen
No, no, no
Because we were about to get our way
10-day investigation
That's what we were
Nonsense
So there's a new narrative that's gonna be spun about the 6th
Sure
And this has to do with somebody
An insider in the Trump campaign
Sure
They set them up, they did them dirty
Of course
They got done dirty
Of course they did
So what ended up happening, apparently, something like this
Roger Stone
No
Oh
Not entirely clear, somebody didn't play a video
That Ali wanted them to play
Right
At the Ellipse rally
So revolutionary
They would have given some instructions on something
I don't fucking know
Okay
This is a silly, uh, argument
Alright, so if he was on, say, Flight 93
He's just concerned that they didn't play this video
Sure
So people could know not to break into the Capitol
Absolutely, it's a good video
And then we walked right into a trap
Trump walked right into a trap
So go into what you know
Are you ready to release her name?
I mean, maybe she didn't mean it
Maybe she didn't know
But we know who was in command of everything
We know who removed the jumbotron directives
We know who, I mean
You're not gonna direct a million people with no direction
So you wanna talk about it?
So yeah
So we got the person has taken the jumbotron directions down
Done Alex and Ali dirty
Do you wanna make a guess on who this is?
You know it's a female
Oh, I know it's a female?
Oh, you said she
Oh, okay
Oh, let's see
You know what? Fuck it
I'm gonna go with Sarah Huckabee Sanders
Sarah Huckabee Sanders is incorrect
Damn
Are you gonna release
Which I already thought, I already told my people
Three weeks ago I think was behind it
Yeah, I mean, I'm gonna just say it
Katrina Pearson is a campaign advisor
She makes a quarter million dollars on the Trump campaign team
She's one of the highest paid advisors to do nothing
She lied to the president in November
We caught her, we called her out
Me and several members of Stop the Steal
And she was behind this coup
To ditch out part of the coalition at the ellipse event
And that led to no leadership with the masses
When we walked into a trap set to us by leftist agitators
And I think that the president ought to totally distance himself from this grifter
This is getting a little bit too much
This narrative is a little
We're getting out of control
A little thin
It's a little thin
Guys, okay
I am just gonna have to stick with the simplest explanation
Which is that this is what you've been telling people to do
And then when they did it you were mad because it looks real stupid now
Yes, and it's pretty easy to look at your rhetoric
And the content and the conspiracy theories that were being thrown around
About how you kinda gotta stop the certification of the election
No matter how
So wait, now let me ask you a quick question
If you are telling me that getting your video up on the jumbotron
That would have saved everything
Would have influenced people
What you're saying to me is that broadcasting somebody's words
Can cause real life actions to happen, correct?
I mean, that's certainly
Yeah, I mean that's something you could take away from that
Yeah, it seems like that would suggest that you guys are aware that
Yeah
Well, yeah
I think that this is just dumb
Like, you just
It's too far
It's too far to walk
To make this make sense
So we now come to the end of our content
And we just have a few more commercials
Love it
To bring us home
Perfect
And this just is the beginning of a commercial
I just, I can't
Like, this isn't how you start a commercial
Look
We've already come a long way together
What?
Hey, look
You need paper towels
Bounty, buy them
No, no, no
Look is how you start a fight
Look
Yeah, you're in a bar and someone's not listening to you
This September
The new Marvel movie
Look
Ant-Man was pretty good
Nope, that's how Alex is starting a fucking commercial
Look
My pillow
God damn it, buy it
I'm gonna buy my pillow
So yeah, here's a commercial
Look
We've already come a long way together
We've already changed the world
And I warned listeners
Four and a half years ago when Trump was president-elect
I said, he's just one wave
I told Vice TV that
I said, populism, nationalism, a pro-human future
Brought Trump in as a surfer
And whether he is a traitor
Or whether he's the real deal
Or whether he's a weak man or a strong man
That doesn't really matter
Because it's the ocean of liberty
This system of freedom
This title forces
That actually conjured Donald Trump
And I think Trump was a great man
He lost two billion dollars
He got kicked out of every organization he was in
He paid a mighty price for trying to stand up for this country
Or
But on a scale of one to ten
I'd give him about a 9.5
I would say Trump's done a way better job than I've actually done
In the fight against these people
So it's easy to play Monday morning quarterback
Or be the backseat driver
But as for the man in the arena
Great job
It's incredibly fashionable to throw President Trump under the bus
But let's just move on from President Trump
Okay
So
Wow
Yeah, he rambles a bit more
And then he makes this metaphor that I think is a little strained
Let me give you some good news today
Trump was a big royal flush hit
He held him back, had a lot of victories, wasn't perfect
But that was an amazing hand in poker
Okay
Or I guess, use the blackjack analogy, he was 21
You don't get that hand every time
That hand's been moved aside now
But as for nationalism and freedom and a huge awakening
It's been incredible
So don't take Trump having the election stolen
And all the martial law and all the tyranny is a sign that we're losing
That's a sign we're winning
Yeah, they stole the election
Yeah, they're trying to set up martial law
Yes, they're creating racial division
Because they're weak
Again, the message needs to be like really stressed hard
That like, ah, tyranny is upon us, but that is a good sign
Yeah, yeah
That means we're winning
No, no, no, you're all dying as we speak
Be scared, but we're winning
You are dying and that's how you know it's going well
Yeah, yeah
That seems to be just like the through line
But also, a royal flush can't be beat
Ah, yeah, that was a little bit frustrating to me
Yeah, that's a bad metaphor
If you are saying that he got a winning hand, why did he lose?
Yeah
I mean, you could tie with a dealer if you get blackjack
But, I mean
Yeah
You still can't lose
Right, yeah
Brutally
Yeah
So this was the last commercial that we got
And this one was actually, I thought this one was pretty funny
This might be my favorite
Although I will say it's pretty tough to top look
I just like look because look has a subtext which is parentheses asshole
Yeah
It's always look, asshole
Here's what we're doing
It has a tone that's very similar to listen up
Yeah, exactly
Yeah
But this one is great because it makes no sense
It is very stupid
And it reveals something
We're already in the second month of 2021
And we all see it's a dystopia
The globalists are out in the open announcing world government
Announcing medical tyranny
UN contact tracers to come to your house
People have their doors kicked down
This is all them trying to submit their dominance over us
Because they know humanity is waking up
And is in the process of leaving one age
This whole globalist time of evil and darkness
And traveling not into some new satanic luciferian new age that's perfect
But into an age what I call challenge
Or the age of real conflict
The age of decision
You're not going to read this stuff in books
It comes from my soul, my prayer, my research
My understanding of the planet
No shit
You may disagree with that's fine
But I'm telling you we're leaving the old age of being asleep
We're in the new age of being awakened
And not some new age of the new age
But God's age of the understanding
Every product you hear me on air advertising
We have in stock in our warehouse in Austin, Texas
Every product
So if you order it, we've got it shipped out in a couple days
Sometimes the same day
Leisure's getting confused when they hear me talk about the fact that
The supply chain's breaking down
And it's future orders
That second part is the same part from the first commercial
Same part
It's just added it on
This is wild
They just added it on
The part where he's talking about how they have everything in stock
At the end of a minute of him rambling about how we're in the new age
But it's not the new age
Not the new new age
It's a different new age
It's the age of challenge
But also, I like a huge selling point being
Our products exist
I can show you where they are
They're here in the store
They're in the store
Um, yeah, I'm pretty amazed
I really do think he probably just sat down, talked shit
Has to
Has to be
Put it together
100%
Wow
Man
But also, I love that he's like talking about how we're getting into the new age
But then he realizes that new age is a thing
Sounds a little too
Well, it's a thing
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly
It's a thing that he's associated with Satanism
Right, right, right, right
So he has to like really try and like, ah, it's new age
But it's not new age new age
It's like new age
It's a different new age
I do appreciate how either his audience has made it very abundantly clear to him
With all of their questions
That they do not understand basically anything
Or that he has to reiterate things constantly to himself
Like, people say that they're worried about
Because I say that the supply chain's going down
And then, but that, no, no, no, that's future orders
Like, we all get how the supply chain works, Alex
I don't know why you need to explain how that works
In an ad
Well, it's because I think that he thinks that he's
Talking about the supply chain is supposed to make people feel a need to act now
Right
But I think that he believes that his audience interprets it as
There isn't anything
There's nothing anything to buy, yeah
But that's also because he does do a lot of yelling about how the shelves are empty in the stores
Exactly
Yeah, so I would understand why the audience might get that impression
Yeah, exactly
So he does need to clarify, man
I know, it seems like you've made poor choices if you've gotten to that place
That's what I would suggest
And that might explain why he starts commercials with, look
I'm sick of people asking me questions about how to buy the shit that I tell you you can't have
So, Jordan, this was not the most serious episode we've ever done
Downey, we have paper towels in stores
Just the
They're there
The brawny man just turns and says, look
It's there
And so, Super Bowl commercial special it is
Yeah
And we'll be back on Wednesday to discuss Alex's immediate response to the impeachment trial
Indeed
And see what he's up to, see if he can rise to the occasion, come up with something interesting
We'll see
But until then, Jordan, we have a website
We do have a website, it's knowledgefight.com
We're also on Twitter
We are on Twitter, go to bed Jordan
We're also on Facebook
We are on Facebook, if you could, please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people doing God's work right now
Yeah, we'll be back, but until then, I'm Neo, I'm Leo, I'm DZXClark, I'm Daryl Rundis, this is one time Jordan and I were doing a podcast
And he's like, hey Dan, you want Coke? And I said, give me a cup
And I pissed in it, and I was like, no drugs
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan, I love your work
I love you