N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledgefight, knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying we are the bad guys.
I love knowledgefight.
Dan and Jordan, knowledgefight.
Red alert, red alert, red alert.
Need, need money.
Andy and Kansas, Andy and...
Stop it.
Andy and Kansas, Andy and Kansas.
It's time to pray.
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a system caller and I'm a huge fan.
I love your world.
Knowledgefight.
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight.com.
I love you.
Hey everybody!
Welcome back to Knowledge Right, I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan!
We're a couple dudes, I can sit around, drink novelty beverages and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones.
Oh indeed we are, Dan.
Jordan.
Dan!
I have a quick question for you.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, Jordan, is something interesting.
I learned something.
Indeed.
I was unaware of this.
Is that your first time in a long time learning something?
I listen to Alex a lot, so yes.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Yeah, I haven't learned shit from that guy.
I learned something that honestly I had every reason to know before, and I don't know why
I didn't quite frankly, but as it turns out, I only know when things come to our P.O. box
because I get an alert from the store.
Sure.
Where the box is.
They don't send you alerts when letters come.
Oh!
I didn't know that, and unless the person who's giving you the packages checks the mailbox,
you'll never know.
That's not fair!
No.
I found a bunch of letters in there the last time I went to pick up packages, and also
we're way behind on zapping up the mailbag, so we'll get around to opening some of that
up in the near future, but on the last trip I went down there, I got to these letters,
and I got a particularly amazing letter from someone who I just want to call Dr. Justin.
That's what I was going to say.
Dr. Justin to protect everyone's anonymity and their privacy.
I feel like this letter is delayed because I have no idea when things come into the mailbox,
but it was just amazing.
It doesn't get more us than to not know when mail is.
Just an amazing letter, and I appreciate it so much, it really meant a lot, and has been
so thank you.
Yeah, no, just tears, just tears, weeping, just non-stop.
Thanks for sharing that letter with us, Dr. Justin, and congratulations on your doctor-ness.
Hell yeah.
How about you?
My bright spot, Dan, is I have finally finished my two months long project, and I'm done with
Taylor Swift.
Okay.
For good.
It's over.
You've listened to the whole catalog.
I've listened to every one of her albums, and I'm done.
I'm pretty proud of myself.
How do you feel?
Fine.
Yeah, I expected that was probably the answer.
I've intentionally not read anything you've written about Taylor Swift because I don't
want to get mad at you.
Of course.
I've never read just this before.
I don't want to pick a fight.
I don't want to be like, look, I love blank space.
I don't want to talk about it.
Sure.
I understand.
I mean, it's unfair.
I wasn't trying to pick a fight.
I was trying to go so far over the top, no one could possibly imagine that I would be
fighting.
At a certain point, I insisted that the guy who wrote Bloodsport was the writer of one
of her songs.
Do you understand?
I'm not going for realism here.
I think the audience wants to know what your next extended exercise in misogyny will be.
Maybe a bunch of articles about Mariah Carey not being as good as everyone thinks.
Well, that would just be impossible because Mariah Carey is exactly as good as everyone
thinks, Dan.
Maybe the next series could be about Pink.
Now you're just finding people you're defensive about now.
I like Mariah Carey.
Everybody likes Mariah Carey.
Everybody likes Pink.
I don't know.
I've met some Pink haters in my life.
That's fair.
Well, congratulations on finishing a project.
It's over with.
Yes.
I'm proud of myself.
Let's not talk about it again.
Ever again.
Jordan, something we are going to talk about is Alex Jones today.
Oh yeah.
You're going to be talking about the February 8th, 2021 Blackjack episode.
No, I'm not even, I didn't even have a chance.
I was watching your lips move and I was like, boo, and you had already finished.
When you see a pro like me, everything happens in slow motion.
So no matter how many times I sit there and think in my head, I know he's about to say
the date.
I'm still caught by surprise every time.
It's also not quite fair because I can just keep talking.
Yes, that's true.
I can say 21 Blackjack.
Yes.
I can say it as one word almost even.
You're playing at a disadvantage, but I'm also very good at it.
Yeah, exactly.
There's the double whammy.
This is Monday.
We're talking about the day after the Super Bowl.
Right.
There'll be some thoughts on that.
I imagine so.
Oh, Nelly, are there some thoughts on that?
Oh boy.
But more importantly, I think there's a big broad push that Alex is engaging in that I
think will be the direction of his content in the near future.
And before we get down to business on that episode, Jordan, let's take a moment to say
thanks to some folks who have signed up and are supporting the show.
Oh, that's a great idea.
So first, Commie Wizzo.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Commie Wizzo.
I've never seen The Room.
That's a, well, he wrote The Mark's Room, I believe.
Oh yeah, it could be.
Have you ever, have you ever seen The Room?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I think everybody but me has.
It's very funny.
Yeah, that's why I don't want to see it.
I understand.
It'll actually make you sad and you won't like it.
You will not appreciate it.
You'll be like, this guy was trying so hard and it's a bad movie.
I don't know if I will.
I don't like everything that I've seen surrounding it and so I'm not interested in what germinated
all of these plants.
That's fair.
Anyway, Lady the Dog runs the simulation.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Lady the Dog.
Thank you.
Next, Biggles Dictates a Letter.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Biggles.
Thank you.
Next, Ima Holler Back Girl.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Don't you write a series about Gwen Stefani being bad.
I might.
Actually, she...
Alright.
Next, Tomorrow's Warm Flat Seltzer.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
Next, Joined Just to Ask What the Hell Do You Have Against Accountants?
We're Not All Oogie Boogie Sympathizers.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
I believe that's a question for you, George.
I didn't know that.
I'm speaking as a former accountant.
I don't have anything against accountants.
I'm just saying that you can't be both an accountant and a boogie boy.
I feel like that's right.
You can be a boogie boarder.
Well, that's...
See?
Of course.
And you'd be a cool accountant.
Yeah.
It might be very cool for an accountant.
Then finally, I'd like to say thank you to a couple of people who donated on Elevated
Level.
I appreciate that very much.
So, Introskipping Joe.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
And Grim Squeaker.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate.
That's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
We gotta go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Ah, yes.
Thank you so much, Joe, who skips the intro, and Grim Squeaker.
Yes.
Thank you very much to the both of you.
Jordan, did you watch the Super Bowl?
I did not.
And I'm grateful for it.
Mm-hmm.
Did you?
I saw some tweets.
And then, because of this episode, I watched the Halftime Show.
Oh, yeah.
And I didn't watch that either.
Mm-hmm.
I did not.
Although, I did hear that Weeknd did stuff off House of Balloons in the fucking...
What does that mean?
House of Balloons was his first little EP that came out.
Oh, probably.
And it is...
He had a lot of...
He did a lot of songs.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was...
Yeah, that one was, like, really dark and just basically about doing coke and fucking
the whole time.
Well, there's that song, like, I can't feel my face when I'm with you.
That was about drugs, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's all about drugs.
That's what I thought.
I don't know that to be true.
I just think I've heard that somewhere.
Yeah.
Yeah, he did that for sure.
Cool.
And then, uh, Starboy, except, like, the chorus of that is...
Was Daph Monk there?
No, they were not, and I think some people were mad about that.
Yeah, well, I would be.
But the chorus is, I'm a motherfucking Starboy.
He is a motherfucking Starboy.
You can't say that in the Superboy.
Yes, you can.
Why not?
So you have to say, I'm a Starboy.
This sucks.
Oh, man.
Uh, I watched that halftime show, and we'll get to that at the end of this episode a little
bit.
But the only thing I was thinking was, like, I can't believe that The Weeknd is this big
of a star.
Yeah.
Like, I'm nothing against it.
He seems like a talented guy.
He's great.
But just, like, I'm so disconnected from pop culture that I'm, like, wow.
There's no surprise guests.
There's no, like, I remember the days of halftime shows when it's, like, one star is not enough.
Five people.
Five different bands.
Aerosmith's gonna be there.
Metallica's gonna play a duet with Katy Perry, who gives a fuck.
In Sync is gonna come out of the floor.
Exactly.
And then Nelly's gonna parachute in.
Shit comes out of the floor at the Super Bowl.
That's math.
Yeah.
And it was just The Weeknd.
It was a fine performance.
I didn't like all the songs.
I think maybe some were a little bit boring, but, hey, I'm not the target demo.
You didn't write nine different installments of something about it, so you're fine.
Although, give me time.
Your turn next, buddy.
So yeah.
That's about all I saw.
I guess I saw a little, like, a couple of, like, choice plays, like at Mahomes Pass where
he was falling.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Pretty amazing stuff.
I don't know, I don't really have any strong feelings about it.
The game, I guess I'm from Missouri, so I should love the Chiefs.
I have some friends who really like the Chiefs, so good for them.
All right.
Yeah.
Anyway.
We start with Alex in an out of context drop.
That is a rare situation where I'm going to give you a little question ahead of time about
this out of context drop.
He's telling somebody to burn in hell, and I'd like you to try and guess who he wants
to burn in hell.
All right.
That is a lot.
No, you have to guess.
Oh, before?
Yes.
I thought you were going to guess, okay.
Let's see.
And this is after the Super Bowl.
I am going to go with, why not Bill Gates?
You're going to burn in hell, Springsteen, burn in hell.
Nope.
Bruce Springsteen's going to burn in hell.
Did he just find out that Bruce Springsteen doesn't like the far right?
Did he just learn that Born in the USA- I was going to say, did he just find out about
Born in the USA?
He might have.
He did not like that commercial.
Someone explained the song to me, and now I'm mad.
He resented the commercial, I guess it was a General Motors commercial, where Bruce Springsteen
was doing some voiceover talking about how there's a church in the middle of Kansas,
right in the middle of America.
It's hard to get to the middle, but it's like-
Oh boy.
That somehow that pissed off Alex to the point where Bruce Springsteen's going to burn in
hell.
All right.
Everybody should burn their Jeeps.
Okay.
I'm fine with that.
Whatever.
Anyway.
There's never less carbon in the atmosphere to burn your Jeep.
But Alex thinks we need all the carbon.
Oh, that's true.
So, we start off the show, and Alex is in the exact mode that I like him to be in.
This is when I know, okay, this show's going to be weird.
Okay.
I tend to get up here on air and get really excited and cover a lot of news and still
kind of not get to all the points I really want to break down, so I'm going to try my
best here today to just be calm and we'll see how long that lasts and just cover all
of this, but it is becoming extremely, extremely clear exactly what is going on and what is
unfolding.
Now-
Uh-huh.
Let me just, I can't do the show right now, I just can't do it, I got to reset, I got
to go rebroadcast.
I mean, this is all just too heavy, this is all too insane, this is all too serious, and
I just need people to know that this is not a game, okay?
Okay.
I'm coming out of the gates, a lot of energy, and then within a minute, I can't do this.
I can't do this.
Fuck it, ah shit.
Look, we're going to focus, we're going to calm down, I'm just going to get through this.
I quit.
I am not going to be here for any longer, I'm done.
Fuck this.
I got to get out of here.
He doesn't actually go to rebroadcast, but he does play some special reports.
So funny.
But not before teasing a little bit of what's coming up on the show.
Sure.
And I learned something interesting because of his tease.
Okay.
The writer is going to be in studio with us, he's a great author and researcher and knows
his stuff.
He's done more deep research on the globalist end game than even I have because-
Did he make a movie about it?
I did most of my research 30 years ago, 20 years ago, 10 years ago, because I already
know their operation, but he studies it going back as well, hundreds of years, but then
on their current stuff.
So I kind of use him as a Reader's Digest with his show and the things he does to go
hear him boil down these books he's reading like every day, new ones, where they're going
to just tear us apart and put us in camps and brain damage us and sterilize us and they're
just foaming at the mouth like satanic piranhas.
It's hard for me to read their stuff, but he does it and then boils it down.
Alex could have probably just said it's hard for him to read.
It is hard for me to read is all I heard in that sentence.
So yeah, apparently Alex doesn't read primary sources anymore, but pretends to pretty extensively
on air.
I can't read all this stuff, I just accept Jay Dyer.
You can't say yesterday I do all my own research and then say today I can't really do any research
so I just read this guy.
Yeah.
That's not fair.
And then I accept whatever interpretations he apparently has about primary sources that
he probably didn't read either.
Are you kidding me?
This man claims to read a book a day.
How could I not take everything he says at face value, Dan?
Certainly.
Ah!
So I got excited.
I'm like, Jay Dyer, alright, I can't wait to assess you.
I've heard him bit on the show before, he's boring and stupid, but I was like, well, alright,
I'll get excited for that.
Alex is in a bad mood.
He clearly wants to storm off the show.
Oh yeah.
He's got this guy coming up that I think I can sink my teeth into and instead Alex just
like he plays a special report about Marjorie Taylor Greene and like it's this weird, weird
thing where John Bowne, one of Alex's employees, is trying to make an argument that Marjorie
Taylor Greene having these committee appointments taken away is somehow a purge of all conservatives.
Yes.
And it seems like a dumb argument to make.
It seems like a bad.
Oh yeah.
Because what you're doing is essentially equating whatever you believe in and your rhetoric
with her and if you believe, if you want to, if you want to make that association you're
more than welcome to.
Yeah.
That's a losing argument.
It might not work well.
And then like this argument extends to like what we need to do is we need to get them
off of their committees.
Okay.
And it's like, all right, go try.
Fine.
Yeah.
That's called being politically active.
If you want to start a petition.
You can, you can do that.
You can vote.
We vote on things.
Call your legislature.
Yeah.
Just go say vote.
Not hard.
Yeah.
This is a dumb video.
Anyway, I got bored with that.
What I'm always not bored with is there's some more commercials.
Okay.
Uh, last episode we talked about Alex's commercials and it was a big hit and I thought we need
a little more of a taste of these commercials.
I have a question cause I have not heard of any really standout commercials, Dan from
the Superbowl.
I think we won.
I think we had the best commercials of a Superbowl Sunday.
Yeah.
I think, um, can't think of whatever, like an advertising publication, but that, that
I think they would give the crown to Alex.
I think they would have to.
Yeah.
Better than that Oatly commercial.
Better than the Bruce Springsteen commercial.
What are you talking about?
Oh, there's a small town.
No, look, there's a small town.
That's how you do the line reading.
This commercial might take the cake.
Okay.
I think it's my favorite.
All right.
I have to warn you.
Teasing it big.
Jordan, it's four minutes long.
That's not a commercial.
This is a special report then.
It goes all over the place and it is so mopey and it's very, it's a bummer.
Okay.
So it was four years ago.
I was in a custody battle with my ex wife and her lawyers were trying to introduce a
video of me like 10 years ago and I dressed up like the joker to do an anti Prozac ad.
I said, Oh, kids take your Prozac.
You'll see pretty colors and act all crazy because the inserts of the Prozac class of
drugs, anti-depressants, serotonin reuptake inhibitors admit it increases suicide risk
and all sorts of the problems.
And so my lawyer at a hearing that I wasn't even at said, uh, he's playing with joker
there just like Jack Nicholson isn't really the joker.
That's not really Alex Jones.
This was actually a defense of introducing any video of Alex on info wars.
The lawyer's argument was that he's a performance artist.
Now he did say that it would be like compare like saying that Jack Nicholson is playing
the joker.
Correct.
But it wasn't just about a specific video that Alex is referencing where he does have
joker makeup on.
He's trying to conflate those two things.
But yeah, I was like, Whoa, this is like the first minute of this commercial.
I'm really struggling with the commercial aspect of this.
We'll get to it.
Many commercials begin with, of course, I was in a custody battle four years ago.
Four years ago.
I was in a custody battle.
My lawyer said something weird and uh, so that one wasn't, that one didn't surprise
me at all.
Uh, in order for me to not have my kids taken away from me, my lawyer need to make a really,
uh, really desperate argument to keep my public persona out of court so I wouldn't have to
answer for why I scream about how my enemies are demons and literal devils and how I'm
a psychic.
And I wouldn't have to answer any questions about that because I'm a performance artist,
but technically I don't want you, my audience to think that because then the sales pitch
won't work.
But anyway, have you tried Tom?
That's a preamble to a great commercial.
Yes.
Yeah.
And I got turned into Jones admits he's a character in court.
Well, I'm the opposite of a character.
I am.
I stand for him, I stand for how I stand.
I'm the most unscripted person out there.
That said, when I do research and I'm getting ready to do a video and I'm getting ready
to break something down, I wouldn't call it performance anxiety.
Instead of getting butterflies, when I get in front of a crowd, I get really hyper and
then I have all these ideas and things I want to say.
So I move really, really fast and sometimes you can lose all the key information and how
fast I'm moving.
But if you slowed it all down and search engine, each thing I talked about, it's all huge stuff
like world government, new world order, eugenics, agenda 21, agenda 2030, the human biological
diversity assessment, 2002, 1992.
I mean, all these things open Pandora's boxes, but, but see, I'm already getting excited.
We are not two minutes in.
This is not a commercial.
This is a voicemail on his like ex-wife's phone.
This is a voicemail.
This is something that he sent to somebody drunk at like 3 AM.
Okay.
Listen, I'm four years ago.
All right.
I was in a custody battle.
First minute is about the custody battle stuff and how I'm real.
I'm real man.
100% real.
Second minute.
Sometimes I get real excited and I just yell shit where it's time to deliver information.
I kind of forget what I'm doing probably because I'm on drugs.
If you would like to rerecord your message, please begin again at the dial tone.
Let me, the time I have here, just be really straight with all this.
A part of me wants to not be able to continue on at this level because my body's exhausted.
My spirit's not, and I talk about all these incredible things that have happened.
People can now see that I wasn't exaggerating.
I wasn't lying.
We're in a corrupt, psychotic, anti-human world government that wants to bankrupt us
and make us really poor control our lives.
Sure.
And there's this paradox where people say, well, Jones, you've got so much credibility
now.
You need to continue on.
I do want to continue on.
It's just that I can't continue on because they took all my sponsors, took most of my
taking away.
And I've had to rely basically purely on people buying products at mfullwarestore.com.
So I had a lister today on the Friday show called this.
That was a great time for a plug.
I wish you'd do more and expand your network.
Look, I'm not complaining, but I spent about half my time trying to raise money.
I'd rather be on air fighting the globalists instead of trying to raise money.
I don't like coming to you either.
I'm a proud person at a certain point.
But look, we're all proud people.
The point is if you, what is happening in this fight, there's no reason for that.
Things happen.
There's no reason for that.
You have to understand that we're all proud people.
You can do whatever you want and they've really helped a lot of people.
They're high quality.
No matter what the product is, they're all excellent.
And on top of it, our mission is absolutely clear.
And so I understand that it's kind of passé now because I was like, okay, Jones told
us all this.
It came true.
Okay.
Thank you, Jones.
What do we do?
Well, we have to continue fighting into the future.
So it's really up to you whether we stay on air or not.
It's up to you whether we're able to reach out to new people.
So I know you already know all this stuff, but think about the new people and then just
understand how important it is.
You buy products at m4store.com.
They're amazing products that make your life better and they fund the M4, a 360 win.
So think about where we are and what you've done in front of this operation.
In advertising classes, they could break down how this is an effective call to action.
Here's what I'm seeing in my mind's eye.
End of season one of Mad Men, Don Draper is looking at that carousel and he's thinking,
I'm going to say everything Alex Jones is saying in this one right here.
Hey, look, I'm not telling you what to do.
You can not buy a Kodak.
Look, if you don't want to see these pictures, that's up to you.
I mean, we all like seeing pictures, but some people don't.
I mean, that's fine.
I'm a proud man.
To a certain point, so many qualifications, so many constant like, listen, you don't have
to do this.
I heard that and I thought, who is in charge of quality control?
I don't know.
Who's in charge of like any of that could have gone?
Here's what you could have done.
Are you so desperate for something to be four minutes long to fit like in a break?
The only explanation.
Yeah, because there was a lot of fat in there.
There was not a lot of substance and you know what you can do?
You can edit the video.
None of it at the end relates to what he said at the beginning.
At no point in time in his call to action, please go buy from Infowars store.
Do you need the added context of four years ago he was in a custody battle?
Nor do you need the second minute.
You don't need any.
Just cut it out.
Yeah.
Cool.
I think he's having problems with employment.
I think maybe he does not have the most capable hands on deck.
I think maybe he has very few hands period.
So we get in this next clip here.
We get to Alex getting actually down to business and you know I think that you see him complaining
about Maxine Waters and Hillary Clinton and straight but we also see what I think is going
to be the direction moving forward and how Alex is going to try and cope with the end
of the Trump season I guess and the only way I can express it really is I feel like we're
back in 2009.
And they are projecting the union psychology of the shadow onto you period.
You think Maxine Waters likes her evil ugly ass?
No.
What?
You think Nadler likes his evil ugly ass?
No.
You think Hillary likes her evil twisted butt?
Maybe?
But she projects it on you because these people are not retrospective and they cannot look
within themselves.
Introspective.
Wow.
Alex.
Knowing thyself is the highest order.
Then you can know God.
Alex.
Once you know yourself.
But if you don't know yourself you don't know anything.
Know thyself first.
These people do not know who they are.
They don't even know where they came from or where they're going.
They just want to pull down everything good.
So just as night follows day and day follows night they are preparing massive false flags
in this country to blame us and they're going to try to move against us and they're going
to do it because they never got in trouble for all the things they did before.
Because the corrupt lawyer run justice department is so full of pedophiles and corrupt people
they literally existentially want to make a run at the American gun owner and the American
Christian and they're going to do it.
There's an overwhelming sense on this episode of feeling like exactly like the narratives
of 2009.
Yeah.
They're coming for your guns.
Guns.
They're coming for a false flag to make us look bad.
Totally.
It's just it was exhausting on a certain level because it was just like I feel like we've
been here before.
Yeah.
And if you were somebody who was listening to his show like I don't understand how you
wouldn't be like hey you've played this song before.
Yeah.
Well I mean you know Fox News is going hard on hating immigrants now too so everybody's
trying to step back and be like remember when we could just be racist for fun?
Come on guys.
This is going well.
Yeah.
I think that there's a difference with Alex though and that is that he's playing this
game that he played before with the same intensity before and it didn't come true before.
True.
So or what if he just said it did?
Yeah I guess that is an option.
So it's going to be psych warfare.
They're going to false flag.
Of course.
We've seen it all.
The warrior run Justice Department is so full of pedophiles and corrupt people they literally
existentially want to make a run at the American gun owner and the American Christian and they're
going to do it but they're going to do it first through psychological operations and
it's going to be bad.
It's going to be rough and you better get yourselves ready for it and you better know
what the different scenarios are that are going to unfold out of this and I'll cover
it all when we come back.
Separately.
We're not going to be on the air unless we have your support plus we've got great products
that everybody already needs.
You just did four minutes of a rambling nonsense commercial.
Sure but I mean that commercial was great.
Did you hear that?
That was what 10 seconds tops?
It goes on from there.
Oh well there we go.
Never mind.
There's a bit I'm not playing for you.
Damn it.
Where he talks about winter sun being awesome.
Okay.
But yeah I mean like you know you have this false flags are absolutely coming.
They're all going to take a run at the gun owners and Christians.
They hate all that is good and you know hey we got good products.
It's just classic ad pivot business.
It's just not fair.
They just shouldn't be allowed to just be like okay these past four years we had a grand
old time, ran rough shot all over your bullshit, killed a lot of people and destroyed essentially
anybody's faith in democracy.
Anyways we're going to go back to just being mad about regular stuff now.
Is that fine?
We're just going to do what we did back then.
You guys seem to like us more back then right?
We're going to crawl in a little hole.
The angry tea party type us again.
Oh I don't like immigrants.
Hey doesn't everybody like the stakes being lower I guess?
Well yeah everything has pretend deescalated.
Like I thought Biden was the devil.
He was the devil.
I thought the whole idea of him getting into office was an existential threat to literally
everybody because he's controlled by China which is controlled by the devil and also
the devil's controlling a whole bunch of other things.
But like Alex reveals how he and his staff talk about Biden and it's like you wouldn't
talk this way if you actually thought he was the devil.
And so I remember on that same conversation on January 8th with some of my crew, some
of the managers, they said well don't be too down Alex.
You know once Trump's out and everybody doesn't think everything's fine we'll have even more
listeners because people are going to hate Biden.
And I said you mark my words as soon as that inauguration is over and Biden's sworn in
up there people are actually going to give up and they're going to actually fall away
to a great extent.
That's OK because we've got a bigger number than we had 20 years ago or even 10 years
ago or even five years ago but all the sunshine patriots aren't winter soldiers they're not
going to be involved.
They wanted to be part of the fantasy but it doesn't matter.
So Alex and his managers have a conversation and the conversation goes along the lines
of they think it's going to be good for business that Biden's in office and Alex says no people
are going to lose interest.
That's the way they're talking about this behind the scenes that's how they're processing
this.
Whether or not this is good for business it has nothing to do with their pretend nonsense
about Biden being the fucking devil.
All that is performance.
Anybody who thinks otherwise is I mean deluded.
Now at the same time there is a real world implication of a lot of this stuff and that's
where this discussion of how there's false flags coming up where that becomes really
important and I have some thoughts about that.
Guaranteed.
100 percent confirmed.
They've done it before.
They stand to gain from it.
They have a history of doing it.
They have the means they have the motive and they are now pre-programming at a level I
haven't ever seen even before 9-11 even before Oklahoma City even before other events that
right wingers are going to engage in terror attacks mass shootings bombings everywhere
and then anyone that's pro-America or anyone that's pro-gun or anyone that's pro-life is
a terrorist and they're going to try to get the general
public then in mass the same ones that wear the mask the same ones that do what they're
told to then literally in a Maoist revolution not work with us not talk to us and actually
physically attack us and they've already beta tested the whole thing.
When Alex talks like this generally what you should take away from that is he recognizes
that he and his entire information economy their information space have made things too
hot.
Yep.
They've got things too hot and stuff's gonna bubble over and they need a preemptive justification
and narrative for it.
That is all you need to hear when Alex says I guarantee false flags are coming.
That means hey Trump has an impeachment trial starting on Tuesday there's probably going
to be some fucked up shit that ends up happening.
Our people have been radicalized to the point of no return thinking that he had the election
stolen from him a narrative that I have been instrumental in pushing and we need to make
sure that all this is fake if it does happen.
Yeah.
It's very sad.
It's not just sad it's I mean perhaps not legally criminal but at the very least morally
debased.
Yes.
Yeah.
I would say so.
And it's woefully transparent too.
When you watch enough of him and you see these behavioral patterns it just becomes really
obvious that I'm not saying that like Stuart Rhodes called him and said I know someone's
gonna do something.
No no no yeah.
That would be conspiratorial and very irresponsible to suggest.
But I think that Alex knows well enough to read you know the signs that are out there.
I would suggest that it's more just chatter.
Alex is Alex is plugged into enough chatter where you're like a lot of this is too hot
I can see you somebody out there doing something.
He claims he reads the comments on Info Wars.
Yeah exactly.
So that should be some indication of the public temperature.
Some people are talking.
Yeah yeah exactly.
If he even does that.
Right.
But even if you don't like you don't even need to go that far to say chatter you could
just say like look at the scenario look at the world look at what's happening.
Look at what just happened a few weeks ago.
Sure.
Yeah.
There was a bombing on Christmas morning.
Oh yeah.
Anyway I think that that is what's going on and that is the big push that I was talking
about being like what Alex's content and his stuff is going to be moving forward.
It's going to be a lot of that like return to 2009 and then really really stress that
there's a fault there's false flags coming and that's just to do preemptive damage control
for people in those pro-Trump communities should anyone take violent action.
Absolutely.
So all the other moves in the past that the globalist have made all just leading up to
this move.
This move right now.
This one.
This is a false flag that will lead to the civil war that will lead to dominoes.
I have a quick question before we go any further.
What happened to Plan B?
He didn't say that.
Oh.
And Harrison Smith doesn't work at influence.
Well shit.
In case you don't realize it they're making their big move all the other moves were probes
all the other moves were tests all the other moves were just beta.
This is the main assault.
They're going to blow up federal buildings they're going to shoot up colleges churches
schools malls.
Then why didn't you tell us that all the other ones.
They're going to dump chemical weapons in lakes in reservoirs they're just going to
be terror attack on terror attack as the globalist chai combat combine takes America down and
causes a civil war.
Yeah so all the other everything was prelude.
All of the other ones all of the ones that I have screamed at you for 25 years being
the most important ones that have ever happened it turns out all of them were just probes?
Yeah.
Alright.
Curious Minds might ask is it possible that you're wrong this time too?
No no no no he's only been wrong every time for 25 years.
Is it possible that you have a currency bias that you think whatever is happening now is
literally the most important thing?
Could be.
So the dominoes Jordan are essentially false flag tips over right?
Sure.
And then it goes off and then it's used to make patriots and right wingers look bad so
the public turns against them.
Do we need help with that?
Seems redundant after the storming of the Capitol.
I think we already did it.
So that goes down and then there's a civil war but the civil war is only to like collapse
the United States.
Sure.
And then death camps.
Okay.
This is all meant to trigger the civil war that's the goal so the false flag triggers
the war on American patriots that triggers the civil war and the breakup of the country
and the end of the dollar which they plan to have done in a year.
And Biden's the symbol of the dying old America who will carry it out he will then step down
once America collapses.
We're about one year out from the end of the country completely.
Well that seems unfair.
We're a year away from death camps.
You just get to step down after you've destroyed the country there's no like fanfare he's just
like I'm out of here guys.
I mean I'm sure it wouldn't be you know the smoothest exit.
Listen folks I got a cabin I'm gonna get out of here.
I gotta go.
This place is a shithole by the way.
Um yeah I think this is nonsensical and it's also deeply irresponsible to tell your already
terrified and paranoid and gullible ass audience that you're a year away from death camps because
of fucking Joe Biden.
Why in God's name would somebody bother with a false flag whenever you just said that you're
a year away from death camps so you should be out and out being like we gotta terrorize
these people otherwise we're gonna be in a death camp.
I mean yeah it's you know terrorist edging mixed with terrorist pre-rationalization and
denial.
Absolutely.
But there's other folks in the past who have had death camps and Alex is a scholar on the
matters.
I disagree.
Hitler got into power in 1933 he wasn't sending people to death camps until 1942.
Oh.
He was sending people to prison.
Oh wow.
First he took the job.
Holy shit.
He wouldn't let them have businesses put them in ghettos but that's how this works.
So Alex doesn't know anything about Hitler's rise to power as he fully demonstrated a couple
episodes back but this attempt at rewriting Holocaust history is really upsetting.
Yeah this is not good.
According to the United States Holocaust Memorial Museum quote the first concentration camps
in Germany were established soon after Hitler's appointment as Chancellor in January 1933.
After the Night of Long Knives the purge of the SA that took place between June 30th and
July 2nd 1934 Hitler assigned Heinrich Himmler to formalize the system of camps that was
going on.
The camps that were primarily for the purpose fully of extermination did come later but
even if you want to give Alex the most generous interpretation possible Operation T4 started
in January 1940 which is aimed at the systematic killing of people with disabilities in Germany.
Alex's claim that the Nazis weren't sending people to death camps until 1942 is probably
just him knowing that that's the year that Operation Reinhard began when the Nazis attempted
to kill all the Jews in Poland.
There's a larger picture that he's unaware of or weirdly ignoring and this should be
another signifier that Alex has absolutely no idea about the reality of world history
nor does he have any respect for majorly traumatizing and traumatic world events.
He should never be taken seriously as claiming to know anything.
Yeah yeah no and it's not just that he's and it's not even like he wants to remain ignorant
or he doesn't want to learn things it's that he actively wants to go out of his way to
learn and propagate things that did not happen in order to justify his bullshit now so anything
he says about history is said entirely to be like it's totally okay for me to do whatever
I want today has nothing to do with anything.
Yeah it's and it's false depictions of yeah of like very very serious things and it's
I mean that's disgusting that's just wild yeah fuck him fuck him so you know how Hillary
Clinton projects her shadow her Jungian shadow on people she doesn't like her butt is that
an important thing that I've heard her and Nadler and Maxine Waters all don't like their
but they don't like their butts so they project this Jungian shadow on you so they think that
you're bad because that's their Jungian shadow that they see on you but that's really them
for Alex to say somebody else is projecting it's it's very rude well Alex he admits it
he projects his shadow on people too okay good and that's why he thinks that everybody
else is good at fucking oh I project my shadow on people I think people are powerful and
amazing and have incredible ideas and are have an incredible sexual prowess and amazing
dynamics and are just meant to build civilizations and and love freedom and justice but I've
learned not to project what I believe and who I am on to others I can only hope now
I love myself we know I have written a poem of myself to myself yeah there are no snakes
under your bed I have learned not to project myself onto others I can only hope that everyone
is as good at sex as me there is nothing wrong with masturbating you are very good at sex
you do not masturbate at all what a doofus what a fine moron yeah unreal so now now
we get to one of my favorite types of moments and I think it's this is let's let's just
really like boil down his projection his understanding of Jungian shadows yeah comes down to Maxine
Waters doesn't like her butt I have a huge dick I think metaphorical butt no I know I
understand but metaphorically speaking Alex is literally talking about his sexual prowess
he is literally talking about his sexual prowess with Maxine Waters it was just the butt you
know she doesn't like her stinking butt she hates her butt I love my dick it's a metaphor
with one it's literal with the other maybe it is so this next clip is my favorite kind
of shit this is where Alex I think kind of forgets what he's talking about sure forgets
he's on air then tells an incredibly depressing story and a story that makes him look pretty
bad he does not kill another dog no no no dog killing okay good I want to take your
calls and listen listen like coming to somebody and saying hey you need to go home we just
got a call you're not answering your phone your dad just got killed in a car wreck or
I don't like getting a call and going and telling a family member hey grandma's dead
this was already really confusing as as a jumping off point but hold hold on hold on
to your horse all right he doesn't like bad news doesn't like to give it doesn't like
to get it doesn't like to do it it's unfortunate gotcha
but it's our job to do this and if we're not honest yeah I had to see my grandmother in
probably six months my dad's mom gosh I guess she's been gone my son was two years old he's
18 now so I guess she's been gone a year and a half old like 17 plus years so close and
I called my dad that afternoon before she died the next day and I said we got to go
see me ma he goes you know funny you said that I feel like we need to go see her and
then I was on coast to coast am till like four in the morning and my dad got there like
seven he said let's go I was laying there on the bed came to my house I said back then
I was younger I couldn't get out of bed when I was tired now I didn't have no problem doing
it preparing myself to get up instantly and I said no no no and I went finally got up
and I had a beer for breakfast and I had one more for dessert because I was really tired
and only had like two hours sleep what is happening I'm just joking and then I got in
the car on Rabiness Texas and 30 minutes before I get there he calls and says I just got there
when she died and you missed it see so there's that invisible internet that the enemy knows
about spiritual and they are so pissed they want to control it they don't they'll never
dominate us what the fuck is going on man so let me break down that story because first
of all he wasn't joking when he said he was drunk absolutely not get the fuck out of here
just realized that like oh this looks really bad shouldn't have said I drank a beer at
seven whoops and then another one for dessert and then another one for dessert and then
I drove Jesus Christ what is happening I mean the real the real like headline of that story
is I missed saying goodbye to my grandma because I was drinking in the morning well you could
say that that's the answer to that because your dad was there at the house he was he
got there on time but you decided to stick around and have a drink while beers yeah before
you drive yeah in the morning looks bad Alex it doesn't look good no just don't tell stories
like that don't tell stories at all no and I don't know how this connects to an invisible
internet that everybody has I guess he thinks that because they got it they were like let's
go visit her and then she died coincidentally and they were like oh we just got this psychic
idea that she was going to die soon yeah but again even if that's true yeah Alex you were
up and you just drank beer in the morning and then drove to visit her this is a story
about you ignoring psychic powers it would be yeah yeah yeah it would be a story about
you believing that your psychic powers were less important than your desire to have a
breakfast beer I gotta listen listen I I had a rough one I stayed up till four I gotta
drink a Guinness in the morning to get going yeah look George Norie was chewing my ear
off last night exactly talking about ghosts or something oh my god so anyway that was
a little bit weird yeah but now we get into what I'm gonna call Alex's main breakdown
of the Super Bowl okay okay I forgot the Super Bowl happened yeah he doesn't talk about the
halftime show or any of that stuff nearly as much as you might think wow because there's
another thing it's too obviously satanic there's a no I don't think so there's just another
thing that's a little more important okay and that's Alex is racism so Tom Brady won
his seventh Super Bowl and they're just calling him a cross between Hercules and Apollo he's
being worshipped but again it's only a game at the end of the day but we understand that
human competition and human striving is what makes us great so in a way it's very wholesome
men competing against each other women competing against each other but on to this they add
all the globalism they add the propaganda they add the anti-family the racial separation
messages what so they know you hunger for this competition oh what now and then they
show the so-called black quarterback oh what now the Kansas team the Kansas City team oh
what now this is about as wide as I am and the media says it's racist that Tom Brady
won oh that means Ronald McDonald's black too he's got curly hair oh boy oh boy oh boy
it is absolutely not racist that Tom Brady won what that was was racist oh yeah Alex
while Alex once again has put on one of his famous hats that is the I get to decide people's
race hat yeah yeah suppose wow wow this is this is ugly it goes on quite a while that's
wild so the media didn't say that the game was racist Alex is just pointing to a bunch
of anonymous people on Twitter who posted jokes about a black quarterback losing during
Black History Month and then pretending that it's a serious argument the media is making
I grant that a lot of people rightly don't like Tom Brady because he's a dick but this
angle that Alex is taking is stupid it's based on literally nothing and it's deeply deeply
racist very racist it gets so much worse yeah if you are if you are like oh I hate it when
the media points out racism in the wrong way right but your defense of that is to get more
racist huh I don't think the first part happened at all and I think you just want an excuse
to be racist I think it feels that I feel it feels a lot like that it feels like you
just really don't like black quarterbacks because of one Colin Kaepernick and so any
chance you have to be like oh the media blows whatever yeah I think that's oversimplifying
it because we could you can even greater oversimplify and just say Alex is a fucking huge racist
wow there's definitely that it's not even about Kaepernick it pre-existed that that
is true that is true and also it has to do with vegetables sure all of it is the attempt
to project onto anything and everything going on racial division remember AOC said don't
grow cauliflower she saw cauliflower growing at a New York community garden and she said
it's white cauliflower is from Africa you dumb monster what does it matter what color
it is whether it's purple or black or brown or green or red if it tastes good as nutritious
but that's total mental illness ladies and gentlemen we've talked about this before but
just because it's relevant here's the full quote quote what I love too is growing plants
that are culturally familiar to the community it's so important so that's really how you
do it right that's such a core component of the green new deal is having all these projects
make sense in a cultural context and it's an area that we get the most pushback on because
people say why do you need to do that that's too hard but when you really think about it
when someone's saying it's too hard to do a green space that grows yucca instead of
I don't know cauliflower or something what you're doing is taking a colonial approach
to environmentalism that's why a lot of communities of color get resistant to certain environmentalist
movements because they come with a colonial lens on them yeah this is not about cauliflower
being white it has nothing to do with that but see one the thing the reason that I read
that quote again even though we've talked about this is because you wouldn't cover this
that way you wouldn't cover this the way Alex is covering it unless you had a vested interest
in trying to create a white victimhood argument for your racist audience to enjoy yeah and
that's kind of exactly what he's doing with the Super Bowl too and it's bad I mean it's
real bad it's hard not to look at all of these things because it's it's so awful how these
people think of just like oh there's no way that this thing could be racist that's just
silly you're just making a mountain out of a molehill you know but if you actually just
listen to what people are saying and then look into it you can find like the tiniest
things are built on a fucking mountain of racism yeah and if you look into it if you
would be interested and if you would be curious about it you might find holy shit there's
racism under all this stuff that I would think oh the penny you think the penny's racist
and you probably look into it and it fucking is you know like it's that kind of shit and
it might not be but you should take people's word and like it'd be interesting yeah I don't
know I think I think that a lot of folks are guilty of this I mean it's the sound biting
of of culture and information transfer sure but the people do it out of laziness sometimes
and out of racism sometimes yeah and a bunch of other motivations but never forget you
can do it both ways yeah yeah so but I think and the intersection there is that Alex is
racist and he's also super lazy because he's really just reading a Paul Joseph Watson article
because Paul Joseph Watson knows that his audience eats this stuff up so they like the
thing that I kept thinking while I was listening to this is like these dicks thought this was
worth their time I saw Paul Joseph Watson article this morning at info wars.com saying
Tom Brady winning Super Bowl is racist oh this is a joke so I read about 20 tweets by
black people saying it I didn't believe it I went to their accounts they were serious
and I read hundreds more ooh they said it's so insulting he beat a black man there was
a lot of black men helped Tom Brady win that Super Bowl and I'm telling you they were black
folks whoa the quarterback I guess it's a gimmick kind of like who's the leader one
of the founders of Black Lives Matter he's totally white what is happening got that other
white lady said she was black and she said have one drop of African in her I mean what
are we doing this is insane do you think you're winning because you know Brady had at least
like a half white team with the New England Patriots oh god it's white people winning
but is his Buccaneers teams almost all black what the hell does it even matter what color
he is but this is the mental illness I thought the tweets had to be a joke but it's all about
the fact that he wasn't ashamed of President Trump who was a fan before he was president
you seem to be the one who's upset you seem very upset very upset ridiculously over-the-top
upset and pretty racist very race and then once they slaughtered him I didn't even watch
the end of it because it was just such a collapse by the other team and they're like look the
black quarterbacks losing dude that other quarterback had whiter skin than I do I just
I'll curl my hair and say I'm black oh it doesn't even matter it's like what the hell
does that have to do with anything what color a quarterback is it's actually it's how good
they play why if Tom Brady was a black guy he would be just as famous or probably more
so and I would still think he was an amazing quarterback I see I challenge personal successes
not just like oh my skin's pink but that's mental illness ladies and gentlemen talk about
colors I like there's nobody green my dad knows that he gave me a green watch maybe
I'm a Martian I mean I got a purple shirt on folks and I like purple people like eggplant
this is mental illness ladies and gentlemen I got a black microphone what does that mean
I like how it looks what's back in the day nobody had black microphones everybody copies
me don't know what's going on anymore I don't know what's happening what was that what was
that I don't know if your uncle started at a certain point you put rolls in your uncle's
mouth to keep him from talking I would I am honestly confused by his idea that everyone's
ripping him off with black microphone I'm just I just don't know I think that it's that
is all just about rush used to have a gold microphone and Alex is trying to like be like
I was different sure something I don't know that's that's a startlingly racist thing that
he's oh wow yeah and now he goes back to complete comparing Mahomes to Sean King and Rachel
Dolezal and man this is just this is it's not good no it's not good but I know you all
know that but it's the way they project yeah what's that idiot's name Sean King no African
blood I mean just look at him boy takes on identity of black people so you can raise
hundreds of millions of dollars and then who's the other lady the blonde haired lady that
like frizzes her hair out and puts puts what's her name Rachel dolls are yeah I mean it's
sick folks it's absolutely sick and it's mentally ill but but I'm digressing I'm almost out
of time this segment I wanted to illustrate let's just keep rolling it Tom Brady knows
that it's not as bad as the flu or pneumonia knows that it's a hoax refuses to wear his
mask at the beginning after the game and they're so mad and he did that on purpose that makes
me like Tom Brady way more than the fact that he is the greatest of all time no doubt in
the NFL he's now the greatest of all time not being a coward like the other white dude
posing as a black dude on the other team that got his ass ran over maybe if you'd had a
black quarterback you would have not lost I got some real black quarterbacks and another
quarterbacks great that right there is the tell that Alex is racist trolling oh yeah
that right there when he's laughing is like other quarterbacks actually pretty you know
he's pretty good that's the that is the signifier but my point is me like throwing passes when
he's being tackled that people are catching yeah I mean look at this ladies and gentlemen
there's Rachel dozell or whatever the hell her name is but this is all the global is
trying to get us to in-fight with each other yeah there's the quarterback and I mean you
know he's look at that look at that hair he's getting that curled folks he's in there hours
a week getting it all like that so he can say he's black what was his great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great-granddaddy
black this is where we realize that Alex doesn't realize that Mahomes dad was a professional
baseball player yeah yeah he's not very interested in that this is now this is wildly racist
to a to adjust just I'm amazed that you can keep going I feel like you already nailed
your racism and you you're done you know like he said he might as well just be like I don't
believe anybody's black if I don't want them to and then you're done Alex is white you
finished Alex is white insecurity and his white identity got it really alarmed by people
making jokes about Mahomes losing during Black History Month and the only way that he could
deal with that is to do an outrageously racist segment on his show yeah that goes on and
on and on where he tries to be the arbiter of saying that he's not actually even black
yeah to what end is this I am confused yeah I am very confused by um I don't know just
the continued existence of the universe in a certain to a certain extent you know like
part of me is like I don't understand how this country has made it as long as it has
if it is rewarded this moron so much you know like there's there's a fundamental confusion
I get from listening to this of just like how who why what are we doing I don't know
what are we doing so Alex plays a clip of Joe Biden has he had a little message before
the Super Bowl see that's what sorry sorry I have to this is what I this is what got
to me this is what I realized was screwing with my head apologies for interrupting sure
and derailing this entire problem where I'm fired I get it no problem I I remember something
important happening right now that a sophisticated news political show would talk about and that
is not Tom Brady at depth it's the president that he thinks is God is being impeached have
you like is there anything have you seen my home's hair though Alex needs to talk about
it you can't be that mad about the devil being the president so Biden gave a little bit of
a little message you're right in a moment of silence for the people lost to COVID-19
yeah at the Super Bowl and Alex has a video of it where it sounds like people are booing
Biden sure it's unclear if this video is authentic because there are other videos that don't
really have you know there's like some applause and then some crowd noise sure but who cares
yeah I don't give a fuck I don't remember Alex reporting about how everyone booed the
shit out of Trump no that baseball game no that wasn't a big deal so anyway I don't care
but he does cover that and he's like ah look at this guy getting booed and then he gets
into his analysis of the commercials mostly just the Springsteen commercial it's Bruce
Springsteen riding around like he's John Wayne he supports taking your guns he supports breaking
it he supports transgender stuff in the bathrooms of your kids he hates Trump look it up oh
but now he's the good guy gonna bring you together he's Bruce Springsteen he's the spirit
of America here is this disgustingly condescending ad
four years ago I was in the middle of a custody battle there's a chapel in Kansas standing
on the exact center of the lower 48 it never closes all are more than welcome more companies
here in the middle I don't care for that ad myself but I don't think Alex has any right
to complain or critique commercials no it's uh it's a little bit uh obnoxious so Alex
had you know he said he's going to take some calls and so he gets around to it but he comes
in from break and the uh the the board op or maybe whoever it is tries them with a little
bit of Elvis oh so we are just counting down here counting down oh is this Elvis let's
hear a little bit of this we're counting down to the false flag next hour I'm gonna premiere
the proof of them coming for you and me he doesn't at least you know they're coming little
less talk a little more action wrong so I guess that's what the left wants to give us
emergency alert bubbles preparing massive false flags so pretext for soviet-style purge
watch live and just watch it all happen so this Elvis song that is not a little more
a little less conversation a little more action it's just let yourself go yeah this gets Alex
into a little bit of a mood and he starts rambling you know he's been mad about black
people and white people playing football so it's nice to listen to music whoever white
man stealing black people's music it's nice yeah and that makes Alex that makes him want
to kill I mean the shotgun shack in the middle of the woods my lady listen to this
real tight enjoy yourself and baby don't fight I'm gonna stop being bad I'm not gonna drink
any I'm joking oh let ourselves go in a war too that gonna be fun a little bit still war
kind of the same type of deal isn't it whoa what's going on nobody's scared no more except
those people that are dying when the killers come when the killers come when the dying
starts when the praying to mommy starts don't look like the left's much ready for a war
but they sure want one cuz they ain't ever been in one all right now they're gonna play
that old bumper music that's how I like me some Elvis I apologize for ranting here we
got Catherine we got Pastor Sam we got Harry we got Tyler we got Terry we got Kevin we
got Steve we got James we got Chris we got Mike and Russell we got 20-something callers
and I said I want seven on that board because I don't want to keep people on hold but let's
just go to them now while we sit here waiting for that big old juicy false flag terror attack
so they can start that civil war and break this country up real nice I think Alex might
have had a meeting with somebody in the bathroom yeah yeah that's yeah buddy got a little bit
of a little pep in his step so he takes so his first caller is a guy who calls in all
the time named Pastor Sam and one of the things that I find really interesting about Alex's
techniques with callers is he creates false conflict with them often whenever they disagree
with him on like a minute point he'll create a false fight with them to sort of frame their
position in a certain way that he can respond to that doesn't allow the nuance of the the
matter to be dealt with in this case Alex had made some comments about how you know
if the gun confiscators come you don't want to be at home you don't want to start a fight
with the police because that's you know that's how the whole civil war is going to start
if you end up doing that no you got to target the the high level globalist sure sure sure
sure and Pastor Sam's position is more like if they're coming to take our guns then it's
it's already past the point you would think and and and that nuance is dangerous for Alex
to have because it hurt his brain well and it would it would it requires that his actual
positions sound a lot more like aggressively and immediately violent than he wants them
to and then he thinks can be profitable so he starts a fight but don't worry we got patriots
think it's time for war too Pastor Sam I see you strongly disagree with me this is not
the time to lie down you know Pastor Sam I didn't say lie down I said if the cops are
coming to confiscate guns at your house it's a good idea to not be waiting for them and
kill them because they've been brainwashed I get it a certain point it's going to start
up here but uh well it's not lying down I'm saying the target isn't the police so if they
get the police to come for our guns I'm a big boy I'm a smart boy then I would want
to go after which I'm not saying do the actual people that were running the show nice save
there you call that lying down tell me Pastor Sam how to be a man tell me how to do it well
I know you said to dispense with the niceties but first I'm going to tell you tell me how
to be a man Sam I'm going to tell you that I love you and that I'm a prayer partner for
what you're doing and I I've followed you for 20 years yeah so Alex is he's created
this tone that is completely artificial with this call so there's no hope of any point
actually being discussed and there isn't it just goes nowhere that sounds about right
yep uh so he goes to another call and this person has a very very easy to answer question
okay Catherine in Canada you're on the air welcome hi there hi Alex how are you I'm
all right go ahead welcome okay I want to make a point about the January 6th event for
all these people that think there was just Trump supporters for five years there was
a counter protest at every Trump event I just want to ask these people that want to explain
from people where was their counter protest that day people in those communities felt
very strongly that it would be too dangerous yeah they dissuaded people from taking part
because they didn't want people to more people to be killed yeah they were like hey stay
away these people are violent Trump supporters might kill people at this thing and then they
were roundly mocked and then Trump supporters killed people at that thing so yeah I mean
it's a question it's a super easy to answer question yes this is not the first time that
this has happened there were greatly diminished counter protesting that happened at the gun
rally in Virginia yeah the the one that Alex went to and they tried to be very insightful
at in the sighting at not insightful yeah yeah that that happens sometimes the counter
protest folk I believe prioritize safety they like to live yeah and and a lot of times those
people will be a little bit more responsible and in the case of January 6th there was pretty
pretty consistent messaging that I saw from people that that I'm aware of that this is
not a good thing to go counter demonstrate what I'd like to know what I'd like to know
is where were the counter protesters at the thing that we said was going to be a violent
display of our power yeah the implication of course is that they were mixed in the crowd
of course but that's all bullshit so I you know Alex is yelling doing this fake fighting
with his calls and I'm like this guy is fucked up I think he's I think he's doing speed yeah
it's so hard for me when I'm cutting ads and I get overly excited agree people ask me all
the time they go Jones are you on cocaine or you want meth yeah are you so excited why
are you starting another ad if people are always asking you if you're on drugs there's
a decent chance you're on drugs oh and when you go on Joe Rogan's show and Joe Rogan
asks you about how you told him that you have a problem with Adderall well that's a little
bit well that one's a little bit more like the pictures are starting the pictures starting
to come into focus yeah we had a real rough start of this show and now the energy is flying
high yeah that's so almost like someone took something yeah it's all because usually as
you work throughout the day you get more tired you know and maybe I and I've had this happen
before Dan have you ever been working for like six hours right yeah and you know you
got some more work to do but right around that six hours you're just so tired and you
could just really use a pick-me-up you know sure so you go get a cup of coffee or you
go into the bathroom and you snort some rails you do what you gotta do to make it through
the last two hours dad I'm not saying that that is the case but I'm really coming around
on the idea that he's on drugs yeah like it just it makes a lot of sense and I think the
fact that Rogan asked him that question really really makes me a bit more open to the idea
because why would Rogan bring that up if it wasn't something that Alex had brought up
with him and it's and it sounded like it was coming from a place of genuine concern as
well passion yes friendship yep yep hey I don't want you to keep hurting yourself man
yeah yeah and yeah and there we are and Alex keeps saying that everybody insists he's on
drugs everybody keeps saying that I'm taking these two drugs that I consistently write
you know and it's just like oh yeah I take a little coke and a little meth but you do
a little bit of each that way you don't have to do as much look give me a cup I'm pissing
it now um so I got like I told you at the beginning of this I got really excited because
Alex said he's gonna have Jay Dyer on yes and they're gonna talk this guy is the guy
who's the primary source reader right and all this I immediately lost all respect oh
no what would you call this period of time we're in right now I think it's pretty clear
they're getting they're saying patriots are terrorists they're gonna arrest us all we're
about to stage terror attacks clearly they're getting ready to stage terror attacks in my
view do you agree with that and what would you call this period of time we're in and
what are you doing to get ready for it because every few generations goes through some real
tyranny we're about to go through a big one this is the age of transition right this is
their phraseology for how we go from the way things were during this Christian period of
the age of you know Pisces the age of the fish to the Aquarian Age which is what Blavatsky
right one of the esoteric philosophers that the elite always like to look to she called
this the externalization of the hierarchy holy shit go tell Carrie Cassidy about it
no shit oh god now my worldview is based on this woman from the 1830s who thought she
could do magic Jesus and my fear that other people have learned to do magic from her you
know the problem that I'm having look he's a moron that's to be expected the problem
that I'm having is Jay Dyer is a great DJ name it's such a great DJ name yeah I would
love to be Jay Dyer that's so good you know Jay Dilla is great Jay Dyer is great it'd
be awesome to have a collaboration with his ghost because apparently Jay Dyer believes
that those ghosts can talk to oh yeah oh yeah yeah Edgar Casey can connect me with DJs of
the past through David Wilcock spirit you do not need to do any voices yeah you don't
need to do scratching on the record okay so this next clip Jordan I don't really care
about him and Dyer's interview it is dumb yeah no I've already whenever you start when
you start with Helena Blavatsky I'm out yeah I'm out yeah that's yeah that's kind of a
rule of mine you can have fun conversations with friends about these sorts of things and
you know we can we can talk about stuff but when you want to make me scared of your big
bad guy enemies and and insist that they follow the teachings of Helena Blavatsky yeah I'm
out that's like that's one step further than if somebody's like you know the Unabomber did
make some good points though I'm just look I know there's stuff you know I think it's
a little more fun because at least there's magic involved that's true anyway so Alex
gets to talking about Trump a little bit here and he says something that I find unacceptable
okay if you listen to this clip and you understand what Alex is saying the last five years of
Alex's life have been wrong uh-huh they've been meaningless yes and Alex has been an
instrumental part of the globalist plan to bring in tyranny does he know that I think
Trump meant well he was a nationalist he knew America was being screwed over but that the
establishment let him win he did win by landslide four years ago because they knew they could
run circles around him and use him to energize the left to basically commit any crime and
then support a total police state and abandon any values they had and I think that's clearly
evident now from from my perspective that at a sophisticated level we were all all played
wow so you are a useful idiot exactly like you claimed you were not to a guy three days
ago yeah I mean there's there's really no other way to interpret that because I mean
I guess the left wouldn't have been turned into whatever this is that would facilitate
tyranny if Clinton had won sure so I guess the only way to reach the point where actual
tyranny could happen Trump had to win right and Alex has said many many times that Trump
wouldn't have won if it wasn't for info it does seem like that and that would also heavily
imply that Roger Stone is working for the globalist Alex to hell yeah you know be this
bully pulpit for Trump yeah I'm you know what I could believe that or maybe Alex is making
all of this stuff up Dan yeah Alex is making all this stuff he might just be making it
all up yeah he's just spitballing and nothing he says means anything but if he were being
serious he would then have to the next thought should be and I should shut up yeah because
you quit yeah because clearly I make all the wrong decisions that laid us to this but this
is my fault in the last half a decade I have been leading you to tyranny exactly state
and I've made multiple documentaries with police state in the title I'm supposed to
know better exactly and not just that but you followed me to get to where we are meaning
I am the reason that we are where we are and I am a bad leader and you should not follow
me anymore now four years ago I was going through a divorce oh okay well now I'm back
on your side are you selling anything uh maybe wait around for three minutes we'll find out
we'll see we'll see look we got one last clip here okay and it's like I think everybody
kind of expected there to be more talk about the Super Bowl halftime show as opposed to
Alex just being racist sure but that's every time when you think he's gonna zig he zogs
that's what he does um so he uh he talks about the halftime show a tiny bit with Jay Dyer
and like this clip is just titled stupid talk about halftime show because this is stupid
but you were mentioning to me did you see that halftime show and I I don't normally
watch Super Bowl because I knew Tom Brady wouldn't be wearing a mask I know I like him
I watched it they're all wearing a skull mask they're subhuman but the one guy has speech
and they all like puppets do what he says this was very sick at a subconscious level
it means you are robots in a fascist event you are skeletons you are dead I control you
exactly a lot of things going on here symbolically speaking it began with this choir of robots
drones right so everybody's up in the in the choir with the weekend guy they're singing
and they're all just sort of doing what they're like you know puppets like they're they're
on a marionette right I just my response to all of this kind of conversation is like if
you guys are just high kicking around like a hacky sack and this is the conversation
you want to have great but if you're adults on a presumably grown-up news world events
radio show that you very seriously this is unbecoming yeah this kind of conversation
is laughably stupid oh oh oh you're all drones and only the weekend has a voice yeah and
the only people who should be allowed to publicly discuss the semiotics of this event would
be somebody it would be like Umberto Eco who could be like I'm gonna put this in the context
of all of this others but even then it's a fucking Super Bowl halftime show guys go go
to bed here's the thing go to bed here's the thing that I want to ask as a rhetorical question
but I also want an answer these types of things have been going on forever talking about the
symbology of halftime shows and the show ology of these music videos and all this shit yeah
I want to know these motherfuckers people like Jay Dyer they pretend that they study
this stuff uh-huh that it's like an actual field of totally of information I want concrete
examples of things that they've known in advance because of these symbols that they read in
music videos and halftime show Dan I would love it's all around you what the evidence
look out your window Dan see that's why that's the halftime that's why I wanted it to be
retort that's the Super Bowl halftime show I just want I just want to know what magical
like psychic revelations you get from oh also they took off the masks in the second song
in the performance oh but who cares oh who cares yeah I just I find this stuff really
dumb I used to really enjoy reading blogs that would talk about like people have cover
in one eye yeah sign of the Illuminati yeah when I was young yeah and I all the time has
any how many Super Bowl halftime shows are even memorable and none of them for their
semiotics Janet Jackson exactly that was not the semiotics of what she was wearing no the
Prince hologram won a couple years ago wasn't there that was kind of bad yeah right yeah
that's it who gives a shit about the halftime show it's a thing we talk about people like
Alex care a lot it's a thing we talk about every year for a day and then we're done just
let's just not talk about it for that day I think that there's a lot of potential for
like interesting performance I think that you know God bless people who you know really
really try choreographers are great and I think that I'm just aged out of the point
where I can get too excited about a lot of the musical acts but I can still appreciate
like I get it you know like I can watch the weekend's performance I can be like this is
not necessarily for me it's not my favorite thing but I get it look at him performing
the hell out of it sure yeah yeah it's it's fodder for people who have a tough time coming
up with things to talk about and for people like Alex who just need to be mad at something
and the Super Bowl is such a perfect thing in that wheelhouse for Alex because you have
the like sublimating of mail drives to war that he can complain about whatever symbology
is on the halftime show he can complain about and apparently the race of people and whether
or not they constitute being black according to Alex Jones which is fucking disgraceful
that is that is really disqualifying as like allowed in polite society ever again yeah
like you should be shunned like that that deserves a shunning it would be interesting
for someone to like sit down and try to explain to Alex exactly why that display was so flagrantly
racist yeah but I don't think he would understand I don't think it's possible I think he just
needs a good universal shunning everybody's shunned him I think most people have gotten
that message I think so too we need some more though Dan let's raise up the shunning sure
so alright we reached the end of this episode and Alex apparently did not enjoy the Super
Bowl yeah and I thought we were gonna get to the impeachment trial stuff today but because
it was Tuesday it got started sure that will come on the Friday episode we'll check in
see how Alex is handling all that stuff but I do think that this this episode is important
to go over because of the incredible racism Wow and because of the clear turn towards
really aggressively being like false flags are coming they are coming yeah coming I guarantee
they're going to happen yeah and you can't read that any other way than preemptive damage
control when it's coming from someone like Alex someone who is so invested in terrorist
edging yep and we'll be back on Friday to discuss impeachment business indeed we will
do I understand you were watching it today because I saw some tweets yeah I had some
fun uh Bruce Castor is I mean that was one of the most fundamentally disgraceful things
I've ever seen in my entire life bad argumentation no no argumentation just rambling gotta call
Barnes randomly just randomly just like hey you know what being a senator is pretty cool
you know we're we're extraordinary people here you know it'd be great like uh uh uh
Trump's lawyers are doing terribly right yeah out of nowhere he's here glass break Oh Barnes
come Barnes walking down oh man all the senators socially distance and he's high-fiving each
Republican just runs up to him Barnes kicks him in the gut gives him a stunner yeah absolutely
absolutely but Larry Klayman coming from the sting spot and drops down right on top about
yeah exactly that's WCW whatever sting and Hogan okay okay the rock I got it I got it
um anyway we'll be back indeed but uh tell them we've we do it's knowledgefight.com we're
also on Twitter we are on Twitter it's at knowledge we're fighting I go to bed Jordan
we're also on Facebook we are Facebook it's rude if you could please find a local charity
or bail fund in your area to help out people doing God's work right now yeah we're back
but until then I'm Neo I'm Leo I'm DZX Clark I'm Daryl Rundis I four years ago I was this
is an ad Andy in Kansas you're on the air thanks for holding hello Alex I'm a first
time caller I'm a huge fan I love your work I love you