N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys.
Dan and Jordan, knowledgefight.
Riddle Earth!
I need money.
Andy and Candice, Andy and Candice, Stop it.
Andy and Candice, Andy and Candice, Andy and Candice, It's time to pray.
Andy and Candice, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello Alex.
I am a huge fan.
I love your room.
Knowledgefight.com, knowledgefight.com.
Love you.
on knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes that surround technology beverages
and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are, Dan.
Jordan.
Dan.
Quick question for you.
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, Jordan, is mochi.
Ooh.
I've, I got.
You've recently discovered mochi.
Yes.
And it is expanded from there.
I am off.
Next year we will be doing 500 new tastes of mochi.
No.
Oh.
I don't think that would be possible.
It'd be pretty difficult.
But I've tried a number of flavors
that I've been able to get my hands on.
And man, it's so good.
The thing that was really tough for me
was that I'd heard such startlingly different reviews.
Sure, sure.
It's a divisive dessert.
Very much so.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I'd worried that I would fall squarely
in the gl-eh category, but I love it.
And it also, I didn't realize it,
but it just takes me back a bit to, like,
things that I had in Hawaii growing up.
Yeah, yeah.
And that makes total sense,
but I didn't think that it would.
Right, right, right, right.
And it's great, I love it.
So another dessert.
Great, another fucking sweet thing for me to eat.
Just what we needed.
The audience was like, what other sweet things
is Dan gonna become obsessed with?
What will capture Dan's sweet tooth today?
Fuck.
Good news is people won't be mailing those to you.
No, that is true, thank God.
Next thing you know, shit just comes in dry ice.
Start, start.
Dry ice.
Damn it!
And then just melted ones.
So yeah, Mochi, how about you?
Oh, my bright spot this week, Dan, is The Swordsman.
It's a Korean movie that's, I don't know, it's really good.
It's about three swordsmen, they do stuff, it's fantastic.
So it's swordsmen plural?
No, the movie is about singular.
Okay, so it's one of those three.
There are multiple that appear, yes indeed.
So it's like The Highlander,
there's more than one Highlander.
Yeah, absolutely.
Although there can only be one.
No, there's not more than one Highlander,
there's only one Highlander.
I mean, there are many people who live in the Highlands.
I thought that there was these immortals
and they have to kill each other.
Sure, of course they do, but the Highlander
specifically refers to that he's from Scotland.
Oh, that's right, Highlander isn't the group of them.
Yeah, yeah, and obviously as we all know
from just appearance and conversational style alone,
Sean Connery is indeed Egyptian in that movie.
And the original Bond.
And the original Bond, yes, we have discovered so much today.
Yeah, a lot of education, referencing things we Googled
just before getting on the show.
So Jordan, today we have an interesting thing to go over.
We're gonna be talking about February 10th and 11th, 2021.
Butt check!
I'll let you have that one.
You let me have that one, you son of a bitch.
Oh.
You son of a bitch.
I was still late,
cause I was halfway waiting for you to say it first.
I am disappointed in you because you had the open lane
and you still stutter stepped.
No, it's like, it's like,
You thought it was a trap.
It's Anthony Davis in the block, man.
You can feel him coming.
You just know, you're not gonna go for the layup
cause he's gonna swat it away from you.
I decided to hang back and just see what you had.
And then I blew it.
Yeah.
So that is Wednesday and Thursday of this week.
And the reason that I wanted to check in on this
is because of course the Trump impeachment is going on.
Sure.
We'll discuss some feelings about that.
Cause both of us have watched a bit of that.
Yeah.
Weirdly.
Way too much for no reason.
Yeah, I blame you cause I wasn't going to.
And then you texted me about it and I was like,
well, I'll watch a little bit of this.
And I'm like, oh my God.
It's surprisingly engrossing.
And at the same time, I'm like, this is stupid.
What am I doing?
Very conflicted about watching it
and spending as much time as I have.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I mean, it feels important.
It should be.
It feels like it's way more important
than people are taking it.
Yeah.
I think it has a vibe of everyone's like,
this is our second one.
We've been here before.
We all know he should have been done in the first one.
So let's get this over with
cause these people are fucking nuts.
We'll talk about some of the specifics and stuff
once we get into the episode.
But yeah, it's weird.
Yeah.
So before we get to business on the episode itself,
let's take a moment, Jordan, to say thank you
to some folks who have signed up and are supporting the show.
Oh, that's a great idea.
So first, Joe asks, thank you so much.
You're now a Policy Wonk.
I'm a Policy Wonk.
Thanks, Joe.
Thank you.
Next, Connor VG.
Thank you so much.
You're now a Policy Wonk.
I'm a Policy Wonk.
Thank you, Connor.
Thank you.
Next, Caroline H.
Thank you so much.
You're nowa Policy Wonk.
I'm a Policy Wonk.
Thank you Caroline.
Sweet Caroline.
Nope.
Bop, bop, bop.
Sorry.
Blackjack Nat MC.
Thank you so much.
You're now a Policy Wonk.
I'm a Policy Wonk.
Thank you Nat.
Next, Becky C.
Thank you so much.
You're now a Policy Wonk.
Thanks Becky I'm a Policy Wonk.
I was trying to get ahead of the oh man. I'm black
Now I'm way too ramped up. Yeah the next Jim J. Thank you so much. You're now policy wonk. I'm a policy wonk
And finally Jasmina K. Thank you so much. You're now policy wonk. I'm a policy wonk. Thank you Jasmina
Thank you so much. Do you organize those cuz I feel like our last episode was
99% fake joke names and this one just all seemed like normal people I
Prepared a little bit today. Whereas sometimes I will end up it
It changes it varies. I got it depends on how much time I have. Yeah, you're a busy man
Yeah before the episode I need to be better at organizing stuff, but I'm just not yeah now
I read an article recently about how podcasters don't really need to do much work and the money is really good in the job
So yeah, I saw I saw yeah. Yeah, I assume that that's what you're up to
Yep
So Jordan also another thing we got to do is gonna take a little moment here to say it give a very special
Delilah message Oh Delilah
We got an email beating up Sampson lady
We got an email from Mike. Uh-huh, and he wanted us to play. I'm holding out for a hero
To play a little bit of James Ingram
Yep, that sounds right
Real tough time coming up with
But he reached out and he wanted us to give a little bit of a happy birthday message out to his partner Lauren
Whose birthday is actually yesterday when this is coming out. All right, you know, some people have a birthday week
Yeah, and no, I hope not. Yeah, some people do that. That's not fair. You've not worked in an office in a long time
I don't remember
I don't remember that there were birthday. We don't remember people who would just be like this is my birthday week
It's like yeah, but that's Thursday. Oh
But it would be Tuesday and they'd be like
I choose to believe that we are not dealing with people who manufacture a personality based on their birthday. I
I
Think these people are great dad. Um, so Lauren, happy birthday. Happy birthday, Lauren
And you know what? You can have three days not a week
And I'm sorry Mike that I couldn't improvise a better song
James Ingram's name holding out for a hero. Yeah, I'm gonna go with 2d 2f
Mmm, nevermind. The only James Ingram song I can come up with right now off the top of my head is yamo be there
featuring Michael McDonald
Just listening to the yacht rock podcast
Michael McDonald was usually halfway good. Yeah, so Jordan
Impeachment. Yes. What about it? It is upon us anything going on. Yeah
You know
watching watching this stuff
The one of my big takeaways is that Castro looks solid with a beaster. Oh, no walking Castro
Yeah, yeah, I got you. He does look better with a beard. Yeah, nice-looking beard. Huh? It's about all I got doesn't it?
It does his twin have a beard. I don't know
Well, we should call him because that's a man who needs a beard. This is a
Would be to have a twin so you could try out facial hair
Be awesome twice as much done in terms of trying out styles. No, I think you are talking about a clone did you?
Yeah, I just think his beard look good
And then beyond that I don't know. I feel like the image that's gonna resonate with me. Is that video of
The officer running down the hallway running past Mitt Romney Mitt Romney turning around and running the other way
paired with all the video of
Protesters talking about hanging Mike Pence and yeah, it's just the the imagining what could have happened had that guy
Goodman not said good, you know run the other way the other way, you know, just the idea that someone
Who's a very?
High level politician someone who's very notable in politics who ran for president who's in the Senate
They probably would have killed him. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, there's there was a little there was a little bit of me that was watching that part thinking like and then the next thing
You should say is if it weren't for him Mitt Romney would be dead guys
Hey 45 senators who are gonna vote to uncovick say you want Mitt Romney to die or shut the fuck up
Well, yeah, that's one way to put it and I think that would be fair
Yeah, I think that's pretty much the only way to go. Yeah, I I it's it's it's a really surreal thing to be seeing
this conversation that's happening and the people you're trying to persuade are like
Do you know they're they're chanting to kill the vice president who they elected? Yeah
You understand that they Intel
Moments earlier they were fine with the idea of supporting my pants if he subverted the Constitution you understand
Your name is very
Replaceable with that. Yeah in terms of who they are looking to kill see the problem
There is I think they thoroughly understand that which is why they will be voting to acquit. Yeah
I don't I don't know the dynamics but it's it was it's pretty it's pretty fucked up to
To to see the information presented that way. Yeah, cuz it's it's coherent. It makes sense and it it's it's almost
hilariously over-the-top
comprehensive where like I was watching yesterday and then today and they were talking about how this is almost guaranteed this is
Guaranteed to be the shortest impeachment trial in history and after watching those two days
I was like that does make sense. Yeah in a normal real-world situation because you'd watch that and go
Boy, the defense better come up with something real good. Yeah, it's open
You watch the defense's opening argument. You're like, they're fucked. They're fucked. They got no chance. They're opening statement might as well a bit come on
Come on he's not even president anymore. Get out of here
Yeah, and I was that caster is yeah
Yeah, it's yeah his statement being like oh they made some good points. Yeah, that's not good. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, I don't know. We're all august members of this body. I just want to say you guys are all great
I love you now, obviously the prosecution makes some good points my clients guilty
But I want you all to know that you're spectacular people. I thought we were gonna bicker about jurisdiction
I am not prepared for no. No, oh boy. It really does look like he's committed those crimes
Yeah, and all the all these sort of defenses that you see thrown around are like well
The Trump's rally couldn't have incited this because the people were planning for weeks and it's like well, tada here. Yeah
Exactly. Here's the all the stuff that Trump was saying for weeks
Yeah, it's yeah, and I have no faith in any conclusion
Like I don't have any faith that there's gonna be a conviction and I also don't have any faith that
You know, there's not going to be also like I just I see this and I'm there. Yeah
Yeah, yeah. Yeah
so I wanted to see Alex's response to a lot of this because I figure if anybody is gonna be
Mad about this it'd be Alex
Yeah
He for the sense the impeachment the second impeachment has come around has been really really
Insistent that Trump needs to get up there and put the whole system on trial
Yes, that would be great Trump needs to get in there and insist that he won the election. It was stolen from him
He still can
Alex is not happy that that is not happened
I imagine so and so we'll get get into a little bit of his response
But first here is an out-of-context drop from today's show because I actually worship these people. I hate them
I can't stand them, but I actually know everything about AOC everything about Joe Biden Kim Jong-un GG ping
I shouldn't be looking at GG ping ever
I mean what the hell's going on, but I have to because he's always up my ass. Yeah, man, that's tough
Yeah, we really shouldn't be looking at Alex Jones. He's there
But I can't I can't look away but we have to because he's up America's ass can't can't not look. Mm-hmm. So
Alex discusses
The UN building a little bit at the beginning of this show here on February 10th
He's talking about how you know, he he made that documentary endgame and it is the UN building on the front of it
uh-huh, and
He wasn't supposed to be on air when this stuff was going on now
Oh, you know all the stuff that's supposed to have been taken off the air way in advance, right?
Yeah, and you could either believe that or you could believe that all that stuff
He was saying about they have plans to take me off the air when their plans come to fruition was just nonsense
Yeah, that's possible. We are not supposed to be on air right now
You're supposed to be shut down long before they launch this operation
If you saw my film in game
Also a green mist on the cover
You will notice that I specifically say they're gonna release
bioweapons stimulants to practice a lockdown and
Then that they would launch
Stronger attacks each successive wave while posing as the saviors while will be the United Nations that launches the attack
You guys just type into a search engine in game blueprint for global enslavement and click images
Or maybe go out on the bookshelf and bring a DVD and I want to show you the cover. It's the UN building
In New York City paid for by the Rockefellers and the land it sits on paid for by the Rockefellers
Strangely enough, I won't get into that story
My mom said own that land sold it to then come start the Texas Revolution. That was the heirs family, but that is a side issue
That's right back in the 1820s, that's not a family where Yankees in New York folks
anyways
You can't really count me as a Texan and my family's only been here on both sides since the 1820s
Just once you're from New York. Yes, you're always from New York, but I am digressing. Sorry. Yeah
Much so we have a nine-hour series about endgame and you can go and decide for yourself if
That documentary is actually about what Alex thinks it is. I believe he's literally asking us to judge a book by its cover. Yes
Yeah, a DVD by yeah, let me show you this cover of the DVD
I love the idea that Alex is, you know, he's making this physical land where the UN building sits into a personal issue for him
Yep, like but there's a couple problems
so
The relative that Alex is talking about here is a guy named David Ayers who?
He he and his family were the ones who Colonel Travis
Left his son with and that Alex claims to be related. Sure. Sure. Sure. This dude came to Texas in 1832
Also Colonel Travis didn't like adopt his son to them
Like Alex likes to pretend his son just stayed with the Ayers family to attend school
While his dad drunkenly pretended to be a soldier at the Alamo. The son only stayed with the family for two years. It's not like
You know long enough to build a bond. I will I'm not gonna get in a problem. I'm not gonna I'm not gonna
Ayers on that one. I'm not gonna split Ayers exactly
I think that that's fine. But the way Alex presents it is like they gave him his son. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, he raised Colonel Travis's son. He was founded a manger. Yeah. Yeah. Also David Ayers himself actually wasn't from New York
He was from Morristown, New Jersey where he was born in 1793
According to the Texas State Historical Association David quote came to Texas to buy property and build a home
Prior to that he quote was a merchant in Ithaca, New York
Ithaca is about 230 miles from New York City
So I have some doubts about this whole story of him owning the land that the UN building is on
Sounds like a load of bullshit that Alex tells himself in order to keep this fight with his imaginary enemies personal. Yeah
That's my land
Man here's the thing about that. Yeah. All right, it's if that's what you want to do
Okay, I have a claim to that land back from the 1820s
Then you also have to acknowledge that maybe somebody else had a claim to that land in the 1500s. Nope
Nope, why not? Alex's property rights began in the 1820s. I did not know that
I should have was that in the Constitution. All right, so there's this
Thing in life where stuff happens gradually
Alex tries to discuss how taking COVID seriously
will lead to negative consequences much like
Taking the Klan seriously leads us to kicking Trump off Twitter
This is one of these
I'm gonna need to hear this one. It's an SAT all the way through
So the first domino was the KKK and the white supremacist most of them run by the southern property law center in the ADL
And the FBI that's come out mainstream the ADL
Mmm, and then the next like oh, I'm over the Nazis. So let's take their speech away
Let's take their bank accounts away. And then next it's oh, it's Alex Jones. Let's take everything
He's got and then two years later. It's the President of the United States
No, I think these are all lumped in with the Nazis for these masks for 15 days, I'll just stay in your house for 15 days
Sounds reasonable. It's the little domino then it's all six months. It's all two years. Well, just take this COVID test
Well, just have a contact tracer in your house. Well, it's ten years in jail if you're seen outside your house period I
Got the video they announced it yesterday
In Parliament
In Parliament ten years in prison if you're seen outside your house when they tell you to quarantine
So the problem with the argument that he's making is that like if there is behavioral
Similarities between the Klan Alex Jones and the president
I don't understand in that they're all breaking the terms of service of a certain platform
I'm getting kicked off is it's not like some kind of a dominoes falling situation. It's more of just a
Consistency of the rules only Nazis would expect justice to be applied fairly. Yeah, that doesn't make much sense
And then in terms of the the evolving situation with COVID, it's like we didn't do any of those things
No, no all of those things. It's like he had 15 days 30 days or like we didn't do those things
Or at least people some people didn't to large enough extent that those were not
effective or at least as effective as they could be yeah, and then secondarily the government didn't provide
material support to people to enable them to do these safety measures in a way that would have been meaningful and so
We end up with we end up with a situation that gets worse and worse and yeah the mitigation
Take things that you would prescribe for that become larger. So it's not the dominoes falling
It's just us not taking care of a problem
Not just that but mitigation efforts that were already planned for and in place that Jared Kushner according to witnesses denied
Specifically because it would only hurt Democrats more making it more of a genocide situation
Just saying just tossing that out there. So but if you're outside your house, you're gonna go to prison for 10 years
Oh, okay in the UK. This is nonsense
Yeah
the actual story is about how the UK government has rolled out new rules where if you're returning to the country after visiting a
Country that's on the red list of high-risk countries
You're required to quarantine at a government-designated hotel for 10 days, which costs approximately
1750 pounds
the discussion of a 10-year sentence is for people who knowingly lie about where they're returning to the UK from in order to skip
And skirt public health measures and the required quarantining everyone can still go outside their houses
Alex is just trying to scare people. Yeah, it's all a bunch of bullshit
Yep, and I am positive that you know, that is a high figure for a lot of people
Mm-hmm
but also I
Would assume that people who are coming from these countries or people who are coming in from vacations to those countries
Yeah, possibly people who would be able to afford the quarantining and I would also assume that if not the there's probably
At least some sort of a program in place to help people who don't have the means. Yeah for the sake of public safety
Yeah, it's not I don't know. Anyway, it's all a load of bullshit. Yeah, Alex is lying. Oh, yeah, so
We know that Alex is a violent chap
But you from all of his words and deeds. Yes. Yeah. Yeah, those would be how we identify. Yeah. Yeah his regular tone
Yeah his insistence on encouraging people to be violent his behaviors in all of the stories
He tells about accosting people as though he's the hero. Yes. Yeah, but it turns out he's not
We were right now
By we I mean Alex and his audience. Yes, we are in a riptide
And if you fight when you're in a riptide, you're gonna drown. All right, so you can't fight
I don't know anything about riptides. You don't know. Oh see much like mochi
Riptides were a part of my grown-up
Well naturally, yes
Yeah, there is there is a certain amount of truth to it
Like if you get taken in an undertow or something
You will generally end up like just getting like fighting you gotta slide it
And you'll come out not a great strategy, right? Right?
Cuz you're just gonna stay under and drown it can be it can be very bad. Gotcha. It's really scary
I've been through similar things. I believe times and in my younger years, but
This metaphor doesn't quite work the way Alex wants it to
Because what he's sort of saying is like we're gonna take some bumps in this
Riptide and then we'll be spit out from the riptide and be in safety
It'll be scary but you know, you can't fight because if you fight that's when you're gonna drown
But then at the end he also says that people are coming to kill your family
I like in this to getting caught in a riptide and I'm one time foolishly when I was a teenager. They had red flags out
I'm like, I'm a great swimmer. I'm in hell before I quit doing almost 13
I was a champion swimmer when all the blue ribbons in Dallas and I thought I'd get out there
I'm 18 years old
I got grabbed in one of those things and I knew what to do and it sucked me under I said just hold your breath
And relax don't fight it. It spit me out in 50 yards and I was okay, but it scared the living hell out of me
Well, let me just tell you we're already being pulled under so it's not time to even get air
You're just hold it relax baby because you panic you're gonna die
So this is not negative. This is biblical. It's all gonna happen and
It's gonna get so bad within a few years. You're just gonna be totally blown away
They're gonna tighten tighten tighten release a little and then clamp down even harder and then release a little and clamp down even harder
Mass suicides death there'll be COVID deaths from the vaccines everywhere
It's already happening and they'll just normalize it and then all these college students that don't have jobs are gonna have government paychecks their own uniforms
They're already coming to your house
The communists are coming armed for you and your family and they're gonna kill you so get ready so we shouldn't do anything
We're in a riptide that we should just just hold your breath
Okay, relax, okay, or should I be worried about the armed commies coming to kill my family?
Well, those would seem important to you, but they're not coming to kill Alex's family
So we need to just sit tight and we'll get through this much like how a t-rex can't see you in the movies
When you sit still but the commies come to your door if you hold your breath and relax, they can't see you
I just kick why do you also have to have blue ribbons and swimming?
What is it always gonna be every time there's a new he's like a Stevie P's in high school
He's like he I was there I did all of the stuff is the best at everything everything
And not all of it can be true, but that's close enough to like I could believe that sure
I don't have any problem with that
I just have a problem with this is yet another in the long list of things where he tosses off
You know, I won all the I won all the awards when I was there. Anyways, I won the title for most specialist boy
Yeah, exactly. It's like Jesus. Come on, buddy. Yeah, come on
Yeah, so that that's an incoherent message that he's sending his audience there because at the end of it I
Feel like he'd negated a lot of the ideas that you'd want to be sending when you tell people you're in a riptide relax
We're gonna get out the other side of this
Yeah, I feel like he's telling you to fight that riptide no, no, no see cuz he said relax first
Yeah, it's it's like I said, it's incoherent. I don't know these clauses are dependent on each other
So first get the riptide and then die. So what do you know about Pablo Escobar?
Not
Did you not watch Narcos? I did not watch Narcos. They knew to die. Yeah, I think he was man had elephants
I know that he was in the movie blow
He was featured as a character in the movie blow all-time great mustache, I believe. Yeah all-time great. Sure. Yeah Pee-wee Herman was also there
Yes, of course. Yeah
all-time great mustache by the way, I
Learned from listening to this and not only did he have elephants he also had hippos. Ooh, and
Dangerous. Yes, Alex goes on a very long
a ramble about the dangers of hippos. He was voted best hippo in high school. Best hippo wrangler. Exactly
I used to do I was like a matador but for hippos
So Pablo Escobar had these hippos and they got you know
Now they've bred and now hippos are somewhere where they shouldn't be sure sure
And so now people want to cull them. Mm-hmm
This leads Alex to saying that there may be some good arguments for human culling cool
And I would like to remind you he is a noted eugenics disliker this guy
Theoretically Pablo Escobar down in South America got what was it for hippos?
Something like 40 years ago
back in the 80s
Back when I was a little kid and now reportedly there's just thousands of these hippos running around and by the way
We didn't know the hippos the most deadly animal in the world. It'll kill an elephant and killed a lion
It'll kill a grizzly bear. There's nothing more powerful than on land than a hippopotamus
Everything runs in fear of the 20-foot crocodiles run in fear
You watch videos of a hippo just grabbing a 20-foot crocodile just throwing it around like it's a it's a it's a toothpick
Okay, there's the most know that so now all over where Pablo lived. There's this giant hippopotamus is everywhere
And so now they want to call them now
They want to call the hippopotamuses
And I'm like, yeah, they don't come from there yeah, they're killing everything okay kill them but see I'm a human being
I don't need to be called
But see the globalist they say Jones you notice you're telling people this and they don't care that's because they're not conscious
They're just eating food and their genetics are bad and they're breeding and we need to get rid of them and we're not racist
We're gonna kill the dumb black people the dumb white people the dumb Hispanics the dumb Asians
And that itself's playing God is evil
And I don't support that that's the problem. There's an argument there
But then you say the globalists they're into Satanism. They're into playing God
Their real documents are they want to overwrite everything and not save the earth and believe they're gonna just be able to make all the planets
They want once they become AI
artificially intelligent singularity godlike
And they're just in a mad race
Sacrificing the earth as a testing ground to this ascension
So that's a lot of nonsense
But yeah, I just find it really interesting whenever Alex has these like hypothetical conversations with globalists
And he's like, oh, there's an argument to be made
Off the dumb. Listen. Listen, I'm not saying it's a bad idea in
That's very weird. In practice it can go wrong. Yeah. Yeah, I would say that if your branding is the such
That Alex puts forth should never say that there's a there's an argument to be made. It's not eugenics if it's dumb people
That's not a race
Sure, it's never been used in a way that's not racist
Sure
There's a track record of some people maybe using this for their own racist purposes. Oh, hey Alex
You know how you see some people as dumb, huh? I
Just think about that
Hmm is he thinking that it's playing God because God had already done the Noah thing
I don't know maybe so he's so he's almost a little mad at God. He was like, what are you doing?
You should have just got rid of the dumb ones, right? We could have had plenty of fun
Yeah, shouldn't let the dumb dumbs on the boat and then you put all those goddamn hippos on the boat. They're everywhere now
We're calling them classic mistake classic God
Um, so Alex is not afraid of anything probably he's a strong strong boy
Who's only slightly afraid of riptides afraid of shadow gate? Well, he's afraid of his former employees probably
So people ask how I'm doing. I am totally committed. I have no fear. I've gone away past everything
I'm not worried even about my family
I love my family
But I've just had turned over to God because the enemy's done horrible things to my family
Horrible things to me behind the scenes that you even know about and I've just said hey, it's okay
It's God's plan. I'm not mad at God. I appreciate it. I
Understand because my children don't have a future. Anyways, if we don't beat this you don't either none of us. It's okay
And you watch
That first lawyer that got up and groveled like a dog with his tail between his legs
That rolled over and pissed all over itself and just oh, you're so powerful Schumer. I love you, sir
Oh, you're so much better than us great job with your presentation on Trump
He was just shaking because there's not men in this country. I told you Trump was surrounded by a bunch of damn cowards
Not by invincible fat deep s you talked about the dimensions and chess quite a bit
Yeah, don't fucking pretend. Yeah
That transition was as jarring as it seemed it felt so yeah, it felt felt a little bit a little weird
Yeah, it took a turn. Yeah, Alex is now mad at these lawyers being soft, right? Right? Yeah
Yeah, I think everybody pretty universally agreed that Kester did a real shit job. Not great lawyers
so Alex kind of is a little bit like touch-and-go on the
On the impeachment trial yells about the lawyer being weak a little bit, but then doesn't doesn't spend too much time
Talking about it. Yeah, I kind of halfway assumed that today we would be talking about a secret migrant caravan
And they we wouldn't even know the impeachment happened
No
It's sort of dancing around a little bit, you know
Like side issues to the impeachment like for instance the fact that Democrats all have Chinese spy hand
In their office that sounds right now. Not only that they all have Chinese spy
handlers
Nobody knows what the name of the Chinese spy agency is called. Okay
most of Democrats are Chinese spy
handlers of Chinese
Intelligence so secret the name of Chinese intelligence is not even known but I know its name
What is it?
And you all know its name what is it because everything hides in plain view
Like what?
America is the red white and blue
China is the red dragon a
What?
What's the name of the snake?
the old serpent
Diablo
the devil
So let's talk about some positive news
We're just doing word association game, that's all we're doing who would have thought the
It's actually the the Ministry of State Security, but yeah
Oh Diablo he couldn't come up with old scratch there. I think he was probably pretty pissed in the moment
Snake come on bad scratch is way better. Dude. Anyway, Alex is thinking about the devil and so sure
This clip is actually just titled. This show is stupid
They want you by increment to get caught by this and to be too late
You've got the whole blueprint folks the blueprint for global enslavement the blueprint for global extermination
You have the enemy operation you have it in Revelation. You have it in Daniel. You have it in Ezekiel
You have it all around you you have it in your soul
all you've got to do is
Decide that you don't want to be part of it and make the metaphysical decision to cut yourself off from Satan
Then God will extricate you out of that you need God to do it
But God says you've got to let me in and I come knocking. I come knocking. Let me in let me in
But you've got to open the door
because God is it like Satan that rams down the door and lies to you from the time you're a child to steal your
Essence to steal your will to steal your ability to interface with God and your free will
God doesn't touch that. Satan's all about encasing you from birth in a matrix so he can fool your soul
This is the only way he can win because he's not a god
He's a fraud. Wait, can he win? He's a liar
He's a devil
Not so impactful to yell that the devil is a devil. Yeah, not he's he's a he's a devil
Yeah, that should come with a more upwards inflection that passion seemed so fake to me
Yeah, it was just it just so boring and then cookie cutter
Anyway, one thing that's very exciting
Maybe another bright spot is that my cat has jumped into my lap and is insisting on being very affectionate right now
Well a car horn just went off a few times
Little guest appearance there on the mic
There it is. Get off my lap
Get kick on
I guess she probably, you know Selene probably heard some devil talk. Yeah, I gotta get in on this. Gotta protect him
Yeah, so actually she was trying to delay the inevitable and that is that I need to tell you about a couple guests
That we have on this show. No
They just got kicked off Twitter. Okay. It's Jim and
Jim's brother, Hoft. I can't remember his brother's name
Jim Hoft and Joe Hoft maybe? Something like that. Yeah, they're the brothers Hoft. The brothers Hoft
I like that. Yeah, the Gateway Pundit dudes. They got kicked off Twitter. And so they come on to complain
About that and I don't care. Yeah, we don't want to listen to an hour of whining
No, not really. But you know, Jim Hoft his main point seems to be that
You know, like this isn't a cult of personality about Trump, okay
You know, we're not gonna have another candidate like that for a while. Donald Trump was, you know, once in a lifetime
candidate so these Republicans better wake up and I think it's also imperative that a lot of these rhinos get replaced by
other pro-Trump
Populist candidates in the next primary
We have to get rid of some of this dead weight in the Republican Party
If you don't want to sound crazy, I would recommend you not say
Whether or not a candidate in a future election is pro the president who is no longer in office
Yeah, I would say that that is a real designation of a crazy person. It's not a cult of personality Dan
I just want everyone to agree that a single person is the
Greatest human being that ever lived and we should do whatever he says
Yeah, if you were running a Democratic candidate and they were like, this is the pro-obama candidate
Mm-hmm. I would look at that. It also as weird. Yeah, very weird. Yeah, very comfortable strange
So Alex's is you know, he's talking about how like, you know, the they've they've
Stolen the election, you know, they steal the election sure and then we know that they've stolen the election
So that makes us not vote and that makes it easier for them to steal and then it goes out to break with something really
Upsetting in blue states and blue cities people get to knowing that once they take over
It's permanent. Then we stop voting then it makes it easier for them to cover up the fraud. Say hi to your brother
Let's talk. Look, let's talk about how we still get people to vote even though we know it's a fraud
Should we keep voting when we come back or what is our recourse?
Is it the cartridge box? I hope not. You cannot hide a grand assault
We'll get to that in a second. Okay. Um, yeah, is it the cartridge box? Yeah, I hope not. Mm-hmm
Gross, so you heard that at the end you can't hide and the assault. Yeah
Alex's commercial here is a little weird. I'm now back to listen. Well, it started off great
I'm listening to this episode on the GCN feeds
Mm-hmm. So this is a commercial that would have been played out on the radio, right? And I will tell you it is a very
Different tone. Oh, then the commercials and reads that we've heard Alex give on our recent episodes
It's a little bit. It's a little bit more fucked up. It also sounds like he's jacking it. Yeah. Okay. All right, please
Listener discretion advised he sounds we may be tubening by proxy. So creepy
You cannot hide a grand assault
America is about to have its energy cut off its borders destroyed
It's dollar brought down to nothing all of you that have served Satan
Believe that you are the right team
You're about to find out how pathetic you are
So I ask all of you who are awake and who love God
Stop living in fear
The enemy is about to expose itself. The enemy can't help itself
The enemy comes to kill steal and destroy
We sit here as good people get upset about that and try to stop it
We should but once it comes through once it hits us
Once it's dominating us and raping us and attacking us. Jesus. We just have to point out we tried to stop us
This is on the radio pair yourselves America. You're going under judgment. Just like all the children that were aborted. This is the truth
This is the info war
Wow quite a bumper. Hey Alex, uh, it sounds like your voice is a little bit scratchily or there than usual
You realize we're cutting promos today. Yeah, I forgot and I smoked an entire pack of cigarettes about 20 minutes ago
I'm three quarters drunk
I'm jacking off. I'm hiding from my wife. I am recording this under a blanket
No, I'm not going to bed yet
That's supposed to be like a billion-dollar operation. That sounded like shit. Yeah, that was garbage
I think I think one of the things that's going on is I think he was probably fucked up
But yeah, he's also like trying to really do that movie. Yeah
Yeah, he's trying to do that really dramatic voice. Yeah to because I think that this is tailored more towards a
Possibly random person. Yeah, that could be listening on the radio right to really pique their interest to be like, what is this?
This is exciting, but he missed the mark though. Oh sounds creepy
I heard that and I thought ooh, I need to know more but you compare that to the meandering random bullshit
That's on the like actual infowars feed because he knows that that's targeting his audience. Yeah. Yeah, it's it's pretty clear
I just think that the it's really funny that this is what he thinks goes to the like
It's amazing that he can fail in multiple ways. Yeah. Yeah, it's it's remarkable. It is it is, you know
I like to imagine that
You know, I'm not I if I failed in a different arena, I would be aware of it
I wouldn't just be like yeah, I killed it. I can do literally anything
It Wow, it's done who gives a shit. Yeah, right
So this is a good strategy for Alex to try and get new listeners in
Just do these creepy jack-off commercials about the end of America Alex. This sounds really creepy
I only do one day. Yeah, you're not paying me for two
So that's a good strategy
Another good strategy might be a Paul Paul Joseph Watson my oldest friend
Yeah, why don't you promote my shit? Maybe I'm not mad about it
Please remember everything the enemy does is about shutting us down. That's why we built Bandai video
So we updated info Wars calm news Wars calm Paul's got his summit dot news
But she promote us more on there, but whatever still love Paul not mad about it
I was thinking about it. Like yeah, what isn't it for Paul to promote it for Wars zero reason
It's really in his best interest to play down as far away from info Wars as possible
There's nothing else that he can get out of it other than like not making Alex mad
Yeah, that's the only thing that he has to worry about. He's gotten as much publicity as could come out of info Wars
Well, that's why the arguably bigger
That's why the band on the Titanic kept playing is because they didn't want the captain to be angry
So they were like, well, I guess this is where we die. I don't want to piss that guy off. Yeah, it
Only hurts Paul to remind people that he worked at info Wars for 20 years
Yeah, if I were him, I would do the exact same thing. Goodbye
So Alex is mad about Trump's lawyer being polite
For the most part, I mean incompetent too, but Alex seems more mad that he's polite. Yeah about his presentation
Yeah, you know they're in the chambers bordering on obsequious. Sure
Yeah, but there's there's a certain there's a certain decorum that comes along. Sure. Sure congressional speech
There's the pageantry of being in the Senate halls
That was literally just stormed you refer to people as the the gentleman or the lady from New Hampshire, whatever the fuck
Alex is mad about that. Mm-hmm. I just wanna play a few clothes from yesterday
We got some of the new stuff today coming up as well just to show you with enemies like this
Well, imagine what your real enemies are like Oh what nailed it that's the old saying with friends like this who needs enemies
So when you look at just this this this foppish
Creaming
just classic BS artists a lawyer in there in gray shading himself and
and groveling to Chuckie Schumer when all Schumer takes out his weakness and
Congratulating him and and just all of this and then saying this will turn around and bite you later if you do it
Yeah, they're tyrants. They don't care about chivalry. He's just mad. There's not a lot of analysis at all
Yeah, and I think the big thing that he's mad about
in terms of the conversation that happens throughout the impeachment stuff is that
like the defense is not
Arguing that Trump won the election. No, they're taking as granted that Biden won
yeah, and Alex is pretty mad about that because
That's the only thing you could really get people like distracted by yeah that stupid argument
Yeah that you can't but the reason they're not doing that is because that doesn't belong in court that belongs on
Infowars and right-wing media out
But yeah, he's he's a little bit upset that that world isn't being like taken over by his right his shit, right?
I mean it is maybe
Maybe it's their best defense
Honestly after after looking at the the opening arguments
Maybe their best defense would be like we're putting this whole thing on trial actually Trump is president
That's why it's fine
That everybody did this and you're all the ones who should be impeached if you want to gum up the works and possibly create
New problems for yourself. Yeah, I I think Caster's already gone far enough. He might as well jump off the the edge
Yeah, I I mean look if you want it to be interesting. Yeah, probably that's the way to go
But it would be a disgrace. Yep. It wouldn't work probably not
Yeah, I think that Alex has gotten a little bit used to the last, you know
Four years five years of like politics descending to his level right and this is a concrete instance of it not
Yeah, and that probably would be pretty frustrating and then at the same time you have, you know
Biden's comments of you know
Like the Senate has an important role to to play and to do their job trying to stay above the fray and trying to keep
himself
Removed from the process sure and that's got to really piss off
Yeah, I would imagine so
So he does the only thing that he knows how to do and that is talk to a comedian. Oh
Boy, he has comedian. Let's see if you know who this guy is. Oh, no, I can't give you any clues though
Okay, if you ever heard of Dave Landau, uh, I mean I have heard of
I've heard the name before it's funny cuz on band.video the like the segment that he's on
I believe it refers to him as a top comedian. Ooh, that's not good. Usually means they're not
He apparently hosts
Or co-hosts with Anthony Kumiya, Anthony Kumiya's new show. Okay, or whatever show the fuck he's doing
Oh, man, I'm shocked that I didn't get a call to co-host on that one, too
I feel like I'm the I'm the guy for that. Are you comparing me to Anthony Kumiya?
Because you better not be
I'll take that is quite quite an insult
So yeah, Dave Dave Landau is on and I think he tries to make a few jokes and how's it go? Not great
Yeah, Alex is not a good scene partner. No as we know
I only have one clip here cuz I don't care about what Dave Landau has to say about cancel culture. Oh, yeah
No, no, no, no. I don't particularly care about his perspective on the
Impeachment because it's not interesting right and then anything that he has to say about cancel culture
I'm like you fucking co-host a show with Anthony Kumiya who gives a yeah, I gotta go
I have very few very little interest in what any white comedian has to say about cancel culture strike one
You host a show with Anthony Kumiya strike two. You're on info wars strike three. You said this on info wars
It's not even so much taking that big of a stand
It's just telling people not to be completely blind
And I think the only thing that most people are really saying is that this is gonna end in some kind of bloody civil war
And the way that it's starting to look I can see that I can see their point
But I just think if people just calm down and stop turning on mainstream media
Which I just can't imagine what it's like to sit in your house all day long
Stare at the television and have fear pumped into you. Yeah, totally unlike the show. You're on that would be terrifying
What kind of monster would force people to watch four straight hours of fear mongering? Yeah, I
feel like you really
Look like like a real ding-dong when you say something like that on info wars
Yeah, cuz that either means that you accepted a booking on a platform as maligned and notorious as in fours without having it
done any due diligence about
The place you're on or somehow you don't see what Alex does as rank fear monger. No, that's not rank
People up screaming about the fucking devil. It's it's really simple what he's doing
He's just asking people not to be blind and that's all he's doing. It's the mainstream media
That's pumping fear into your blood all the time by reporting news
Hmm, I would say that anybody who works for any kind of mainstream media outlet if they behaved in any kind of way
Close to like what Alex does they might be in jail. Yeah. Yeah
It at least would be sued over and over and over they'd be they'd be fired
Mm-hmm. It's just it's wildly irresponsible or they would be Brett Stevens. That's also a possibility possible
Yeah, that leads me to believe that maybe this Dave Landau guy is not incredibly sincere
I would maybe a little bit disingenuous with his his perspective. Mm-hmm
So that ends the 10th the 10th was the brothers hoffed. Yep weird comedian
Yep, surface level fairly certain that one of the big deals of stuff is happening right now on the 10th
Yeah, you mean the impeachment? Yeah, well, I feel like that's important
Yeah, but a lot of that's a lot of the hearings on the 10th were happening after Alex was on it. That's true
That's true. You're right the some of the stuff he had he didn't have any way of knowing
Got until the next day the 11th when he's on air
And he's still a little surface level. I'll be honest. He's not
He's not covering it nearly as much. I mean because from Alex's perspective that makes sense
The election was stolen according to Alex. Yeah, this is all bullshit. It's all imaginary
Yeah, so why engage with the substance of the thing if the thing?
That kind of seems to be where he's at explain to me how
Alex seems to have a more cogent position on what he imagines is imaginary and how much we should talk about it
Then the rest of us do
I
Won't okay. So he starts off on the 11th talking about Bill Gates
because of course this is the most important news of the
Our lifetimes it is official what Bill Gates called for on Bill Moyers and what he called for Ted Talks
And when he called for on CNN, we have three clips of it in the last few years
Calling for
The
Euthanasia of old people because we quote can't pay for the aging population in Europe the United States Australia, Canada, New Zealand
And he says so you kill a teacher
Then you can or excuse me you you you you kill an old person and you can hire ten teachers
And that's not how it really works
But they put that you kill ten teachers and you fish for a life job the moral thing to do
And and and so the reports are pouring in
Every day five died here four died here three died here ten died here seven died here
And it's only in the nursing homes
where the employees notice all of the death and
Say something
Most these places know to keep it quiet and say they died of something else
But in many of the cases I'm gonna read to you from the CDC's own website
Oh, they even have a record of this some of them die within 15 minutes
15 minutes
So Alex is claiming that someone died 15 minutes after getting a kovat 19 vaccine
And then he presents that as evidence that the two are causally connected sure that's the level of work
He does he just associates two things and insists that he is then proven that they're connected when he's done
No such thing Alex could legit show me a news story about someone dying as they're getting vaccinated
And it still doesn't prove the claim that the vaccines related to that person's death
There's an unfortunate reality here, and that is that Alex either doesn't understand that dynamic of reality
Or he understands all too. Well. How easy it is to trick people into thinking that correlation proves causation
Yeah, I think the latter is probably more likely yeah
But also Bill Gates wasn't advocating killing old people as he could hire teachers
It's easy to misconstrue his words that way, but the conversation he was having that Alex always takes out of content
Our context is about exorbitant medical costs, and what can be done about that right?
Which is a thing that literally most of the world is?
Dealing with right now as population explodes like it's not unique to anywhere. It's like oh shit
What are we gonna do those fucking baby boomers wrecked us?
it's
it's easy to look at that conversation that Bill Gates has had in these public forums as
Being like well mathematically if we just kill all the old people we can
Hire and that's not that's not the the conversation, but that would be a facetious argument that I would make in a
Debate where somebody's like oh well old people are trying about like then let's kill all of the old people
I bet you could sarcastically make that argument. Yeah against Alex and win. Yeah a debate
Yeah, totally he is he's got a lot of nothing actually that's a really good idea
So Alex is now more mad at Trump's lawyers. This is intentional. They're fucking setting them up
officially we now know
That the lawyers that Trump hired because the first groups were bad the second group was bad the third group was bad
Have all either sued him or Democrats that hate him and say that Trump's a criminal and they're actually sabotaging him
Publicly saying he deserves to be kicked out of office and that voters were smart and voted him out
So instead of putting on evidence of election fraud the lawyers are all slipping in by the way
The Americans are smart. They kick Trump out
Trump's getting sandbagged. Yep. Yep
When when that lawyer was saying that he was trying to get the shit thrown out
Yeah, and he said that you know, like hey, there's another president and it seems like the process has worked fine
Yeah, elections are how we solve problems like corrupt dictators
Historically you have an election. Let's not do this
If the goal is winning the case that is maybe a decent argument to try
Anyway if we didn't have any precedent for it if this was the first time if this was like
1810 and we were having one of these and people were having that argument. I'd be like, I don't know
Have we ever tried this before? Maybe give it a shot. So look, this is about the January 6th
This was about the storming of the Capitol. This impeachment trial is about that
It's easy to lose sight of that from time to time. Sure. Because of nefarious shitheads who, you know, make stuff up and whatever
but look that was not cool that happening because
Provocateurs did it to make Alex look bad because people who are in the same communities as Alex or appear to be are being violent
Right. Now at the same time violence is cool, too
Look, we are well past the point of being able to righteously use violence against these institutions and organizations
But having a few Democrats and a few infiltrator groups
Trigger out of hundreds of thousands of peaceful people in DC a few hundred to go in the Capitol so you can be called
Insurrectionist terrorist is not the place of the time for it. Okay
Coherent messaging. No, I think that one is actually really coherent. We should absolutely storm the Capitol
This was bad planning
They tricked us into not storming the Capitol on the 20th when we would have all been able to actually kill everybody
Maybe I think he's essentially saying that it wasn't the right time to fire the shot heard round the world
Yeah, yeah, I guess so. But the reason it's incoherent is because I don't think he wants to take responsibility for that
Cut and dry message. Yeah, that's why it's incoherent. Yeah, that is the what's behind
Well, yeah violence is obviously justified that this was this was a misstep. Yeah, that's why I blame it on agitators
They tricked us into shooting before we were ready to shoot
So in that case, I'm pretty sure he's saying that well, yeah, obviously we wanted to kill everybody and overthrow the country
Well, we just wanted to do it at the right time. So we would win. Yeah, of course
I mean Alex even gets into his blood loss. Sure
I was in a halfway decent mood today and but I was already aware of the euthanasia of the old
And how would I come on air and give it the gravitas it needs so we don't all just get conditioned to accepting this
Five years ago. I was reading the statistics of the numbers and just going through the stacks
and
I physically
Became nauseous. No, you didn't because my nervous system was telling me you
Need to go visit violence upon the people that are doing this
If you let them kill old people like this and kill babies already born and they admit they're doing it
You are an accomplice. My very cells are telling me
Defend these people. So for all of you out there that are mad at me because I'm saying let's not be violent
Let's not be offensive
I understand your guts and your blood and your soul and your mind is burning with the desire to kill
Pull up, pull up
I want to stop these people just as much as you do, but we've got to be wise as serpents and peaceful as doves
and walk
Gently but carry a big stick. I don't think you pulled it off. What was that?
I'm gonna end with two cliches because I realized that I just basically told everybody that it's fine to kill and that I want to
too
So you got to walk softly and carry a big stick Dan
I feel like Alex might not be lying about reading Infowars comments because that sounds like him
Responding to a lot of feedback of people who are like Alex you're soft. Let's just go kill him
Let's just go kill him. Yeah, I think that Alex that's Alex trying to like have an olive branch to the yeah the murderous audience
Yeah, and also do you know who else anthropomorphizes their murderous intentions? Who's that? Uh serial killers. Mm-hmm
Look, he wants to kill. Sure. And he understands that the audience wants to kill and they're connected on this
I feel like there's a problem there. But you got to be wise as a serpent
I feel like there's a problem there too. It doesn't get better.
I just want everybody to know the left and Apple and Facebook and Twitter and Mark Zuckerberg and
Jack Dorsey, you know what you're doing and you are just as guilty as Bill Gates
Especially Mark Zuckerberg who works directly under him
He's the next guy in line for to be science officer of North America
For the new world order and you guys are mass murdering killers
And I know who you are. Everybody knows who you are and you will pay for what you've done murderers. I
Don't care what you do to me. You are you you are guilty
Everybody else is scared to call your asses out
So I'll just tell everybody I
Was on the other day and I said it was a civil war starts don't go after the cops and military
That's a diversionary tactic to wipe them out for the Chinese to have a civil war don't have the civil war
It's why they've had the lockdowns black lives matter
Antifa try to provocateur us is to get a civil war where we all kill each other. We don't want a civil war
We want a removal of the globalist and their collaborators
Yikes, you just named a number of people what we want to do is remove these people that I have pointed out
For you guilty of murder and I have specifically said that violence and everything is okay because they're murderers
So and we're well past the point of being able to write
Way back now granted the storming of the Capitol was bad planning
But what would be good planning is how he's clearly implying what would be good planning
What are you guys doing storming the Capitol with only a few hundred people?
You can't win what you should be doing targeted
Assassinations, you know, it's stupid, you know, it's unfortunate to like Mark Zuckerberg is one of the people that's on Alex's list
Yeah, but Alex constantly calls him Jeff Zuckerberg. Yeah. Yeah, like there might be a Jeff Zuckerberg out there who he's targeted
He's because Alex can't remember dude's name. Oh, man. He wields too much power and is too dumb to handle it
Yeah, so this is really irresponsible and I think you could make a pretty good argument that you know using shifty language Alex is
Probably telling his audience that should maybe kill my enemies
I think one of the things about the evidence in the
impeachment trial that I've noticed was how many times that they did a really good job of avoiding allowing that kind of clause
To like excuse any behavior, you know, like so often they had they played Trump's words and you're you're literally like
Yeah, we all know he said peacefully
Mm-hmm. Yeah, we should we should all protest peacefully and then they're like, yeah, but we've got 300 examples of him saying otherwise
Yeah, so you can't pull that bullshit. This is a pattern behavior like Alex Jones is essentially on trial in the same way
Well, I mean in our show in some ways is a on
rigorous
Completely without legal backing. Yeah
And I would say he's guilty
It's just that there is not a specific crime yet, right?
It's just the behavior that would lead to that. Just thank God people have not carried out his his his clear
man, yeah
So yeah, he's mad about this trial because these these these lawyers are throwing the case, man
Here's another question are Trump's lawyers
Taking the impeachment trial on purpose. I don't know or are they just shitty folks. Everybody knows these lawyers
These are very competent lawyers
They are sabotaging Trump because they've been told to they wouldn't have had a trial unless it was rigged
That's why his lawyers are like Trump actually lost the election and you've done a great job and you proved he's bad
He's actually you prove he's guilty
Because it's a bunch of cowards
The globalists are making their move all these so-called men are a bunch of pinstripe wearing
knuckle-dragging dirty stupid crooks that have screwed this country over and sold it out to China and
You've got a consortium of dirtbag lawyers and a consortium of pedophile leftist
Bunch of nasty hunchback globalist that just absolutely gonna mount this country's head on a wall. I'll tell you why
I'll tell you why because they hate themselves and they're going down
Hollywood's going down all the leftist cities are going down and that's because they're run by the same slave master Satan and now they want
To just drag us down with them. Whoo
Well, how's he gonna explain it when Trump gets acquitted like
Like it really is gonna be difficult to explain for a lot of people. Yeah beyond saying these guys
We're just gonna quit no matter what why why if Trump gets acquitted then why?
I like how are you going to rationalize his lawyers are in on it. They're throwing it
They wouldn't have it a trial if it wasn't rigged. Oh, it's rigged to a quit
Yeah, the fuck are you talking about? This makes no sense
he's not rambling and you could tell the real dead giveaway that he's probably just
Fucking coked out of his mind and rambling about nothing is you get to the Satan at the end. Oh, of course
Then that always comes back to you know, why I'll tell you. Oh, yeah, that's that's a real four in the morning party
I want to leave kind of moment. Yep
Anyway, Alex gets to talk about these vaccines
Did you know that there's thousands dead already from the kovat 19 vaccine feel like I would have heard it if there were no
They're keeping it on the low. Oh, that's smart of them
One of the things that I think is interesting about this which is first of all, it's not true
Second is that if Alex believes that then he has to believe that there's
About as many deaths from the vaccine as there is from kovat. Yeah, that's outrageous
They estimate that one out of ten conservatively
Of adverse reactions gets reported a lot of daughters will tell you it's about one out of a hundred probably really
I mean how many times you take something of an adverse reaction and you call the CDC and then tell them?
okay, so
Thousands of dead people so far from the Pfizer mRNA vaccine thousands
You count Europe the US Australia. I think Pfizer could sue him. I think so, too. Yeah
Yeah, also, he's just making up numbers at the beginning totally and also you don't call the CDC
Your doctor ends up calling the CDC to report adverse. Yeah, that's why you go to the doctor
Yeah, if you have an adverse reaction to something you will go seek treatment and then they will yeah, they'll be like
Oh, we got a report this it's our job. Yeah, it would be a really inefficient system to force everyone to be like
Hello CDC
What frustrates me a lot about Alex's narratives regarding this type of stuff?
Is that yeah, man, people have already thought of those as problems
They happened a long time ago and people were like, oh, let's not do that
Like the reason we have the reporting system is precisely because you wouldn't call the CDC
Yeah, you wouldn't do that. So the doctor does it for you now the issue that
Where you could get to Alex may be having a kernel of truth
Although he's still making stuff up is that like if you have a headache that could be an adverse reaction
Yeah, and you might not report that right, but it would be something so trivial that you don't seek help with it
And you might not even know if it's related, right?
So yeah
Maybe one in ten if you count like minor nonsense that maybe you maybe my back hurts
Yeah, slight dizziness is off a headache or yeah, or I got up too quick
But but what he's saying is just a load of shit. Yeah, and I honestly think that some of the stuff that he's saying
Has a real potential for public health
Problems and then you look at what else it does. Holy mackerel
When you come across a COVID virus the most common in the world coronavirus in the future
Most people will have a violent autoimmune reaction and they're gonna call that COVID
2022 probably be the name. I think about 2022. They'll hit us with it. Maybe sooner. Hell maybe next month
And it'll be everybody dying. Oh
By the way, that's what I didn't tell you
Most of these old people that died they said it already tested positive for COVID obviously most that's fraud
But that's the thing. They also said that that's what Wolfgang would are
Another scientist said they said if you've already had a similar COVID
Virus or a coronavirus the same family or COVID-19 the vaccine may cause an autoimmune response and kill you
Or make you very sick or later. It'll cause the autoimmune response when you come in contact with one
I mean, this is a death sentence total death sentence
And they're just people to be dying all around you. It'll just be Bill Gates up there smiling like a psychotic at you
I mean, they're never gonna get away with this never they're crazy
But Hitler didn't get away with it either, but he wanted to kill everybody
Yeah, that's uh, that's deeply deeply irresponsible, yeah
Yeah, this is this is fuck
Yeah
Like this is the level of thinking that this is is which level like this is like a pure
We've never advanced beyond thinking that the person with two cats is actually behind illness
Yep, that's where we're at. That's where Alex's brain is at. How is developmentally?
How is it that we can develop a vaccine for a brand new virus in less than a year?
Yeah, and at the same time we have people who are like nah, nah, nah, nah
See if you're physically unattractive chances are you're the one killing everybody
Yeah, and I read I read a little bit about some of the folks who have died after getting the vaccine and some of them
did test positive for COVID and with the belief that they
people who were writing about this had were that
They had gotten the vaccine when they had already been infected
It was in the incubation period right and then the vaccine wouldn't be effective right at that point. It's too late
yeah, and you know you're talking about high-risk communities and people who are prioritized for getting the vaccines and
You know that doesn't it's not even that high of a number either like it's it's not in the thousands like Alex is saying
But but either way like this this kind of misinformation it stands to really
Persuade people to have either a belief or an inclination to not disbelieve
That this shot is a death sentence. Yeah, and that can be really really dangerous. Yeah, it's hard even to imagine like
Okay, it's not the best
Vaccine and it does have some of my adverse reactions, but it's gonna save a million lives
You know like or like that kind of level of thing where it's like yeah, that's worth it
Yeah, half a million people are dead man. Yeah, Alex does the straw man shit all the time of like everybody pretends
The vaccines are totally safe and like there's never been a bad reaction like no no one says that
That's a fake argument that you're making in order to to to straw man, and yep
Yeah, it's just it's it's childish, and I wish that people
Would treat him and his arguments with the disdain that they deserve yeah
Um so Alex gets to talking about Bitcoin
Of course yes of course because Elon Musk
It was just on Rogan apparently again, and maybe he is into Bitcoin now sure
He also has a guy named bit boy on as a guest later. I'm a motherfucking bit boy
the weekend
You want to laugh, but you can't
That was that look oh, I can't laugh at this it's a cuz it's wrong
Dan I'm well past the point of righteous violets that was going through
Anyway, this guy is just a youtuber who's into Bitcoin sure to currencies sure his interview is not interesting
I'm surprised youtubers are always fascinating
I bet he actually has some interesting things to say and I don't get it
I didn't get any sense of like you know him being a bigot, but I don't know sure
He just was talking about crypto currencies
Anyway, Alex is against them, but then he interviews this guy
In a pretty positive. This is very confusing gotcha, and there is a global government openly
Announcing itself and they need to end the dollar as the world reserve currency and bring in the new global digital currency
Which will be based on Bitcoin?
Which again is obviously a giant inside job from the beginning just like you and I told you that ten years ago
And now you can see it, so why are you having a long interview with a guy? Who's into Bitcoin? Who's giving a really positive?
Perspective it's very confusing. Yeah, also Alex hasn't been super negative about Bitcoin
It's much more complicated than that yeah
Yeah, he hasn't been a promoter of it
But if he actually thought it was something that was meant to replace the dollar as part of the globalist plan
He wouldn't have had Max Kaiser on for the last ten years on his show to constantly promote it
Yeah, that would be an issue. Yeah, he wouldn't
His behavior would be totally different, and that's the same actually as with Q
Yeah
If Alex actually thought that there wasn't some thing in it for him to not fully denounce
X Y or Z whether it's QAnon or Bitcoin sure his behavior would be totally different
He thought that there was an angle yeah, he could play some sort of hedge in the middle
Yeah, and then once that was clearly not the case. Oh, I've known this was a setup all along right bullshit. Yeah
yeah, his
His pattern of like denouncing something softly and gently, but then having pro guests on it for an
eternity is
Clear evidence of some sort of like issue he has with I can't piss someone off
There's always someone that can't be pissed off in these situations
Or or just like gather might be might be worthwhile to not alienate this
Yeah, maybe maybe down the road QAnon becomes something that is profitable for me
So let's keep that lane open until it's too late sure and then I can always have been against it with with the
Bitcoin it could have collapsed left people
I with nothing sure could have been something that everyone hates and then Alex it'd be great for him to be able to say I've
Been against the whole time right right right, but maybe it's a cool thing
And then I could be like I've had max Kaiser promoting it on my show for ten years
I'm an old-school Bitcoin guy sure you know if you play both sides, and then you look like a prophet
Yeah, yeah, but you're not you're just dumb dumb. Yeah, anyway
Trump is on trial because
He said some things sure that's people did some things sure and hey what about Kamala Harris
She said some things who hasn't said things
here is
Kamala Harris cackling like the witch she is
Talking about killing Trump will she be
Impeached here it is if you had to be stuck in an elevator with either President Trump Mike Pence or Jeff Sessions who would it be?
Just
One of us have to come out alive
You know what people think I was overdoing it play it again. She can hear the actual cackle
I mean, I hear they're coming out with a new Wizard of Oz she's got the job as the wicked witch here
It is a possible interpretation of that joke is that she would kill herself before going in an elevator with one of them
Yeah, so I don't know. I think this is a little bit thin
You think also the laughter and crowd applause?
Indicates that this is a different setting maybe maybe I I would argue that there is a different contextual
interpretation of someone saying a joke on the Ellen show and someone saying that you should kill one's political enemies in a
Rally after having said that killing them is fine for a long time. I would be dealing with this situation
Entirely differently if Ellen DeGeneres killed Jeff Sessions in an elephant. I would be furious
I would say that Kamala Harris was very irresponsible
a generous killed Jeff Sessions in an elevator then we would be I mean
How could you not that yeah, then she should be impeached? Yeah, I mean, it's still hard not to add the context of
the cop was killed and to
Yeah, so in terms of the the impeachment stuff from the the day before on the 10th
Um, Alex doesn't deal with much of the let's say previously unreleased videos
There are real problems over their issues. Well, I mean they certainly contradict his narrative quite a bit
it's particular again resonating the
People chanting hang Mike Pence and like people wandering through the halls yelling for Nancy Pelosi
The just the person the first person going through the window wearing full tactical gear
Confederate flags following along. Yeah, I
Think that everybody has different images. That'll probably stick with them
that chanting was one that was really really tough for me and particularly because you know, I
Spent so much time with Alex's rhetoric and his narratives and like how directly counter
This reality is to the game that he's spinning totally. So he just pretends a lot of that didn't happen
Yeah, sure, but this Raskin guy, right the lead
Counsel, yeah
He I know that from watching the impeachment not from earlier before that
Said some things that Paul Joseph Watson wrote an article about that. Alex is pissed about
Oh now, let's start getting to it the slimiest rat-like creature
I've seen in a while. Jamie Raskin is when the leader of the persecution
He said that Trump impaled police and stabbed them to death on the 6th and then on the 6th Trump supporters burned
down a church
Well, it's funny because that church is the one that BLM firebombed that church
Ladies and gentlemen is the church that Trump wouldn't visited with the Bible
Why would you tell such a gigantic lie out in the open?
Why would you say that St. John's Church was burned by Trump supporters? He didn't
Well, that would be an issue. That's like saying
That Abraham Lincoln killed Abraham Lincoln
No, John Wilkes Booth did I mean, it's just it's just a it's like saying my background. My background is red
You're like no your background is green today
What I mean you might as well just get up there and say the sky is red at high noon in Texas
But again, why does he do that? Because he's a lying criminal
Everything comes out of his fat mouth so loud. I put out all these fake videos everything else and then his fake crying
He couldn't get an acting part in a third party
I couldn't get an acting part in a third-grader play with that kind of projection. Man, the master of similes, Alex Jones
Projection. Yeah. Wild. Yeah, outrageous. Yeah, so
Raskin didn't say that people were stabbed on January 6th
He was clearly talking about people who were using flag poles as a weapon against Capitol Police because that's a super resonant image
The idea that they're the Capitol Police and they're being attacked by something that has the flag on it. Sure
It is hard to avoid. Yeah, if we're taking things super strictly literally then yes
No one was run through with a pole
But that kind of gives you a sense of the difficulty that Alex and his ilk have spinning this stuff
The previously unreleased video, like I said of the storming really disprove a lot of Alex's narratives
And you know, you really just don't want to deal with that stuff
So you retreat to dumb semantics arguments that mean nothing to pretend that that's the entire argument against Trump and it's all a lie
No one was impaled. No one was impaled by a javelin thrown from 40 feet away
We were slamming the cops head in a door. Come on. Get it right. As for the church burning Alex is playing dumb
Raskin said quote that's before the second million maga march a rally that ended in serious violence and even the burning of a church
This sentence doesn't say who burned a church
But Alex and Paul Joseph Watson who wrote the article that Alex is covering are pretending that it's making an accusatory claim
The essence of what Raskin is saying is that Trump has a pattern of inciting events that lead to violence, which isn't really debatable
So Alex and Paul have created this fake claim to respond to
They're also pretending that Raskin must be talking about the burning of the St.
John's church, which was the church that Trump did his photo op in back in May
The person or persons responsible for that fire are still unknown
So Alex can't actually prove that anyone from one of his villain groups did it
Sure, but he's just decided to report as if that is the case. Yeah, as long as it's unknown. That's fine for him. Sure
Raskin could have spoken more clearly
But what he was talking about was the proud boys vandalizing the Asbury United Methodist Church and burning banners
They've stolen from the church that said Black Lives Matter
This is a secondary instance of Alex creating a fake thing to argue against and he knows exactly what Raskin is talking about
The guy who took credit for burning that church's sign has been a guest on Alex's show and the night of January 5th
Alex's employee Owen Schroyer recorded himself burning a Black Lives Matter flag in D.C. Yeah, there's that one
Yeah, come on grow up asshole. No shit
Anyway, what's really funny about this is with that lead-up that Alex has, he didn't actually watch this clip
Oh, that's a problem. And you can kinda tell at the end because
In the lead-up to this he's saying that Raskin claimed that
There was all this on January 6th. Totally. Whoops
And just listen to this BS
And that's before the second million mega march a rally that ended in serious violence
And even the burning of a church
And as the president forecast it was only the beginning
on December 19th
18 days before January 6th. He told his base about where the battle would be that they would fight next
January 6th would be wild, he promised. Be there, we'll be wild, said the president of the United States of America
And that too turned out to be true
You'll see in the days that followed, Donald Trump continued to aggressively promote January 6th to his followers
Okay, so he's saying that the march that we coordinated that was peaceful
That happened in December, was the June 1st BLM event that burned the church
Did he say that?
It's like six months apart
Is that why you didn't say that?
And it's a public event that happened. Trump went and visited it. So what does this guy do? He inverts it
So you can hear him kind of re-spinning in real time because he realizes that the clip doesn't say what he had already prefaced it to say
And you can hear it very clearly
You can hear it very clearly. Oh, okay, okay
All right, see now what he's saying is something different from what I said he would say and uh
So he's uh
Liar! So whose fault do you think it is that Trump has bad lawyers?
Ooh, I let's see would it be the entire legal profession thinking that his case is both nonsensical and unwinnable or
Him? Try again. Oh specific person. Oh, Nancy Pelosi? Nope. Oh, here's Bruce Castor. Let's play clip three
Trump's a so-called lawyer who it turns out has sued Trump before. Oh, yeah, Trump didn't know that. This is people they give him and
And this other guy called he called him another one lawyers called Trump a crook just three months ago and said he's a horrible person
And that's his lawyer. That's who Trump gets
He can say well Trump's an idiot. Yeah, I don't even know how to use Google, but my god
He better search, but see it's all
It's all the son-in-law
Man, Trump is under the spell of that Kushner. Okay. All right. It's Kushner. Yeah, okay
Wow, all right a lot of buck stops there kind of show the secret leader of the deep state has been Kushner the entire time
I think Pachannik has said that maybe yeah, I think this is a relatively Shakespearean tale
Of a son-in-law betraying his father
I would love to just be able to be like my dream job if I could have it
Would be to be a person who hacks in to Alex's earpiece
and
I could just respond like from Fletch to I've never seen Fletch to but
Alex has an earpiece in that the producers talk to him
Yeah, and just to be able to hack in and respond in real time would be so great because I just hear that as we boo
Well, you're saying that the bad lawyers who
He hired a lawyer who sued him in the past and he didn't know about that and this is Kushner's you could absolutely
absolutely convince him
Absolutely convince him that that is an anthropomorphized voice in his head. Oh, yeah
There is no doubt in my mind that he would have that like Alex. Oh, I got my self doubt in my ear again
I'm your conscience and that was bad. That was dumb
Isn't this guy supposed to be king shit hero guy and he?
Hired a lawyer who sued him because his son-in-law tricked him. Yeah. Yeah. Yep
This is this is stuff that even this is the man. I want leading the country. Yeah, so
Alex, like I said, there's not there's not as much about the impeachment as as maybe would be
Interesting or seems should be merited by yeah this
show
But he spends quite a while talking to bit boy. Sure. He's a motherfucking bit boy. Yeah
We have two clips left. Okay, cuz I'm not talking about bit boy. No, I'm good
We have two clips and I want to ask you if you'd rather go culture war or gossip first
whoo, I feel like
Culture war is going to be more offensive and yet somehow I feel like gossip also might wind up with some really fucked up shit
So let's go with culture war. Okay Disney. All right. See I knew it
Um
Disney has fired Gina Carano. Ah
So from the Mandalorian so a man who is absolutely not a fan of Star Wars absolutely not
Appreciative of Star Wars at all. It's very angry about one particular character being removed from the Mandalorian. I didn't know that
If I were Disney, I would blame her for Grogu
On her way out. Yeah on the way out she'd be like toss all of our baggage onto her. What else do we got?
Let's get all of it. Yeah
Everyone else everyone be mad at her for all of this shit
So in reality, what happened was that she had some social media posts
Including a particularly offensive one where she compared being Republican to being a Jew in the Holocaust
I
People didn't care much for that. No, and she was out
Alex may not quite understand why she got fired. Yeah, what's crazy about it is
Disney's virtue signaling
Kicking this former MMA lady out because she looks like a big tough man
That's the image they want as women as you know
All the leaders what now and her idiots goes back to married with children and all those shows where dad's always a moron
I mean that's come out of memos not just gamer gate today. I
Want to show an emasculated society, but but even that wasn't enough for her playing the part of the big male hero
Pedro is the Mandalorian us trends after Star Wars cancels Gina Carano
And I'm not saying she's a bad actress and I'm not saying I dislike women that are strong and have that
a
Amazon type look I think it's very attractive
But the point is she actually groveled in and said it was so horrible what happened the Jews
What she was bad what Hitler did and they called an anti-semitic Wow?
Wow
Alex may not quite get the conversation. Oh
Boy, Alex Alex. You might be too used to people saying worse things than that
Yeah, I mean like that's anti-semitic well
It actually does make sense cuz Alex has compared himself to a Jewish person during the Holocaust like so for him
Yeah, obviously yeah
That's what she's saying is like
Almost like he's like you're gonna fire for her for that. I have Steve be on my show all the time
Yeah, he's throwing anti-semitic shit out like fucking candy in a parade
Yeah, it's it's interesting to me the part that I find the most interesting outside of Alex's bizarre
Need to have a sexual psychodrama with his audience. Yeah, I don't know why you need to do that
Oh, I can't stand that they put strong female women in roles and make them look strong and powerful now
It doesn't mean I don't want to have sex with them. Hey, but now this is something you should deal with your therapist
It's not your audience
I absolutely have to air out this problem that I can't sublimate which is that I both attracted to strong powerful women and want them
Destroyed it's weird
I wasn't quite sure where he was going as he was talking about this like what side he was gonna land on cuz he
Was being very weird, but then when he said she groveled and said the Holocaust was bad, which it is
Why did you say groveled? Well, I mean when you say the Holocaust is bad
Obviously you're caving to the ADL and the Ku Klux Klan. Why do I don't understand that at all?
Anyway, what should she have said that Hitler was a complete badass?
Would that have been what she should have said?
Maybe anyway now we get to gossip
It is it would be kind of ridiculous
If the guy who said that Hitler was a complete stud and a badass was like, yeah, Gina should have been fired
I wish that I had a soundboard so I could just play that
Yeah, all the time. I'm afraid that there may be new listeners who don't know that we had a drop
That we used to play where Alex says that Hitler and Stalin are total badasses
complete
Badasses studs. That's how we used to thank people for
Yeah, so we move on to gossip to close the show
I'll say one of the more rewarding things about listening to Alex's show is getting to find little
Threads that you can pull that you wouldn't you know, you'd never had like there was the story of Buckley's birthday party
Oh, sure. Yeah a couple years back the ever-growing changing story
There was the Nazi hat
Sure, sure
There's little glimpses that you get into Alex's life. The globalist in the hot tub is always a classic Barton Springs tales
Oh, yeah, all the times he would go down to Barton Springs. Yes, the hike and bike trail
Tails of the hike and bike a lot of interesting things have happened on that trail
Another thing is that we know a lot about Alex's wife's tennis habits a lot more than I would have expected to learn
We know that her tennis partner I believe
Was scoping out antifa. Yep
Has strong ability to do some reconnaissance
She had some Intel on antiva and now we learn that
Maybe not all is good in the world of Alex's wife's tennis. Oh, no, maybe there are some haters
I was playing tennis
With these women she's down a few years and one of them walks over the real ugly look on her face
And I like this what's wrong just I just what's wrong is what you did at the Capitol tried to overthrow our country
Well, I said we were protesting the election. That was a handful. It was just oh, yeah, right
sure
This is this whole act of like, you know, oh gosh what you did. Oh, it's like the Democrats were just saying
Jamie Raskin says Trump supporters burned down the church to that BLM did publicly that quick
Yeah, she's getting the news that quick the turnaround is fast on that. It's quick. I
Mean I understand that it's most likely just a device for him to do like a character or whatever
But I love that there's a like an entire genre within Alex's world of like stories where he complains about the people
yeah, his wife plays tennis with yeah, he's almost doing like a
A nursery rhyme levels of explaining things in in like entail, you know
Like this is why we don't touch fire because there's a rabbit that goes around and it touched fire one time and you were like
This is bad. This is her tennis instructor was like, hey, we should listen to this guy and that's bad
See now children. Let's move on. I feel like more his
his wife's tennis
World is like a world that's populated by fictional characters that he just gets to cast in little plays
It's like a little anime. Yeah. Yeah, whenever he needs somebody to have seen antifa setting up at the grocery store
Well, it's somebody involved in my wife's tennis games
you need somebody to play the role of
nosy
judgmental
Democrat it's somebody that my wife's playing tennis with now it is strangely enough the only both
a combined tennis club and private investigatory
Agency on you know, it's like whenever you first saw Baskin-Robbins and a KFC in the same place
You're like, what are we doing here? That's the tennis club. I think you're thinking of Dunkin Donuts
It's all the same shit. There's never been a Taco Bell and KFC is what I meant
What am I supposed to know never be a Baskin-Robbins?
It's not the same company
I'm talking Taco Bell and Pizza Hut. They're all young right? Right, right, right understand this and then
Duncan and Baskin-Robbins, I think
A lot of me mistaking this, you know, it's a meal Taco Bell KFC and Pizza Hut all together with good meal, but
Don't eat it before you go play tennis without his wife
you will you will probably wind up taking a nap and missing out on some crucial information either that or you'll become a story that
Alex tells on the show
About somebody who ate too much shitty food before playing tennis with his wife
That's somehow illustrates how the Democrats are evil
That's the new way to fuck with Alex Jones
You join his wife's tennis club and you just every now and again walk up to her with a ugly look on your face and
Just say something
Reasonable. I if I had all the time in the world. Mm-hmm
I'd still not do that. That sounds like a real wife's time. Absolutely not
Anyway, Jordan we come to the end of this and I expected a little bit more fireworks, but I mean he is mad sure
Don't get me wrong. He's mad sure sure, but it almost makes more sense to me
You know like you're saying this is a coherent ish response. And yeah
like he shouldn't be
Like upset about the impeachment thing. He think he's supposed to think that Trump won the election. Yeah
No, that's why we were should be disappointed in whatever
Defense there is because they're not saying that Trump won the election, right?
Yeah, it's even better for him that they're terrible lawyers. Yeah, because then you can pretend that they're
Sandbagging on purpose, of course, and then whenever they whenever Trump wins and is acquitted
He's gonna be like see even in spite of the lawyers that the globalists gave him right? Yeah, he's so innocent
Mm-hmm. His defense was literally two men going bi POS
For four hours and he won. Yeah
Anyway, we'll see how this develops indeed. We will but until then Jordan we have a website. We do have a website
It's knowledgefight.com. Yep. We're also on
We are on Twitter. Is that an algorithm? If I go to pet Jordan? Yeah, we're also on Facebook
We are lazy. Will you do that downscales in that if you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area
We'll be back, but until then I'm Neo, I'm Leo, I'm DZXClark, I'm Daryl Rundis
I have no other place to mention this and it it seems perfect here. Danny
Sent me a message and Norm Pattis's beard is fucking crazy. Norm Pattis trim your goddamn beard. It is inappropriate
Anyway, Andy in Kansas. You're on the air. Thanks for holding
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan. I love your work. I love you.