N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am SWEATING
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledgefight
knowledgefight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
saying we are the bad guys
knowledgefight
Dan and Jordan, knowledgefight
RIDDLER, RIDDLER, RIDDLER
I need, I need money
Andy and Kansas, Andy and, Andy and
Stop it, Andy and, Andy and Kansas
RIDDLER, RIDDLER, RIDDLER
It's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan
I love your work
knowledgefight
N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're a couple dudes, I can sit around, drink novelty beverages
and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are Dan
Jordan
Dan
I have a quick question for you
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, Jordan, is Pannino's Pizza
Pannino's Pizza
Okay
I used to live fairly close to them and it was sort of a
bit of a thing where I'd go there and get a slice
pretty regularly
Sure
Like it, good, slice
Good, it's good stuff
I have moved since then, I no longer live near Pannino's
But I did see that there was a place that will go nameless
because I don't actually remember what the name of the
place was, but there was a by the slice pizza place
Alright
Nearly near my house, I was walking in the terrible snow
Sure, sure
A couple days ago and I saw this and I said
It's tough to walk out there, you built up a hunger
I said I would like a slice, see this is as good as Pannino's
Right
Terrible
Not as good as Pannino's
No
So my bright spot is remembering how much better
Pannino's was
No, a couple days after that I ordered Pannino's
because I was pissed
I'll see you in hell
Yeah, so I ordered it and it was as good as I remember
Shout out
That's fantastic
Congratulations to Pannino's for making good pizza
Sure, how about you?
My bright spot, Dan, is I finally tried out Hades
Oh yeah, the video game
Fantastic
Really, really fun, it's nice and it's got a great
I like the mechanic of the like, you're supposed to die
You die and that's part of the story
It's that Sisyphean trapped in the sense of
And you get to talk to Sisyphus too
Yeah, exactly, it's very fun
It's a nice little take on mythology, I enjoy it
I don't know if I have made this complaint
but I have one complaint about the game
What's that?
And that is I don't think Hephaestus is in it
I have not seen Hephaestus yet
Hephaestus is the reason, Hephaestus should be making all of these buffs that you're getting
He should, he's the armor of the gods
Yeah, yeah, that's a good point
Yeah, very glaring omission
That is a huge one
Yeah, anyway that was the one thing I just thought when I was playing it
But yeah, it's a lot of fun, I'm glad you enjoyed it
It's a good time
I recommended it to another friend and she enjoyed it quite a bit as well
Yeah, it was delightful
Seems like it's a beloved game
It's a good game
Seems like all the good reviews are merited
Do you know what it makes me, it reminds me of an old, old PlayStation 1 game called Azure Dreams
Okay
And it was that same kind of infinite dungeon crawler that would populate a new dungeon for you every time
But you would capture monsters, it was like a mixture of Pokemon and that same kind of Hades dungeon crawler
That sounds fun
Fantastic game
Yeah, it was that weird kind of PS1 game though where it was like, also there's a dating simulator for some reason
You know, you're like, I don't need this guys
I've heard the relationship system in Hades compared to that as well
Really?
A dating simulator kind of thing
Oh yeah, that's a good point
Because you have to give gifts to all those people
You do give gifts, that's right
And boost your relations
Yeah, and that opens up different, yeah, yeah, no, that's almost exactly what it is
This to Hades is a rip-off
They remade Azure Dreams a very weird PlayStation 1 game
But without a Pokemon
Yeah, that's true, you don't really
Anyway, Jordan, today we have an interesting episode to go over
We're going to be talking about Valentine's Day 2021, Blackjack
I was even ready for it that time, I was like so prepared
I was hoping I could distract you by not saying the date, the holiday
Talking about February 14th, Sunday, Alex has a special
Every year he does a special Valentine's Day episode
I just love it
Well, it's a family show and you know
I'm being completely facetious, this is not a special Valentine's Day show
I'm fairly certain that I wasn't being serious about it being a family show
So we have some interesting fun things to talk about
But first let's say thank you to some folks who have signed up and are supporting the show
Oh, that's fun
So first, sign me up to be a globalist
Thank you so much, you are now a Policy Wonk globalist
I'm a Policy Wonk
Thank you so much
Next, Molly M, thank you so much, you are now a Policy Wonk
I'm a Policy Wonk
Thanks Molly
Next, Rand D, that's W-R-E-N
Thank you so much, you are now a Policy Wonk
I'm a Policy Wonk
Thanks, Ren
That's a great name
That's a classic, classic name
Also classic, Truthquark, thank you so much, you are now a Policy Wonk
I'm a Policy Wonk
Thanks Truthquark
Next, Michael, thank you so much you are now a Policy Wonk
I'm a Policy Wonk
Thanks Michael
And finally, Bill Walton's favourite tie dye t-shirt, thank you so much you are now a Policy Wonk
I'm a Policy Wonk
Thank you very much
Bill Walton's favourite tie dye t-shirt
Now it's interesting Jordan cuz Austin right now is in the state of Texas. That's true currently it has been for a while
But right now in the state of Texas
They're experiencing an incredible ice storm, and I hope everybody you know all of our listeners in that part of the world are staying safe
It ain't no joke yeah from what I understand. It's not for you guys. We're we're meant for that
That's where we're that's what we're for even us. That'd be a challenge. Oh, yeah, it's not fun. No
um and and so Alex decided who cares I'm coming into the
So he does come in for a Sunday show on Valentine's Day when he could have very easily done it remotely
Not done the show no problem Harrison Smith ramble about white genocide everybody been fine
Yeah, so here's an out-of-context drop from today's show
So here's the video the granny being thrown off the cliff
Okay, okay, all right glad all right glad you came into work. I I assume that wasn't a Walker, Texas
Ranger kind of situation here no
So Alex came in and he starts off the show as anyone would try if they had just come in to work
Through driving through chaos, and that is complaining about driving
This has got to be an incredible show today because I've grown up
Born in Texas
And I've grown up in people not being able to drive with ice on the roads cuz it only happens a few times a year
But I've never seen anything like this. This was road warrior level. I probably saw a
Hundred wrecked cars on the way here smash signs glass
Firefighters trying to block major roads
I wouldn't even be here if I hadn't just gone ahead and gone around them because I was driving my wife's all-wheel vehicle
I was driving my wife's all-wheel vehicle my favorite thing about
I need more explanation for how he went around him if his next line is with an all-wheel drive vehicle
We'll get to it. Okay. Let's talk more about that
Okay, um, but I do love the idea that he's starting off the show with like this better be a fucking great
Road warrior, it's gotta be worth it. Yeah, so you you're asking about this this car situation
Yeah, little did you know he would just talk more about well and this basically turns into a car commercial sure
Oh
I tried to leave the house in my a truck and it was not four-wheel drive and that that truck isn't and I had to turn
Around go back. I got her car
That's the only good thing that German car is good for but she wanted an Audi and man
I was just going cuz I live in West like up these big hills. Everybody else is wrecked
I mean just wreck I saw 300 wreck cars not a hundred it was
And I'm just like going I mean I'm not trying to an Audi commercial here ladies and gentlemen, but my lord that vehicle is incredible
And there are all these other four-wheel drive cars just wrecked everywhere Range Rovers are all-wheel drive
They were wrecked Subarus wrecked everywhere that Audi was like I was just a robot on rails through black ice
20 miles the office unbelievable
But a lot of people died in Texas, it's really sad Jesus Christ tonal shift Wow
That sounds sincere. Yeah
A lot of people died Audi's great, but a lot of people died because they didn't buy an Audi
I'm not making a car commercial
But if you don't buy an Audi you're gonna die about a minute of rambling about a great his wife's car is yeah
We leading into going out to break reminding you that there are have been fatalities and there have that's that's fucked up
Yeah, it's it's a little uncouth. Yeah, it makes me feel bad for making fun of something. That's awful that he did
Yeah, and now I feel like
One degree removed from being an awful person. I think that's what we do though. We live in that shame
Yeah, that's fair so I wanted to cover this episode number one cuz it's Valentine's Day number two because
This is the point at which Alex would know that Trump had been acquitted
Yes
He did his he did a special report on Saturday
Which I tried to watch a bit of but it was mostly him talking about vaccines and I got really bored
She wanted to hear about his take on the yeah
He had said it was a setup
He said this was this whole trial was a sham and it was all just set up to get Trump
So now what happens whenever it worked out the way that we all knew it was going to well
I think Alex has a I mean, it's bullshit, but he has actually a pretty decent spin. I think all right
We have the insane trial of the president that they suddenly ended ish you had three days Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday
Ten hours a day of total lies against the president 30 hours of garbage
Three hours by his lawyers doing half a decent job
I'm gonna kill Trump the vice president. We're gonna burn everything down and they had to put their tail between their legs and drop it
Because it was another giant fraud. Yeah, so I mean that's that's not a terrible spin of like AI
They showed all these videos of Democrats saying things and then sure sure he had to quit him
Yeah, it's having a conversation about like they weren't gonna I mean they weren't going to vote in
a convicted and the fact that what how many Republicans voted with the Democrats
Seven, I believe more than one is a crazy number. Yeah. Yeah, like that's it. That was a pretty high one of them was
Directly going to be murdered. So there's that I would I would assume he would be a guaranteed. Yeah vote to come Romney's a lock
I'm just saying that if you're going to be murdered, like I assume if Mike Pence was in the Senate
He would be like, yeah, I'm gonna have to
No hanging for me, you know, like that kind of feel. Mm-hmm. I prefer not to acquit this
Yeah, and Alex doesn't want to talk about like things like McConnell's comments about
Totally is it was his fault, but we have a constitutional
Yeah, cuz that that just that gets too messy that's so stupid
Yeah, I I feel like you should know you should be embarrassed if you even try and say they did a half good job
Van der Veen, you should be embarrassed. That was really really shameful stuff. It was yeah, although
You know, we learned a little bit about what happens in Philly. That's true. He did learn a lot about Philly little Philly Delfia
Yeah, yeah, I enjoyed that the portion that you and I watched
He was talking about Philly and then a different point. He said Philly Delfia
Yep. Yep. Yeah. Yeah, that's good stuff. Yep. That's good stuff
so when you're you know, a radio show host and you come in on the Valentine's Day Eve through a
Movie like storm sure. Yes a perfect storm. Yes, you got it. You got a
Cover the important stuff, right? You got to take care of the really important business this Audi
We've got a lot. We've got Saturday Night Live is on a jag. They're on a roll
more jokes about pedophilia not existing and
more attacks about children being abused
Ritualistically because I can tell you a large part of the writing staff are pedophiles and our devil worshippers Wow
I'm gonna I'm gonna have to send a couple of texts
I
Heard some disturbing news Alex Jones is informed me
That is a bit a bit much
So what's going on? Is that the last two weeks there have been QAnon jokes on
night live sure sure sure the first one was about the Super Bowl commercials and
there was a
A commercial for QAnon where it's like Papa John's Pizza, you know, we know sex trafficking in the basement. Yeah
And then apparently this week Kate McKinnon did a character where she was a witch
Like a QAnon witch who was really interested in eating children
You know, I did an interview with weekend update and Alex is like they're up there pretending. This is the news
Yeah, yeah, yeah, no, it's SNL man. He's very mad. He's very mad
Have you ever imagined for a second?
What the SNL cast that we grew up with would have done if QAnon was around then there?
They just what is Chris Farley gonna do about QAnon? They're just not prepared for that kind of stuff
That's just not in the in there in their wheelhouse. Yeah, I don't want Adam Sandler doing prank QAnon fun. Never mind
I want Adam Sandler doing prank QAnon phone calls. Sure. Yeah, um, so that's important business
Sure, very important to talk about how SNL is making jokes about QAnon
Yeah, that Alex tries to misconstrue as them making jokes. The pedophilia doesn't exist. Yeah, good job. Yeah
and other
Things he does are you know kind of distasteful, too
I don't I don't know how to say this, but I found this really repulsive. Okay, Alex plays
a
Fight fight fight fight fight fight. Alex plays video of the pileup it
Outside Fort Worth. Oh that giant 100 plus car pileup
That's fucked he plays video that someone captured from like the other lanes
Yeah, and so it's just playing the entire
like
Collision, it's terrifying and there's no real value to it. But Alex tries to pretend that there is yeah, but I want to give you
Some viewer discretion when we come back. I don't show
horrible tragedies
To just show you a horrible tragedy because some people like a train wreck I see this I
Was shown this on Friday by the crew. I
Didn't know after 24 hours of this stuff happening up by Fort Worth in Dallas of what really happened
I've seen the helicopter footage of a couple hundred cars all piled up
We come back. I'm gonna show you what really happened
From someone on the ground when it happened up close
I've never seen anything in a Hollywood movie like this when cars are crashing and flipping and exploding
wait till you see on the ground the actual pileup and the reason I'm gonna play it
Will be explained when we come back
So viewer discretion advised because people were dying
seven people died on the footage you're about to see and
I'm showing it to save some lives and to illustrate something
Okay, let's stop right there
We're not gonna be on air in a year and you backed us last year
I told you that last year you came through we made it this year a little bit in the black just don't do it
We'll be able to keep our projects going. You don't have to fund some other secret projects
We're working on gosh. I could do a lot better if I had more money. I'm not
I'm about to show you footage of seven people dying. Yeah. No, I need money to stay on air. Yeah
Yeah, this was repulsive that is fucked. I was
shocked by the
Sort of the gross coldness. Yeah, the cynical ness of this the like and when he was saying
I'm gonna show you what really happened. I was like, are you trying to say there's a conspiracy here?
He wasn't there is no real value to this unless
He wants to turn into a road safety show sure and then it's still a little bit first of all too soon
I don't think you could use this footage to illuminate any particular finer points of hazardous driving
Yeah, it was just like there is no reason to play this other than shock value or something
It's it's offensive. Yeah, I mean, it's it's nakedly
exploitative and macabre in a way that like makes you
like
It's hard not to think that he gets some sort of like weird fucked up like well
You know that the people who watched faces of death where you're like
There's something that you get out of this that I'll never understand. Yeah, I just won't be there for you
Yeah, you know like that kind of thing
Yeah, it's a deal-breaker. Yeah, it's a real big. Yeah, it's real bad
Yeah
So he said that there's a reason and it's gonna become clear next segment
And this next clip kind of is him expressing what that reason is
But I I would say one this reason is stupid. That's to say bad second
And the connection that he's trying to make you don't need to watch the video to get I'm showing you footage of Dallas
Texas a live
Shop there from top of one of the little tallest buildings. You can see it as a icy wasteland. No one on the streets
Now if you're in Chicago or you're in New York you laugh at that you say hell we drive all the time
Well, we're not used to it only happens once or twice a year and hundreds of people die
Statewide when it unfolds and that's a teaching moment
Americans haven't been under a Hitler
They haven't been under a Stalin or a Mao or Fidel Castro or a Hugo Chavez
So what he's trying to illustrate with playing this video is these people in Texas aren't used to ice driving
And so there's a giant pileup much like Americans aren't used to dealing with a Hitler or a Stalin
Yeah, and the tyranny and therefore we're metaphorically gonna have a pileup
Now you don't need to watch that video to make that metaphor at all. There's absolutely no reason
It doesn't add to your understanding of the metaphor. Yeah, you could just say it. It doesn't matter
Yeah, and also what about fucking Obama? What about Bill Clinton? Nothing. They were fine
They weren't they were no big deal. They weren't working for the devil yet. I think they were according to him
He just didn't know wasn't comfortable enough talking about it. He didn't remember that they were also presidents
He was trying to pretend he was serious back then. Yeah
That's not good. No, I'm not like one of those people who says that everybody's the devil
I'm not like David Icke who have become my best friend in ten years
anyways, we've had about four devil presidents in my time and
All of those we've never even had to deal with anything new like a Joe Biden, right?
I just think I think it was it's
The most tenuous connection to make in order to justify playing this video
Yeah, and I don't respect the decision at all. I think it's disgusting and Alex even knows that
This is on the ground in the other lane
Radio listeners horrible footage. You're lucky. You're not seeing this 18-wheeler 50 miles. You're lucky. You're not seeing this
It gets worse ones going 70 in a minute. Alex is saying you're lucky
You're not seeing this to the radio audience Wow, but he's playing. I know you could just not know everybody could be lucky
Yeah, we could all be lucky right now. Yeah, I would like to be lucky. Yeah, don't be like you don't be like you're lucky
You're not watching my show. You're just listening to it. Yeah, you don't have to do it. It doesn't add anything
It's it was just outrageous. It's cuz he wanted to watch it
I think I think you might be might be onto something. It has to be something with with that's personal
I I found I found that disgusting and
unacceptable
Much like Alex's thinking pattern. Oh, that's fair. So he has decided that
Thousands are dead from the vaccine already when why well for what?
Thousands, okay. He just says it. Okay. Well, then I guess I will move on but you got to know this
Okay, it's actually probably 50 times higher. It's probably 50 times higher and we've now confirmed it. Okay, so
I have a stack of news here where there are thousands of dead admitted and I think about one in 50
Adverse reactions gets reported. So if thousands are dead, that's 50 times bigger
No one knows from the vaccines
So can you wonder can you identify like just really quickly?
It's like it's on a surface level the problem with that thinking
No, no, I don't see any problem if
Some then there's probably 50 times more. That means it's proven, right?
Yep, this is dumb
I mean like if you were to live if I were listening to a professor
I get a school right and I was in a lecture and they said something like that
I would not trust them to teach the rest of the class. I might withdraw. Yeah
Yeah, I wouldn't be real confident in a math class where they were like, okay, what's one plus one?
But remember one is probably 50 or it could be more or it could be fewer
No one knows who knows and I might be making up the one. Guess what? That one is the devil now
Yikes. Yeah, not good
So that that's the kind of thinking that Alex brings to the table just making assumptions and then multiplying things by whatever numbers he chooses
Yeah, whatever he feels good about today. And then the other thing he does is just make shit up
Like he does about this US News and World Reports article. Let's get to the good news
first
Because it's very very important the McRib the Pentagon touts vaccine
Administration rate amid concerns of widespread refusal US News and World Report
It goes on to say that the vast majority of the troops are
Refusing the vaccine because it's voluntary. They try to statistical manipulation
They go. Oh, but we did get a certain group that would said they'd take it and out of that group
80-plus percent did take it
So what do you do when the vast majority won't take it 98 percent?
You take the group that will take it and then say oh
80 plus percent of them 82 percent did
82% that's the statistical game. They play Alex absolutely has not read this article about the troops and vaccinations
He's claiming that the article says that there's a subsection of troops 82% of whom have received the vaccine
That's the statistical game Alex claims
This article is playing
The stat of 82% is actually in reference to the percentage of vaccines the Pentagon has received that have been administered
From the article quote Pentagon spokesman
John Kirby told reporters the department has so far ordered more than 1 million doses and as of Thursday morning had received roughly
968 thousand of those
800,000 or about 82 percent have been administered almost 600,000 were first doses and more than 200,000 or second doses
So they Alex has just seen the number and made up what it means. So they took the small subset of people
Otherwise known as the people who possibly could have gotten it and they're manipulating those numbers to say that those people did get it
I don't and then the people outside of those numbers. Well, they didn't get it
No, Alex has just skimmed the article seen numbers and written a story in his head about what those numbers mean
Yeah, this is what he does. He's really really bad at this. Yeah, I can't believe people actually take him seriously
Yeah, he does. He does seem to play mad libs and then search articles for like numbers to circle and like what if I put
82% here. Oh, it's great too. Cuz if you watch the video, he's got like 82% underline. Of course he does
Yes, that's exactly what he does. He goes through articles underlies the numbers
Do did it?
Saw the underlined 82%
He's like, I gotta figure out what I think that means. Yeah. Yeah. What could that 82% be? I can't possibly read a sentence
Can't be bothered to do that kind of work. It's very hard. Yeah, as he makes up some more shit about this article
We just saw on US News and World Report. I mean the military these evil people
I mean you heard you can't trust them from Joe Biden
They said pregnant women shouldn't take it because the British military said they shouldn't
They were the ones that started before the US military British military said yeah pregnant women shouldn't take we had a bunch of miscarriages
Oh, oh, but you don't say that in US News and World Report
You just say the US military the rank-and-file pull that out of their ass, didn't you?
Pisses me off. Excuse me. The pregnancy stuff is simply covered on a past episode
So I don't get too bogged down in it here
but this is just another instance of
Alex making more shit up about this article because he hasn't read it and he's just using it as a prop to get mad about
If Alex had actually read the article he would have found this quote from Air Force Brigadier General Paul Fredericks quote
Are we seeing people who are declining to it? Yes, I've had people say that for a variety of reasons
They're pregnant which is a very reasonable concern. They want to talk to their doctor first very reasonable concern
So there are people who've said they don't want to get it
This whole article is actually a big problem for Alex's narratives because he's been insistent that the vaccine is mandatory or it's gonna be mandatory
But the fact that the military is allowing enlisted persons to decide if they want to get it or not makes him have to change
The subject because the thing he was making his audience afraid about didn't happen
He now has to pivot to making it look like the enlisted persons who don't get the vaccine or somehow being maligned
Which this article doesn't support he didn't read it. No one listening is gonna read it. So this technique works perfectly
It's all just meaningless though. Yes, just like it might as well not to do this
yeah, and with the military that thing is you're most people aren't gonna look into it and for most people I would imagine that there
Makes a certain sort of like sense that well the military would be mandated to get it because they're the military
And that's that's the perception that Alex goes exactly and that's what you can you because most people wouldn't even
Follow up on that or especially not Alex's listeners. They'd be like, yeah, the military is forced to do everything. Mm-hmm
Yeah, so in this next clip Alex claims to have some information that he does not produce which means he's making it up
Yeah, I got so many adverse reaction death reports
I got over 200 upright here in just the last three days in the u.s. Alone. They shoot old people up
They're dead in 15 minutes in many cases
I mean folks here's thing. I used to be worried about stuff cuz I wanted to win the fight
I was worried about my family and everything. Oh things are so crazy. Now this ain't gonna go on long
Whatever is going on. Whatever is happening the number of people they're killing. Whatever is going on, baby
We ain't never seen nothing like this. This is big. I
Thought they put something in there kill you in five years. Oh, no, they don't kill your ass right now
So yeah, I mean if you have these these
200 why don't you talk about any of them doesn't produce any yeah
Yeah, I would I would I would argue that I mean, you know
If you just say something and you don't prove it or demonstrate it at all. I could just ignore it
Yeah, especially something that when tied to your other rhetoric
Is I guess license to go murder whomever you want, right?
Because they're killing you in 15 minutes. They're killing your grandma right now in 15 minutes Dan
Well, you thought you were gonna have a lovely five years to like hold your grandmother's hand as she dies from the government murder vaccine
But now you don't even have that much time
The only comfort I really take is hoping that people who listen to this would ask themselves at some point
Does Alex actually read the things he talks about and look into it and then that might erode public confidence in his dumbass
I could so a lot of the times when Alex is just rambling about something on air. It's something that our old friend
Paul Joseph Watson. Oh, I've written it and Paul has struck again Oh
Oh summit dot news links to BBC UK government could grant vaccine exemptions to ethnic minorities
I heard this a few months ago in NPR
Well black people are dumb, you know, we're liberals we can say that there did the UK say take shots
They just they're like the US military. They're dumb
You know, they just they just don't trust us. And so we're gonna have vaccine waivers for them
All right, but they won't be able to leave their house or have a job, you know how they are
But white people you're gonna take it
So show the black people not to be scared you roll up your sleeve and take your shot
This is just a total attack by these criminals to cover up Jeffrey Epstein and
Whoa
All the corruption the banking and the derivatives of the scams of the dollar implosion and the New World Order and the rigging and
The cloning and the and so they just want to make the whole world hellish with mask on and checkpoints and passports
So you forget all the crimes they committed and don't do anything about it. It's a dumb plan
It's a dumb dumb plan boy
It is hard not to think about what would have happened if you and all of your right-wing
Lunatic dumb dumb friends had decided to take this whole fucking thing seriously way back in February of last year Dan
Well, I think they did take it too seriously
I'm sorry, I apologize in March of last year
Would have been it would have been interesting would have been interesting. So quick point
There is no link to the BBC and Paul's article
There's a link to a story in the spectator and one in Sky News
The Sky News article says nothing about exemptions
But what Paul does is he cherry picks a very minor side point in the spectator article?
Which he then turns into his headline because it has the potential to help boost white victimhood feelings
This is an editorial column and one of the concerns it raises
With the idea of vaccine passports being required for travel is according to this column
Vaccine skepticism is higher in non-white communities in the UK sure
It's really interesting how Paul works here Paul takes this quote from the Sky News article quote a government insider stressed
There's nervousness about when such a system will even be announced publicly let alone rolled out for use if you read the article
It does seem to be implied that the nervousness in question is about the vaccines efficacy and not moving too fast
However, here's how Paul uses that line quote part of this nervousness is based around the perception that mandating
Mandating vaccines for travel could be seen as racist because suspicion of vaccines and poor inoculation rates are commonplace within BAME
communities
He's taken the concerns raised by the editorial of the spectator and applied them to the quote from the Sky News
Article without in any way demonstrating that the two are connected at all. No, they're connected
This is Paul
Just kind of making things up in order to justify writing a blog post about white identity fears that Alex can then report on
In a super racist way on air because that's what their audience needs to stay interested
Yeah, I do appreciate
The the real lack of effort that went into that for Paul
Yeah, like it is it is always real, you know heartwarming to know that some people
Wake up at 9 go to work and they're done at 10
Yeah, you know, it's just nice to know that that's a that's a dream that somebody can accomplish, you know, yeah
And so transparent about it. Yeah, that's not very very weak. So not good
So so far, I think we've seen just a real tragedy of a show. We see real sad Alex play a car crash
Just make up nonsense about a couple articles. I didn't drive through a snowstorm and an outstorm for no reason
I'm gonna deliver the guns cuz I'm alive and I'm not backing down in the name of Jesus Christ
I declare war on Satan
Good work
Yeah, you know what four out of ten four out of ten
Maybe I would argue that this is a good teaching moment as well for Alex. All right now
I understand that we're not gonna get anywhere with the corona virus with him
It's too we're too far gone for that
But let me toss this out for you Dan if there were fewer cars on the road during an ice storm
Mm-hmm. Don't you think that would be better at preventing accidents? Yes, right
So perhaps if Alex wanted to do his part to prevent accidents
He could have stayed home and done the show remotely now
Do you understand how those things might be a connected?
I understand the metaphor that you're making but I'd also like to say he did come in see now
That is the problem that we're having all across the board. It is it's an issue
So when Alex comes back for break after that pathetic growl
very fake very long
Passionless growl. Yeah, he starts complaining about how people think that he supported Trump because it somehow is good for his business
Now, I know that I've heard him a hundred times say that his traffic went up
Ridiculously. Yeah, once he started to kid in with Trump and all that was really good for his business. No, no
No, it hurt his business. He was persecuted. Sure. Alex was
Persecuted I got persecuted for supporting Trump you got persecuted for supporting Trump
But we're not losers because we supported President Trump. He really won that
Election and I don't just say that if he lost I'd say he lost I'd still say we have a Chinese agent in charge
I don't lie to myself
Okay, I did when I was 10 years old but not since about then. I want to know what's really going on
That's what gives me an effectiveness in my life read that US News and World Report article then that's a good starting point
I would I would argue he really wants to know what's not going on
Or he doesn't want to know what is going on. Yes. Yeah, he desperately needs not
Avoid what's going on? Yeah
Which is why you support Trump, yeah, but there's bad news about Trump, but it's bad news mixed with good news
Okay, but it's all bad news. Okay, but maybe it's good news. All right
Trump's basically bankrupt. He's not just lost two billion out of the inside baseball
They've got four or five thousand lawsuits against him
But you know, we have the treated man. He's actually stronger than ever
And he understands that and if more men were like President Trump if more men were like the supporters this broadcast, I mean that
Who would be in this position, but he understands leadership like Colonel Travis did at the Alamo
Drunkenly Travis knew he's gonna be killed. He sent that final letter. He knew what was about to happen
But he couldn't back down because he believed the cause he signed on to it. He wasn't suicidal
I can't get out of here so much like Jesus Christ said he was one to lay it down for others
So that's what this comes down to Colonel Travis had nowhere else to go no
No, no, he had nowhere else to go Trump may have nowhere else to go. Yeah, that's probably true
So Trump put out a little statement about the impeachment acquittal. Did he?
Yeah, and Alex Alex is kind of pissed off that no one's reading the full statement. Oh nice. Yeah, so nowhere
Do you really see the president's statement you hear he made one, but you don't really it may be a line here a line there
Let's read the whole thing together
right now as
Beautiful what he said, it's totally true
National fall wrote the story. It's up at in full words calm president Trump releases statement on second impeachment acquittal
President Trump through the office of the former president was a statement celebrating this
Second Senate impeachment acquittal damn, right? He's the man the arena like oh look. He's under attack. You're like Oh Jones
You're under attack. Oh boy. They're coming after you. What'd you think?
I did you think I did this not to be attacked you think I did that cuz I don't expect a war
You people don't get and I'm talking to our enemies
You think I just want to line my pockets and sit around with you in some country club that I do think
Yes, I agree without fighting evil. I feel alive. I feel strong
You understand that you can put a gun to my head on my back it down you dumb sons of bitches
It's real shame no one's reading the Trump statement I
Do I do appreciate that it does it does appear that for most of the world
We're finally past like having to deal with stuff. He says on the daily. Yeah, that's nice
Yeah, everybody everybody enjoys that I I had I have personally some trouble whenever I see too much of him
Yeah, yeah
I don't want I don't want people that I would normally think of as sane
To talk about him and not because I want exclusive domain over Alex don't know. I just don't think it's worth it. No
Yeah, this is a problem for us, too. Yeah. Yeah, I don't value my own time
Save yourselves. Yeah, we're too far gone. Yeah. Yeah, this all means nothing. Yeah
We're not the people who hide a zombie bite. We have a zombie bite kick us out of the mall
We're not supposed to be there. We'll be on the roof
So
Alex does get around to reading the statement and I will say I think he reads it in full
But he does add some commentary and some of it is a little bit ridiculous
No president has ever gone through anything like it and that's true
That's the key and it continues because our opponents cannot forget the almost 75 million people
Way more than that the greatest number ever for a sitting president who voted
I was just a few months ago, and that's thing Trump had victory. It's there even though they lie about it folks
He won those other six states by half a point or less. He won him by five points on average
You understand that that's like what it's way more than quadruple the number of victory numbers
That's why they're crapping their bridges. That's more than quadruple the number of victory numbers
Yeah
Kind of feels a lot like that
50 times the amount of imaginary
Vaccine deaths. Yeah, that doesn't sound like a reasonable number for someone to toss out there. I feel like Alex doesn't know much about
Numbers. Math? No. Anything? Nope. Very little. So he gets to complaining about SNL
And of course this leads into him yelling a bit about abuse towards children. Sure, sure. I don't respect his position on the issue
Man, I got a lot of complaints about SNL. I I think we can let that one go
Mm-hmm. I don't think we need to worry about that. No, there's there's really not not any reason to
Engage and so that's that's one break and then he comes back and I want to tell you
He's not killing time. I
Would argue even mentioning SNL on your apparently political talk show would be killing time
Well that that you know debatable if it's killing time. Sure. This next minute
Definitely not. It sounds like alright ladies and gentlemen Alex Jones here back live two more segments left than Owen Schroyer
If he can get here in this snowstorm, we can run a rebroadcast if he can't or just loop this show
info wars live six to eight
Sunday nights is coming up if Ellen can get here
Will you guys call him and see if he can get here because it is just insane
Yes, this hosting ask him to come to work. Oh my gosh, Tom Pappert
Emperor Palpatine
the Sun
He's like a hundredth generation clone of Palpatine as you know that happened a long time ago in a galaxy far far away Tom
Pappertine. Oh, you don't know about star. He's great. Great. Great. Great. Great. Great. Great great great thousandth clone
Is gonna be hosting with Sheldon after the broadcast. You don't want to miss it
All right, I have a lot of stuff to hit here in fact I've got too much material
It's not like I'm stalling out because I don't have information to cover here with 25 minutes left to go
it's because
This is surreal, I mean it is it's just surreal there's too much
There's too much got a riff on Tom Papperts name being similar to Palpatine. Yep. Yep for a bit
Dick what a dick people dying outside people dying outside. Let's see if Owen can get to work
Yeah, great. Good boss. Good boss. Love working for you, buddy
I'll say for what I would expect of Alex as a boss the fact that he's like we can go to rebroadcast if he can't
That's true. That almost seems like that's that kind of a stand-up guy. Yeah, that is that is to be like no
He gets here now or he's fired. Yeah, but that is also Scrooge being like you get Christmas off like
Yeah, I guess that's nice. So he's not killing time
Well, maybe he's killing some time. Okay, so here's the video of the granny being thrown off the cliff
So, he plays this video that's a guy rolling a woman in a wheelchair
Through a park and then it ends with him dumping her off a cliff
So it is like that Conan O'Brien Walker, Texas Ranger sketch. It's well, there's a little bit of well, I mean
There's some racial undertones for oh god. Damn it
Look at her fighting back that old white lady. That old racist.
Get rid of her!
Yeah, there we go.
Ahh, good, liberal.
Oh, liberal ooh.
This video is a campaign ad that was targeting Paul Ryan because he was gonna take take away Medicare.
Yeah, yeah. This is at least a two-year-old ad that was against the GOP that Alex is playing as some kind of attack
on liberals or something?
Boo this man! Boo this man!
Boo!
Yeah, I was like this is this is surreal and Alex clearly hadn't watched it in advance
He just knew it was an old lady getting dumped out of a wheelchair because he looks pretty surprised when the thing comes up
and it says call Paul Ryan
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on now. Hold on one second.
Oh boy.
Yeah, so Alex, you know, he's in a bit of a fatalistic mood, you know.
He already said earlier that, you know, we might not be here next year. Fuck that, we might not be here tomorrow.
I got a final segment and a bunch of news I want to hit. I'm loaded for bear on that.
But I'll just tell you all this, ladies and gentlemen, it's been a great pleasure to be on air with you.
I don't know how long I'm going to be here. Things are so bad. Things are moving so fast
that I'm not even sure we'll be here tomorrow, next week, next year.
It's all up to God right now, but the bottom fell out.
And it's just they're euthanizing the old people.
I mean, we've got probably 5% death rates at nursing homes to take the shot
and they've successfully covered up most areas.
OK, that's a ridiculous number.
All right. OK, hold on. Even then.
He can't just make up numbers like that.
No. No. But even then, what's the current bet? Never mind.
I don't even know. Just stop. Just stop. Just stop.
One of the things that I think is interesting is Alex is talking pretty fatalistically.
He's talking a lot of, uh, we're gone. We're done.
It looks like Plan B is back in play.
Now, I won't say that I'm falling for it again or anything like that,
or thinking that he's talking for real, but I do need to tell you this, and I do think it's important.
What's that?
He's playing a lot of doors.
He's playing a lot of songs by the doors as bumper music.
So he's in a mood.
There's a lot of, like, this is the end, my friend.
A lot of those sorts of songs.
And it honestly bums me out, mostly because I don't like the doors,
but also it has, like, such a scent.
Like, the mood of the music that he's playing on a very regular basis,
like multiple coming in from commercials per show.
Little Mothlin?
Yeah, or Doors songs. It has the tone of a dirge.
Okay. All right. Let's see how this goes.
Yeah, I don't know.
I just, I think...
I will say that if it doesn't end soon and he keeps playing the doors, I'm gonna be pissed.
You know, one thing that I realized after the impeachment trial was that
I don't think that's the appropriate punishment.
And I think the same thing for Alex. I don't think the appropriate punishment is to, like, take him off the air.
I don't think the appropriate punishment for Trump is to take him away from politics or anything.
They should have no money. Zero money. Take their money.
If the impeachment trial was like, yeah, sure, run for office again, with nothing.
I got broke.
I think if people do things that have civic, or civil penalties,
then by all means they should be sued and what have you.
And I don't want what I'm about to say to be like, no, don't sue Alex.
Like people who he has wronged.
Sure, sure, sure.
But I think that I'm not particularly concerned with him having money or not having money.
I'm concerned about the impact that he can have.
Sure, sure, sure.
I think a far greater punishment for him is the illumination and explanation of how bullshit everything he does is.
Right.
And how he's basically defrauding people with the posture of, like, some guy who's against the system when all he really is is a fucking idiot.
Right, and I want to take away the thing he cares about most.
Memories of Colonel Travis.
I'll take those too.
If I could sue him for those, I would.
So, this show has been largely devoid of meaning?
No, no, no. SNL.
Well, and there's some more pop culture grievance.
Sure.
Because Alex has found a video of Run DMC.
Run DMC, the current stars?
Well, it's just DMC.
Current stars Run DMC?
They did a little song about the vaccine.
Okay.
And Alex is not happy about it.
Alright.
Run DMC members now put out this, I guess the money must be good, this type of garbage.
Then I got something even sicker.
Here it is.
I got the vaccine, you got the vaccine, they got the vaccine, we got the vaccine.
We can get back to normal, let me inform you, let's all get the vaccine.
Look, I think that there's plenty of valid criticisms about this song.
Oh, do you mean that it's great?
That it's too good for the rest of us?
This isn't really my territory to critique too much.
But I will say that Alex was far less critical of Mike Adams' rap career.
That is fair.
His weird Ebola rap songs.
I mean, I respect what they're doing, it's tough to hear an afterschool special from DMC.
It is tough to hear a PSA.
I just, I don't really know, I don't know, it just seems weird that Alex would care that much.
Why?
Because he's filling fucking time.
Right.
No, that's what I'm saying.
Yeah, he's got nothing.
Like, this is what he spends his other time with at the end of the show.
Bill Gates says he wants to depopulate you.
You're gonna take his shots, here it is.
What if Bill Gates disappeared?
No problem.
I will buy many Gates and solve the problem.
Alex plays a video from like a YouTube channel called OMSOM, I believe, OMSOM.
And it's like, it's for kids.
It's an educational video for kids.
They have a big series of videos of what would happen if blank disappeared.
And so one of the recent ones is what would happen if the year 2016 disappeared?
What would happen if numbers disappeared?
And it's like animations for kids.
And there's one about what would happen if Bill Gates disappeared.
And some of it is like, well, he's a big philanthropist, a lot of that money would be gone.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
And then the last one I think is like, Warren Buffett would miss his best friend.
It's like, why are you commenting on this stupid video for kids?
Because that's the first thing that he can engage with on an equal footing.
Yeah, it's embarrassing.
It's for kids.
I mean, look, I'm not gonna say that that doesn't have a kind of propaganda feel to it.
I'm not gonna say that making a video where you're like, what if Bill Gates was gone?
That didn't also include like, well, it's possible that his money would be shuffled back into the economy
and put into places where maybe he doesn't have half of it.
Sure, he's a philanthropist, but maybe he's still got $20 billion and he should go fuck himself.
That might be complicated for children.
It might be a little bit difficult.
I accept the point that you're making. This is not the critique that Alex has.
No, that's true.
Yeah, hey, I get what you're saying. I hear it being a little bit weird, but it's also a giant public figure.
Yeah, totally. No, of course.
I don't know. I didn't watch the whole thing, but the stuff that Alex plays is just like, alright, this isn't like Bill Gates is our god.
Yeah, you know what? If he went more like a Starship Troopers route where he's like,
doesn't it seem a little bit weird that we're making these kind of campaign videos that lionize these types of public figures
when what we should be doing is talking about the issues and policies and stuff like that?
But even then, he's talking about a kid's video.
But then look at Trump ads.
No, I know. Of course.
That argument cuts both directions.
Of course. That's never stopped him before.
True. I don't know. I just, you know, I was feeling like there wasn't much happening here, but there was a lot happening.
You know, it was really disgusting, the playing of the crash, the going right into an ad after talking about it.
And so much of this vaccine nonsense is sad.
And it really makes you think that this is how he ends the show.
I will now go into an incredible gauntlet of frozen roads and road warrior level crashes to get back to my family
and hopefully back tomorrow at 11 a.m. Central for the live broadcast. I want to thank the crew for a great job.
Coming up on the other side on the Infowars Network stream is Tom Pappert of NationalFile.com.
There's no reason that he needed to come in at all.
Nope.
Tom Pappert is in, you know, he's not in Texas.
Like, he does it remotely. Alex could have just set up a little cam at his house.
Wouldn't have been hard.
No need, no need. This is all for nothing.
Yep.
It's all a waste, just to get out of the house on Valentine's Day.
Alright. Okay.
Oh, also they debuted in, I don't know if it was debuted, but this is the first time I saw it.
There was a new commercial for my Patriot Supply.
Uh-huh.
And Alex is at their warehouse that is in Salt Lake City, Utah.
Okay.
That's why he went to Utah.
That's why he went to Utah, to cut a clip? Oh, what a dick.
Yeah, he's there at the warehouse.
He's shooting promos?
Yeah.
What an asshole.
I think that must have been why he went, or at least part of it.
Yeah.
I mean, maybe it's, maybe it's, you know.
Eh, kill two birds with one stone. You're already there.
But that's at least part of it.
Yeah.
That explains why, like, I mean, look, again, I love you, Utah, but not the number one vacation destination, necessarily.
Um, so yeah, he was, I, uh, I don't have any clips of it because it's just that I'm talking about how great the food is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, of course.
Although, there is a kind of a funny part where he's like-
You know what that's like? That's a little bit like if you were to say,
hey, all you viewers, or all you listeners, you're lucky not to be watching this video right now.
But instead, you just didn't play it, Dan.
True, true.
Yeah.
Think about that.
Hmm.
Restraint.
Yeah.
Um, did you know that if you get my Patriot Supply stuff and you open up one of those buckets-
What's that?
You gotta be careful.
You might not be able to get it closed because there's so much food in it.
They say that like three times.
It's all just one, it's all just a muffin. Like, you pull it up and then it pops out and they're like,
haha, it's a big muffin. You can eat it forever.
I would be charmed by that.
Um, so yeah, I don't know. I found this episode to be a little frustrating.
No, it's great. There's a lot going on.
Children's videos, Run DMC vaccine songs, SNL complaining, like everything just seems so trivial.
I feel like-
It's trivial.
Big stuff is happening.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
I think that Alex on some level didn't have as much skin in the game with the impeachment as you might have thought he might.
And then the spin of they just played clips of Democrats saying stuff and how do you defend against that?
Right.
As if that was legally relevant.
Yeah, no kidding.
And I think that works for him. So, I don't know.
I'm excited to see if he keeps playing the doors.
Yeah.
And if that is a bad omen-
You want to see how sad he gets?
Yes.
I'm excited to see how sad boy he goes.
Yeah.
Oh, I can only imagine. If he comes in from break with like the sound of silence, then we know it's over.
He's just singing along with Elliot Smith instead of you belong to the city.
Oh, it starts raining at the Interwar Studio.
How?
Oh, I paid $50,000 for a rain system.
We got sprinklers up there. They're always going 24-7 now.
Yep. It just fit the mood.
It's just how I feel.
Yep.
If you can afford to have your environment reflect your inner peace, then yeah, but I'm just sad.
Well, I guess we'll be back to find out what the next step in this adventure is.
Indeed we will.
But until then, we have a website.
We do have a website. It's knowledgefight.com.
Yep. We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter. It's at knowledgefight.net. Go to bed Jordan.
We're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook and iTunes.
If you could, please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people doing God's work right now.
Yep. We'll be back, but until then, I'm Neo. I'm Leo. I'm DZXClark. I'm Daryl Rundis.
I'm Alex Jones's wife's auntie.
Andy in Kansas. You're on the air. Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex. I'm a first time caller. I'm a huge fan. I love your work.
I love you.