Red Alert!
N-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-knowledge fight!
Dad!
Blech!
Damn, and, Jordan, I am sweating!
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray!
I have great respect for knowledgefight!
Knowledgefight!
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying,
We are the bad guys, knowledgefight!
Dan and Jordan, knowledgefight!
Red Alert!
Blech!
I need, I need money!
Red Alert!
Andy and Kansas!
Stop it!
Andy and, Andy!
It's time to pray!
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding!
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan, I love your work!
Knowledgefight!
N-n-n-n-n-n-n-knowledgefight.com
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledgefight, I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan!
We're couple dudes who like to drink novelty beverages in their own homes and sit around
and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
It does appear that that is our plan for the time being right now, Dan.
Yeah, Jordan, we are recording this separately, probably the first actual episode that we've
recorded over a distance.
It's a little bit weird.
Sure!
Yeah, that remains to be seen as to whether or not it's an actual episode now.
I set out with the intention of a regular episode-ish, kind of, kind of a mini episode.
I don't want to, again, I want to stress to everybody that we're not going to have episodes
every Monday, Wednesday, and Friday, but the circumstances kind of demanded this week.
We had to jump on the horse and get something together.
Yeah, I don't think that's a terrible idea.
But, simultaneously, we can't get together.
Because Chicago has waist-deep snow outside.
It's bad.
It's really bad.
And I ran out of coffee.
I ran out of coffee last night, Dan.
So this morning, I was about to take the dogs out for a walk and I always start a cup of
coffee, a pot of coffee, before I take the dogs out and I realized in that moment I have
none.
So, I had to walk through close to a mile of waist-deep snow to get some coffee.
It was the most brutal morning I've ever had.
Yeah, I walked down to the grocery store because I needed some salad stuff for lunch and it
was just a dead zone.
There was nobody there.
It was fantastic.
Yeah.
I mean, other than the logistical problems that everyone's dealing with, the fact that
there was no one at a grocery store was pretty nice.
There are some advantages.
Yeah.
So, I guess my bright spot is that you and I are both doing relatively alright with this.
I mean, it was coming down all day, all night yesterday.
Just a disaster.
Last night, it was one of the first times I've seen that kind of snowstorm and I was
like, man, I think I'm actually scared for Chicago.
Look, we get covered in snow.
That's fine.
But this one was like, oh shit, this one might be too much for us.
Yeah, yeah.
Whenever people start talking in feet, it's like, alright, hold on.
You didn't say 16 inches.
You said multiple feet.
That's trouble.
Alright, so the reason that we needed to jump on the old Zoom here and get an episode together
was because Alex is also dealing with inclement weather.
Naturally.
He's got some, you know, Texas is seeing some unprecedented winter storms that are happening
right now and Infowars Studio has been struck by the ice, the Winter Queen.
What's the name of the character in the Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe?
I think it's just the Ice Queen.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, anyway, Alex wants some Turkish delight and...
Alright.
Okay.
Running out of references.
We'll stop there.
Let's just name all of the...
Voyage of the Dawn Treader.
Boy and his horse.
Or Horse and his Boy.
Sorry.
Yeah.
Silver Chair.
Prince Caspian.
Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe.
Right.
I think I said that first.
You did.
You're missing two of them.
You're missing the final two.
The Magician's Apprentice.
Oh, close.
Sorcerer's Apprentice.
No.
Oh, real close.
The Magician's Nephew.
Yes.
There you go.
What's the last one?
I think I forgot.
I think it's just the last battle.
Oh, that's probably it.
Very boring.
It's a really boring book.
Can't believe I forgot The Magician's Nephew.
What a stupid name for a book.
You know what?
I think that one's always been my favorite.
I always liked that one.
The little rings that they go into the little middle of the world to teleport thing.
Always fun.
I read the hell out of those books and I don't think I remember the plot of any of the...
At least the last four of them.
Oh, no.
That's fine.
That is totally fine.
Magician's Nephew is the prequel, though, and that's why I've always liked it.
It's the prequel to The Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe.
Oh, okay.
So it's like the Tokyo Drift of the...
Exactly.
Yes.
Before the main characters die.
Sure.
So, Jordan, we got some Alex Jones stupidity to deal with.
It'll be a little bit of a briefer episode, but I wanted to check in with how he's doing
in Occupied by Ice, Austin.
But before we do that, Jordan, let's take a moment to say thank you to some folks who
signed up and are supporting the show.
Oh, that's a great idea.
So first, Bill W., thank you so much for your policy walk.
I'm a policy walk.
Thanks Bill.
Thanks, Bill.
Next, Jordan th, not Jordan th.
Thank you so much.
You're now policy want.
I'm a policy walk.
Thanks Jordan.
Great name.
Oh, look at that.
Ah.
There we go.
You're playing on my side of the streets.
Next, Nicholas B. Thanks, Nicholas.
Next, Andrew A. Thank you so much for your now policy walk.
I'm a policy walk.
Thank you Andrew Aa.
Next, Amelia are thank you so much for your now policy walk.
I'm a policy walk.
Thanks Amelia. And finally, Drax. Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk. Thank you very much, Drax.
You want to say hi to Drax? Maybe a hi Drax?
I don't know what I did. I saw it. I saw that joke coming.
Yeah, a mile away. I tried to duck, and you still hit me in the face with it, so that happens.
Yep. Well, sorry, I have cookies on the mind.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. And I think we've got one more little piece of...
I think we've got one more little piece of... We're getting into this place of...
We're just shouting people out for no reason at this point, but we do have one reason for
this particular shout out. We have one particular reason, and that is it is their anniversary
today, I believe. Bonnie and Eric, happy 20th wedding anniversary for Wednesday the 17th.
20 years, Dan. That's exciting. That's the piano anniversary, right? The 20th is the piano?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. First is paper. Second is silver. No, wait, that's much later.
You know, the customary gifts thing that you're supposed to give on anniversaries.
Sure. Of course. 20th is pianos. I hope you guys
exchanged pianos, and... That would be the right way to do it.
Yeah. This is taking me back to my hosting stand-up comedy days. I like to do, you know,
you start out every show at Zany's with, hey, anybody celebrating anything tonight?
The difference here is that people have told us that they're celebrating something as opposed
to us starting the show having to fish for something. That's fair. It is different.
It's more celebratory, less sad. So, Jordan, on the 16th, or maybe it was yesterday,
I think it was the 15th, actually, Alex put out a series of short vignettes of himself at the
Infowars studio. Lights are out in the studio. There's also a couple of them where he's outside
yelling in the snow. Sure. Well, that just makes sense, though. It's a load of nonsense,
and we're going to talk about it. But first, here's an out of context drop from today's show.
If a dog starts running at you, don't be scared. Yell at it, throw rocks at it. It'll run off most
of the time if you're not on its property. Whoa. Dogs know about property rights.
Wow. That's the plan. That's the trick. Yeah.
Dogs are very interested in borders. They don't like immigration from house to house.
That's the situation. Dogs are libertarians. They're part of the Austrian school.
I feel like this is just Alex protecting other people from his mistakes. He's hurt so many dogs
because he was afraid of them, and now he's sharing his wisdom with the rest of the world.
Hey, guys. Just throw a rock at it. It's bad to be a dog murderer.
Just throw a rock at the dog. That's fine. That's enough.
Yeah. Don't shoot too hard. So, Jordan, we're here recording on Tuesday,
and as the time of this episode being put together,
InfoWars has essentially been off air since Sunday evening.
Cancel culture.
Austin and most of Texas is dealing with a once-in-a-lifetime winter storm that has
left countless people without power in severe conditions. It appears that the InfoWars studio
has been left also without power, and that means no show for Alex. It makes sense, and I don't
think anyone would bat an eye if he just got on air and said that there was a weather emergency
and they had to take an unplanned break in programming. It could be an effective way to
push emergency food sales even, so it might not end up being a total money loss if he did that,
but Alex does not go that route. Instead of just expressing solidarity with the people of Texas,
encouraging people to stay inside if possible, and donating to a mutual aid fund,
Alex decided to record a video of himself at the InfoWars studio with the lights off,
explaining how power outages are actually a globalist conspiracy.
Really? We had to get there, huh? I would prefer a scaler attack. I want a scaler attack. I want
aliens if we're gonna do this. Globalist conspiracy. We'll get to the specifics of
this, but right off the bat, I wanted to explain why Alex feels the need to make this conspiracy
instead of just being, you know, a normal kind of thing. You know, you're a human. You accept that
inclement weather happens, and sometimes it gets in the way. I have a reason, I think, that he might
want this to be a conspiracy. Let's see if it's on my list. I'm just gonna go with mainly one of the
large contributors to this disaster being so much worse is his state actually being interested in
following the policies that he himself advocates for. All right, I'm gonna cross number four off
the list. That was number four. There we go. The first reason is that Alex has a vested interest
in infantilizing his audience. He needs their critical thinking skills to be on a child's level,
so whenever he has the chance he creates childish narratives. When you're in bed and you hear a bump
you could either think that it's the water heater or you could think it's a viking who's invaded
your house to come and get you. Adults are really capable, you know, they're able to reason it out,
that there's no reason a viking would be in your home, but for children their minds gravitate to
the more exciting possibilities, which is often nonsense, but it appeals to a particular emotional
need and a drive that children have. A quick question, is it around like 860 AD? In which case
it is a terrifying time for viking. Time travel is possible. You have a time traveling water heater.
Knowing that the noise is the water heater doesn't prompt an irrational response in a person.
They can ignore it, or if it's a serious noise they can choose to call a technician.
If you can convince people though that it's actually a viking who almost got them,
you might be able to sell them all sorts of products to protect against vikings or even
documentaries where you explain how vikings operate and how to avoid their attack plans.
Keeping the audience in a state where they don't deal with the problems that come up in a boring
but ultimately real way and keeping them fixated on childish emotional interpretations of every
stimulus they receive is essential for Alex's business model, so even a giant storm can't
just be a storm. It's clearly an attack on conservatives. Absolutely. The second reason
that Alex has a strong interest in presenting this storm as some kind of an act of foul play is that
it's really something that just happens in nature, and if so, he should have been prepared for it.
His brand is largely built around being a prepper type of guy, so the first question that comes up
in the case of his network being taken offline by a storm is naturally, why weren't you prepared for
that? A winter storm like this hitting Texas is obviously a very unlikely event and something that
the infrastructure was unprepared for, and my heart goes out to everyone who's dealing with the
consequences of it, but for Alex, the fact that he could be caught off guard by a natural event,
that's a contradiction of the way he wants the audience to see him, and so obviously you're
supposed to be prepared for the literal end of the world. I would imagine that includes some
sort of the power grid going down, right? Yeah, you touched on the fourth one, which is the
state of Texas and how they operate, and we'll talk about that a little bit down the line,
but the third issue is that a storm like this brings into sharp focus some of the elements of
the climate change conversation that Alex doesn't want people to think about. As the climate changes
and weather events become more severe, they're going to test long-standing assumptions about
infrastructure and how we build. For instance, houses are designed differently in different parts
of the country, like in California they prioritize earthquake protection, whereas in Missouri where
I grew up, every single family home that you're going to find has a basement because of tornadoes.
Right. So, you know, basements are less prevalent in flood prone regions. Yeah, Florida is not known
for having tons of basements that are literally underneath the swamp. Yeah, and as, you know,
different sorts of weather patterns and more severe storms hit different areas, you're going
to see those things, the long-standing assumptions that we've had, not be enough to suffice, and Alex
doesn't want the audience to think about that because it requires shifting ideas and paradigms
and he's not into that. Of course. I have a plan. Here's my plan, okay, because as shifting weather
patterns are going to test our assumptions and our architecture, what if now, and hear me out,
we've got a lot of real estate, now admittedly it is being held right now, but if you go underneath
the get, all right, no problems with weather issues, no problems with, you know, all that stuff,
you go into there, you knock out a few Nazis and then you got a home for life, Dan. There is
essentially a city under the Getty Museum, if we were to believe the people we've heard from. We
got space down there. Yeah. So, you know, these are the kind of things that are essential for
Alex to have his audience not think about, like, wait, this is a natural storm. This is bad,
but, you know, you should have known that it was a possibility. You are not prepared for this. You
got caught on your back foot. Weird. Maybe I shouldn't trust you about everything. Yeah,
instead of a conspiracy, maybe go, like, no conspiracy, buy snow tires, just in case. Sure.
Well, you know, it kind of felt like that was the direction he was going to go on Sunday after
obsessing about the, like, the traffic accidents, but it turns out not. Turns out that Alex is in
the great reset and that is why the power is out at Infowar Studios. Our power has been turned off
40% of the state without power this morning. All the great reset. I told my wife that this morning,
I told my security people that, and then my head security guy walks up and goes, here's the
Austin American statesman admitting that since they shut down the coal plants in Texas under
Obama, the windmills in West Texas failed and the power may be off for a week or longer.
Rolling blackouts because coal is evil. So here we are at Infohorse and we have to open the windows
up to have light. Here, let me give you a tour real quick. So Alex wants to pretend that the
wind turbines freezing in Texas is what caused the blackouts, but that is absolutely not true.
From an article in Bloomberg, quote, while ice has forced some turbines to shut down as the brutal
cold wave drives record electricity demand, that's been the least significant factor in the
blackouts, according to Dan Woodfin, a senior director for the electric reliability council
of Texas, which operates the state's power grid. The main factors, frozen instruments at natural
gas, coal, and even nuclear facilities, as well as limited supplies of natural gas, he said.
The article goes on to quote Daniel Cohen, an associate professor of environmental
engineering at Rice University, who said that it, quote, is really a red herring to blame
renewable energy production for the blackouts. If the wind turbines were operating at full capacity,
things would still be bad because of the infrastructure of Texas's power grid and how it
was unprepared to deal with a weather event like this. Alex doesn't want to address that point
because it's real and it requires calling in a technician. He would rather blame imaginary
Vikings. Yeah. Yeah. You have to pay for a technician. You have to pay for maintaining your
power grid. You have to pay for all of this stuff. But if it's the imaginary globalist, somehow
they're paying Alex. It makes perfect sense. Yeah. That's the way to do it. So Alex doesn't quite
understand the conversation that a lot of people are having surrounding climate issues. And we
heard this kind of position be expressed on when he was on Rogan's show, this idea that like
everybody wants like there to be no carbon. You're like, sure, sure, sure, sure. It's,
it's very strange. Here we are watching the most high tech, clean burning coal plants in the world
that nothing comes out of them, the carbon dioxide and water vapor, and they shut them down.
But Obama had already shut down thousands over a hundred in Texas. And then I'm reading the
Austin American Statesman and they admit the whole thing and say, this is green energy,
but it's worth it. Folks. This is the new dark age. Let's not, uh, I didn't see that in the
Austin American Statesman article. And, uh, you know, he just doesn't understand the, the issues
of like it's excess carbon dioxide. It's not like there will be no carbon dioxide in the world.
I don't, I don't, I don't think that that anyone would advocate for that.
No, it's, it's, this is a, this is a child going, okay, what? So I eat 35 apples a day.
You want nobody to have any apples? Zero apples then, huh? Not, Oh, you're saying I should have
a moderate amount. Fuck you. You want to take apples away from the honest working man. I don't
know why that's a six year old kid, but yeah, it's creating a false argument. Yeah, it's stupid.
And that's because, and Alex is able to do that because he's a climate scientist, basically.
Carbon dioxide are trace gases, trace gases. And if you look at the earth, it was a lot hotter in
the last few hundred thousand years and then was going down and now has gone up a tiny bit. Yes,
we've raised the temperature like maybe half a degree and thank God that's us terraforming it
in a good way. Unknowingly. Wow. He knows a lot. He's very, he's very insightful on these things.
Yeah. Yeah. That's not good. No, that's not good. Also, oxygen is specifically not a trace gas.
No, it's a trace gas. There's only like what? Zero percent of oxygen in the atmosphere? Nothing.
And saying that CO2 is a trace gas is meaningless in this context because the message he's seeming
to suggest is that there's so little of it that we should just make more. That's dumb. Ammonia is
also a trace gas, but I think that Alex would realize you don't want a ton of it in the air
because of obvious reasons. All right. You're making a good point, but have you ever walked
near a volcano and just breathed in pure sulfur dioxide? That's the good stuff. That's what gets
you breathing real good. You know, that's what you want in the atmosphere. It's a trace gas.
We shouldn't limit the amount of sulfur dioxide. Don't you want to chew your air?
Oh, so good that we raised the temperature.
So good. Yeah. I don't know. I think at this point, if you're a climate denier, it has to be
like, ah, I think I can wait out the clock. Right. You know, like there's no way Alex isn't,
isn't like at a certain point, like, oh shit, the climate really is fucked. I can't ignore this
anymore, but I'll probably be off the air by the time people want to really hold me accountable for
it. So fuck it, you know? Yeah, it could be. I mean, I mean, there, there has to be a certain
amount of, I'm not going to have to pay the fiddler and then there's, there's another part
with Alex though. I really do think that he is just like, dumb. He is just not interested.
And someone has explained it to him in such a way that like, Oh, Hey, the power plants are totally
clean. And he's never seen fit to have to look into it. Cause why would, yeah. Yeah. I just
don't know what, how stupid do you have to believe be to just believe that on like a gullibility
scale, I wouldn't trust a coal plant. If I walked through like the people who run coal are
demonstrably evil and have been for 150 years. Yeah. But they also tend to politically align
with the, the sort of things that Alex is into, you know, generally sure. He's, he's, he's inclined
to, to trust them even though maybe, maybe on some level, I mean, he does fucking Darth Vader
impressions all the time and talks about the dark side is the good people. That's fair. So Alex is
inside in the hallway at this point in the video. And then he, he now tells us we're going to go
outside. Let's go outside outside and show you Bill Gates, wanting to cool block out the sun
and look where we're at in a fricking frozen tundra with the power off freezing our asses off
like surfs. That's 21st century war. That's the great reset. And the great reset has cut
the power off in Texas. He is not established that he did not demonstrate this in any way.
Um, no wind turbines, real cold coal destroyed by Obama. See, it's the great reset. Oh, you could
say those things, but it doesn't mean it. There's no, no connection to reality. Really? No. If it
was destroyed by Obama, it's the great resets fault. Dan, do you understand? Yeah, sure.
And so Alex goes outside and he's just a man yelling in the snow. He is, uh, hanging out
with a snow backdrop being mad. And I, I think this is really interesting because if you take
him at his word, he seems to be lamenting the industrial revolution and how, how it made it.
So we don't have to make our own power or something that made us soft.
So modern society is great in many ways, but it's domesticated since man is very dependent
on the system. Now the average American, the average person in the industrialized world
flips on the light switch and just expects power or they pull into the gas station and they expect
gasoline or they go to the grocery store and they expected fresh food is going to be flown in or
trucked into where they're at. Even in the winter, people have been taken away from the land and have
been made very, very soft, myself included. But at least I know that that's going on.
I don't understand what he's complaining about. We're so soft because we expect there to be power
when we, you know, have all agreed to collectively pay for a power company to take care of that.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You know, one, uh, hello Unabomber. It's been a while since we've talked.
And two, no, I think it's far worse. Look, if you, if you and I want to say we're unaware that,
uh, that technology has domesticated us and we have moved away from the land and then act like
that, that's fine. But if we are aware of it and don't take steps to avoid it and instead only tell
other people to do it, we're hypocritical pieces of shit you wish you didn't listen to.
Oh yeah, absolutely. His, his pretending that like, at least I know is, yeah, it doesn't matter.
It does make it way worse. It's worse. Yeah. You should, you should be, uh, not putting out
little tiny videos, uh, should be underground somewhere. Maybe if you want to, if you want to
join the land, if you want to broadcast, you should not ever have inclement weather get in
the way because you should have a ton of generators and you should be broadcasting from a compound
somewhere that no one knows where it is. And you got a bunch of potatoes growing, so you don't have
to worry about anybody. Hello, Unabomber. It's been a long time since we've done it.
It is strange. Although it is, it's, it's really interesting thing that Alex is like, okay, so
our uplinks are in another state, so they still have power. So what we have to do is we have to
shoot these little videos and then send them over somewhere else. And then he's got an elaborate
system to get like little tiny videos, which is just kind of, yeah, that's great. Yeah. It seems
like you should just not do this. I don't know. Take the day off. Yeah. That's my snow day.
That's my feeling about it. And the argument that he's making is so not compelling that I
don't even know why you bother, like why try to make this a conspiracy? Just like stay home.
Yeah. You don't need to risk driving. Yeah. Yeah. But on the other hand, he could risk other people's
lives and still probably make it to work, which is maybe his favorite thing to do. Yeah, sure.
And I mean, there's employees there too. It's not like he's alone at the studio too. So yeah,
that's true. Even better. I wonder if his wife is still playing tennis today. Probably. Yeah.
So Alex, uh, well, I mean, I think the reason he's doing this is because he wants to gloat
because he saw this coming. He knew what was going to happen. These guys have written about every
damn bit of it. How do you think I could make a film 13, 14 years ago called in game blueprint
for global enslavement. And you watch the damn film and almost all of it's come true
because I know their quotes and their statements and they think you deserve to have this done to
you. What's now unfolding because you're not fighting back. They all have private jets.
They all got a bunch of kids. They all have palatial mansions. They all live. However,
they want to have huge yachts. They're telling you when Obama goes to Africa,
that you can't have a car. You can't have an air conditioning. That's a lie. Yeah. Yeah.
It's an old, old, fun lie that he, I guess the snow pulled out of his little brain.
Um, but like this is nonsense and I'm starting to get feelings of almost like stolen valor on his,
like his part of like being right about things. Yeah. Yeah. How dare you? I resent that. He's
just pointing to end game and being like, I was right about everything. I was like,
you should go and rewatch your own work. This is not good. No, here's the worst part. Okay.
Okay. End game. Was this a large amount about a road jet had it been built would probably
have ameliorated a lot of problems they are currently experiencing. So not only was he
not right about that, it should have been built. So he didn't have to deal with it today.
I'm not positive that the road would have helped as much as you think, but it was a really big road
that it was pretty big. It was pretty big. Yeah. And also Alex does need to do this show, not only
to gloat about how he was right, though he wasn't. Um, he also needs to make an announcement. There
are new numbers out the new numbers. Do you know what, do you know what these numbers are? Uh,
Querkin is Querkin a new number? Nope. It's not, no, no, no. Hold on. Hold on. It's not
brand new numbers. You misunderstood. No. Okay. I've not discovered a new number. I was just
checking to see if maybe they discovered a new number. No, you never know. I recognize that
that's a fair interpretation of what I said. That is not correct. So the globalist, right?
Yeah. For a long time, they had claims of how many people they were going to kill.
They're going to kill a bunch. Sure. Sure. Sure. Sure. There's new numbers.
Like you're part of the establishment and going along with this. That's why they always taught,
Oh, we're going to get rid of half the world population in the seventies. And then later,
well, once we set up real government will be about 80%, but the good people will still be
around to guard the earth. Now they probably say 90% will be exterminated. And the new numbers are
down to 1% of world population. Do you understand? You've been taught to hate yourselves. You've
been isolated. Big tech media is designed. They admit to make you depressed to make you alone.
You are under a reclamation program to remove you and build a new world.
You were under a culling program. They decided to dynamite us. They decided to remove us. They
decided to blot us out. Like you destroy a building with a wrecking ball. So at least admit what's
happening to you and recognize what's happening to you as it happens and realize that the inhuman,
degenerate scumbag, filth and garbage that is carrying this out and doing this all lives
lavish lifestyles are all completely wicked and hateful. Most of their children commit suicide.
They're totally disconnected and they are ruthless scum and only have a will to dominate control
others. And if you lay down to them, you allow them to hurt other innocence and you cut yourself
off from God. So don't be part of it. And that's why we need to primary weak Republicans.
I'm confused. Is this not okay? All right. You need to take back the house.
This is ridiculous. This is so inciting. It's just nonsense,
but it's also just an idiot standing in the snow, yelling for no reason.
This is kind of, it's kind of a preview of what his life is going to be like in 10 years.
The visual of it is really jarring because it is like, I mean, it's Alex Jones. So like he's,
you know, this, this notable firebrand, ding dong idiot, but it's also a complete impotence
that he's showing because he's just standing in the snow, yelling about his enemies.
No, he's an apocalypse preacher.
Yeah. But also, but also how little import or meaning is there to him being like,
there's new numbers that 99% of the population is going to be killed. Like, okay, now you can't
make it smaller or like the survivor number smaller. Like you have just backed yourself
into a corner where it's like, okay, now a hundred percent. This doesn't mean anything. You're just
making up numbers. And now you've gotten to the end of the line. There's no more numbers.
I like the idea that there are quarterly, uh, extermination reports, you know, like every
quarter there's new numbers like, Oh no, no, no. We were going to kill 99% at the end of the first
quarter, but now re looking things into the second quarter, we're projecting a 97% murder.
Some weirdo like Daniel calls Alex and he's like, hey, build a bird. They were saying that,
uh, it's 99 now. Yeah. Yeah. There was a action that was saying 98,
but they lost the negotiations were fraught. Yes. All fell apart. So not to, not to spend
too much time, uh, uh, talking about why he's standing in the snow. Uh, Alex decides now time
to yell about the vaccines. Sure. There is hope. As I said,
Merck had to pull their vaccine three weeks ago because it was making people sick and killing them.
And they admitted that even if you take it, it doesn't protect you. They recommended you just
get COVID and get over it. And it was a scam, huge move that they, they got scared and said,
this is too evil. That would be a huge move. South Africa banned the vaccine,
make people sick and killing them. Australia had to ban their vaccine that they put out.
Cause it was going to be HIV positive stuff. India just banned the MRNA Pfizer shot HIV stuff.
What? Yeah. All right. Most of that shit we've covered in the past, uh, in episodes.
That's all nonsense. The India one though is a new narrative. So I wanted to just clarify why
India didn't approve the use of Pfizer's COVID-19 vaccine. It was reported by CNBC back on February
5th that Pfizer had withdrawn their application for emergency use of their vaccine in India after
quote the government in January approved too much cheaper shots. There were a couple of other
hurdles, namely that India requires local studies to be done to approve vaccine use. And the studies
of Pfizer's vaccines had not been done in India. The second issue is that vaccine, uh, the one that
they had created the Pfizer one, it requires storage in very cold conditions, which creates
a concern about the ability for it to be rolled out all over India. You know, there's, there's
concerns about the supply of deep freeze, uh, capabilities. Alex is pretending, Alex is
pretending that they banned it because it's dangerous. When in reality, it's really just
kind of a boring logistics issue. Again, this is a water heater noise. Alex is trying to tell you
is a Viking. Yeah. That's a, that's like India being like, listen guys, we're going to have to
ban the import of snowballs. Now I know they don't get far once they get across the border,
but we just can't let this happen anymore. There are cheaper options that will do the same thing
that a snowball does. And yeah, we'll, we'll go with those. So Alex, uh, still, uh, being dumb
starts talking about how Texas used to supply everyone with power. They have shut our power
systems down so much that we can't even provide power in the summer and the winter and the great
state of Texas that up until 10 years ago was supplying power to 15 States and was doing an
incredible job, but we've been shut down. That's a complete lie. Uh, Texas is a unique state in the
country in terms of their power grid. And it's actually one of the reasons that the situation
in the state now is so much more complicated. Texas is the only state in the country that has
its own completely autonomous power grid called ERCOT, which is run by the electric reliability
council of Texas. Houston public media recently posted a very concise explanation of how the
system works and how it got to be the way it is, which I will paraphrase now. It doesn't and they
fucked it up. When electricity started to become more prevalent, the country saw utility companies
begin to combine and link up, uh, and, uh, create regional things. In 1935, FDR signed the federal
power act quote, which charged the federal power commission with overseeing interstate electricity
sales. The federal government could only really get involved with regulating interstate power
exchanges. So in order to avoid that regulation, Texas has remained the only state in the country
with its own power grid. This has been breached a few times, notably in 1976, when a Texas power
company sent power to Oklahoma very briefly in what's been called the quote, midnight connection.
Alex is completely making up that the state of Texas formerly provided energy to 15 States.
I suspect that he doesn't even know that his state's energy set up, uh, is the way it is
and how some of the problems he's complaining about are the direct by-product of his state
following his own anti-federal government paranoia. It's kind of embarrassing that, uh,
that he has no idea how it works, uh, and that because everybody else does it differently,
it's their fault despite not knowing how he does it. Yeah, probably. And you know, uh, it's, it's
really, it's really weird to me because like it should be a point of pride to him that the Texas
doesn't supply our to other States and other States don't supply power to them. It should be
like, this is a rugged individual pre-industrial revolution. We are not pacified instead. We mine
our own coal, we burn our own coal and that's what we do. He's still, he's instead choosing
the more attractive narrative to him, which is that Obama made it so Texas doesn't supply most
of the country electricity. Somehow it's still, you know, the anti-Obama pro-coal
kind of narratives take precedence over his state's rights, uh, jacking off, I think. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, I think that depends on the day too. Probably. Yeah. I would, uh, I would also argue,
uh, that in this circumstance, Alex is, I guess trapped, you know, like everything that he says
is going to be wrong. Yeah. Because the reality of it is like, this is all fucked up beyond reason
because, you know, we made choices to get at this place. Um, I think that Alex might be literally
trapped as well. Uh, he might, his wife might be driving the Audi, so he might be stuck at the
studio. Might as well scream on the street. I'm not going anywhere until five. Yeah. So Alex gets
to rambling about some other stuff. And I found this particular, uh, thought that he has a little
bit upsetting. This has to do with the storming of the Capitol. Because the globalists fear what
you saw at the Capitol. It was a few hundred that got the big mass to do it. The globalists
the globalists provocateur it had security stand down so that what they feared in the future could
be discredited. Now, a million people in DC with a serious mission to take over and overthrow
an illegitimate government is powerful. Okay. So what I'm hearing is the globalists are afraid of
what happened on the sixth. And so they did the sixth in order to make sure that Alex couldn't do
it better later. Yes, you are correct. That is exactly what happened. Great. And Alex's Alex's
point, I believe is that a few million people overrunning the Capitol, that's a W guys. That
means we win this one. A few hundred people were fucked. So yeah, I think he's really against the
principles of what happened on the sixth. Yeah. I think, I think it's, I think it's become quite
clear that now he realizes he's not going to get arrested or anything. He can sort of now sort of
subtly, just, just chill out and, you know, Hey guys, guys, two weeks from now, anybody
not busy two weeks. That's when we got to get a couple of million, two weeks. So, uh, we know
that Alex is a scholar on the, uh, matter of carbon dioxide, um, climate change, world war two.
Yeah. Alex does. He, he, he seems to think this I've heard him say this before. And that's why I
wanted to play this again, because it's such a dumb thought that I'm, I'm surprised he repeats
this multiple times. It's clearly something he actually believes. And that is that people are
only afraid of carbon dioxide because it sounds like carbon monoxide. Oh boy. Yeah. This is very
bad. The sun is energy. It drives almost all of our climate, light, carbon dioxide, oxygen,
and water is the carbon cycle. And if you take any of those very, you have death on the planet.
Well, people know water's good. Folks know oxygen is good and they know the sun's good.
So what is it? They attack carbon dioxide. Cause it sounds like monoxide Penn and Teller did it
20 years ago. I did it 15 years ago. We ought to go out and do it again. You go out, you give
people the name of water scientific 95% saving it. And we talked to over a hundred people and
only a few went, wait a minute. We're like dihydrogen monoxide. It's everywhere. It's toxic.
If you drink too much of it, it can kill you. Um, it, it, you know, it, it, they're like, yes,
I agree. We should be in that. That's water even better. 99% of the studies we did out of the
public, unofficial study, if you give them the name of table salt, Oh my God, it sounds like
Satan. I mean, table salt has a really scary name and the average person will come to you
and we'll say, let's be in that. Alex couldn't remember the name of table salt. Yeah. I was
going to say, why didn't you say it then? If you're so proud of knowing what it is,
Jordan, I hate to say a demonic word here, but sodium chloride, get the fuck out.
You guys can't see those are Jordan is doing a cross the sign of a cross.
I might be crazy. I might be crazy, but I'm going to toss this out for you, Dan. Yeah. I think
somebody who knows what dihydrogen monoxide is yet believes that the president is secretly
controlled by the devil is still dumber than somebody who thinks things are what they are,
but it's like, just say one. Yeah. That's my belief. And I think that, you know,
we're leaving all that aside. I think, you know, you may be right. You may be wrong,
but my conjecture is sure. Anybody who thinks one of these kinds of studies of the public means
anything is a dick. Oh, that's fair. And they don't, they don't have much going on. I mean,
you don't, you don't remember the greatest poster before there was five 38, Dan,
there was Jay Leno. All right. And when you do jaywalking, you get the right results. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I tricked you scientific poll. Fuck you. Yeah. So we just got one last clip here. And
I mean, the, the report ends with Alex sitting in a dark studio and it actually ends with him
yelling about how the new world order is going down and just the visual of it, of him sitting
in a completely dark studio. That is like a review. That is Andy daily review. It is exactly
that. It's like, guys, where's everybody. Why is everybody leaving this show? What's going on?
Yeah. There's a, if I didn't hate him so much, there'd be a little bit of pathos
in the moment of, of him sitting alone in a dark studio, insisting he was going to destroy
the globalists. But I choose not to end our episode with that clip because honestly it's
angry. It's kind of funny to think about, but it's, it's meaningless compared to this,
this clip, I think says everything that you need to know. I understand the average person doesn't
read 300 books on world war II. Correct. I understand the average person doesn't read a
hundred books on Rome. The person doesn't read 50 books on British naval history. The average
person doesn't read 30 books on us history in the revolutionary war or five books. I disagree.
The civil war or a couple of hundred books on globalism and perfectly in Zbigniew Brzezinski and
Klaus Schwab. But I did. Nope. And so I know who these people are just because I happen to
get into it when I was like nine years old because these books were all over my house.
And so I had a piece of chip earlier, so I keep licking my lips.
Cause all the stores are closed. There's no food. The grocery stores are all closed.
So I went out and got the crew some food, got some potato chips and
some candy bars. That's that. That's about all we get right now. Cause the power's off
because the government shut the power off by shutting the power plants down.
Yeah. I think that's a good summation of Alex. Just like bragging about books he's read that
he hasn't read. What hundred books are about Klaus Schwab? Get the fuck out of here.
I don't know. He's just rambling about how well ready he is. And he's not like normal people
cause he's, he's figured all this out because he's so smart and read all this shit. And then
he gets completely derailed by a chip. Just, Oh, I ate a chip earlier. That's all we get now.
Cause the power's out, man. The greatest minds of my generation. I saw it taken down by a little
chip in the tooth for want of a toothpick. The greatest minds of my generation have been torn
asunder. Yeah. This is a bleak. Yeah. That's not good. So I, yeah, I just wanted to check in with
you and let you know how things go. We're going for Alex. And it turns out, yeah, it turns out
this is how it's going. Last we, last we know of him at the time that we're recording this,
he's just sitting alone in a dark studio and no, no telling when he'll be back.
I, I do like the idea of somebody showing up at the office tomorrow,
turning the lights off and Alex is just sitting at the desk. Just like eyes haven't
blunt for 20 hours. Just Aaron. He's actually wearing a tie. Yeah.
It's more put together than usual. I slept in the office for the first time in a long time.
It feels really great. Really great guys. I didn't, I don't know if you know this,
but you can read in the dark, probably have better comprehension of stuff than he does
at this point. Guys. I started reading books with my hands, even if they aren't in braille,
I'm figuring it out, man. Yeah. Really doing it this time. Did you know that
Klaus Schwab didn't say all the stuff I said, he says, we're going to be real trouble if people
find that out. Oh shit. Oh no. So, uh, Jordan will be back on Friday, but, uh, until then,
uh, we have a website. We do have a website. It's knowledge fight.com. Yep. We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter. It's at knowledge. We're fighting that go to bed. Jordan was on Facebook.
We are down shy Tuesday. And if you could please find a local charity or bath under your
area to help out people do in a God's work. Yeah. We'll be back. But until then I'm Neo,
I'm Leo. I'm DZX Clark. I'm Daryl Rundis. I, uh, uh, uh, uh, we'll hope the best for everybody
going through tough times with the weather all around the country.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air. Thanks for holding.
Well, Alex, I'm a first time caller. I'm a huge fan. I love your work.