N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledgefight
knowledgefight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
saying we are the bad guys
knowledgefight
Dan and Jordan, knowledgefight
Riddle Earth, Riddle Earth, Riddle Earth
I need, I need money
Andy and Kansas, Andy and, Andy and
Stop it, Andy and, Andy and Kansas
Andy, Andy, it's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding us
Hello Alex, I'm a first-time caller, I'm a huge fan
I love your room
knowledgefight
N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to knowledgefight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're a couple dudes, like to sit around, drink novelty beverages
and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are Dan
Jordan
Dan
Quick question for you
What's up?
Shut up
Oh shit
That's the trick daddy
Now we're doing a different show
Immediately we just skip into a different show
What's up?
Remix
Remix knowledgefight
Uh oh, y'all thought you were coming for Alex Jones
One of my two favorite things, that, what's up?
Shut up
And then the other one is the, hey, you know, what's your favorite ice cream flavor?
Jordan, I'm serious, what's your favorite ice cream flavor?
It doesn't matter what you're favorite
The Rock
You're gonna ask what my bright spot is, Jordan
Yes, what is your bright spot?
Today my bright spot is, we're checking in on the Hot Sauce of the Month Club
that Policy Wonk Lisa signed us up for
This month, I was a little late getting over to the box
because of snow and schedule and stuff
but this month we got the Slow Death Hot Sauce
and this is, this is good
It's good
This is quite good
For now, you don't know what's gonna happen later
It's the slow death
I might die slowly
You don't know how slow it is
It's very hot, but it also is a
Trinidad scorpion pepper based sauce
and I like the flavor of that a lot
What kind of hot?
Now that I'm a hot sauce guy too
Taste a little bit
Let's talk, no I'm not ready for that just yet
You said very hot and I don't think I'm comfortable with very hot
I think you could handle it
Sure, but not before the show is over
It might, yeah, it might make things go down a strange path
You can try some after the show
Okay, sounds good
It's pretty good, I like it a bit
I could use it, I could see myself using it for like dipping chicken maybe
or adding to a sauce
Nice little, kick it up a little
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Throw a little in some soup
Maybe a little meat sauce, put a little hot sauce in there
Sure, why not?
Do it
Yeah, if you're getting a little bit of marinara together
What's your favorite flavor of spaghetti, Dan?
I don't know
It doesn't matter what's your favorite, okay
You have to interrupt
You understand, you're too fast
So what's your bright spot?
My bright spot, Dan, is, we were talking about this earlier today
My bright spot is the Chris Gethard show
Oh sure
As you and I have spoken
Going back to our early seasons
We have spoken about this show so much and you know I'm a huge fan obviously
Chris Gethard got you a cameo
You cruelly forced him to say nice things about me through the medium of money
Like some sort of indentured servitude
Yeah, you thought your book was in Barnes and Noble
Yes, and we've developed a great friendship since then
Yes, absolutely
But yeah, no, I've been starting so many projects
I've been trying to find something new to like really sink my teeth into
And watching the Chris Gethard show and just that like unfettered creativity of it all
Is very inspiring and it's like, don't give up on doing weird shit
Yeah, it's good to reconnect with that from time to time
Like that sort of mentality
Absolutely, and that whole like, we're a public access show
We know no one's watching
That's why we're free
You know, that's something beautiful about it
That embracing of like, no we're not trying to get famous or anything like this
It's really interesting too to consider that both Chris Gethard and Alex Jones grew out of public access
That is interesting, yes
The two people who affect my life most today
Two very divergent individuals
Very different paths they have tried
Yeah, both of them started at UCB
It's true, no, no, Alex was a groundling
Oh, that's right, that's right
Sorry, my bad
So Jordan, today we've got an interesting thing to go over
We're talking about Friday of last week
It's February 19th, 2021
Blackjack
I think that counts, you got 20...
I know
We're gonna leave that to the judges
Okay
The judges in the audience will determine
I think the only question is whether or not you fully finished the 21
I think you started before I finished, and that's why I stopped
I think
Anyway, it's Friday of last week
This episode is nuts, so
Okay, I imagine so
Yeah, power's back on
Pretty much in the info studio, although maybe it's running on generators
It's unclear
Alex is really, really mad
He is really mad
Well, yeah, I, yeah
He has a lot of breakdowns on this episode
and some will be fun to laugh at
and discuss what he's lying about in order to get himself in the place where he can freak out
Yeah
But before we cover this episode, Jordan, let's take a moment to say thank you to some folks who signed up on our sporting show
That's a great idea
So first, I liked his name a lot, it's an affirmation
I'm a worthy human being, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, thing I have never said to my mirror
Okay, next, on American Podcast, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much on American Podcast
Also, thank you for happy birthday Alayna, you are now a policy wonk
This is a week late
This is a week late?
Yeah, I was late on the messages
Anyway, happy birthday Alayna, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Happy birthday Alayna
Next, Alphren with two Ns, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks Alphren
Next, Heather M, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
you very much Heather and I'd like to give a little technocrat shout out to
someone who I think has two aliases so I'm gonna this is just one shout out
right to two names so it's old dirty dirt McGirt Oh dirt McGirt
old dirty Chinese is he back no knock knock you busted oh okay of our first
bits way back one of the beginnings yeah who's there oh and then yes thank you
very much to the both of you you're now a technocrat I'm a policy wonk crikey
mate that's fantastic have yourself a brew how's your 401k doing bro we got to
go full tilt boogie on this Watson all right let's just get down to business we
ain't making that money off that heroin why you pimps so good my neck is
freakishly large I declare info war on you yes thank you so much to the both of
you yeah thank you so much very complicated now I don't want so Jordan
what's up um shut up you know what the deal is a little
dancy I've had very little sleep because the neighbors downstairs have been
partying oh I'm a little bit on fumes right a little bit loose right my
connection with the present is tenuous you've got a runner's high a little bit
yeah I think that there are some college students who live downstairs and I was
gonna I will text you and complain about this every now and again I can hear them
yell singing through the floor so they'll just be like singing wet ass
pussy yeah this sucks I'm waiting for you to get a saw and just get a whole
circle in the topping I've thought about drop it down I'm I am inches away from
old man stomping on the floor but I just can't do it and I feel right knocking on
the door cuz it's kovat yeah anyway yeah you're gonna need a broom that's why I'm
a little silly but the good news is Alex isn't in like a totally centered present
presence of mind himself that's good episodes we kind of match energy we're
all playing on a level playing field yeah here's an out-of-context drop from
today's show that's why we're in the position where as a bunch of lawyers a
bunch of candy-ass lawyers cover their ass so much the Chinese are running the
tables on us get ready to nuke our ass because you little chicken-net America
hating bastards have taken over the damn country
if I were Alex in the position he's in right now I think I'd probably hate
lawyers too yeah I like this I like getting back to where we should be which
is everybody hating on lawyers we've had it's been a while since everybody's
really agreed to just hate lawyers you know what I'm saying sure used to be
what we did all their early 90s Jurassic Park
everybody hated lawyers lawyers were more of a villain in Jurassic Park than
the dinosaurs exactly exactly that's the whole thing um yeah I don't know Alex is
it and we're in a weird state so Alex starts the show by talking about how
like maybe I shouldn't do the show which is nice that's a good way it's always a
good sign for the show that's about to happen start you know I learned
something during the Trump administration I had never tried to be
in LA or be in New York or be in DC and to be you know around the power I had
never tried to go be a sycophant and and and in the system but I noticed very
early on they would work around the clock to try to make sure that I didn't
have access to the president or access to anybody high-level government because
I always just thought inform the public about things and then that would
percolate up into government and into governance and then we would be able to
stand up against tyranny triple up lionomics take action against the
globalist but it's a balance it's a balance you also need to target
obviously people that are in a power structure and I'm almost tempted right
now with the news I have that I've been working on the last hour to just not do
the show today it probably would be better if I just call Tucker Carlson
call Steven Crowder call Roger Stone and try to get on the phone with Trump
cuz I get on the phone with them if I need to can you come up with the
audience down we cover so much hardcore stuff here but but we're here every day
no one kind of takes it serious we just drop bomb after bomb after bomb after
bomb after bomb after bomb after bomb after bomb but film but familiarity
breeds contempt and I get it I have contempt for myself too I don't realize
how important we are in the great work we've done this is an interesting head
space that is a startling number of words for a very simple concept to
express yeah yeah I people other people have better reach than I do I think I
need to probably yeah I could do but it is also like really shitting on the
audience yeah yeah it's my job you guys you guys are so used to me being the
best you don't even give a shit how great I am so good you don't even have
to try I wish I was worse at my job so you guys would have to raise your level
if only I kill time most of the time and then drop the bomb every now and again
you would know to amplify that bomb exactly exactly that's my problem also
why do you need to get a hold of Trump he's not the president anymore no he's
the president president he's the secret president it's very strange very strange
you ever you ever been at a comedy show Dan where for whatever reason the host
has just like their opening set was just something really weird and everybody in
the audience and all of the comics got the vibe of like this is gonna be a
weird show mm-hmm that's not gonna change mm-hmm this just happened it
doesn't matter that there's an hour and 20 minutes left yeah for the next hour
and a half it's gonna be weird yeah you've set the energy exactly you could
dig out of the hole and we might have some enjoyable whatever but it's still
gonna be weird it's gonna be yeah yeah it's gonna be strange this is what I'm
hearing right now yeah and you hear it a lot too like this this tone of like I
don't even want to do the show anymore but it's particularly severe distance
makes the heart grow fond familiarity braids content a contempt so I'm gonna go
to rebroadcast for a while we're gonna get real re ready to shoot the show go
live here today and then I may not do the show today just because this is too
important I don't have the smoking gun absolute total complete master plan of
the enemy we have them by the short hairs completely and no one is gonna
care it's always the same it's always the same all of you listeners I bring
light I give you all their plans that nothing happens I've got a call Tucker
Carlson and Steven Crowder I'm gonna be honest with you I don't think that
familiarity always breeds contempt you know it does though contempt that would
breed I would also argue continually starting the show with my news is too
big for me to do the show is something too familiar for me not to be
contemptuous about yes yes there's a lot of there's a lot of intersections of
familiarity in this equation so yeah Alex freaks out he's just screaming how
he wants to quit sure but I'm here to tell you we're gonna we had to get back
in the new studio today we weren't quite ready to launch it's okay not blaming
the crew that's okay time ready to go and to prepare my broadcast because
here's the deal I'm not just gonna sit here and put this information out and
just have it nothing happened I'll quit today because we have all the evidence
of what the enemy's done and I don't know why people don't have an instinct
to victory but it's incredible it was bleeped out he said no one gives a shit
he is very mad I like he is pretty mad I I do I mean there's something there's
something weirdly noble about the tenacity he has because every other
human being I think on the planet would at a certain point go like well I've
seen every other major news organization release huge information and then change
the world mm-hmm and I think I've done that literally every day for my entire
career and not once have I changed the world yeah perhaps it is me yeah maybe
my radar is busted maybe I can't tell what's big news maybe it's me maybe I
should look a little bit harder at the stories I cover nope nope nope it's
everybody else's fault forever gotta get so mad the end everyone else's fault
always and one of the things I really love about his broadcast style when he
gets into these moods is like he doesn't say what the news is yeah why would it
it's too big you can't handle it I enjoy that busy being petulant I enjoy that
because it's really the tell that this is performance yeah on some level yeah
like I think he's really mad there's something that is definitely pissing
him off for sure and it's probably financial and maybe the staff so I would
imagine it has something to do with lawyers probably lawyers the staff
probably also is incompetent and not not doing the job that he needs them to do
yeah but it he's not that mad about what this big news is he's clearly still
using this like this breakdown lashing out as a way of like anybody who's
watching oh they'll tell people that he's saying he's gonna quit on air no
it's him being like use it there's something else pissing him off I'm gonna
use it in my speech today yeah yeah what am I talking about what's the big news
no one cares I shouldn't even say it probably at least when I call other
people that are influential they care and look into it and put it out I call
Paul Watson with this oh he's busy out on a date or something I'm not mad at
Paul he already wrote like five articles today it's just that I don't have the
people I don't have the infrastructure I don't have anything and we can have the
keys to put Lucifer into the pit of hell no one would care they'd be busy get
their fucking nails done if I were Paul I would not appreciate the way Alex
talks about him he seems professional oh man weird weird to have to work with
that guy yeah it's almost like he lashes out at the people around him as well as
the audience on a constant basis yeah yeah like he's a child almost yeah we
get to the big news sure Alex does eventually let it rip what the story is
and it is bullshit you understand ladies and gentlemen we have the smoking gun of
what did the power outage 100% it was the Department of Energy and their order
to keep the power off you understand we have that and no one gives a damn I I
quit then screw this whole frickin place man I mean this is just all out of
control unbelievable we have released so many smoking guns so much proof Joe
Biden is on TV on CNN saying Gigi ping is doing a good job invading Hong Kong
and running giant death camps fine if America wants that then frickin have it
if you want your power turned off by the Department of Energy then enjoy it I'm
gonna run some tapes I'm not even sure let it all burn then I mean we can't
even admit aborting babies is murder so we don't deserve to have power
I'm gonna lead you into the next okay Trump did win but it's a setback I'm
still gonna lead you in it nope yeah everyone dies all this emotional
outburst and this childish pageantry yeah but he's still able to say frickin
he's still able to recognize he's on the radio and he doesn't want to get fine
totally so I find this a little false yeah so also it appears that Alex is
very mad about a document from the Department of Energy that he's been
shown and I would guess that he hasn't read this document he claims that it's
smoking gun evidence that the power outages in Texas were intentional which
is why he's putting on this shamefully childish display of fake rage at the
start of the show we'll get into the document as Alex covers it but at this
point let me just sum things up to say that Alex is entirely wrong about it
that's not hard no that's not hard to believe no but it does it does like the
the level to which he's wrong about it makes all this outburst really really
funny what I do appreciate about all of this is there is you can't deny that
being your own boss is great right sure I mean he technically said I quit yeah
exactly like that kind of outburst you just get that if you work for someone
else and Wolf Blitzer is not going on TV on election night being like shit I
don't even know what the results are I quit let's let's imagine that Alex did
have a boss but he had such a good contract that they just couldn't get
him out of it like firing him would require paying out ten years it's
something ridiculous if he did that and he was yelled I quit on air and I was
his boss would be like he said it he said he's gone he's gone I accept your
letter of resignation immediately that's the other good thing about not having a
boss means anything exactly so like this is a smoking gun sure there's another
smoking gun and then there's another there's so many Alex has so many guns
okay this is smoking gun stuff and then I've got a bunch of other big giant
smoking guns but I'm too angry to do the show right now I am too damn angry to do
this broadcast right now and there's a lot of other stuff going on so I'm gonna
just I've got to go find my stack of news from yesterday I got to do a lot of
stuff around here sure I watch somebody walk out oh no you've got the stack
well I'll go get it myself but I'm not even bitching anymore I just can't do
this six seven days a week and just with the public like zombies everywhere just
like walking into globalist machine-gun fire and then that weird reanimated
corpse Biden's stumbling around up there just all of it just it's just it's a
joke because people are unconscious from watching TV and playing on their phones
all day ah that's it yeah that's the problem yeah the public yeah hmm he's
having a bad day yeah yeah you know I can't help but feel like I've been there
before and what comforts me all the time is when I just go oh no I'm just an
asshole yeah you know like everybody else is asleep and everybody no no I'm
just being a dick my bad guys I'm an asshole I just I'm having a bad day I
didn't like you know some I got too overcharged for something totally maybe
I'm taking it out on the people around me subconsciously I'm sorry and you tell
them and they're like you know what I get it yeah it happens and then you're
just like we got a de-escalate for Alex it's an essential piece of his
showmanship dwelling in that place he's having a bad day yeah and that means
everyone's got to die yeah people are unconscious from watching TV and playing
on their phones all day it manipulates all the dopamine receptors where people
think that's the real world and the real world they're all like this and I just
don't want to be around this anymore maybe Bill Gates is right just kill
everybody but use a neutron bombs at least and kill them quick man don't
mutate them and torture them and dumb them down but Bill Gates get a deal with
the globalists and start neutron bombing the public just neutron bomb everybody
then we don't kill the earth and the humans are gotten rid of baby he's right
maybe I should go work for Gates and just come up with a neutron bomb plan I
know Bertrand Russell had one before they call it a neutron bomb do you know
anything about neutrons the answer how to start over you know God did it so I
guess there's imitating God maybe I should just salute Bill Gates right now
on there pledge allegiance to him nobody else cares do it at least he actually
wants to run something it's me the devil do it I have the giant news but no one
no one cares of course I'm serious no one cares maybe I freak out maybe I cut
a few fingers off with loppers and people and this is really important this
will bring down the globalists here let me cut my pinky off oh now you pay
attention the Department of Energy on record told Texas you can't produce more
power I have the damn document with a direct link to them they'll just have
Snopes say it isn't real hell we want to be able to pull it up in there probably
so anyways I'm gonna go to rebroadcast for a while I'm gonna try to settle down
and then I'm gonna come back and lay all this out for you so incredible it's
incredible that is what wasn't a display that was a show that was a baby just
man you know what suck it would really suck if his conspiracies were actually
true oh yeah cuz that now the movement about these things are so beholden to
him that like like the imagined like having to fall in line behind him Oh
brutal oh this guy's onto something brutal this whiny little asshole you
know you know thankfully he's not you know goes down in history for being a
hero people who weather adversity you know when you think of Nelson Mandela
and you think of being put in prison for all those years and then not just
surviving through it but then going on to help found a fucking country for a
real opportunity at equality but you write you read his speech yeah no one
cares you guys imprison me for 25 years and I don't even know if I want to help
any of you people I quit no one gives a shit about me Bishop Desmond Tutu's an
asshole yeah yeah that's who I want to follow it to the noble noble leader yeah
so I think part of his anger is coming from a place of like he wasn't on this
sooner cuz like this document was available before and he could have been
covering the story at this way before and said he had the sort of childish oh
it was the windmills narrative and what have you I think I think that's where a
little bit of this anger comes from before I went live on air I got a bunch
of extra news that I would already was told by a very close person to me and I
dropped the ball on Monday and just I've been told by inside sources in Texas
power plants that the feds ordered them not to increase power I should have
followed up on that I already knew there was those agreements I already knew
about those documents I should have gotten the current ones I should have
found out well let me see the directive instead I just went and poured another
glass of wine and set a fire in the dark and then son of a bitch a whistleblower
inside Department of Energy contacted someone that works here and said why is
Jones not covering this no one else is and I read it 20 minutes for I went on
air and I already knew all that was real we went and checked it's on the
Department of Energy website and it was like being punched in the chest and the
stomach over and over again to read for sure they raped us for sure they're
doing it I am so freaking pissed man I can't take much more of these people
and the way it's you sound like the demons all slimy the way it's written is
all slimy what is wrong with this man I don't know I'm not sure exactly what the
definition of slimy documents are but I guess for Alex it's when the document
says the opposite of what you need it to say and so you have to argue that when
they say yes they really mean no exact is slimy is super slimy super slimy
also I think that I think thug thinks it's slimy Dan I think Alex is really
using the term whistleblower too loosely here is a publicly available document on
the Department of Energy's website so I would say that this is a tipster if
anything well maybe someone who's doing Alex's work for him I don't know maybe
somebody who's just been to that website it's not a whistleblower no the document
in question is titled order number 202 dash 2 1 dash 1 it's four pages long so
there's no way I believe Alex read it and it's really easy to find and if you
go do do find it yeah what you'll read is an order that is designed to increase
the electric capacity of the Texas power grid in order to deal with the emergency
that the state is going through sure on February 14th quote the Electric
Reliability Council of Texas an independent system operator whose
service territory includes 90% of the electric customers in the state of Texas
filed a request for emergency order under section 202 C of the Federal Power
Act the beginning of the document lays out how ERCOT had foreseen the possible
issue and they quote this weather event is expected to result in record winter
electricity demand that will exceed even ERCOT's most extreme seasonal load
forecasts to try to adjust for this ERCOT attempted to maximize energy
generation by doing things like having the Railroad Commission of Texas put out
an emergency order that quote specified increasing the priority of gas supplies
to ERCOT generators one of the main things that this order is about is that
the electricity generation that they were needing to engage in would almost
certainly not be possible quote without violating federal air quality or other
permit limitations so ERCOT appealed to the Department of Energy to get an order
allowing them to work outside those regulations due to the emergency
situation right on page two of the order it says quote given the emergency nature
of the expected load stress the responsibility of ERCOT to ensure
maximum reliability on its system and the ability of ERCOT to identify and
dispatch generation necessary to meet the additional load I have determined
that the additional dispatch of the specified resources is necessary to best
meet the emergency and serve the public interest for purposes of FPA section 202
C okay so the document Alex Jones is saying is them saying you can't have
more power is them saying yes you can have more power with some limitations
well sure I mean you can't destroy the earth right yeah the order is the acting
secretary of energy replying to ERCOT saying that they have permission to
break regulations up to a point sure yeah yeah yeah the order literally says
quote ERCOT anticipates that this order may result in exceedance of emissions as
well as wastewater release limits to minimize adverse environmental impacts
this order limits operation of dispatched units to the times and within
the parameters determined by ERCOT for reliability purposes that's great it's
pretty simple this is just an order where ERCOT asked for permission to
wiggle around some regulation in order to be able to meet the increased demand
of the energy emergency the Department of Energy replied that they could do so
but that wiggle room only existed for the purposes of re-establishing
reliability of the power grid they couldn't just flout all federal
pollution regulations but some be less rigidly enforced given the human need
that existed yeah we don't want to destroy the earth but people are
freezing to death so let's find a better place than find a way to make this work
exactly there's nothing here honestly it doesn't sound like which is why Alex is
doing this high school drama club play about how serious and smoking gun it all
is it's actually a document that says the opposite of what he claims it does
and because that is the case he has to claim that it's slimy this is the level
of work that he's doing and it really makes you wonder why he doesn't just
quit like it's it's this is nothing I don't know cuz he's his own boss I guess
slimy slimy start all over again anyway I don't think he's even read it so I
don't I wouldn't expect him to understand some of these like dynamics
and all of this yeah but I think that he realizes like I don't know if I can
really even fucking explain this to the audience in a way yeah it's gonna make
them motivated this might be too hard for me yeah better call Tucker oh boy I
can get more done if I call a bunch of influential people I know and tell them
to look into this and let them break it I don't care about breaking it and then
it will actually get have an effect instead the audience is great but I say
so much stuff people just hear it and just think oh that's another thing Alex
just said no it's not it's whatever happened to plan B smoke and God I ever
saw to quote Robert Duvall in network it's a big titted head okay I mean this
thing would hurt them so freakin bad I hate the New World Order I can't stand
Bill Gates I can't stand Warren Buffett I can't stand Ted Turner I can't stand
Barack Obama I can't stand them anymore I want them off my back now you mothers
and then I sit there and I read exactly what I was told by my family that works
in these damn plants that they're ordered to go at zero or quarter power
under the frickin federal government because Biden put them back under the
son-of-a-bitch two weeks ago now we all knew that did we I feel like we did not
know that no and I don't know I read this document I died I don't I still
don't know it yeah man you know I here's my pitch for Alex and I mean this is
gonna sound crazy all right but he's sick of being under the backs of sure
Bill Gates Warren Buffett Ted Turner for some reason uh-huh join the socialist
buddy we want to try and get rid of these rich people and remove their power
come on man no get rid of them let's go cuz socialists are working for Ted
Turner they don't just don't know it oh well how about this all this what if Ted
Turner here's here's my cell here's my cell back to you Alex yeah what if Ted
Turner thinks we're working for him but we're actually working for our own goals
using his money and power that he thinks he's bought us with another possibility
would be moved to Antarctica okay now that's also a good one
Alex you can also go to Antarctica so one of the features of Alex's coverage
of this document from the Department of Energy is one of those
strategies he uses a lot I call it making things up oh that's a good one
and guess what's in the document the Department of Energy told Texas under
federal law you'll be prosecuted unless you exhaust outside power supplies first
there's no mention of prosecution the relevant part of the order that Alex is
talking about is as follows quote consistent with good utility practice
ERCOT shall exhaust all reasonably and practically available resources
including available imports demand response and identified behind the meter
generation resources selected to minimize increase in emissions to the
extent that such resources provide support to maintain grid reliability
prior to dispatching these specified resources this makes total sense and
Alex is just writing a story about it to make things seem more nefarious when in
reality this is very much a document that is the Department of Energy giving
ERCOT a fair amount of leeway and trying to keep the system online frequently in
the document you see it made clear that if the determination of what is
necessary is that they need to put on more save lives now yeah save lives now
the determinant the determination of when it's necessary to put on all these
other things that's at the discretion of ERCOT yeah that is not that's that's
left up to them yep and so like behind the meter generation resources for what
it's worth is like solar and batteries and stuff like that so I don't know I
just don't I don't I don't see I don't see what he's saying I don't find this
very compelling at all no Texas always had more power than anybody we should
supply before Obama came in the states all around us remember that our grid
supplied much of the country that's what we were proud of it remember the US
under Trump got to where it was the biggest supplier of energy in the world
for the first time since the 50s again this is just something Alex is making
up the power grid in Texas specifically exists in such a ways to not supply
power to other states to avoid interstate energy sales regulation from
the federal government someone's the pretend persona that Alex has should
really understand that dynamic well and be proud of it also Alex is just
reporting something Trump lied about and pretending it's real Trump basically
lied in his State of the Union speech about how for the first time in 65 years
we're net exporters of energy but that's not true no anyway prices for energy
you're going up oh well yeah I imagine so Reuters Texas wholesale electric
prices spiked more than 10,000 percent amid outages and what does this little
sweet document show that I'll show you the print of the next segment they had
to first only buy from outside sources including available imports and demand
response you look those terms up that means demand response is a term meaning
outside power when you don't have enough demand response is a key term means you
buy from available imports these are all lawyer terms once again I think that
one's just an economics term well making things up because he knows that his
audience doesn't care and they're never gonna check on any why would they demand
response according to Alex's lawyer speak for that means you got to buy
outside power he knows this because he looked it up yeah this is made up out of
thin air yeah demand response is an energy efficiency strategy that involves
giving customers the ability to adjust their electricity usage away from peak
hours by doing things like offering cut rates at other times when the burden on
the electric grid is lower or putting small tariffs on power during peak
periods this Department of Energy document is saying that in addition to
using available reserves demand response strategies should be employed where
possible to maintain the functioning of the power grid oh so you mean
incentivizing people to spread out the usage of power yeah oh when possible yeah
I was I'm fairly certain that you did just say buy all your power from China
sure it would be easy for someone to hear me make this correction of Alex and
say that I'm just nitpicking and fact-checking him pointlessly but
there's a really serious phenomenon that I'm trying to illustrate here Alex Jones
constantly pretends to know things he has a consistent pattern of just making
up definitions of words and details about news stories and then pretending
that the thing he's making up is the product of research or investigation
it's important to recognize that he does this about the small details of his
day-to-day conspiracies in the same way he does with the larger worldview level
conspiracies his workflow is essentially like walking watching a shitty improv
show rooted in terrible racist politics he uses headlines and words he skims and
stories as the suggestions from the audience that he takes on any riffs a
scene out of it I would implore anyone who takes him seriously to consider that
dynamic and to critically engage with the things he's saying you'll almost
always find him fabricating details about the stories that he's covering in
order to make them fit his predetermined narrative and worldview which he
absolutely wouldn't need to do if he wasn't full of shit as for the
skyrocketing prices of energy some consumers are seeing that is being
reported in reputable outlets and it does appear that some of this is going
on the Public Utility Commission of Texas is opening an investigation into
possible price gouging and I would guess that if they find companies that were
engaging in that then the customers will not be responsible for paying those
outrageous rates there's one thing to keep in mind however a small number of
people in Texas use a company called gritty to provide their electricity
which operates on wholesale prices most people use providers who have fixed
rates but going through a company like gritty actually saves people money on
their electric bill generally the downside is in a situation like this
their rates are not fixed and they can skyrocket even so I would guess that
these people won't be stuck with these exorbitant bills and the solution will
be reached I I don't I just I find it hard to believe that but I don't know
yeah I mean I don't know at this at this point in time it's safer to assume that
people are going to get fucked over in some massive fashion possibly possibly
but I I would I would guess that there will be some forgiveness yeah yeah but
something but the examples that you see are these like really really high bills
and the ones that I've been able to see and someone could correct me if I'm
wrong but the ones that I've been able to find being reported are wholesale
prices okay which are not the majority of electric users right in the state of
Texas most people have fixed rate and they're obviously their prices will go
up too but not per like the right right right they will need to use more
electricity to heat their house because it's colder outside right yeah but they
won't you know that's just a natural phenomenon you know and like I mean
just price gouging is illegal yes that's going on people will get to the bottom
I will help yeah so Alex you know he's got this document that he's lying about
yes he feels really excited about this lie he's pretty pumped about it and he's
like you know what these fucking people in Congress in Texas and our governor
they need to lie about this document too oh no and all Ted Cruz has got to do to
change the subject all Greg Abbott has to do to redeem himself all John Corn
has to do is come out and read this on air and it's game over by the way I've
had my problems with Ted Cruz but I think he's a good constitutionalist
Ken Kuhn is like going out to get a cheeseburger in Texas it's an hour and
45 minute flight his daughters were going down there why do I care if he
flew down there with his daughters to get out of this hell when it turned out
his power was off my powers was off a bunch my water just came back today most
folks still don't have water now you're there out of school why not go Mexico
see we live by Mexico folks we go down there but I'm not even defending that
how is that the news how is he horrible and the Democrats are all oh look he
doesn't care about you he didn't want the lockdowns he didn't want to wear the
mask it's not like he's for a lockdown he's caught getting out of one ladies
and gentlemen Alex Jones with a master class and intentionally missing the
point yep yep yep remarkable I think the the point could very easily be made that
he doesn't see that as something very difficult to do because he too is rich
could be could have something to do with that could be could be one of those
things where rich people don't really understand why poor people get mad yeah
and I think that it's a it's a really interesting way that Alex engages with
Ted Cruz and his responsibilities as an elected official yeah yeah as opposed to
the responsibilities of other enemy yeah you know it's weird just because you
don't need to be there doesn't mean you're sure so Alex is mad at ERCOT now
I should say that he doesn't know that it's the Electric Reliability Council of
Texas well he doesn't really know what it is he doesn't he thinks he seems to
think that ERCOT is like basically Enron oh okay I get what you think it's a
company yeah of course he does yeah it's weird and I'm just reading it made me so
angry that I almost turned this desk over seriously man but you know what
that's a normal response to learning they not just robbing our future they're
blaming us they're starving people they're bankrupting all these
communities they killed over 50 people and and then now they're gonna rape us
more and are telling us permanent blackouts because the feds put ERCOT in
control because you can't have the state managing it the feds put ERCOT the feds
put ERCOT in control Alex has no idea what that is well he seems to think it's
like a power company as opposed to being the management entity for Texas's power
grid which is run by a board of directors that's overseen by the Public
Utility Commission of Texas and the state's legislature the Public Utility
Commissioners responsible for overseeing ERCOT are directly appointed by Texas's
governor there could almost be no system imaginable where the state would have
more direct control over the power system other than one where the state
itself runs all the power plants itself which I can't imagine Alex advocating
for no no no Alex knows nothing about the subjects he's covering and he's just
making up a story to tell the audience that fits the show's larger themes and
narratives none of this is based in reality at all yeah outrageous also you
don't get to you don't get to care he doesn't get to care you already did the
coronavirus thing where you denied all of that shit do you don't get to be like
oh how dare they do this now now fuck off it's remarkable how everything is a
conspiracy shit yeah anyway Alex gets back to this document and this is this
is kind of I guess one of the other reasons I'm in a nice mood beyond the
sort of slap happiness and sleep deprived ness cuz he's talking about the
docks he's talking about a document yeah and I always like it when we can get
ground you like the dock yeah in the ERCOT region that's Texas the
generating unit specified resources that this order pertains to are listed on the
order two zero two dash two one dash one resource list as described below and
it's Oh hydroelectric and it's all this it takes them a week to turn a coal
plant up didn't let him do that so Alex is reading this part of the document
that he's skimming and it should come as no surprise but he's just making shit up
the resource list that's referenced in that Department of Energy order is
available and it's easy to find it's just a list of power generation plants
in Texas that are relevant to the order each plant is listed in the third column
in the spreadsheet is the type of energy that they use okay literally zero are
solar or windmills or hydroelectric because that's not what the order
pertains to it doesn't seem like those would be important no particular one
these are all natural gas lignite bituminous coal or distillate fuel oil
power generators which are being given special permission to operate in ways
that would exceed environmental rules specifically only when doing so would be
needed to maintain the reliability of the grid Alex hasn't read the actual
document nor has he seen this resource list he's literally just making up what
he thinks the story is then repeating that to his audience as a fact that's
what he does yeah it makes up stories he's a storyteller yeah also this should
make it more than abundantly clear we have an order saying that these evil
power companies can destroy the earth in order to save lives but all the
renewable energies are just like yeah you guys keep on going like it seems it
seems very obvious that one of these is a serious polluter destroying the world
and the other one they're like okay well you guys are fine mm-hmm yeah so Alex is
you know again it's really confused about about ERCOT and what have you and
the relationship with the federal government the feds are in charge man a
lot of people are confused as to how this happened mm-hmm we're gonna come
back and read all this for you it's really bad right here it's really really
bad but the point is the feds are in control the feds wouldn't let them up
the power till the power grid was going down and then limited what they can do
and then sat back and said Texas is a bunch of idiots a bunch of hay seeds
well I'm watching he-haw right now I'm aware no Joe Biden go take me over Joe
Biden knows how to cook a possum oh yeah
I'm not sure that's what's happening I'm fairly certain that I have heard many
calm comments on Biden's ability to cook possum mm-hmm the jury's out on it from
what I've heard sure some people like it some people don't yeah be just above
board and totally clear any kind of like Texan bashing that's going on I think is
wrong yeah I think it's misguided counterproductive yeah at least to the
extent that that is going on I am I don't know what extent it is I have not
really been exposed to much of it myself sure I imagine if I spent more time on
Twitter maybe I would have seen some dumb comments yeah get him out but
whatever that said what Alex is doing is trying to take valid criticisms about
how Texas their power grid is operated and then he turns that into people
saying that Texans just watch he-haw all day and cook possum he doesn't have a
response to the arguments about the grid because he doesn't actually even
understand the conversation the people are having not even a little bit but he
can get his audience personally offended if he makes the whole thing about how
the coastal elites think people in the middle of the country are stupid that's
pretty much the tactic that you see being employed here it's infuriating I
do not appreciate that he is talking about a problem that is almost entirely
the result of a state desiring more than anything else for the federal government
to get out of their fucking business and then to blame the feds for being in
their business yeah I mean I think I think that I think that there's a piece
of it that you can probably blame on the organizational structure short of the
disconnection from the interstate yeah sales of energy but also like I think
that you also have to be very careful with that because of how severe this
storm is like oh totally like even in ideal circumstances there would have
been power outages like it 100% perhaps not to the extent that it you know we
have seen sure and maybe not as severe as we've seen but a storm like that in
Texas is something that is just a recipe for there's going to be a lot of trouble
sure sure I am I'm just saying that if the reports of them being that close to
having no power for months are true right that is 100% look there are gonna
be power outages they happen here they happen everywhere and it can be dealt
with but if you have a system that is like well we were a James Bond moment
away from fucking never having power for the next year then yeah you done fucked
up in the planning somewhere along the line yeah and it's it's really tough to
say if that problem is essentially related to the non interstate energy
sales it's just unrelated mismanagement or something it's highly possible I
don't know enough to say for sure but I think that those things are important to
tease out sure before you make too much of a judgment but it does seem like
whatever it is it's something yeah yeah I mean at the very least it would be
hard to imagine if there was some sort of unified or greater area of power
control where it wouldn't be able to be transported effectively much much better
to the point where the we would have a better response time at the very least
you know it may be yeah but who knows for now all we do know is that Alex
over prepares indeed for his show that sounds true I want to be totally clear
with you I massively prepared for the show I have one two three four five six
seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen
stacks of news that I was a friend over and read and I've not even hit can't
believe he counted all the way like one story a segment and they go coming up is
this no no no no I will not sit here and watch the Department of Energy override
Trump's executive orders and tell Texas they couldn't increase power when I have
the smoking gun I just want to I just want to see this all over the news I
want to see them go to prison got bad news yeah that's gonna be trouble yeah
it's probably not gonna happen yeah good luck buddy so Alex is personally
offended because this is about Texas yes of course you know yeah and what he
wants you to know is the Texas what about you look at me I am looking
straight on right on the eyes Texas what about it those people take action and
Alex might have the worst example that he uses okay there's a mistake that this
operation comes out of Texas there's a mistake Kennedy got his head blown off
down here people are ready to take action down here ladies and gentlemen
I'm not defending what happened to Kennedy I'm just saying the new oh what
with a lot of fire and they take our kindness as weakness because they're
stupid because they haven't studied history and they have no idea about
people dedicated to an idea dedicated to their family dedicated to God dedicated
to war to defend it if need be why did you say look Texicans Texans will
fucking kill the president we'll do it right fucking now that's weird I thought
it was a right now I guess I guess if there's one thing I know about the South
it's that they murder presidents dad huh this this adds a wrinkle to the
conspiracy I guess yep yep this is interesting it's not the mob is not the
Russians it was not a single lone actor it was the lone star state George HW
Bush Connecticut yeah yeah yeah I don't know this could be a tough one to sell
do you think it's a coincidence that infowars comes out of the same state
where Kennedy was killed what I don't think it is I don't think I was hoping
it was a good no it's not Ted Cruz's dad did it no Alex Jones's dad did it he was
a CIA dentist oh shit yeah shot him with a tooth exactly the magic bullet was
actually a no it was an exploding tooth it was a dune situation yep totally
that's dr. Jones's calling card so Alex goes to calls and not a lot of these are
worth even mentioning although I will say that this next call is probably the
saddest I've been listening to Alex in a long time nobody with my three kids I
live close to the Memorial City Mall right in the suburbs right in the thick
of this whole thing and I can just want to say thank you to you guys because
there is not a chance I would have gotten through this with my myself my
wife my three kids without two things first thing the water filtration system
is incredible anybody listening please please get prepared you do not want to
be a victim to this government to this squeeze bank info wars and Alex and this
entire crew because every day you guys get uncomfortable and you have the
uncomfortable conversation and you teach us here on the ground to be
uncomfortable and to talk to people and to have the uncomfortable conversation
and the reason why I let you so much much much so much Alex is you're real
you stay when you make mistakes you say when something got by you and when the
Q thing and you're just a real info wars is as real as it gets in America and I
can tell you from listening to you guys from my generator power this week you
kept my connection to humans you kept my connection to God Alex and I'm telling
you I have been freezing my butt off me and my family in 40-degree weather all
week long but I can promise you every morning when I wake up I was going to
band on video waiting for your reports because you guys keep our connection to
God and our human connection well that's exactly what John John the boom
I'm ready said doesn't matter Jones you blew up earlier that's real looking for
red blood and that's it all I've got is I'm real oh boy
Wow that just bummed me out so much like everything that dude was saying is so
wrong Wow just brutal just oh that is that's just so it's the uncomfortable
conversation I don't know but that that guy has just enumerated a crime like
what he is just described is somebody so destroying his mind mm-hmm that he is
enthralled to the point of death the idea that in a in a disaster no I will
say that this is one of the situations where some of Alex's products actually
probably be quite useful like I take less issue with this guy saying I bought
a water filter like hey man hey how about that it paid off yeah yeah so that
I take less issue with yeah but the the idea that in a disaster in this in this
scenario that he's in he goes to the generator to try and find Alex's videos
to keep his connection with humanity and God is just dark yeah that is a dark
thought yeah that is a dark thought especially when like okay your
connection to humanity just quit earlier in the show no shit your humanities your
connection to humanity said fuck this good Bill Gates should neutron bomb
everybody I mean it just it just makes you like you think about all the
horrible shit that's happened in the past and you're like why would people
follow that guy and you're like oh people follow any old asshole apparently
yeah I believe the expression they used to say in Missouri was it takes all
kinds yeah it takes all kinds yeah so why would anyone listen to a 13 year old
Pope and then you get that guy and you're like well yeah I guess believe
whatever you want man so I gotta ask you I don't know I don't know a lot about
this 13 year old Pope mm-hmm is that the young Pope was that that HBO show no no
no that was a that was what what's his face I don't know British dude was he the
type who told his audience to prepare kill lists yeah actually he was oh he and
Alex have that in calm I believe you ladies and gentlemen I don't have words
to describe to you how serious the times are I know you already know that and I'm
not saying be violent either because that'll be misconstrued and used against
us and the people we go after are just minions they don't count but they don't
count the globalist and the people Bill Gates controls need to know in not a
threatening way they're assaulting us they need to know that we're aware of
what they're doing and that God is going to hold them accountable we're gonna
pray for God to bring vengeance upon them and that as they officially assault
us as they come after us that we reserve the right to defend ourselves he said
threateningly I don't shoot my mouth off I'm not mr. big badass you know talk
about I'm a big leader of the military and all this I'm not I just I can't sit
there and lie to you and tell you that you're not being assaulted and so like
Santa Claus you should be researching who's been naughty and who's been nice
who's gonna get cold they're stalking and who's gonna get little bicycle or
toys or candy so that's where we are we'll be right back stay with us your
calls are straight ahead so Alex talks a lot about this idea of making kill list
yeah and like I don't know I I don't know if it would hold up in court or
anything but I could see somebody like trying to kill Bill Gates or something
and then being like I was advised that he was trying to kill everyone with a
vaccine yeah and that we needed it was a defensive really he was attacking us
yeah well who told you that Alex Jones every day simply every day I don't I
don't know if it's like the kind of thing that he could get in trouble for
legally but like spiritually or or just morally yeah he's doing everything that
would lead someone to do the thing yeah just the thing hasn't happened yeah I
would I would just say that it's time to write a sequel to miracle on 34th Street
where Alex claims that Santa is making kill lists out of this naughty and nice
list listen we all know it's in the white papers it's uh no I'm Santa Claus
I'm real oh we know you're fucking real you're killing all of our children they
got kill teams of reindeer going around and elves why is that nose so blood-red
huh Santa yeah so we get another caller here and he actually brings up
interesting point that I have an answer for there were people in Oklahoma without
power freezing that you know cuz we got hit with the same storm you guys got hit
with them and they're sitting in the cold freezing and we've got a National
Basketball Association team called Oklahoma City Thunder and the whole
arena the power you know they played their basketball game and that was all
good and fun while people sat in the cold freezing that's what technocracy
is is they go Oh downtown Austin stays open all air caught stays open but I'm
in the dark for six days so some of the places that retain power during the
Texas storm seemed a little bit strange but a lot of it's actually really easy
to understand if you take the time to care a lot of it have to do with
sections of the grid where essential services were located like hospitals
being a higher priority than ones that say didn't contain hospitals sure this
could easily create the impression that there was power in downtown Austin but
not in outlying areas but if you look at the proximity of downtown to not only
the Capitol building but also Dell Seton Medical Center all kinds of warming
centers and st. David's Medical Center you start to understand how it might be
impossible to retain power to those buildings without also keeping power on
for some 6th Street businesses that maybe you were like why are they why
do they have a light also it appears that you do correctly understand why
people are mad at Ted Cruz mm-hmm oh is the basketball being played but people
are done oh are you flying to Mexico but people are dying yeah there we go now
you get it and and to be fair I would guess a similar thing is going on in
Oklahoma City where the Thunder play at the Chesapeake Energy Arena which is
within walking distance of the county courthouse the county detention center
and st. Anthony Hospital as well as the entire University of Oklahoma Medical
Center complex including the Children's Hospital and the VA yeah but you know
that everybody needs to suffer equally sure I mean it's it's a pretty simple
explanation I just don't I don't understand why people get mad or
confused about things that are like they're pretty easy to understand well
because it would be hard fine so Alex has max Kaiser on and they just talk
about Bitcoin yeah Alex gets really mad about how he could have bought Bitcoin
when it was like five dollars and now it's over 50 grand well the thing is or
whatever it is max ten years ago offered him 10,000 Bitcoin and Alex is like how
much would that be now it would be a lot of money buddy I was like I missed the
boat oh you might have missed the boat there was one funny clip but I actually
wish I would have pulled this but max's whole interview is just who gives a
shit it's just talking about how great Bitcoin is sure and Alex being like I'm
ambivalent stop giving out your web address makes it sound like you're a
sponsor but when when Alex is talking about how much this Bitcoin would be
worth now makes some kind of joke about like oh that's why you've got to sell
these boner pills it was really dishy nicely done man yeah max geyser has a
freedom as you are the Eve that is kind of enjoyable but it also makes his
interviews not really all that worthwhile for our show but after he
leaves Joel Skousen comes in oh shit Joel Skousen is a mess yeah he is a
weirdo and I just have four clips of Skousen's interview okay that are four
reasons why you should not take Joel Skousen series all right the first is
that he also along with Alex seems to think that ERCOT is of like a federal
agency or a company all right they want to set themselves up as the Savior's I
think it's important Joel that you grew me the evidence shows that it was
federal mismanagement and control with ERCOT removing the state from the
process that took one of our best power systems and made it one of our worst no
I completely agree with you Alex why the federal problem the federal EDX but so
why like shouldn't you correct him if you know that ERCOT is a Texas specific
if you understand the dynamics at play you shouldn't go along with Alex saying
a literally the opposite I completely agree with you sure what it is that he's
saying is 100% so that's not good and I'm maybe just not going to go ahead and
listen to anything that Joel has to say about the the storm and the power grid
if he doesn't know this basic yeah yeah that would be that would be a problem I
don't think I would want to learn calculus from somebody who doesn't know
algebra now here's where it gets weird reason number two not to take Joel
Skousen seriously where do you think fossil fuels and oil comes from oh god
no personally yes I think it comes from God and he put them there about 10,000
years ago to trick us in the big line petroleum geologists now it's becoming
recognized that that oil is not fossil fuel what is it well I'm afraid I have
to get theological here this was part of the creation of the earth oh my god you
know the Lord in his creation actually put oil deposits look if fossil fuels
exist if you create oil from deteriorating animals and you look at
all of the trillions and trillions and trillions of tons of oil which would
only represent a tiny fraction of the decaying bodies of any dinosaurs you
would have had to have the dinosaurs a hundred feet deep all over the entire
earth plants marine life Wow dude this is what's up yeah no Dan carbon only
comes from all dinosaurs thank God when he was making the earth put oil down
there I swear to God yeah I swear Dan yeah I mean I would I would say I don't
know this is really narcissistic and I'm gonna go ahead and preface this by
saying I don't actually believe it okay but it's kind of fun to think about I
felt a little bit of resistance on Joel Skousen's part to say that oh yeah and
part of it I'm hoping is him being like god damn it Dan's gonna make fun of this
him being like well to answer that question I have to get the whole okay okay
so Joel thinks that God put oil down there for us to to use that's another
reason not to take him all too serious I just I just suppose that look I'm
religion blah whatever but you can't do that you know like a demonstrably
ridiculous thing you can't just believe like that you can wrong you can that's
wrong no no you can you're more than free to believe whatever you want to
believe sure however it will implicate how I view your beliefs in other
subjects no I would like that to be true as well unfortunately that is not true
for most people sure yeah like if you want to believe anything like that God
put oil in the middle of the world I think it's harmless belief unless you're
using that to argue against climate change there we go right I'm going to
use your belief that God put oil down there for us to use I'm gonna use that
to inform my view of your arguments about anthropogenic sure I'm a chair
sure I just I would just prefer if we had if there if okay holy books now have
to have footnotes that's my new rule if something is demonstrably true it's a
footnote in your book I get it you stole that new rule from Bill Maher is that
from fuck off I swear to God if it is I'll kill myself sounds like something
he would say he's all anti-religion and shit any other segment called new rules
I just don't want oh that well that fine yeah yeah fine I quit that's the joke
I'm old and I'm useless Dan why don't you go turn into fossil fuel
nicely done cuz I'm not a dinosaur and I'm still only six feet below ground so
where do you think fossils come from Oh God no hmm I don't I I'm you know what
fuck it Samson every whenever he pulled the temple down he made all the fossils
okay that's interesting yeah it seems like it was intelligently designed
exactly intelligently designed and I I'm you know I'm not even sure that you know
desire you know a lot of the fossils we find of those actually lived on the
earth it's very very possible this earth was created by layers from other
previous planets where these things are previously grown and and put together oh
boy this is some this is Camelot this is some project right oh yes and to be
honest like I knew that Joel Skousen was a bit of like he has some weird beliefs
in such a lot of like it comes from his his family anti-communist royalty yeah
yeah yeah of course everything is a fucking false flag to him strange ideas
about what communism is and is not but this is this is out of my I did not know
that the planet itself was a false flag from other planets it could be could
possibly be right other planets false flagging us with themselves these
fossils they look weird that's well okay that's from space man all right so I
will admit that there are millions of people who have dedicated their entire
lives to studying and understanding what fossils are and I could listen to any
one of them however they look weirder to me than those people do so guess what
God space God yeah but see here's the thing that you don't understand about
all those people study fossils yes it's all a scam do you study fossils because
if you did you would get into it and then someone would come and put you put
their arm around you and be like listen it's all from fucking space we're
scamming people with I gotta get into this yeah yeah that's why Indiana Jones
was so cool he knew it was all a scam that was predictive program yeah exactly
it's a perfect grip that's why you steal it from the thuggy cult yeah yeah so
yeah I guess fossils coming from space is gonna be another reason I'm not gonna
take Joel Scousum too seriously that would be a good reason now I think he
might also believe in divine alchemy of some sort this is this is also kind of
weird you know when you look at the chance of this orbit of this earth being
so perfectly designed and the tilted ears to have the perfect seasons and the
moon is in the perfect spot there's just no way that these things can happen by
chance this earth was a design divine creation and you know most Christians
believe in and they should all believe in the fact that the Lord has power over
the Intel over the elements meaning the elements are intelligence enough
intelligent enough to obey commands no no it isn't natural no that most know
what the rock and water poured out it wasn't a natural spring you know the
Lord can command that elements reform and form any element necessary because
God is in command of everything created and we're made the small image of God
we'll be right back way that way to throw it to break now that that is a
thought process that I appreciate if God can command the elements then the
elements must be smart enough to understand God yeah see now I didn't
think of that yeah I didn't think that the elementals could also obey or
disobey commands I suppose yeah I guess the the staggering
unlikelihood of life leads one to just decide arbitrarily that it must be fully
designed and also the Bible is literal yeah how could how could we have such a
perfect environment a perfect planet where massive weather events are
occurring almost regularly due to our fault where people are being destroyed
over and over and over again by droughts because they get a perfect amount of
water wherever they go on the problem the problem I'm guessing is that we're
not burning enough oil well carbon is good for the planet is what I was told
that's what I'm hearing we're carbon dioxide starved damn where's my buddy
Mark Moreno at when you this dude is strange yeah yeah and I was listening to
this I was like wow you're a much weirder dude than I think I I can kind
of see why you normally stick to weird geopolitics as opposed to some of these
yeah more esoteric beliefs because they're very strange they kind of make
you look like a project Camelot person to answer that I'm gonna have to get
the object theological oh well then I'm gonna have to leave sir if the question
is why is there oil and I have to get a theological to answer it goodbye yes it
was lovely speaking to you don't have an answer I mostly bring this up and show
this to be like all right Joel Skousen is somebody who Alex thinks is super
credible very important source on like geopolitics like is Iran up to
something sure and he's also a person who thinks that God injected oil in the
world for us to find it maybe fossils come from outer space yeah yeah cuz
they're weird look like this is this is the level of expert that is hanging
around here right right beneath the surface and you're going to find them
saying things like this it's which is not to say that you can't have some out
their beliefs and not be you know like Jack Parsons everybody who trusted him
as an expert when it came to rockets and shit mm-hmm not when it came to
elementals not not true sex magic was not real yeah yeah it would be good if
you stayed in your lane stay in your lane now unfortunately his lane is also
bullshit that's a problem the difference between what lane you're in
yeah huh I don't know this was really interesting experience for me because
you know you start out with Alex furious and just like I quit fuck this I can't
do this yeah this sucks fuck this place I hate info wars I want to quit yeah but
if he does start quite that bad you know we're eventually gonna get to I'm gonna
have to get theological to answer that question Alex you go along the path you
find out what's making him so mad and it's just lying about this Department
of Energy document yeah and you know he mellows out says some bullshit and then
you get Skousen and I think that this this illustrates two really essential
points one is that Alex lies like this document he's just making shit up about
it's just over and over again finding little things that he can use as like
like as if he's climbing up a mountain little handholds that he can find to lie
about exactly and then the second thing I think this illustrates is that like
people like Skousen are not reliable sources no no so even if they have the
pretense and the aura and the the the attempted facade of being like a serious
minded I look at the documents and you know I go where you know I I've read
Carol Quigley's book and I am left to assume that all Democrats are evil or
whatever the fuck like even if you put on that hat underneath that hat is a
dude who's weird yeah about fossils and let's never forget that patient zero for
kovat 19 was indeed Steve Pachannik true and he cured it with antibiotics mm-hmm
so and he rigged up this whole election as a sting operation against the
Democrats yeah and Alex just can't handle his truth nope nope nope a lot of
his experts are reliable he also arrested the Pope forgot about that
year that's true that's true there are a lot of exploits that are regularly
unmentioned despite their very bombastic nature yeah so anyway Jordan this has
been fun but we will we will get off this this here horse and and we'll be
back but until then we have a website we do have a website it's knowledge fight
dot-com yeah we're also on Twitter we are on Twitter it's that knowledge if I
now go to bed Jordan please find a local charity or bail fund in your area
especially to help out with people struggling in Texas right now yeah we'll
be back but until then I'm neo I'm Leo I'm DZX Clark I'm Daryl run this I'm the
juiciest ice cube Andy in Kansas you're on the air thanks for holding
well Alex I'm a first-time caller I'm a huge fan I love your work I love you