N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Damn, and, Jordan, I am SWEATING
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledgefight
knowledgefight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
saying we are the bad guys
knowledgefight
Dan and Jordan
Riddle her, riddle her, riddle her
I need, I need money
Andy and Kansas
Andy and, Andy, or
Stop it
Andy and, Andy and Kansas
Andy, Andy, it's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding
Hello Alex, I'm a 6-ton color, I'm a huge fan
I love your word
knowledgefight
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledgefight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're a couple dudes, I can sit around, drink novelty beverages
and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are Dan
Jordan
Dan
Jordan Dan
I have a quick question for you
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, Jordan, is a combination of two of my great loves
As people who listen to the podcast regularly, eagle-eared listeners will know
Sure
Um, I have been on a little bit of a rice adventure
Mm-hmm
Um, mochi, certainly
The forbidden rice
That is un-forbidden
Yes, no, it's forbidden
Oh, it's still forbidden?
Oh, it's re-forbidden?
Shit
Um, and another sort of, a little bit in the past love of mine, which is vinegar
Yes
The invariant of vinegar
I didn't know that you could, maybe you're supposed to put vinegar in rice when you're cooking it?
I did not know that either
I don't know if you're supposed to, but some people recommend that you do it
Oh
So I put some vinegar, some fancy garlic vinegar, in with some rice I was cooking last night
Alright, alright
Pretty good
Two great flavors that go great together, Dan
Yup
Can't be a hundred percent certain it was that much better
Meh
But it smelled like a garlic while it was cooking
Well, that's fun
Yes
That helps
Yup
Yeah, there's no problem there
It felt like I was doing something
And that really counts for a lot
Yeah, I think cooking alchemy is a good feeling
Yeah, definitely, so I had a pretty nice time with that, making up some rice and vegetables last night
That's nice
Yeah, how about you?
Uh, Dan, my bright spot is that we are doing this episode at all
Uh-huh
In a very short period of time
You're not fired
In a very short period of time, you turned around an episode which was amazing
Well, we've had a weird couple of days, kind of
Yeah
We set out to, the plan initially was, because I had kind of a strange schedule and a little bit of a
I need a little bit of a step back kind of feel
So I asked you to cover Friday
Yup
Two episodes of Friday
I put together an episode
You did
And we recorded it
Two hours
And it was okay
Yeah
It was thoroughly okay
It was a very interesting exploration of some guys on YouTube
I gave it a shot
Yeah, I realized that there's like, you know, a lot of sort of monotony going on with Alex
And it would be a good time to take a little bit of a break
Sure
See something else
And I don't know if I'm really capable of finding new things anymore
Like I brought Alex and Project Camelot to the table
And I'm thrilled that those have worked
Yup
And Bill Cooper to some extent
But like some of my other efforts have not been great
There's been some trouble
And so I wanted to farm it out to you
And I think you found something, no spoilers
It's not possible to spoil it
It's already been spoiled
I was thinking we should just release it the way it was with a half hour that's recorded
And then two hours of dead silence
No, I mean it's not dead silence
And then call it Jordan crashed the car
Yes, Jordan
Get away from the wheel
Yeah, exactly
Yeah, so we recorded it and somehow, you know, tech glitch
Yup
Something happened
There's audio of us talking for the first half hour
And then after that point, it's just the drops
That's almost like one of those coloring book prompts, you know
Like, hey, you guys listen to the first half hour of us talking
And then fill in the rest whenever you feel like you didn't
You know what we're gonna say
Yeah, you got it
Try your, make your own knowledge fight
There's gonna be 20 minute stretches where there's nothing
There's no audio
Yeah, have a nice little chat
That's for meditating, that's where we do that
Find you
Yeah, so
Center
So in a period of mere hours, you've put together another episode for us to release
By wiping away my failure
Only for us to share it for the rest of us
No one will ever know
Yeah, and you know, hey man
I don't want you to feel too bad
Well
Anything, it happens, these things happen and it's not your fault
I think the only problem really is that puts me at like a, what?
One out of every five episodes I do it disappears
That would wipe off a hundred episodes from our tally
So it's a good thing you run it
Yeah, I'm more used to the sort of troubleshooting
Knowing when something's wrong and that kind of thing
And I think that, you know, it's no big deal
I feel bad for the listeners and for you
Because, you know, you did bring something interesting to the table
Yeah
And maybe, you know, maybe there's something that we'll dip back into later
But certainly not that episode
No
We can't redo it
We can't redo that one
No
No, that one was baffling enough as it is
Let alone trying to do it again
Yeah
Yep
Lost episode
Oh well
So Jordan, today we have an interesting thing to go over that I have scrounged up
Yes
Today we're going to be talking about October 16th, 2014
Double Down!
Oh shit!
Double Down on 14
What's a Double Down?
Like in a Blackjack table
Jesus Christ!
You have thought, you thought of that last night
Maybe this morning while I was laying in bed
There's no way I was supposed to pick up on that one
Yeah
Also bad advice, don't Double Down on 14
No, don't Double Down on a 14
No
Very bad Blackjack hand
Well, I guess it depends on what the dealer has
Eh!
But, yeah, so I decided I wanted to go back to a time before Alex was quite as,
I don't know, overtly amphetimined out
Sure
For, before the time of Trump, I wanted to get a little bit more of a taste of that
And I just sort of scrolled around randomly and I saw a name in the description of the episode
I'm like, alright, here we go
And actually, I was listening to this, it is hauntingly appropriate
Really?
Yes
You're a witch
Yes, I think
We've done this too many times for you not to be officially a witch
Yeah, I think this might boost some of my credibility as a witch
Either that or nothing ever, ever changes and it is all the same
Or everything is the reverse
Yeah, that's true
Of always the same
Yeah
So I'm excited to get down to business on this episode
But before we do, Jordan, we're gonna take a moment to say thank you to some folks who signed up
And are wonking it up
That's a good idea
So first, this is a two-named person
This is a very exciting, rare double alias
Okay
But they're both good, so I'm gonna allow it
Alright
The first is North Korean ballot boat
Hell yeah
Piloted by the skipper Roger Stone
And the other is private chef of Alex's wife's tennis partner
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Thank you
Next, Captain Details, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, person I'm not good at emulating
Next, Caitlin Dingo, girl, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks Caitlin
Thank you
Next, Nuttsack, father of Theo, Parker, and Tucker, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Thank you
Next, Adrenochrome Annie, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much Adrenochrome Annie
Do you prefer adrenochrome or adrenochrome?
I prefer a drenachrome, I think dren has a nice little more dreadful feel to it, you
know what I'm saying?
It has a sort of phonem similarity, sound similarity.
It feels good.
I prefer a drenachrome.
Really?
Why?
It seems classier.
Well yes, I see we have a, that clearly illuminates the differences between our personalities.
Sure.
Next, Glitch the cat, thank you so much, you're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you Glitch.
Thank you.
I'd like to say thank you to someone who is now a technocrat.
So thank you so much, Raptor King William the Impaler.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey mate, that's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
Alright, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this Watson, alright?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much, Raptor King William the Impaler.
Yes, thank you very much, RKWI.
You don't go with a T. Never put the the in a...
I've never put a the in an abbreviation.
We can agree to disagree on that.
Always.
Put a...
Nope.
What about that?
So what about...
Articles never go in.
Okay, so Game of Thrones is GT?
Uh, yeah.
Not got?
There's a reason O is lowercase in that.
O is simply there as a placeholder.
Everyone abbreviates Game of Thrones as GOT.
And maybe they should.
Okay.
Yep.
Hey, Jordan.
Let me ask you a question.
What's up?
Do you ever get spanked on your birthday?
You ever get birthday spankings?
Have I ever been birthday spanked?
I think I was birthday spanked one time as like a 11 or 12 year old.
And everyone immediately went, no, this wasn't a good idea.
That's gotta be really weird because like you didn't on your 10th birthday.
It's not like it happened up till then.
So it was just a new innovation?
It was very much like somebody at my birthday party had just heard of birthday spankings
and was real excited to try it out like, ooh, this will be a new thing.
And everybody stopped and was just like, no.
What is...
No!
I don't think I have ever, I don't think that spankings have ever been a fun thing in our
family.
I don't think it was ever playful.
No, that's probably, that's true of my family.
Yeah.
But there are some people who are celebrating a birthday.
Okay, well let's spank the shit out of them.
I'd like to give them a little bit of a spanking by way of a podcast.
All wonks line up.
Wait a second.
All wonks line up for the birthday spanking.
I think I might have gone down the wrong road with this setup, but earlier this week on
Monday, Pat had a birthday and wanted to say happy birthday to you, Pat.
Oh, happy birthday, Pat.
Sorry we missed that on Monday, but I'm not great with inboxes.
So tomorrow, Greg G out in Cary, NC, North Carolina, it rhymes.
Oh, G and NC?
Yeah.
All right.
Having a birthday.
Happy birthday, Greg G.
Happy birthday, G G.
I hope you're having a good one out there and I hope, Pat, you had a great one on Monday.
Indeed.
Happy birthday.
Blow out those candles, make a wish.
Spanks all around.
I was trying to transition to candle talking, so spanking, because I realized it's a little
weird.
Well, what you gonna do?
I'm gonna get into this episode.
That's a good transition.
Jordan, October 16th, 2014, what do you know was going on around that time?
What do you have a feeling?
Let's see.
2014, I would have just woken up from a three-year sleep or a fugue state, if you will.
Rip Van Winkle over here.
So I was just welcoming awareness once again and I had moved to Bloomingdale, Illinois,
gorgeous one-bedroom apartment.
This episode is, shockingly, mostly about residential pricing in Bloomingdale.
All I'm saying is those are the only things I remember from 2014.
This is surprisingly right in your wheelhouse.
I may be a witch.
Excellent.
No, in October, it was Ebola season.
It was during the middle of the period where there were a couple cases of Ebola here in
the United States.
The primary patient, the first patient that came into the United States, had passed away.
And we are right on the cusp of the second nurse who had treated him has been diagnosed
now with Ebola.
So we're remembering when a possible pandemic was averted.
We have done an episode, I think two years ago, about the first day when there was a
case in the United States and Alex's response to it.
And it's really interesting to take a little bit of a look and see what is going on a couple
weeks later.
Sure, sure.
Absolutely.
I mean, did he go from there will be lone survivors back to there's no problem at all?
It's interesting.
So I would say his trajectory has a lot of similarities and a lot of differences.
Yeah.
And that's what made this particularly fascinating for me.
So here we go.
We're going to start off with him talking about some sort of fear-ish narratives.
I'm your host, Alex Jones.
They are telling 911 dispatchers, Fox Television out of DC is reporting not to say Ebola over
the radio or when they're basically talking about a call that they're on.
We have Obama saying there's nothing to fear, that it's a low probability that an epidemic
will start in the U.S.
Even as we learn that the second nurse to contract Ebola traveled all over the place
on aircraft and that the plane was not even cleaned, that is wiped down.
They picked up the trash on the floor, but not a deep clean for five more flights after
she was on it.
Five more flights.
So this story that Alex is opening the show with about the 911 dispatchers not being allowed
to say Ebola on the radio is not from Fox DC.
Fox DC did run a story about it with the headline that Alex is reading, but that article is
just a link to the original story, which is from the New York Post.
The reasoning behind this- Trustworthy New York Post.
But the reasoning makes total sense.
There's tons of people who aren't first responders who listen in on emergency radio channels
and you could easily imagine how a panic could break out if every call that came in where
someone was worried that they had Ebola was misinterpreted by someone listening in as
a definite or probable case.
People would lose their minds.
You could really do some damage.
Did you know that words can have an effect in real life?
That's weird.
If you actually read the New York Post article, this is exactly what it's about.
A source speaking to the post said, quote, just like you can't say bomb on an airplane,
we can't say Ebola.
Back in the 80s and 90s, taking universal precautions meant someone had AIDS.
We weren't allowed to say AIDS then either.
Dr. Jay Varma, the deputy commissioner of the city department of health, gave some idea
of how many opportunities there had been for false panics to start.
Quote, we have now had about 133 calls since July concerning patients with possible Ebola
symptoms and all 133 were false alarms.
That's alarming.
Yeah, and people listening in could have taken any one of those 133 and tried to present
it as like, look, look at all these people, they're covering up all these cases.
It could be really dangerous.
You could definitely get into a fear mongering panic where somebody like Alex Jones convinces
you that you need to buy survival food.
Yeah, so from an emergency response perspective, I do see how it could be best practices to
use language that wouldn't necessarily be exploitable by people who may have ill will
and are listening in on your communication.
Right, which is unfortunate because, boy, it would be nice if we were just allowed to
say words.
Or even, let me even walk what I'm saying back.
It's not even necessarily people with ill will.
Some people could just get confused.
Just panic entirely, just already be paranoid.
So as for that nurse story, that was true, sort of.
It's true that she did fly the day before she was diagnosed with Ebola, but experts
don't believe that it was as big a deal as it sounds.
The first reason is that at the time of her flying, she wasn't exhibiting symptoms that
would put people at high risk, like vomiting.
Even so, Thomas Frieden, then the director of the CDC, was clear that, quote, she should
not have flown on a commercial airplane.
And he immediately put in place guidelines that anyone who had been exposed to somebody
with Ebola would only travel by way of controlled movement like private flights and chartered
vehicles.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, immediate?
Well, prior to that, this was just recommended by the CDC.
But after, quote, the agency would work with state and local authorities to enforce this
restriction.
I found a Washington Post article about this, and it seems to directly contradict Alex's
claims about there being five more flights before the plane was cleaned.
From that article, quote, the plane, Vinton, that's the nurse, traveled on, arrived in
Dallas at 816 p.m. on Monday and remained overnight because it was done with flights
for that day.
And then when we found out she had Ebola, we blew that shit to the moon.
We exploded it all over the fucking place.
After that, the plane received a thorough cleaning per our normal procedures before
resuming service Tuesday, Frontier said in a statement.
I was able to find the article that Alex is misrepresenting.
There was a piece in the Denver Post with the headline, quote, emails out to passengers
on five Frontier flights after Ebola patient flew.
As it turns out, the airline did send notification to the people who were on the same plane that
the nurse had flown on, but it wasn't because they hadn't cleaned it.
It was out of an abundance of caution.
The plane had been cleaned, but later the nurse was diagnosed with Ebola, and by that
point that anyone knew anything, the plane had already flown five additional flights
the next day.
Informing the customers is definitely the right thing to do in terms of making sure
everyone's informed.
Totally.
Even if you followed every preventative, appropriate step, it's still above board to tell people.
Yeah, absolutely.
So they can make their own choices from a healthcare perspective.
Yeah, no, and not telling people would be a far greater scandal for you.
You know, if everybody found out a week later, they'd be like, fuck you guys!
It would be wrong.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It would be negligent.
This article points out that after this nurse was diagnosed, the plane was going to undergo
even further cleaning, quote, including replacement of seat covers and carpet in the vicinity
of the passenger's seat, but this still doesn't support Alex's all they did was pick up trash
narrative.
Sure, sure.
I think he's just trying to scare people.
I think we should treat all diseases like the Velveteen Rabbit and just immediately
burn everything involved.
Everywhere.
I think that might be going a little bit...
The plane.
Pendulum the other direction.
The airport.
Everything.
The whole place.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
All stocks and bonds in the airline.
We've seen what it's like to live through a pandemic.
We have not seen what it's like to burn everything to the ground in case one starts.
I'm just saying that we should go the other direction.
You make some interesting points.
Yeah.
I would love to live in a world where we still have a pandemic and then also everything is
burning.
Great.
That would be, that would probably be an issue.
You're probably right.
So Alex is covering this news and I will say he has a classy take on things.
He's dealing with things in a really, just a newsman.
We are the Ebola vomit bag, the Obama, excuse me, Ebola toilet.
You know, memes are very, very powerful and that's why we've launched this contest that's
only running for another week to go to infoawards.com forward slash contest, print off the flyers,
hang them up, shoot video of it, send us the video, we'll post it and then a week later
on Halloween, I will announce the winner.
Hashtag Ebola contest.
Oh boy.
Wow.
Hashtag Ebola contest.
And it's contest, as best I can tell, is he has posters that are advertising for info
wars and you record yourself putting them up faces or something.
I think this is a weird contest.
I think it's just, Hey, could you be my street team?
I think what we've realized here is that Alex is paid by big disease in order to spread
disease.
Man, it's, it's really weird.
You would think that somebody engaging responsibly with the topics they were covering wouldn't
be like, Hey, let me try and use this as a cheap stunt meme promotional opportunity.
Here's a possible pandemic that could murder and incapacitate millions of people.
We need a contest to advertise my shit based on that.
Yeah.
That's a good dude.
Yup.
So, um, to Alex's credit or not, I'm not sure I'll let you decide.
He doesn't spend the entire show talking about Ebola.
Well, that's nice.
He also gets around to some nonsense narratives about how Christians are under attack.
Oh, that's good.
We have just absolutely over the top important news on the Ebola front, on the economic front,
on the second amendment front, on the police state front with Houston, literally trying
to intimidate churches and to not giving sermons that criticize transsexual, uh, behavior or
homosexuality and a lot of libertarian groups have been coming out.
And even though they are open to other lifestyles, cause the libertarians, uh, they are defending
these preachers because if you're going to have your right to live the way you want somebody
else has to have their right to live and, and, and, and speak as they see fit, flaming
authoritarianism pun intended out of the Houston mayor and the rest of them at best that's
wordplay suing churches.
This is what Europe and Canada are doing.
This is the model.
Everything you see with political correctness out of Europe and Canada is coming here.
They arrest preachers that criticize homosexuality.
So this isn't going to surprise you, but Alex is lying about this story.
I'm not surprised.
Here's what happened in 2014 Houston passed an equal rights ordinance that included protections
for members of the LGBTQ community in terms of housing, employment and what have you.
This was on the vanguard of the right wing panic about trans people in bathrooms.
So one of the hot button issues was that, uh, according to an article in the Washington
post quote, transgender people barred access to a restroom would be able to file a discrimination
complaint.
Right.
It's worth noting that religious entities were also exempted from this ruling.
So they weren't even, so they weren't even involved, right?
A group of citizens filed a lawsuit aimed at repealing the ordinance as part of the
uh, and as part of that lawsuit, quote, city attorneys issued subpoenas to five local pastors
during the cases discovery phase.
These pastors were alleged to have connections to the people who filed the lawsuit and were
active in the effort to repeal the ordinance.
So the attorneys requested quote, all speeches, presentations or sermons related to hero.
That's the ordinance, the petition mayor, a niece, Parker, homosexuality or gender identity
prepared by delivered by revised by or approved by you or in your possession.
Sure.
The question that was being posed by these subpoenas were whether or not these pastors
were using their churches as political organizing grounds, which would put their tax exempt
status in jeopardy.
Since Texas exempt churches, quote, are not allowed to engage in partisan politics.
By October 16th, the day that Alex is here on air, controversy had been raging about
this and the subpoena was revised to just ask for quote, all speeches or presentations
related to hero or the petition prepared by delivered by revised by or approved by you
or in your possession.
Right.
And as we know now that we live in the future, the government really cracked down on that
and churches were no longer allowed to advocate for political positions from the pulpit.
That would just be wrong, Dan.
Didn't you see so many churches across this country after Trump was elected?
Didn't you see them lose their five oh one C three status all over the place for advocating
for political positions?
I, it's just terrible.
Anyway, this is a complex topic that gets into a lot of those issues more than anything
else.
You know, you could make an, uh, an argument that there was overreach and over broadness
in terms of the subpoenas that were, uh, put out by the city attorneys.
Oh sure.
I think that is a fair position you could take.
But Alex is reporting this as like they're suing these churches.
No, no.
Someone sued the city and the city is doing discovery.
Yeah.
Anyway, he just wants to take this and uh, you know, he wants to boil it down into a
misrepresentation that's easier for his audience to understand and more importantly, be mad
about.
Yeah.
Just trying to make it about fucking out of control PC culture.
It's nonsense.
It would be nice if Christ had lived and just been super cool because then maybe Christians
wouldn't constantly feel like playing the victim is the only way to deal with life.
I don't know.
What if Christ was just a cool dude?
What if Christ was just like the Buddha and he got old and everybody's like, man, you
kicked ass.
Good work.
That would be great.
He uh, invented hang loose.
Exactly.
First person to say cowabunga.
So Jordan, I gotta say one of the things I didn't expect, um, on this episode as I was
getting into it, because you know, Ebola is a pretty big topic and it certainly has mirrors
and echoes in our current, uh, COVID-19, uh, situation, but I didn't expect as a large
portion of this episode would end up becoming a movie review.
That I believe and did expect.
Yeah.
I was a little bit surprised.
Is he still on Oblivion?
No.
Okay.
The movie review is about the movie Kill the Messenger about Gary Webb.
It's very personal for Alex because he apparently knew Gary Webb.
Oh, I did not know that.
Now, this might be a little too personal.
Okay.
Alex seems to be dealing with some stuff after watching this movie and he might make a confession
that first of all, I don't believe is true, but if true proves that Alex Jones is the
worst fucking, uh, outlaw radio truth teller, whistleblower guy, listen to this bullshit.
I went and saw Kill the Messenger last night and I expected it to be a whitewash.
I expected it to imply that he killed himself and it was absolute truth because I remember
Gary Webb being on the show more than 10 times.
I had all these incredible conversations with Gary Webb off air.
He wanted me to build a website for him.
He sent me all these documents that the CIA had broken in his house a bunch to try to
get.
I was too busy making films and making babies with my wife.
He was, I remember he called back the last time I talked to him a few months before he
committed suicide and he said, Hey man, Alex, I thought you had the courage to put this
up and do something.
I said, yeah, there's thousands of pages of this stuff and a lot of this is court records
and stuff.
And I go, I guess I'll put it out because, well, I thought you've got balls.
I mean, these are epic conversations I have with Gary Webb.
Now a hit movie out about him and it was so surreal to be sitting there in the movie theater.
I ignored that guy and knowing his whole story and it was so accurate.
I am baffled by this movie review.
I think there's a small part of Alex that's pissed off that he's not in the movie.
And then second, it's very weird that he's like, yeah, you know what?
I had that dude giving me all this secret documentation that the CIA was trying to kill
him for having.
I was busy, I didn't do shit with him.
I was making babies with my wife, so I wasn't interested in those thousands of CIA coveted
documents that would blow the lid off of everything.
But come on guys, she's ovulating.
What am I going to do?
I do think this isn't true.
Like I think that his story is not true, but it's interesting the way he gets himself off
the hook for having not broken things.
Like, he's like, I was busy, I was making documentaries.
I was busy breaking other stories.
I didn't have time for this.
So let me ask you a question.
In the beginning, I thought I heard him say, I thought they were going to whitewash it
and heavily imply that he did commit suicide.
Which he did.
And then he said, which suggests to me that he thinks he didn't.
He did.
Yeah, Alex thinks that he didn't.
But then later on, he said a few days before he committed suicide.
Right.
Okay.
Yep.
All right.
So.
Yeah.
Okay.
That might've just been Alex's like sort of subconscious sneaking through and being
like, you know.
You know he killed himself.
He wasn't murdered.
Come on, man.
You know, one of the reasons I think this is all bullshit is this.
I'm not even here bragging.
Oh my gosh, this show is important.
I felt incredibly guilty.
That I don't even know where that disk is.
That CD-ROM that I opened up and it was just, I don't know how to process all this stuff.
I need to tear apart our storage buildings and find that.
And then I don't even want to talk about how I had that disk because you're like killing
people over this stuff.
And then I went and searched last night when I got home, I went to bed and then I woke
up in the middle of the night and went and searched for like an hour at 3 AM, 4 AM.
And I couldn't even find one interview I did with Gary Webb.
Kind of makes me think maybe you didn't interview him.
I mean, I bet he did.
I could see that absolutely having happened, but like I wonder at a certain point, you
kind of got to wonder, it's like, did you imagine all of this?
Did you dream this?
Did you have a quiet conversation with Gary Webb in your head?
Yeah.
You know, like you have the CIA to kill anybody who has all this information and like Alex
has the CD-ROM that Gary Webb had given him.
CIA was following him.
They wouldn't know that he made the handoff with Alex, absolutely.
But the CIA is like, fuck it, Alex is just going to lose it.
Come on.
I mean, he's got a, it's in an AOL sheath.
We don't need to worry about this.
That fucking dude doesn't even have a file cabinet.
Look, I was surveilling him the other night.
He's just too busy fucking his wife.
They're trying to make babies.
I'm sorry.
He just doesn't have time to expose us.
It's not even like that disc.
It's not even in an AOL sleeve.
It's in a Moody Blues album cover that he is just, it's lost.
He's never going to find that thing.
16-bit floppy.
That's what he's got.
This is weird.
I don't know.
I put myself even in the foot shoes.
The foot shoes.
Of Alex.
I imagine.
When there was only one set of foot shoes.
That's when I was carrying you.
That's when I was carrying Gary Webb.
I feel like if there was a bone of authenticity in Alex's body, the second that the guy who
wrote Dark Alliance is giving you a CD of secret documents.
You drop everything.
This is a priority.
Do you remember when Snowden released shit?
Every news organization was like, okay, we're going to put 15 people on this.
We're all going to read every single one of these documents and we're going to write stories
about it immediately.
Greenwald wasn't like, I'm making Police State 2000.
I'm busy.
I'm sorry, guys.
I want to start a family.
I'm adopting kids.
Yeah.
What am I supposed to do?
Have you ever tried to adopt kids in America from Brazil?
I don't want to shit on the idea of prioritizing family and what have you.
That's all good.
Sure.
If you're somebody who fancies yourself an investigative journalist whose mission it
is to get to the bottom of the nefarious doings of the globalists, this behavior strikes me
as very out of character.
The tip of the spear was busy elsewhere, if you know what I'm saying.
That spear was a.
So there's a sense that I got from listening to this that like Alex seems to think that
that movie might be about him.
And then watching how they demonized him and how they tried to kill his name before they
physically killed him and experiencing a lot of this myself, it was a surreal, I've never
gone and seen a movie where from what I know, it was so incredibly accurate and so incredibly
sad.
And then I resonated with it because they always make it about the individual.
If they can't disprove your facts, they just demonize and destroy the individual themselves.
And I got a sick feeling in my stomach as I realized that the clocks just tick until
they come and shoot me in the head twice or plant drugs on me or shoot me at a checkpoint
or something.
And it just it made me sad to watch all the cowards, his editors and like you, you literally
said that you didn't have Jesus Christ, so sad for watching his cowards.
He gave all those documents to those editors and they didn't do shit with them.
They told him, we're not going to put those out.
He gave a CD-ROM to every one of his editors.
A little bit of an asshole.
A bunch of cowards.
A little bit of an asshole-ish review.
I mean, I was just out of, I was just doing a documentary.
Sure.
I'm not a coward.
Yeah.
Hey, look, I don't get into Shadowgate.
Yeah, exactly.
Look, I don't get into that kind of deep shit.
Turns out that behavior has been pretty consistent throughout his career.
I think he might be faking a lot of this.
I think he might be.
So we get back to Ebola here and this clip to me was actually one of the more interesting,
the glimpses into how Alex operates in these circumstances.
The people that are supposed to be cleaning the aircraft are told that they can't wear
masks and gloves.
Aircraft coming in out of West Africa in some cases with vomit in them because it'll quote
scare people.
We're going to get to those articles in a moment.
Experts offer steps for avoiding public hysteria, a different contagious threat.
So we've been talking about the hysteria being a bigger problem than Ebola itself.
Well, now the New York Times is reporting on it today.
I just thought that the juxtaposition of those two stories is fascinating.
In the first one, Alex is claiming that vomit filled airplanes are arriving in the United
States from West Africa and not being cleaned, obviously trying to create the impression
in his audience's mind.
There are so many more cases of Ebola in the United States than were being told.
Correct.
It's a narrative that can really only lead to people freaking out and behaving irrationally.
Right.
But the New York Times says that freaking out in hysteria is just as bad as the Ebola.
And Alex, he's saying then that Infowars has been saying all along that public hysteria
is a bigger problem.
Don't freak out about this!
Ebola's everywhere, but freaking out is crazy.
How can he possibly not understand that everything he does exists only to heighten hysteria?
Yeah.
Thinking about how the border is wide open and vomit planes are arriving is not only
factually untrue, but it's also designed to scare people.
Alex understands that, and it's one of the things that he does on his show that I think
is incredibly abusive.
It's that trying to push and pull simultaneously in people's minds, and it's not good.
No, he's in a weird, almost experiment of...
His experiment to me of listening to his show would be somebody sitting in a chair strapped
down and every five minutes just a little jolt is given to the emotional center of their
brain, and you just have to sit there for four hours and feel this constant emotional
pressure.
Yeah.
Yeah?
In my experience, I don't think...
That's not wrong.
It's not that far off.
I disconnect from it so it doesn't affect me as much listening to it.
You removed that little part of your brain.
I imagine that that part of the brain would be very antagonized if you believed anything
he said.
Yeah, totally.
But since I don't, I'm a little bit immune.
You got rubber on your brain.
Yeah.
Alex is kind of right in some sense that public hysteria is a very serious concern when it
comes to public health matters.
It's just that in this case, he's one of the most hysterical voices you can imagine.
It's nonsense.
No, and it's cruel.
It's cruel to be like, hey, hysteria is crazy, and you're gonna die!
Like okay, man.
But maybe not.
You won't die.
Maybe not.
The human's killing you!
But maybe not.
Bad!
Now hold on.
What's up?
I thought, listening to the original episode about this period of time and the Ebola situation,
and listening to the beginning of this episode, I thought, you know, this is horrible, this
is irresponsible, and then I think it's kind of tasteless to have this Ebola meme contest.
Right, right, right, right.
But I didn't think it was that weird.
It's not weird enough for Alex Jones.
Here's where it gets weird.
Okay, good.
They'd first said that it was her fault and she shouldn't have done it, but now it's admitted
in NBC News that an Ebola patient who contacted the CDC before a flight agency says was told
that she could fly even though she was an Ebola nurse, and even though she told them
she had a fever.
By the way, I treated the guy that has Ebola, and I'm sick.
Can I fly?
You can fly.
That's like saying, my dog has rabies, and it's foaming at the mouth.
Should I put it into a schoolyard of kids?
Yes, put the dog with rabies into the schoolyard.
Or I found a bat crawling around hissing on the ground.
Should I pick it up and kiss it?
Yes, that's a good idea.
There's a cliff by my house, a thousand feet to Jagged Bottom.
Should I jump off without a parachute?
Yes, jump off immediately.
You have four more examples.
Ring, hi, I'm a nurse that treated the Ebola patient, CDC.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Yeah, we know who you are.
Yeah, you're all over the news.
Yeah.
I'm going to fly.
Of course, this time it wasn't on the news, just had been around an Ebola patient.
So I was treating an Ebola patient.
I'm going to fly.
I have a fever.
Oh, but dearie, that's a great idea.
They're not just turning off the defaults.
They're sending the Ebola kids to school.
They're not cleaning up the apartment.
Something weird is going on.
And why are nurses getting it, but the family isn't getting it?
Either they're covering up that they have it, or it's what that CIA whistleblower said
back in the middle of last month here, Mr. Steele, and we should cue that clip up later.
He said he believed they would release a biological stimulant that wasn't Ebola, but would make
people sick or even kill them to create a false flag.
There we go.
It's a false flag.
Possibly.
Hold on.
Is that Mr. Steele, our buddy?
That's Robert David Steele.
Oh yeah, it is.
I was about to say, yep, that one's got the, yep.
Multiple time Project Camelot guest who Alex had to disavow after he claimed on Infowars
that the globalists had children enslaved on Mars bases, Robert David Steele.
That dude's credibility is incredibly low.
Yeah.
Well, you know what?
When you can't disprove his facts, Dan, you try and go after the guy.
And I can clearly see you just taking this to a personal place.
You can't prove that it's not a bioweapon.
Sure.
Not my job.
Steele had been on Alex's show in September to speculate about the possibility of a false
flag Ebola attack.
But the fact that he was creating narratives about Ebola at that point isn't really all
that weird.
The first case in West Africa from this outbreak was reported in December 2013.
And by March 2014, there was spreading happening.
By July, it had reached the capital cities of Guinea, Liberia, and Sierra Leone.
And according to the CDC, quote, this was the first time Ebola extended out from more
isolated rural areas and into densely populated urban centers, providing an unprecedented
opportunity for transmission.
So Ebola is on the brain as far as any infectious disease is concerned, yeah.
By August, there were Ebola scares being reported to hospitals in the United States.
According to the advisory board's timeline, quote, before the end of the month, more than
60 hospitals reported some type of scare to the CDC, but none of the tests sent to the
agency returned positive for the virus.
So at this point, it was in people's minds.
Right, right, right.
No, that's what you would be talking about.
If you were going to say there's an infectious disease coming to the United States, you're
going to say Ebola.
It's 100% what you would do.
Yeah, you're not going to be like, it's the flu.
No, everybody's thinking about Ebola and is worried about it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Robert David Steele had every reason to shoot the shot when he did.
There was growing insecurity around the outbreak, and it was affecting the psyche of the American
public.
If a case did end up coming to the United States, he would look like he was way ahead
of the story and he had a narrative in place.
If no case ever arrived here, he could just ignore it or claim that the globalists decided
to go a different way with their evil plans.
There's no downside to this kind of spitballing in a consequence-free environment like Infowars.
Yeah, exactly.
As for the story about the nurse on the plane, Alex isn't making up that NBC News reported
that she did in fact check in with the CDC before getting on the plane.
The problem is that Alex is acting like the CDC has a staff of like 12 people and everyone
knows everything that's going on.
This very article that Alex is referencing explains how everything happened.
At the time, it was believed that this nurse had worn all the appropriate protective gear,
and as such, she was considered a lower risk category of person, technically titled quote
uncertain risk.
Before she flew, the nurse called the CDC and talked to a staffer who quote, looked
on the agency's website for guidance, the spokesperson said.
The category for uncertain risk has guidance saying a person could fly commercially if
they did not meet the threshold of a temperature of 100.4.
She had a slight fever, but it was below that reading, so technically she wouldn't have
been barred from flying.
Director Frieden didn't know that she had contacted the CDC when he made his comment
that she shouldn't have flown.
From the NBC News article quote, the spokesperson says he believes Frieden said that because
it should have been common sense to Vincent that she should not fly with a slight temperature.
Even though we have a CDC guideline that says you're fine.
Yeah, I mean look, don't get me wrong, I'm not going to defend all of that, it's bungled.
It's him kind of saying that the CDC is wrong, not her.
Probably, yeah.
We need better guidelines.
Yeah, exactly.
This guideline is clearly oversight of some kind.
I can't see anything more responsible, if you are this person, than literally going
direct to the CD-fucking-C. Not going to the website, I think it also frustrates me a little
bit.
The staffer went to the website.
I don't like that at all.
That's not lost on me either.
That's not good.
I don't like that at all.
No.
Seems like maybe, in this case, you should have rotted up the flagpole.
Yeah, yeah.
I see no fault of hers at all, other than just being like, why are you flying?
I see bases being covered in terms of like, clearly no one was acting with malicious intent.
Absolutely not.
And there wasn't even like overt negligence, it's just this is how an oversight can happen.
Maybe we should revise our guidelines.
It seems like, basically what I'm saying is iffy decisions happened, but it makes sense
how everything happened the way it did.
There's certainly not enough here to justify speculating this is a false flag outbreak.
I would argue the details would suggest anything but a false flag.
Yeah, and Jordan, I don't know if you're picking up on this, but from where I'm sitting, that
sounds hysterical as shit.
Ah, why?
Oh, God.
Look, false flags happen, honestly, it's more hysterical for it to not be a false flag.
Because then it's something surprising.
As we know, false flags happen every day.
Does this sound hysterical?
Let's see.
Also, does this sound familiar?
Okay.
Let's continue here.
911 emergency dispatcher's instructed not to say Ebola over the radio.
That's out of Fox News DC.
They're being told not to create panic and are being given a secret code to describe
Ebola.
See, the cover-up's already on.
As I said, Ebola probably is already spreading in the US.
They had to let it in and let it breed first, and then they'll say they don't know where
it all began or where it started and, oh, it's all Obama's fault.
And it's going to bring in a medical tyranny, forced inoculation, and the Bill and Melinda
Gates Foundation dedicated to population reduction and the Monsanto vaccine they produced.
I'm going to say that again.
Bill Gates, we keep warning you about, people are like, why do you talk about Bill Gates
so much?
Because I've studied him.
He wants to put an Ebola shot in you.
You think that's going to be good for you?
God, it's exactly the same.
Wow.
Yeah.
Jesus.
It's shockingly the same.
Yep.
And that probably felt just as real to his audience in 2014 as it does to people listening
to him now.
Yep.
It's outrageous.
It's just that circumstances were handled differently and, of course, Ebola and COVID-19
are different.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They transmit differently.
They require different responses.
I heard that.
I was like, this is amazing.
It's almost a script.
It almost felt like you could just take Ebola out and put COVID or coronavirus in and it
would have just been exactly the same.
Anything.
It is kind of-
Seven years ago.
It is, I think, illustrative of the level of power that Alex and his ilk had in 2014
as opposed to in 2019.
That level of influence was far lesser and their effect was far lesser.
It's hard not to look at this as a... And it's not, again, there are different diseases.
It's not a one-to-one comparison by any stretch.
But it is hard not to look at the difference between 2014 and 2019 and think, no one should
be held accountable for, at the very least, negligence.
This is truly a fucked up thing that people need to be held accountable for.
Well, I think that one of the differences that you see is that people responded kind
of more appropriately- That's what I'm saying about negligence.
To people like Alex at that time, or at least people who are actually making decisions and
being adults.
We would be like, oh, I don't care.
And the president wasn't repeating things Alex said.
Yeah.
So that's nice.
And I think it was better.
One could make that argument.
I'm gonna.
Yeah.
I don't think it would be a hard one to convince me of.
So now, if you're somebody who's, I don't know, in the past and you're listening to
Alex and you're taking some of the stuff that he's saying about Ebola seriously, I would
say, maybe you should hear this and be like, I'm going to turn this off.
I mean, I hate to get gross here, but you've heard about the phenomenon in government buildings
suddenly that people are peeing on the walls and going to the bathroom and cubby holes
and in the hallways, even though the bathrooms are working perfectly fine and smearing it
all over the walls.
This is what mental patients do.
This is what people who are above the law start doing, is just running around going
to the bathroom as poop bandits as they're known.
This is what has now happened.
This is what's happening.
There's poop bandits.
The government is so out of control and drunk on power that they were poop bandits now.
Hold on.
I just literally wrote a screenplay.
Give me one second.
Jesus.
So I didn't know what Alex was talking about and this seemed really silly.
So I decided to look into it and see if I could figure it out.
Sure.
I figured it out.
So in late August, 2014, there was, there were some stories going around about a particular
EPA office in Denver, which had quote, been beset by roughly a dozen suspected incidents
of restroom shenanigans since late 2013, according to emails, memorandums and incident reports.
Restroom shenanigans.
Yes.
That's fun.
Apparently someone was fucking around and clogging toilets with paper and putting shit
in the hallway.
Sure.
Getting up to all sorts of disgusting nonsense.
This was clearly the work of an unstable individual who worked at that office.
Yeah, who is this fucking guy?
But here, Alex is reporting this as some kind of proof of the corrupt decadence of the government
elites.
They're so bored with being tyrants that there's a new phenomenon of everyone shitting in the
hallway.
It's just a weirdo getting his rocks off in a really uncomfortable way.
Yeah.
All right.
Okay.
I love like being able to look back in the past and like seeing the way that these stories
get like twisted by Alex into being so much larger than they actually are.
He does in a way create more fantastical, interesting stories because I mean it's obviously
a fairly interesting story that someone's putting shit in the hallway in an NBA building.
Sure.
That's kind of interesting.
It's more fun to imagine that our government is run by demon tyrants who are so bored that
they have to shit in the hallway to get off.
It is kind of funny.
It implies a lot more interesting stuff is happening.
See, that's the problem.
I remember when we lived in a world that wasn't so much like Alex's weird dark circus versions
of government, and then we lived in one.
It was bad.
Yep.
No good.
So at this point in 2014, you really had like gentlemen speak freely kind of vibe going
on at Infowars.
Oh, that's not good.
They didn't really have the lawsuits to worry about, so things like this happen.
Why no protective gear for a man with Dallas Ebola patient?
We have video of this.
We'll roll some of it in the background.
The video from CBS News is up on Infowars.com, prisonplanet.com.
This lends credence to Rob Dew running around the office thinking this is crisis actors
because he's been analyzing video and he's worked at national TV, home shopping network.
You know, he used to be a director there, and so he knows state stuff, and he says that,
you know, why are people not wearing protective gear with the Ebola patient as we have right
there?
And is it people just don't care and they're idiots?
Or is it staged?
Or is there a third possibility?
What would that be?
So there was a video of people putting that nurse into a plane that was making the rounds,
and all but one of the people are wearing hazmat suits.
It definitely looks like fodder for Alex to make a conspiracy out of and for Rob Dew to
use to justify crisis actor theories, but it's not really that crazy when you get down
to it or you ask the question and get an answer from somebody.
This person in the video is not in any direct contact with the patient who's wearing her
own set of protective gear as well.
The chances of transmission are incredibly low based on how Ebola goes from person to
person.
That being said, I wouldn't do what this dude is doing, but that's just because of me.
But it might not be that really fucked up or dangerous.
This very article that Alex is citing in order to talk about the headline includes this passage.
Quote, when a member of the Dallas CDC team was shown in the video and asked if it was
a safe moment or not, he said he didn't have a problem with what he saw.
The situations apparently met CDC protocol because the people in the hazmat suits were
the ones assisting Vincent, and the plainclothes man was not.
The CDC spokesman said that the man maintained an appropriate distance from the patient for
the amount of time on the tarmac, and it must be taken into account that Vincent was
also wearing protective gear.
This is how little some idiot like Rob Do needs to justify denying people's illnesses
and deaths.
He just needs some video that looks strange that he didn't care to look into at all.
The thing that I still have a hard time wrapping my head around that we found out from all
those depositions is at this point in time, apparently only PJ Dubs in the entire InfoWars
sphere was listening to this going like, yeee, this is a bad idea!
Stop!
Blokes!
Stop it, blokes!
Yes, exactly!
Yeah.
Of all people!
You know what, that might not be true, but it's the only one we know for sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because there might have been some lower level functionaries who were being like, this is
irresponsible.
There might have been some people who quit, too.
There might have been some people who got fired, yeah.
And I think it's probably in those people's best interests that we not know that.
Because for them to be able to bury the part of their lives that they worked there might
be.
It's important.
Yeah.
Good for them if they've succeeded.
And if they have gone on to live a better life.
Yeah.
Let's hope.
So, it's staged, man.
This stuff's probably staged.
I don't think it's staged, but okay.
I don't know exactly what's going on, but I'll tell you this.
Most of this is staged, it's scripted, and they clearly want Ebola to spread.
Now you can fill in the blank of why.
My head is spinning at this point, and I'm trying to contain my anger, even during the
breaks I'm trying to contain it.
Because I think about how they're trying to bring down this country, now they're trying
to kill our prosperity, it makes me angry.
But you don't want people to be hysterical.
No.
Right?
No, no, no.
I mean, I'm furious because they're killing all of us and destroying proper prosperity.
And they clearly are trying to intentionally spread Ebola, possibly by staging things.
Yeah, but as the New York Times said.
As you said, as the New York Times said, hysteria is a big problem too.
Well, let's keep it grounded.
Yeah, absolutely.
Let's keep this real.
Let's make sure nobody goes too far.
And Bloomberg two days ago was asking, why weren't they sent to the government facilities
that are designed for this?
Because they want it to spread, they want plausible deniability, they probably got sleeper
cells walking around spreading it.
I didn't think they'd use Muslim radicals to bring it in before, I thought that was
just some Islamophobe hype.
But now it's starting to click that God only knows.
I think the other shoe is about to drop.
I think something big is about to happen.
I've been saying that for months.
And now you see this breaking loose.
You can say that for years.
I think what you're seeing right now might be a diversion for nukes they're about to
set off.
Cool.
Remember all the missing nukes?
There you go.
This might be hysterical.
That might be an issue.
Might be a little bit hysterical.
That might be a little bit going too far there.
Yeah.
All right.
Hey, guess what?
I believe that the government is intentionally spreading Ebola all over the place and it's
a false flag.
It's also a diversion from nukes they're about to drop.
Listen, I don't know what's going on.
Let me preface by saying I don't know what's going on.
Now let me certainly describe a false flag attack that, and honestly, I'm going to go
with a 50-50 shot.
It's a diversion and you're all going to die immediately.
Let me go over the top in a comically scary scenario that I'm painting for you as a very
distinct possibility based on my years of research about how these globalists operate.
Yep.
Also, this whole Islamophobic thing, I was like, oh no, I'm not going to engage in Islamophobia.
But then I saw a video where a guy was walking on a tarmac, so obviously it's the Islamic
people's fault.
Probably.
Yeah.
That makes sense.
It's interesting.
So he's going down this road, you know, like hysteria about Ebola, and then also they're
going to nuke you.
Man, we're just in trouble.
Uh-oh.
It is just, we have enemies in control that there is no doubt that we are in the most
grave danger this country has faced in 240 years.
And I just got hardcore chills.
I got goosebumps on my face right now that the camera can probably pick up.
They are getting ready to drop the hammer.
This is the takedown of the country.
I'm getting my immune system ready.
I know that.
InfoWarsLife.com.
Boom.
I'm getting my immune system ready.
InfoWarsLife.com.
Boom.
See, now that is a good, that's a good little super transition there.
That's a good little ad switch compared to what he does now.
It kind of hurts the preceding passage for me.
Absolutely.
The insanely out of control fear mongering that led up to that kind of.
Well there's that.
The relationship between the two does suffer.
But yes, I guess making people really afraid of a nuke and Ebola would lead them to take
zinc.
Uh, yeah.
I would say that InfoWarsLife plug really only solves one of the two problems that he's
describing.
And in fact I would argue the second one kind of wipes out the gains of the first, if you
will.
So whatever gains we've lost shall now be recouped.
Because Alex has a guest.
And boy howdy.
This guest.
Mic down for this.
Okay.
Because what this guest says.
Spoiler alert.
It's Steve Pajanik.
Okay.
What he says.
It's Stevie Pease?
Yes.
Okay.
Did he cure himself of Ebola?
No.
Oh, dammit.
If we had a complete repeat of the present.
No.
That'd be brutal.
I was hoping.
Yeah, that would be great.
No.
They do mention how like he had recently reported from the demilitarized zone for Alex.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
I recall.
Noted info wars correspondent Steve Pajanik.
I recall that he was in Korea for a while.
He's in the shit.
So Steve is on and they're talking about Ebola and he directly contradicts something that
he says in the present.
Sure.
That's amazing.
You're also a medical doctor on top of that so you can speak to Ebola.
Yes, correctly.
And more importantly, I was trained at Cornell University Medical College between 64 and
1968 by a very competent infectious disease doctor who was really the foremost infectious
disease doctor.
Don't do it.
You see him on television.
That is Anthony Fauci.
God dammit.
The director of the National Institute for Infectious Diseases.
Oh, God dammit.
God dammit, Dan.
One you're a witch and two Steve Pajanik is a monster.
Steve, when he's coming on the show now, talks about how incompetent Fauci is.
My fucking God.
I swear to you.
I hated him ever since I was at Cornell.
He's a loser.
This is the worst fucking news you could give me.
This is so brutal.
You know who's great?
Anthony Fauci.
Oh, it breaks my heart.
It really breaks my heart.
It's pretty remarkable to dig back a little bit and see like, you know, this mirror, this
echo is so, the funhouse mirror is the only way I can describe it.
It's so bizarre.
Yeah.
No, I mean, listen, it's not that I believe the entire world is a prank on me.
But when Steve says stuff like that, I'm just like, eh, you know what?
This isn't real.
So Steve, Steve thinks that the Ebola situation is pretty serious.
And I would say that outside of it being hilarious that he likes Fauci now and then in the present
claims to have always hated him or whatever.
Yeah.
That's funny, but yeah, a lot of the stuff he's saying, I really don't take much issue
with.
Yeah.
He's saying that this is serious and that Ebola is a very nasty disease and we have
to do what we can to make sure that responsible steps are taken.
This isn't bullshit.
But he does have a, I would say possibly maybe not good plan of action.
And what I have recommended and repeatedly recommended is that Dr. Friesen of the CDC
resigned that the CDC be placed on stand down because they really have no, they're not effective.
They've been inefficient and they have no authoritative capacity to demand either the
city, the state or any institution to do what's mandatory.
Instead, I think that Fauci, Dr. Tony Fauci should be given executive privilege or executive
authority by the president of the United States consistent with 1892 constitutional authority
on both military powers if need be, because we no longer have the public health service
which is not functioning.
Yeah.
So Fauci should be given executive control to use military resources to deal with Ebola.
These people are just a joke.
I can't.
I love it.
I can't believe this.
Yeah.
This is, this is one of those, you know what's funny?
It's almost like, it's almost like the Mandela effect.
It's almost like we're looking back into a past that didn't happen in the present.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
Like this is an alternate universe where.
But it actually helps me put some pieces together because I always did think it was a little
bit weird that at the beginning of the coronavirus situation, Alex was painting Fauci as a good
guy.
Yeah.
And he said he made some calls and looked into him and hearing Steve talk about him
like this, talk about Fauci like this at this point makes me think like, oh, Alex called
Steve and Steve told him he's cool.
Steve was like, this is a good guy.
And then they got the lines from.
The right wing media decided he's a villain.
That's interesting.
Maybe the biggest thing that happens that we need to go back and, and kind of analyze
is the creation of the feedback loop between the right wing propaganda, creating Trump
and then Trump echoing right wing propaganda back at them.
Yeah.
I don't know how you would ever, I don't know where you would look for that.
Um, I don't know.
Kill all the baby Hitlers.
I think that's what we do.
I blame Drudge.
Yeah.
I would do that too.
Let's just say it's Drudge.
It's Drudge's fault.
It's a bad guy.
So Alex really wants this to be fake and a false flag.
Um, and so I was listening to this, uh, part of the episode and it really felt like Alex
was essentially begging Steve to be like, come on, help me out, man, please.
Uh, doc, I mean, you believe Sandy hook was staged more and more experts have come out
and agreed, uh, the Boston bombing, uh, you know, rigged so many other events, nine 11,
the open funding of ISIS, changing the name from Al Qaeda, all of this is coming out.
But when you look at this Ebola situation, I'm not saying it's not ravaging Africa.
I'm not saying it isn't, uh, you know, living in the body longer before the symptoms show
up 21 days instead of three, it's clearly mutating, getting stronger, but it just, I
can't believe that this type of ineptitude to bring in Ebola patients, they never did
that before to let people fly in from West Africa, from ravaged areas.
When other countries had already banned it months ago, I mean, it appears that ineptitude
wouldn't be this precise at doing everything they could to grease the skids for Ebola.
Are you getting any information on them allowing this to spread, to kind of bring in a medical
tyranny to create a political distraction?
Are there any motives for this to be a false flag?
No, not really, because number one, it is very hard to create an epidemic to create
a false flag.
Newtown was a false flag because Eric Holder had funded a very dysfunctional governor and
a dysfunctional town and a bunch of Connecticut State Troopers who were just pathetic and
it was easy to create and that scenario was nonsense.
Oh boy.
Okay.
Well, interesting answer.
Yep.
Although this did, this did make me think, here's what we should do.
We should call the right-wing terrorists all-white-a.
That?
I thought, I thought like the one that was going around before was y'all-kida.
Was that what it was?
That was, that was something that I heard Alex yell about before.
I think I used to say white-kida.
I think I remember that one.
Yeah.
I like all-white-a.
I'll let you do a meme contest about it.
Look, dude, the thing that I think is really funny beyond just Steve being like Fauci is
a great guy, he should have control over everything in the response.
Yeah, that's brutal.
Alex being a over-the-top.
Give me something.
Give me any reason.
I mean, and blue sky thinking.
I don't care.
Steve.
I'm begging.
I don't care what it is.
Give me even the slightest hint.
Is there a possible motive?
Yes.
Give me the-
No.
Just money.
Just say money.
You could just say money.
Ugh.
No.
Nah, you're kidding.
The answer is even more illuminating and that is that it's really difficult to create a
fake epidemic.
People wouldn't do that.
It's not wise.
It would be a bad idea.
Yeah.
Very easy to get out of hand.
Millions of people could die.
Yeah.
Pretty much impossible to control.
Yep.
Not a supervillain plan that would really work outside of a movie.
But the thing that I think is really interesting is that Alex is talking about all of these
things in almost identical ways.
Medical tyranny.
All this stuff.
He doesn't mention Lockstep at all because he didn't know about that document in 2014.
No, no, no.
He knew about it 20 years ago.
And it wasn't a document called Lockstep.
He found it back then.
It's been in there-
He pretends to have known about all this stuff and is like, no, you didn't.
This wasn't part of your narratives then.
No one had shown you this.
Nope.
It hadn't made the-
Because it didn't exist.
No.
It existed in 2010.
Oh, no.
I mean in the right-wing sphere.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah.
It hadn't been posted on a stupid blog yet.
It misrepresented what it was in a way that was profitable.
And you just see it very clearly.
Like he just didn't have the mana to do that attack at this point.
It's kind of telling.
Yeah.
I'm just so bummed.
It's so easy.
The right-wing propagandist's job is so easy.
You do the same shit every five years for five years and then restart.
Every time.
It's the same shit.
Yeah.
It's so boring.
And God forbid Ebola would have spread more in the United States at this point, but I
could easily see Alex going a very similar way.
It's like, they're trying to lock down our businesses because they're afraid of this
disease.
Just don't have people cough on you or throw up.
And the more effort the government puts into stopping it, the more he'd argue that that's
what they're-
That's the reason that they released this on us to encroach on our civil liberties.
You can almost easily see how the playbook operates based on the incredible similar parallels
you have here.
Yeah.
It is really surprising.
Oh, maybe not.
No, really.
I mean, that's what I'm saying.
You can see it going down the same exact train of thought no matter what time period it is
because it's the thought process itself that leads you to believe action towards aversion
is actually causing things.
It's the thought process itself, not the circumstances.
What changes is the circumstances allow it to balloon out of control or it's contained.
Yeah.
It's deeply cynical and cruel the way that Alex operates in this respect.
It really is a denial and disregard for the fact that there are people who are suffering
and dealing with this and a rank disregard for the people who are listening who are probably
scared and need information.
They need to have conveyed accurate information that allows them to make appropriate decisions
like the emails that were sent out to the people who were on the plane after, even though
there probably wasn't a reason to be worried.
That's appropriate.
You're giving the people the information that they need to be able to make appropriate decisions.
These listeners are tuning into Alex because they think that they're going to get some
kind of insight that they're not going to get elsewhere and he's lying to them in a
way that's designed to scare them and just to get them to get their immune system ready
with the products that he sells over at inflowars.com and...
As the world economy melts down, gold will go up even as other commodities go down because
it's an ultimate store of wealth and a hedge against imploding economies and it is up.
When I heard that bond markets had imploded and the stock market was down so much today,
I thought, man, I bet gold goes down.
I said this aloud, but I said, or maybe it'll go up because when I saw that oil was way
down, I thought, man, I wonder, but man, when I saw gold going up, that's pretty serious
right there.
So the other thing is that there are economic impacts that are happening because of the
Ebola situation.
There's some like airline stocks are going down.
There are impacts that are happening and Alex is using that to funnel gold sales.
Gold started 2014 at $12.05.77 an ounce, peaking on June 30th at $1,327.39 an ounce.
On October 16th, the day this show was recorded, the price was $12.39, down almost $3 an ounce
from the day before.
It would close the year at $1,184.31.
Nothing Alex says means anything.
His syndicator at this point is still a guy who owns a gold sales business, so gold is
super important to his world view in 2014 and it's weird how it's so much less so now.
So in order to talk about the bond markets falling apart and how gold is great, Alex
brings in his financial buddy, Max Kaiser.
Oh God.
Max Kaiser, I will say, does not give a shit.
That sounds right.
He is not taking this seriously at all.
I was so close to Gary North and then it's like all the other crazy stuff in my life.
Not Gary North, Gary Webb, Gary North, another writer with Oliver North and Gary North.
And then I didn't break these big CIA drug dealing stories with him because I was just
like, yeah, I already know all that.
Sure.
Come on the air.
Sell your book.
Yeah.
You're a hero.
They're trying to destroy you.
But why?
Why put out new documents?
Why put out a website with you, Gary Webb?
Because they killed him.
And then he attacked me for saying they killed him.
But the movie basically says they killed.
You said, you know, they show that and his wife, his kids, and that they kill him.
I'm just, I just am speechless.
How powerful kill the messenger and the story about Gary Webb and his whole surprise and
all the rest of it is, I mean, it's simply amazing how all his so-called friends turned
against him when the mainstream media said he was a fraud with no proof.
Have you seen kill the messenger yet, Kaiser?
No, no.
I'm not scared to.
I just felt like I dropped the ball monumentally, not working with him more, helping get his
material out, man.
Oh.
Coward.
Why do you think we're still alive?
We're too pretty.
You know, people, they, they don't want to kill off such a beautiful, beautiful, especially
examples of a human species.
It would just destroy their souls more than what they do on a day to day basis.
No, come on.
Gary Webb had a beautiful soul.
Man, Max Kaiser does not give a shit.
Wow.
He is not taking this seriously at all.
Yep.
Nope.
And I kind of, it's a breath of fresh air.
Yeah, I do like that.
I do like a little bit of eh, fucking, you know, who gives a shit?
Come on.
We're too pretty.
Too pretty.
Their interview ends with Alex comes in from break and he's singing along with balls to
the wall.
Sure.
And he's talking about how this is a, you know, an air, like a pilot term, you know,
jam in the throttle.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then it's also about the Berlin Wall, you know, and, uh, he's talking about how
this is a protest song and a little bit later, Max Geiser's like, I gotta make a correction.
That's about going balls deep.
It's actually a sincerely kind of funny moment and Alex, I think he knows that it's funny
that he doesn't know how to play along with it.
So he's like, this is a family show, Max Geiser, oh, he's a dirty, but he's a dirty guy.
Can't do a two man game.
Just can't do it.
He's a bad scene partner.
But again, it was this Max Geiser just kind of like, he operates outside of the grifts
that are going on.
Cause he's scamming and stuff, but I think he's so rich that he doesn't care.
That's fair.
Yeah.
That's the type of rich that, uh.
He's got fuck you money.
Yeah.
I think that's nobody, you know, only insane people want to be billionaires.
I think everybody wants that point of just like, uh, fuck these guys, you know, that's
what you really want.
Yeah.
I can go on to Alex's show and perpetuate max coin or whatever.
I can try and sell whatever thing that I'm doing and that can be fun, but I don't need
it.
I can also fuck with Alex.
Just a millionaire.
Yeah.
I also have a show on RT.
I don't need his platform either.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's weird.
But someone who does need Alex's platform very desperately.
All right.
Ted Anderson joining us on short notice from California, uh, the owner of the GCN radio
network.
He also is one of the biggest private gold dealers with a triple a rating from the better
business Bureau.
Something you can't say of most other gold dealers out there.
This ride by my gold for 20 years, about 19 years, he's been a sponsor for 19.
I've worked in this time slot for 18 years.
I never wanted to go up against rush Limbaugh.
Ted said, no, we're going to do it.
You know, he's got a monopoly in cities and a lot of stations, you know, want to have
a show to go up against it.
You're on here, not at night, if you want to work at this network.
So here I am.
And funny enough, I'm now beating rush Limbaugh in ratings wherever I'm put up against him,
even on smaller stations.
Are you, I highly doubt that.
Do you think so?
No.
Do you really think so?
I mean like, yeah, some stations can't afford Russia syndication rates and Alex's is free.
So yeah, sure.
It makes sense.
I imagine.
So, yeah, Ted's Ted's just on to sell gold.
Alex is out here like Ted Ebola is causing problems.
We need you on quick to sell gold.
Yeah.
I've been panicking people all day, but he's not onto pitch gold.
Now is the time.
And I didn't mean to even get him onto pitch gold with Midas.
But folks, if you wait until the fall where it historically goes up, if you wait until
there is a big rush, it's already up 20 something bucks today.
Can we pull that up for me CNBC?
Now is the time, I believe, to get into gold and silver, or at least get some of the books
or financial prospectus documents that Midas Resources has.
And then like a year later, Ted would lose his license because he's a...
Because he's a scamming.
Thief.
Scammy guy.
He's a fraudster.
Yeah.
And so, I mean, like this is kind of the payoff, the prestige of the panic and the fear that
Alex has been building throughout the episode with his hysterical nonsense, his talking
about the bond markets falling apart.
That part with Max Keiser is a nice bridge to the interview with Ted Anderson in order
to funnel people to give them the solution to the problem.
We've created this problem that is...
False flag Ebola, a nuclear strike.
Right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You've got to retain your money somehow.
And the only way your assets are going to be safe is with this guy, Ted, my buddy who
I've been working with for 19 years.
Buy some bullion you've never seen and have him put it in a lockbox you don't know is
real.
It's safe.
It's fine.
Yeah.
Yeah, so I mean, I look back on this.
I mean, I don't care what Ted has to say.
It's just about gold.
Yeah, of course.
But looking back on this episode, it was shocking to me.
I mean, the reason that I chose it, like honestly, had nothing to do with Ebola.
I didn't know that this episode was about Ebola.
I just saw Steve Pacanik's name.
You're a witch.
Yeah.
So I was like, I got a fucking 2014 Steve Pacanik, boom, let's do this.
Let's see what he's bringing to the table.
And I started listening to it.
Love Dr. Fauci is what he's bringing to the table.
God damn it.
So bizarre.
Fuck you.
It's so bizarre.
I want to throw a tomato at Steve Pacanik because of this now.
You see the dark, twisted, like distorted version of the narratives that are being
sold in the present about coronavirus being applied to Ebola in seven years prior, just
with completely different clothes.
Back then, they could fuck around with crisis actor stuff because they hadn't been checked
on that front.
And so Rob Doo thinks that maybe these people with Ebola are fake.
Anthony Fauci wasn't somebody that Trump got into a fight with.
And so he's a hero that Steve studied under at Cornell and they're tight.
He should have control of the military apparatus to deal with Ebola.
I think it's fascinating.
It does strongly reinforce my theory that Alex is full of shit.
I would say that if not definitive proof, I would argue that the totality of our work
is definitive proof.
This might be a good argument not to take them seriously.
Although if you need further proof, go to Dr. Fauci.
Poop bandits.
Yes.
Yeah.
Oh boy.
So I hope you had fun.
I did.
Enjoying my wizardry.
I do.
I love when you bring witchcraft to the table, Dan.
I'm uncomfortable with how kind of regular an occurrence it is.
It is really kind of frustrating.
Again, Dan, everything is a prank on me.
I'm beginning to believe that thoroughly.
Well, here's Ashton Kutcher.
Yeah.
Goddamn it.
The coronavirus didn't happen.
Son of a bitch, Ashton.
That would be an elaborate plan.
Yeah.
If I was the only one who actually quarantined this entire time, yeah.
That would be interesting.
Yep.
I don't think it's feasible.
Although I did read a white paper.
I've seen a lot of false flags in the past.
Also, the other thing, before we get out of here, that I was thinking about.
That was with Alex.
It's just a joke that he says, I have the documents.
Yeah.
I mean, he's claiming that he has these documents from Gary Webb.
It's like, do you?
Or are they lost?
Yeah.
Or did they ever exist?
So anytime that he says he has the documents, it might be just some CD rom that may or may
not exist in a warehouse somewhere that he has no fucking idea that should be protected
like the Holy Grail.
You would think that that would be so fastidiously organized, seeing as how it's proof of all
the conspiracies that have ever been.
Well, maybe not proof of all of them, but at least the building block that would get
you to where something is solidly proven that you can maybe build from.
Yeah.
And I think that would be really important for him because as far as I can tell from
the bedrock of so many of these conspiracies, primary sources that you go back to, they
just don't hold up.
So if he did have these secret classified documents, you would fucking handcuff it
to your wrist.
Yeah.
That would be ridiculous to imagine that you would.
No, absolutely.
Especially after Gary Webb dies.
In the episode that we did not record, I played this clip for you.
The two guys that we were talking about watched a 20 minute conspiracy theory video and I
only played you one clip from it and it was the guy narrating it say, about a month ago
I lost all of it and it's like, oh, fuck off.
There is a certain irony to us complaining about this when we're only recording this
episode because of a tech glitch, although we didn't prove anything in that episode.
No, I think that was more an observation.
Yeah.
It was just some laughs were had that will never be had publicly.
Anyway, Jordan, this has been fun.
This has been fun.
Yeah.
Sorry that your episode got lost.
Oh, it'll be okay.
We'll let you take the wheel again here in the near future.
Sometimes soon.
I'm sure you can find something that we can go over.
Anyway, but, uh, but for now, let's, uh, let's end this.
Okay.
Let's travel back to the present.
All right.
Uh, we'll be back.
But until then, Jordan, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's a thanks to Mr. Peabody for bringing us back to the present.com.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's that knowledge.
I'll just go right now.
Go to bed.
Jordan.
We're also on Facebook.
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work right now.
Yep.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I am the leader of the Poop Bandits.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.