N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys.
Dan and Jordan.
Knowledgefight.
Riddle her.
Need money.
Andy Enchanze.
Stop it.
It's time to pray.
Andy Enchanze.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
Knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey everybody.
Welcome back to Knowledgefight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes.
We like to sit around, drink novelty beverages, and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh indeed we are Dan.
Jordan.
Dan.
Yeah.
Quick question for you.
What's up?
What's your bright spot?
My bright spot today is, why don't you go first.
Okay.
I think we might wind up having a very similar bright spot.
My bright spot was last night we celebrated our friend's birthday.
Not a health ranger.
Our friend who is not a health ranger.
No, no.
Not, very strongly not a health ranger.
John.
And it was a fantastic time.
We hung out.
We played video, played games together over Zoom.
It was fantastic.
I had a great night.
Yes.
Delightful time.
Yeah.
It was had.
Later on the bartender asked me to leave, but other than that it was a good night.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
You know, since you've claimed that, I guess I can't have that be my bright spot.
I think you could.
That's what I shall say.
What?
I got a message from one of our listeners, a policy wonk out there, who had some music
that they had made that they wanted a review of.
Oh, okay.
And I gave it a little bit of a spin.
All right.
And this is a gentleman by the name of Derek Avery.
And I checked it out.
You can find some albums on Spotify.
I enjoyed it.
It's great.
It's a pop punk kind of vibe.
That's awesome.
I listened to his album, Here's to Better Misery.
And I enjoyed it quite a bit.
That's awesome.
And I can say that sincerely.
And I think that's probably why it's a bright spot.
Yes.
Because I don't have to be...
I don't have to be like, it's good.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
It's great.
It's...
I love it when a fan does stuff.
Yeah.
I enjoyed it.
So thanks for sharing that with me, Derek.
I appreciate it.
And if people want some pop punk, you should go check that out.
So Jordan.
Yes, sir.
Today we are back into the present day.
Oh, shit.
I've got February 28th, 2021, Blackjack.
Ah, za-za.
Yep.
I waited until you had your vape in your mouth so you couldn't respond.
That was different.
That was kind of cheating on my part.
Just comically easy.
Yeah.
So that's Sunday, today's episode as we're recording this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
One of the reasons why I wanted to do this episode for the Sunday is I wanted to see
like, hey, CPAC has run its course.
Sure.
I just, I remember last year, such heights.
It was a big deal last year.
CPAC was...
So much, so much going on.
It was a celebrity-filled affair.
Alex went there.
Exactly.
And the bartender told him to leave.
He missed his own speech at the end.
He was supposed to be the headliner.
Nick Fuentes basically took over the show.
There were fireworks.
It was great.
Yeah.
It was Enrique Tarrio made a joke about how there's probably an FBI informant in the room.
Which is funny.
Because it was him.
It was outrageous.
It was such a good time, that CPAC event.
There was so much going on, so much nonsense, and it's just such a sign how sad it is now.
He's not even going to DC, he's not going to CPAC.
He's just sitting in his studio, having a show.
Yeah!
I mean, last year, it was full-on the gathering of the Juggalos level, but for white nationalists
instead of cool people.
Yeah, Mike Flynn's son showed up.
Yeah, exactly.
Kind of almost cried, talking about how great his dad is.
I'm so grateful to not have to have paid a single iota of attention to CPAC this year.
Yeah, I saw a little bit.
I didn't watch as much as some have, because I just don't care.
But the value of this episode, of Alex's show, is that it's going on during Trump's speech
at CPAC.
Ooooh!
So he's counter-programming.
He's counter-programming against his God-King!
Which means that Alex just plays the speech mostly for the first hour, and does a little
bit of commentary.
But there's still a couple of things that I find particularly important, and one thing
that drove me a little bit crazy.
What's that?
Well, we'll get to it.
We'll get to it.
God damn it.
I don't want to spoil it.
You're so good.
But before we do any of that, we've got to take a moment to say thank you to the folks
who have signed up and are supporting the show.
That's a great idea.
So first, Miss Elanius.
That's Miss Elanius.
Yes and no, no, no.
I understand.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Mademoiselle Elanius.
Thank you.
Next.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Next.
Guisapina, the juiciest ice cube.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
I guess I'm the second.
Wait.
Guisapina or Giuseppe?
Giuseppina?
Yeah.
I don't know.
I'm not good with names.
I'm just asking.
Okay.
All right.
Next.
Etta and Nessa P. Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
All right.
Next.
Sully the Canadian youth.
From what I hear, this Sully refers to Alex Jones as the shouty man with demon voices.
Yeah.
That sounds about right.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
And then I got a couple of technocrat shout-outs to jump into here.
First, Ben.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
This is tough.
Lauren B. Thank you so much.
You're a technocrat.
And also happy birthday two weeks ago.
This is what we're doing now.
Birthday shout-outs retroactive.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what you get.
We're not doing this current anymore.
Yeah.
We will do six month late.
Exactly.
Sliding birthday shout-outs.
Anyway, Lauren, I hope two weeks ago you had a great birthday and you are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate.
That's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right, we got to go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much.
Yes, thank you very much to the both of you.
So, Jordan, you know, this is going to be a little bit of a briefer episode.
It's going to be a little bit shorter.
And one of the reasons, like I said, is because-
Well, an hour of it is Trump's speech.
Right.
Yeah.
He had set out to, you know, get this CPAC wrap up.
I thought there would be, like, a lot of, some dense things to get into, some reflections.
And no.
It's a big old nothing.
Yeah.
It's a little bit of running commentary of Trump's speech.
Sure.
With a couple of completely absurd things thrown in.
And so, you know, it starts pretty much how you would expect it to.
It's February 28th on the Sunday live transmission.
President Trump has just started speaking from Florida at the 2021 CPAC that the controlled
corporate press and big tech are trying to censor and block everywhere.
But before we hear from the real president, let's hear from the imposter.
Let's hear from the puppet who just did a victory lap Friday in Houston, Texas.
Yeah.
So, Alex says, you know, he's setting the table with Trump is the real president.
Sure.
Which is good.
That's great.
It's healthy.
It's good stuff.
Yeah.
The denial is fantastic.
And he has a clip of Biden saying some words that sound like he is confused.
Sure.
And so this is evidence that his brain is deteriorating.
All right.
Fine.
Yeah.
And I think that this next clip is kind of, like, indicative of how the large chunk of
this show goes.
It's really just Alex getting excited while Trump gives a speech.
Okay.
That's gross.
Let there be no doubt we will be victorious and America will be stronger and greater than
ever before.
Yes.
We will defeat the globalist.
Woo.
Yes.
Yeah.
He's pretty.
He's Ed McMahon-ing it?
Yeah.
All right.
A large portion of the speech that airs on Alex's version of Trump's speech is a lot
of fear mongering about immigrants.
Sure.
Why not?
What are we doing?
It's pretty heavily hitting that tone.
Yeah.
And I found it to be alarming, upsetting.
But I was surprised by one thing, and that is that, you know, there's a little bit of
time to fuck around in this speech, too.
Sure.
I also want to pay my love and respect to the great Rush Limbaugh.
Absolutely.
Kill him again.
Call him a call in.
Call him a rush.
That betrayals.
Rush wasn't perfect.
He was pro-America.
I believe in the country.
Who is watching closely and smiling down on us.
He's watching and he's loving it.
He's loving it.
Do you think he's up there, buddies?
Do you really?
I find that fun.
Yeah.
You know, just to give a shout out to my boy Rush.
He's looking down at us.
He's loving it.
He's loving what he's seeing here at CPAC.
Oh, man.
What is he...
Did he do the cross?
Did he cross himself?
Did he pour one out?
He might have been crossing his fingers.
Did he strangle a parole in front of everyone to celebrate?
Yeah, that seemed a little pandery.
Yeah, maybe.
But also probably sincere.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Without him, he wouldn't have been elected.
So a while back, 50 years ago, right after the election.
Okay.
There was talk after Trump had lost that he was going to start his own party.
The Patriot Party.
Right.
Yes.
People are pretty excited about this because they're nuts.
And of course, rightfully, people on the left are like, please do that.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Absolutely.
Completely splinter the right wing.
No, no, no.
Do that.
Go white nationalists and quieter white nationalists.
That's what we would like you to do.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Divide the voting block.
That's a very smart thing to do.
Turns out this is fake news.
Trump was never going to do that.
Wow.
And so...
Why would he?
He already owns the Republican Party.
Yeah.
And he basically announces that.
Oh, okay.
We're not starting new parties.
You know, they kept saying, he's going to start a brand new party.
We have the Republican Party.
It's going to unite and be stronger than it was before.
That's right.
I am not starting a new party.
Yes.
That was fake news.
Fake news.
No.
Wouldn't that be brilliant?
Let's start a new party and let's divide our vote so that you can never win.
No, we're not interested in that.
Someone had to explain that to you.
Shut the fuck up.
Tremendous.
Mr. McLaughlin just gave me numbers that nobody's ever heard of before.
More popular than anybody.
That's all of us.
It's all numbers.
Yeah.
Hit pause.
We're going to come back with this.
Let's do four.
We're going to come back in Georgia and other people winning with 75 points, 71 points,
69 points, 70 points.
All the super hardcore Trump candidates were winning in districts that had been about 50-50
before by huge 20-point extra margins never before seen.
So Marjorie Taylor Greene won her race essentially unopposed.
The Democrat candidate had withdrawn from the race due to personal matters and that's
why she won.
Yeah.
Also, a simple scan of the history of that district, Georgia's 14th.
It disproves what Alex is saying.
In the 2018 election, Republican Tom Graves won with 76.5% of the vote.
On a pro-slavery platform.
In 2016, 2014, and 2010, Graves ran unopposed.
In 2012, he won with 73% of the vote.
According to the Cook Partisan Voter Index, this is a Republican plus 27 district, which
means it skews heavily Republican.
That would make sense.
That, in addition to her opponent withdrawing, is why Marjorie Taylor Greene won.
Not because pro-Trump candidates are so exciting and they're super mega popular.
Also, how dare you?
You don't care about voting.
You think that the election was stolen.
Don't tell me that they won elections.
Well, yeah.
No, because the election was stolen, but if it hadn't have been stolen, they would have
won with like 80% of the vote.
Sure.
90% of the vote.
Okay.
That's how popular people are who like Trump.
All right.
Thanks for that, Dan.
Yep.
You should know better.
I really should at this point.
So Jordan, I have, you know, around the Super Bowl, I definitely got into Alex's commercial
stylings.
Yes, they were fantastic.
He was doing some very weird ad reads.
It was super bizarre.
Now, this episode I'm listening to through the GCN, the Genesis Communications Network
feeds, which is the company that does Alex's syndication.
So all of the radio stations get this feed, all the radio stations that play Alex's show
get this feed.
And these are the commercials that are put on along with the package.
These are the people who sponsor Genesis Communications Network.
And I listened to one of these commercials and it really, really upset me.
Oh, no.
Here is the thing that blew my mind and almost drove me crazy.
Okay.
The days of extermination is set to commence now.
And as population die-off becomes evident, you know it is the time of punishment in all
that is written.
The cover for mass die-off is evolution and global warming frauds, also used as false
proof of their Christ.
They are from the lines that were disinherited 2,000 years ago.
Now they claim to be his Christ based upon blood type, DNA, and long lifespan.
Go to unveilingthem.com.
That's U-N-V-E-I-L-I-N-G them.com.
Whoa.
Wow.
Do you have any idea?
First, first.
Could you make sense of that?
First, his voice and the way he's delivering it and the kind of choppy nature of the end
of the sentence and the beginning of a new one makes it sound a little bit like he's
a synthetic robot voice or somebody speaking, like somebody wearing a mask speaking through
a vocalizer or something like that.
Well, I know from my time of trying to get into voiceovers for commercials that a lot
of the time, if you're not a pretty good editor, it'll sound rough because you're trying to
jam it into a very specific span of time.
You buy a 30 second block and it's got to be 30 seconds.
It cannot be 28.
It cannot be 32.
Yeah.
And that leads to whenever you're not that good, you'll end up sounding like that.
Sure.
And that's kind of unfortunate.
But I'm more interested in the content and how that...
What did you take away from that?
What I thought I heard was that some people are claiming to be Christ or related to Christ.
Maybe.
All right.
And because it is unveiling them, so there's a group of people who are doing that.
Now what I don't understand is how the population die off and the fake climate change and such
ties into the group of people.
What do you think they're selling?
Oh boy.
That's a good question.
Spoiler alert.
It's nothing.
They're not selling anything.
Okay.
All right.
That commercial hit me a little weird.
And honestly, it speaks to the level of sponsors that Genesis Communications Network is able
to attract at this point.
Yeah.
That's rough.
That's terrifying.
Yeah.
I checked out this website and apparently the person behind it believes that the MMR
vaccine has created iron poisoning in the population, which is the cause of all disease.
Oh, well, I'm glad that that's cleared up.
Now I should be clear.
There's actually, the iron poisoning goes much deeper than this and it goes back quite
a long ways.
And the MMR vaccine isn't really creating it as much as exacerbating it and causing
problems for people who are already iron poisoned.
Okay.
All right.
So even if you didn't get the MMR vaccine is what they're saying.
Don't worry.
You're still fucked.
You're still iron poisoned.
You can still join us.
Yeah.
Apparently the Euphrates River is actually the Mississippi and the real population of
the United States is just about 200 million.
Okay.
As it turns out, only people with AB blood type are safe from this iron poisoning.
And I have to admit this site's argument is a little bit difficult to follow.
All right.
I'm trying my best here.
Sell me on this one.
It kind of inevitably drifts into a little bit of British Israelism.
Well, yeah, of course.
And it starts to feel a little bit anti-Semitic as you're reading through this.
There's one page on the site titled, quote, round them up, which argues that everyone
in any position of influence in the world is in on this plan to poison everyone with
iron.
Uh, I mean, they would have to be.
This includes quote, all of mainstream and alternative media, which I think would include
InfoWars.
That includes damn near everybody.
Yeah.
About these media entities, there's a note in bold letters, quote, commandeer these immediately.
Commandeer these immediately?
There's a note?
Mm-hmm.
Wait, on the website?
Yes.
Like, like it's something that somebody put up on their to-do list.
Like it's on the refrigerator of like commandeer those first.
Mm-hmm.
Gotcha.
Like literally everyone is in on the plan, including quote, all nursing and assisted
living homes, all corporations, water treatment facilities, and food and beverage industry
farms and ranches.
Well, then I think that kind of, that counts half the world, right?
So I think half the world is iron poisoning the other half.
Well, see, apparently this is how this breaks down.
Okay.
There are these people who are AB blood type and thus are, they're not iron poisoned.
Their blood type is not susceptible to the iron poisoning.
All right.
Iron can't touch AB.
Yes.
But it can touch A and B.
And it has something to do with, I wasn't quite able to figure this out, but it has
something to do with like AB blood being found on the Shroud of Turin.
Okay.
All right.
I'm listening.
Everybody with AB blood is related to Jesus.
And they are not susceptible to iron poisoning.
Good stuff.
So they're not going to be hurt by things like the COVID-19 vaccine, which will take
out all of the people who have iron poisoning.
The vaccine will like exacerbate these parasites or whatever that's inside you due to iron
poisoning.
Can we do a follow up on that?
Like can they, because we will know in the future whether or not they're correct.
So I would imagine that next year, let's make a gentleman's wager, me and the British Israelites.
I don't know if this is mainstream British Israelist thought as much as this is a very
weird GeoCities ass page that's spouting a very convoluted conspiracy.
I think that that's basically what's going on.
There's these people who are AB blood type and they're poisoned.
They want to get the vaccine in people who have A, O, or B because it'll kill all of
them off.
Sure.
And in order to avoid this horrifying conclusion, the page literally says, quote, round up every
one of them, account for all 14.3 million in the United States, place them in holding
areas for out-processing.
Okay.
So wait, now I'm against AB blood type people?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They're evil now.
Yes.
They're the Gs.
They think they are.
Oh, those idiots.
I found this very confusing.
That's a little, that's a little, I don't think they're going to win in the end.
I'll put it that way.
On the one hand, this is a deeply pathetic state of affairs that Alex's radio syndication
would stoop to accepting an ad from a website like this that doesn't actually appear to
be selling anything.
Nope.
On the other hand, it's deeply disturbing as a thing for them to be intentionally or
accidentally promoting to their audience.
This website is explicitly accusing people, everyone who has AB blood type of being part
of a conspiracy to kill off the public and that they need to be rounded up.
That seems a little irresponsible.
Yeah.
So I was curious about this and I dug around a little bit more.
Sure.
Apparently this page has been up since 2003 and there are some snapshots of what it used
to promote on the way back machine.
Okay.
It turns out my feelings about this seeming a bit antisemitic were accurate.
From the page, as it existed in 2004, quote, they are murderers and thieves and destroy
the truth and destroy the earth and mankind.
Now is the time to destroy these destroyers.
They are the ones who claim to be Jews who are not.
All right.
There we go.
Oh boy.
All right.
Toss that one on the board.
Yeah.
The site at this point does not appear to have any connection to the iron poisoning
conspiracy, but instead it's just classic antisemitic screeds.
It's basically just protocols of the elders of Zion shit.
Great.
By 2008, the site had added the iron poisoning shit and it seems pretty clear that the argument
being laid out by this website is that Jewish people who aren't really Jewish are running
around and they're going to poison the world with iron in order to kill everyone off down
the road.
All right.
So this AB blood type, I think is a way of talking.
Yeah.
Jews, but I'm saying AB blood type.
Right.
Gotcha.
It's not about how everyone thinks he's a Nazi, it's important to remember that his
radio buddy, uh, you know, who runs all of his, uh, like radio syndication and affiliates,
uh, is, you know, he's, he's, he's responsible for Alex's radio career.
That guy is willing to accept advertising money to promote a website that essentially
advocates rounding up Jewish people.
I would really prefer, and I'm going to go out on a limb here.
And I think this, look, this is going to be an unpopular opinion, but I don't care what
side of the political aisle you're on.
I think rounding people up is usually a bad sign.
Yeah.
I'm just going to go out there.
I'm going to say that.
I know it's an unpopular thought, Dan.
Yeah.
It's, uh, it's, it's not a sign of a healthy, uh, body politic.
Let's think of all the historical examples of people being rounded up.
All of them worked out well.
Nevermind.
Uh, I found this bizarre, um, confusing.
I would never have imagined that something like this would be like able to secure an
advertising slot on Alex Jones's show.
I was going to say, it must be really fucking cheap.
It's gotta be dirt cheap for, uh, for just a random ass website to be like, yeah, I'll
buy 30 seconds.
Well, there's two things to consider.
One is maybe this person is independently wealthy.
Sure.
So maybe it's not that cheap and there's like, fuck it.
I got to get the word out about iron possible.
Second possibility is that it is that cheap because think about it, like there's no big
businesses knocking down Ted Anderson's door to get ads on, on this shit.
No one wants this bottom of the barrel stuff.
I could absolutely also see this as just a favor.
I could see almost all advertising on GCN just being Ted being like, man, I know a guy,
come on, do a 30 second spot, man.
If that's a favor, then that opens up another can of worms and that is like, this is, they
know what's being pushed and they are willingly disseminating and supporting this and that's
fucked up.
I would have to, I mean, there's no way that somebody doesn't know what's being pushed.
You know what, I would, I would believe a world exists where no one knows what's going
on.
That's fair.
They're just like, wait, the check cleared?
Put the eye on it.
I don't give a shit.
He's saying that people are going to be exterminated.
That works for us.
Yeah.
Oh, what's this?
Iron poisoning?
Uh, okay.
Yeah, sure.
Why not?
I'm going to wait for just a little while to find out that you are a deeply anti-Semitic
website.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Uh, iron poisoning.
We sell zinc.
They're close enough.
Get it on, get on the network.
Come on, buddy.
Oh, I'm also not going to check in on what you're, what you're espousing, uh, to the
point where I run, uh, alternative media thing, which you think needs to be commandeered immediately.
There is that.
I do like the idea that there is a 30 second spot.
Yeah.
With the website in it and no one bothered to look at the website.
I honestly, I'm not positive what I think is more upsetting.
Yeah.
The idea that they didn't check or that someone checked and they're like, yeah, it's fine.
It's either, either is pretty, pretty scary.
And the, the idea that like some of Alex's audience might go to that website and be like,
oh my God, if Alex would promote this, if he would allow this on his show, then there's
gotta be something to it.
I think the only thing we can do is get our own ad spot on GCN, Dan.
Wow.
I think we, I think we should try it.
Maybe, you know, we could, I, yeah, we got to get another website though.
Oh yeah.
No, we can't be, we can't be too obvious.
Yeah.
It's good that we're planning this on air in terms of, well, look, if you're not going
to look at that motherfucker's website, we're going to be fine.
Yeah.
All right.
I'm going to, I'm going to work on this.
I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to see if we can, the point is, they'll never know
when it's coming, Dan, we can announce it's going to happen and maybe that's the real
torture there.
They'll always be wondering, right?
Is this the one?
When is it going to, when is it going to, which ad is the prank?
When's the hammer going to drop?
Um, all right, so, uh, we get back to Alex now, uh, that it was a deeply upsetting little
road that I went down.
It's real dangerous.
Um, and, uh, also deeply upsetting, Alex is really thrilled that no one is wearing masks
at CPAC.
Great.
Don't you love how almost no one's wearing a mask in the CPAC event?
These were some, even though they've been haranguing them too, isn't that great?
These are good people.
These are the smart people.
Jesus.
It's not going to look great in hindsight.
Wow.
I would assume.
So Alex started the show talking about how Trump is the rightful president.
Um, and that's upsetting.
Sure.
It's more upsetting when Trump himself, uh, says that on stage at CPAC.
That's pretty upsetting.
Again, ladies and gentlemen, you're watching coverage of president Trump's ongoing live
speech.
We're about 20 minutes behind because we are going through the live show.
Actually, as you know, they just lost the white house, but it's one of those things.
But who knows, who knows, I may even decide to beat them for a third time.
Okay.
Yeah.
He just came out and said it was a fraud again.
Football spike bitches.
Boom.
Yeah.
That's what you need.
That's alarming.
I mean, we just can't, we can't keep doing this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah.
We refuse.
You know, like when, uh, 2000 happened, the election in 2000, that, uh, the Supreme Court
awarded the presidency to Bush.
Using all of the precedent that was available to them at the time, which is none.
And then they were just like, yeah, sure.
Well, and I think that a lot of people, uh, rightfully or inaccurately felt like that
was a stolen election.
I don't recall people insisting that Al Gore was the rightful president and I don't recall
Al Gore giving speeches where he said, I'm actually the president.
No, no.
Instead he went and focused on climate change.
Man, Trump, go focus on climate change.
No, don't.
Oh, no, no, no, not him.
No, no, no, no, no.
He would, he would bungle that.
No, no, no, no.
Go back inside of a very small hole and stay there.
I just find this to be untenable.
Like I, I can't, I can't imagine these kinds of rhetorics, uh, these, these kinds of things
leading anywhere positive.
It's going to get another storming of the Capitol at this rate.
It happened on the sixth and in response to that, they changed none of their rhetoric.
So it will happen again.
That's how it, it, it works.
It does seem that way.
Yeah.
So Alex is one of the most influential voices in the world.
Ah, until he's commandeered by those guys.
Those guys.
The true most influential voices in the world.
And uh, you know, you might be surprised who, uh, who listens to Alex.
It's a famous Alex Jones saying, my son always says it as a joke.
He wants to start a podcast called I'm not bragging.
I'm not bragging.
In fact, I'm a target and to even say this is dangerous.
Okay.
But the globalists know how authoritative and how influential we are, not just with
the general public, but with thought leaders here and across the planet.
You can probably imagine who listens to the show.
I'm not going to name drop.
One of them died just a week and a half ago.
He listened every day.
Okay.
Really?
So this is not about bragging, it's about understanding.
This broadcast is a brain trust.
This broadcast does not have corporate sponsorship.
This broadcast is hunted and lied about and demonized because we go to the source documents
and we're over the targets.
So we're getting the most flat.
We've got great products you already need.
Great.
Um, yeah, there's no way Rush Limbaugh listened to Alex every day.
I can't think of anything Rush Limbaugh did less than listen to Alex Jones.
You know what's, I mean, like he's on air for hours himself and then you imagine like,
oh yeah, he's going to spend his off time listening to someone do a shittier him and
a cartoony version.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
Or he just yells about demons.
Right.
Like I find this to be so fascinating.
The idea that Alex thinks that his audience, and I mean, maybe he's right, but he thinks
that his audience will believe that like really serious people take him seriously.
I mean, they must.
I can't imagine anybody who is like, you know, critical thinking, engaged, uh, listening
to his show and not being like, this is stupid.
This is insanely stupid.
Yeah.
It is, it is, uh, stupid on a level that like I can't really comprehend.
I understand being tricked by like little clips or snippets or something into thinking
that Alex's show is something that it's not, but it is dumb.
It is incredibly dumb.
Um, it's meandering.
It's often pointless.
It's full of emotional outbursts.
Yeah.
Um, it's a psycho drama that he's having that he's engaging the audience in and it's just
bizarre.
Well, I mean, we saw, I mean, literally he's playing a clip of somebody doing just that
to Republicans at a conference.
You know, like he's playing a clip of Trump saying nonsense that no reasonable person
would take seriously at all.
And it turns out 50% of the goddamn world is like, yay, imagination.
It's it's wild.
Yeah.
So, um, Alex is a creature of comedy.
We know that.
Yeah.
He's the meme machine.
He is indeed.
Um, but sometimes he has to be dragged kicking and screaming into doing horribly racist and
disgusting comedy.
Yeah.
Drag.
Oh.
So yeah.
Yeah.
Just pulling teeth with this guy.
He doesn't want to do it, but demands it.
He got it.
There have been a lot of requests for fentanyl, the communist Chinese dragon to make a return.
And so we hadn't done one probably in six months because I get bummed out with the news,
but I've decided to be more pumped out with the dress side to have more fun because the
globalist want to get our spirits down.
So I'm going to do it.
This is a little racy, a little, a little gross.
My wife thought it was a little much.
I told McBreen who made it with a Rob do to make the, when he pulls the anal probe out
to have it be green slime or something and said it's bloody.
But I think I'm gonna have him edit it again and just make it green, green dragon slime.
But kids love it.
Adults love it.
But it's also horrifying.
Yeah.
It sounds like it.
What did you just describe to me?
What did you just describe to me in a way that makes me want to see it?
Black demand is so high that Alex bring back his racist Chinese dragon character, which
by the way has not been gone for six months.
I have seen recently videos.
There was one making fun of that, um, what was that, uh, that guy who had his cat on
zoom.
Oh yeah.
Alex did a version of that, but with the dragon, like instead of the cat.
Wow.
Yeah.
So I mean like he's made those videos as recently as that.
It's not been six months.
He's doing this pretty regularly.
All right.
So he's got one apparently that involves a bloody anal probe.
I am really confused as to why you told me about the anal probe part.
Yeah.
I feel like that's something, look, that's a no spoiler situation for sure.
Okay.
I also love the kids love it.
Adults love it.
Kids love it.
It's like kicks.
It's some shit coming out of a dragon's asshole.
What are we, what are we going to be bad?
It's kid tested mother approved.
Yeah, absolutely.
Oh, choosy moms choose anal probes covered in blood.
Yeah.
This is, this is wild.
I mean, like I would have listened to his wife in this situation does sound like it's
a little bit much.
I would have listened to her tennis partner.
Yeah.
Wonder what they think.
So, um, Alex plays this video of an Australian journalist, uh, or, you know, I don't know.
I don't, I feel like journalists might be a little bit generous.
Seems like a editorial commentator type.
Oh, he plays this video of an Australian.
Yeah.
This guy is, uh, giving a speech about, uh, globalism and how, uh, it's evil.
Sure.
And fine, whatever.
I also thought maybe this was a little bit racist.
He's talking about like how you gotta be skeptical of any organization that has the word world
in it.
Like the world, uh, world health organization, the world food program, uh, and then he throws
this in.
Then of course there's the world food program.
It too is part of the United nations and it actually won the Nobel peace prize in 2020.
Now all that sounds pretty impressive until you remember that Barack Obama won it in 2008
just for having the right skin color.
Eeee.
Wow.
I, I, I think it's a problem that Alex can't seem to find any, anybody who breaks down
complaints about globalism that doesn't veer into that direction.
Ultimately boils down to somebody's going to say skin color.
Yeah.
Yep.
Ooh.
He understands how he got to Australia, right?
Um, like he understands the route that it took.
It was, it was perhaps a worldwide journey, if you will.
Uh, like he understands that, right?
Is that a concept that he gets?
I would assume so.
Yeah.
I mean, cause it seems like he is absolutely, if he's making this argument, uh, white people
should leave Australia.
You should go away.
Well that's, that's, that's interesting.
I just, I, I find it really interesting the way that like you can, and I obviously I think
it's partially because these kinds of things are attractive to Alex and he enjoys it.
Sure, sure, sure.
But you can't like find somebody to talk about these issues of like the challenges of globalized
connections and, uh, you know, living in a modern world where there's so much interconnectedness.
You can't find somebody to play that doesn't say Obama won a peace prize cause he has black
skin.
Like that's fucked up.
You can't find somebody that isn't like subtly racist or not subtly.
And it's the same thing with like, you know, the, uh, the Genesis Communications Network
can't take ads.
They can't attract anyone to give ads except for completely nonsensical, uh, websites.
I mean, what's wild about that is not since, uh, you know, like there are plenty of great
reasons to say that Obama shouldn't have that Nobel fucking peace prize.
Sure.
There are tons of great reasons.
There's a lot of critiques.
None of them have to do with his skin color.
No.
Ansance Yuki shouldn't have her Nobel peace prize either.
But here we are.
Well, yeah.
And, and the fact that like you have to distill it down to throw that kind of like that, uh,
you know, what the audience wants, that sort of poking, Oh, he only got it because he has
black skin.
Uh, he could have said he, he got it and they didn't know that he was going to drone bomb
the fucking world and it would be very reasonable.
Yeah.
But the audience wouldn't find that funny or satisfied because they kind of want him
to drone bomb the world and they just don't like the, he has the wrong skin color according
to them.
Yeah.
So, uh, one of the more delightful things that came out of the CPAC I think was the
video of, uh, the, the people getting booed for trying to tell people to wear masks.
Oh boy.
Did you see that?
No, I didn't see.
I, I want, I wanted nothing to do with this year's CPAC.
So a guy comes on stage and he, we're going to listen to this too, but I'm just going
to give you like a little bit of a breakdown.
Sure, sure, sure.
Um, he comes on stage and he's like, Hey, look, masks.
I know you all don't want to wear them, but we believe in property rights and we are in
someone else's hotel.
Wow.
So they get to make the rules.
Good angle.
Way to do it.
Way to fucking pull that one through.
Hey, that's a good landing.
Hey, yeah.
It's like, okay, I understand you don't want to wear a mask, but our conservative principles
demand that we respect the property rights of the owners of this hotel that are allowing
us to hold this convention here.
And I assume all the people there were like, uh, we don't have principles.
Go fuck yourself.
People weren't thrilled.
And so he hands the mic off to a young woman and she, uh, she says, uh, you know, I know
you don't want to wear masks, but can you work on that?
That's also fair.
It's like, that's also fair.
It's like talking to children.
It's amazing.
And then someone yells freedom.
Oh my God, somebody.
That's outrageously funny because it is, it is so, um, just so, uh, so much of a clear
illustration of this defiance, this oppositional defiance that characterizes, um, these crowds.
It's just like, no, fuck you.
Yeah.
That's insane.
It's childish.
Here's, here's my pitch.
All right.
CPAC, but we get all the conservatives in there and we just play schoolhouse rock for
them.
And maybe we would be at least a better off place, you know, it wouldn't fix everything,
but maybe when they understand how bills become law, they might be, you know, that's a, that's
a globalist Soros brainwashing for the kids, man.
You're probably right.
Yep.
So anyway, Alex plays this clip of the people booing because he's, uh, he loves it.
It's very weird.
Um, this is a, uh, I saw this on CNN too, so I tuned in and found the actual clip.
They were like, oh my gosh, they told them all wear their mask and they didn't and they
booed and almost no one was wearing the stupid mask.
They tried to enforce it.
Oh, this is private property.
Do it.
No, it's all a giant fraud.
It's saying, I'm not wearing your little burka, your little face diaper scumbags.
So here it is.
CPAC host booed for asking attendees to wear their muzzles.
We conservatives believe in the rule of law because we know that when the law is enforced,
our rights are protected.
Our rights are protected.
The laws of fraud.
Such a big effort to talk about the bill of rights, but I also want to mention one thing
and I know this might sound like a little bit of a downer, but we also believe in property
rights and this is a private hotel and we believe in the rule of law.
So we need to comply with the laws of this county that we're in.
There is no law.
Private hotel, just like your house gets to set its own rules.
Statement.
I am the law.
Our CPAC director.
Well, as Dan mentioned, we are in a private facility and we do want to be respectful of
the ordinances that they have as their private property.
So this woman looks like she's had a lot of vaccines in the ballroom when you're seated
or she has her soul sucked wearing a mask.
So if everybody can go ahead, work on that.
Work on that.
I know.
It's, it's not.
You'll work on that.
William Wallace, ladies and gentlemen, you have the right to set the own rules in your
own house and we're borrowing them down.
Thank you.
It's, it's just, I can't imagine having a response to that other than like, wow, that's
bummer.
Like if, even if I were somebody who was like opposed to wearing masks or being required
to, I was just like, Hey, we're, we're here.
It's the rules of the place.
Yeah.
Okay.
I understand.
All of these people should be embarrassed.
Yeah.
They should really be embarrassed because they're fucking children and it's kind of
sad.
It's not kind of sad.
It's incredibly sad.
It bums me out.
And the fact that I'm going to go home and think about how stupid they are is an even
bigger bummer to me.
Yeah.
And I think that that clip just so fully like demonstrates that behavior.
Someone gently trying to come up with an excuse for why you need to do this.
Yeah.
Trying to, it's like trying to trick kids into eating vegetables.
No, totally.
It's the idea that you would have to, somebody, a group of people got together and were like,
we've got to try and get these people to wear masks.
They're not going to listen to medical ideas.
They're not going to listen to, they don't give a shit about other people.
That person could die right now.
And if they didn't like them, they would all cheer.
Yeah.
So what do we do?
Oh, you know, these people really love property rights.
Yeah.
That's something that they're really into.
Hey guys, it's borderline.
Like you have to be, Hey, if we want to carry guns in this place, we got to wear a mask
in this place.
Those are the rules.
That would, that would might work.
Yeah.
I mean, that's about all you can do to deal with these fucking children.
But like I said, there's a little bit of a shorter episode because it's so much of just
Trump's speech and you know, whatever.
Yeah.
I'm, I feel like it is the greatest privilege in the world not to listen to him speak ever
a gun.
Yeah.
And it's, uh, there was one, there's one part where Alex was saying like, Oh, isn't this
refreshing after weeks of Biden, Oh, just so much, I was like, I don't have to disagree.
Wow.
Um, but you know, uh, I, I, I, what was the policy platform that came out of CPAC this
year?
Dan?
And avoid canceling things.
Did they do, did they, no bother with like, we want lower taxes, none of that.
Just straight up, nonstop bile and cheering.
Yeah.
Great.
I was looking at the speaker's list and it was pretty surprising.
Like, you know, you got Trump, you got Trump Jr.
Then that's like, well, don't know why Trump Jr. needs to be there anymore.
I kind of understand Trump.
You gotta appease the lunatics and what have you, but then he had like, James O'Keefe was
giving a speech.
Really?
Charlie Kirk and then Lauren Boebert.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
I was like, wow, this is, this is not subtle.
Whoa boy.
Yeah.
We are white nationalists.
Um, so we have one last clip here and it's Alex, uh, someone has found a clip of him
talking about his Rockefeller document that he calls the lockstep document, which is not,
that's not what it is.
It doesn't have anything to do with it.
Um, that lockstep is one of the four scenarios that have painted, uh, about possible ways
that technology and, uh, governance can, uh, uh, progress into the future.
Right.
Um, and it's interesting.
Someone found a clip of him talking about it back in 2010.
Did they?
Oh really?
And Alex plays this clip as if like this proves I've always been right.
Everything.
But I will make an argument on the other side of this clip that this makes things worse
for Alex.
It makes sense.
All right.
Let's end this with my prediction.
11 years ago, the lockdowns and then Owen Schroyer is coming up with Sunday live.
Please spread the word.
God bless you all.
The Alex Jones show, there is a war on for your mind.
I mean, I'm not even worthy to be bringing you information this powerful.
And I hope that you pay attention to what we cover here minute by minute because I've
had chills, uh, since last night.
This just confirms everything else we've already researched Rockefeller study and visions future
dictatorship controlled by elite millions being killed, mandatory quarantines, checkpoints,
the end of the family, everything that's in the other documents.
But this dovetails with all the other Rockefeller foundation documents about the GMO food to
sterilize you and the forced vaccines and the hell we're already living in.
This is going to continue to intensify until we take our governments back.
So I mean, it's just another headline for him at this point.
He doesn't call it operation lockstep because that wasn't the branding on it at this point.
Now here is why I think this makes things worse.
And if I were Alex, I wouldn't have played this.
He didn't keep talking about this.
It's not like it's shocking that someone was able to find a clip from 2010 of him covering
this back then when I guess it probably someone picked it up and ran with it.
Didn't have much legs.
And so people just forgot about it.
It's not like 2011, 2012, he's still talking about this document.
He completely forgets about it until Jim Fetzer starts yelling about it on his blog in 2020.
Like he doesn't, like this is, this is worse because if you actually believe, like Alex
is pretending to, that this document lays out the globalist plan, you had it and you
whiffed.
Yeah.
You dropped the ball.
Again.
Yeah.
For the millionth time.
And it's, it's astounding to me the way, the way in which he, he just like, he, he thinks
that this is a win and it's actually like, it's, it kind of raises more questions about
his process.
Yeah.
I mean, it makes him look more full of shit.
I would probably argue that the, it is really bad for him because it's basically saying
that this is, cause it's not the same document.
Yeah.
I think it is.
That he's talking about?
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
It's the same thing about goddamn near every document since 2010.
It's been 10 years and not only has he not kept talking about it, none of it has happened.
True.
So.
Ugh.
But he's a prophet.
Sure.
And he's a psychic, but he's not like a psychic psychic, everyone's a little bit psychic.
Well, everybody's a little bit psychic, it's called, uh, memory.
So I found that a little weird and one of the things that I decided that I think I want
to do is I think I want to go try and find that episode.
The 2010?
Yeah.
I think I want to go try and do that.
I think that's a good one.
Maybe we'll do that for Wednesday or something since this is a shorter episode.
Yeah.
I think that would be a good idea.
Cause I'm very curious to hear his coverage of it and compare it to the present day coverage
of this document.
I wonder if he knows what the document is back in 2010.
That would be a really good, oh yeah.
You gotta do that now.
Yeah.
You literally have no choice.
I'm getting to work on it now.
Click!
Yeah.
Um, so.
At underscore.
I, I, you know, I think this is, this is a shorter episode, but I think it's worth it
if only for the weird commercial, that commercial is fantastic.
That is the kind of thing that not only should you not accept a commercial advertising money
from that, you should denounce it.
This is the kind of thing that Ted Anderson should be forced to apologize for accepting
advertising money to air that is something that like, there would be a scandal in any
other media outlet, like getting in bed with something like this.
No, I know.
That's like, uh, that's like fucking somebody running a advertisement from Hitler in 1937
in the New York Times.
Just like straight up, Hey, well, let's kill juice.
It's it's a, it's a bit much.
Yeah.
And I would, uh, I would humbly request that Ted Anderson, uh, pull that commercial and
also apologize.
That's really the point.
And sell the network and go away forever.
That is the point of this episode, really.
Go away.
Fuck you, Ted Anderson.
Uh, but we'll be back.
I'm going to try and dig up that episode and, uh, hopefully we'll be able to put that together
for Wednesday.
Sounds like a plan.
Uh, but until then, Jordan, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yeah.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledgefight.com.
Yep.
We're also on Facebook.
And if you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work right now.
Yeah.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I am the William Wallace of masks.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.