N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledgefight, knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys, knowledgefight.
Dan and Jordan, knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding us.
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
Knowledgefight.com.
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledgefight, it's Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes.
If we're gonna mess up the pace.
We're a couple dudes, I can sit around and drink novelty beverages and talk a little
bit about Alex Jones.
Oh indeed we are Dan.
Jordan.
Dan.
Quick question.
Today Jordan is we are into the month of March and that means that it is time for Munch Madness
on the Doughboys.
I'm very excited.
There are a lot of, there's a podcast that I very much enjoy during my time off from
listening to Alex.
It's tough to find other audio entertainment that I can just sort of like, ah fun.
Sure, sure, sure, unmitigated fun.
No one hates Jews here.
No, just two guys arguing with each other.
I enjoy it and it's always fun every year whenever they have their March Madness food
tournament.
It's a Munch Madness.
That's lovely.
Is upon us.
Yep, what about you?
My Bright Spot, Dan, I was going through my iTunes listening to some music the other day
and Natalie Alford popped up and I haven't thought about her in, or not, I haven't thought
about her, but we haven't spoken since the old cupcake days.
Yeah, she's great.
She's back whenever you were allowed to go outside and I was just thinking, man, she's
so good and I want, I felt very good about that.
Everybody should check Natalie Grace Alford out.
She's fantastic.
Natalie's one of those performers who I kind of like, when I first started doing standup
all it made, I was like, what's the big deal?
But talking about how great she is, I saw her perform one night and I was like, I get
it.
Oh yeah.
She's fantastic.
She is fantastic.
And she's just such a great person to be around.
Yeah, I don't know her super well, but she was always very nice.
Oh yeah.
Loved her.
So Jordan, today we've got an interesting episode to go over.
We be time traveling, my man.
Oh no, we're in the past?
We are.
Or have we finally gone to the future?
We're going to the future.
Oh shit!
It's about time!
No, we're back in the past because on our last episode on Monday, I teased at the end
that I was going to try and find where Alex made that prediction.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
His video from 2010 where he talked about the Rockefeller document lockstep.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
And so I had to compulsively go back and find it and see what his coverage was like.
Naturally.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Man, this is going to be a whirlwind ride.
I fucking love Rockefeller.
I think this is the greatest guy in the history of the world.
Lockstep is the way to go.
I will admit that I had no idea what to expect, and I think that sometimes you fish and the
well is dry.
Sure.
Like Monday.
Mm-hmm.
It happens.
One of the reasons we're doing a Wednesday episode is because I felt very unsatisfied
putting out a 50 minute episode.
That well, very dry.
I felt like, hey, we were looking for the CPAC wrap up and we got snake eyes.
There was one sad three-eyed fish with human eyes.
No good.
Uh-uh.
This time, so many fish.
All right.
Nothing but fish.
Okay, all right.
So I'm very excited to get down to business on that, but before we do, Jordan, we're going
to take a moment to say thank you to some folks who have signed up and are supporting
the show.
Oh, that's a great idea.
So first, Harrison, but not that Harrison.
He's really trashing the brand.
I don't disagree.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Harrison.
But not that Harrison.
Yes.
Next, Horatio Kornholer.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Horatio Kornholer.
I choose to think that it's a game of bags, you know, the college game.
Did Horatio Hornblower play a lot of bags?
I don't know.
We'll see.
Next, the greatest supervillain of all time, The Hintmaster.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, The Hintmaster.
Next, Alex from Tap.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Alex.
Thank you.
Next, to all the knowledge fighters out there, thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Hey, thank you very much to all the knowledge fighters out there.
Next, for the ultimate bastard, Robert Evans.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Someone doesn't like Kid Stays in the Picture.
That doesn't sound true.
I think everybody loves Kid Stays in the Picture, dad.
Once you know more about fisting, you know you're in a good time.
I remember hearing, I think, Patton Oswalt's bit about the Kid Stays in the Picture audiobook.
I remember I was like, I don't know, probably 16, I got the audiobook of it on cassette.
I just remember it being like this giant thing of like six tapes.
It was as good as advertised.
It was very nonsensical.
What did Patton call it?
It's like the devil reading his memoirs.
I think there's a similarity.
I haven't listened to it in a long time, but anyway, also I have a technocrat here to give
a little shout out to.
Pew, pew, pew, pew.
So thank you so much.
Oh, God.
Oh, boy.
It could be Joakim.
Okay.
Or Joakim.
Could be.
Sure.
J-O-A-K-I-M.
Oh, then is that literally Joakim Noah?
No, it's not.
It's a fantastic center for the Bulls team in the early aughts whenever Derrick Rose
rode in the earth like a God among men.
It is not because this is Joakim from Denmark.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate.
That's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right, we got to go full tilt boogie on this Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Head out to Denmark.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Denmark and Joakim specifically, and if you can, I assume all Joakims know each other.
Hook me up with Joakim Noah.
Great fantastic center for the Bulls in the early aughts when Derrick wrote me.
Okay.
I feel like a friend of mine had a story about running into him at the long room.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
That bar on Irving Park.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
I seem to recall the story about that.
Number one, don't know if it's true.
Number two, don't remember the story.
How did he fit in there?
It's very long.
It's my question.
I know it's long, but he's very wide.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Again, story might not be true, and I don't remember the story.
Anyway, Jordan, on February 24th of this year, 2021, Info Wars released a video titled, quote,
video shocks the world, exclamation point.
Sure.
Alex Jones predicted COVID lockdown in 2010.
This was a three-minute clip taken from Alex's July 16th, 2010 show, and this is a little
bit rare, a little bit unconventional, but I want to play the entire thing for you because
this is going to be the launching off point for this entire episode, so it's important
that we give a fair hearing to the original source material.
Okay.
How long is this?
Three minutes and 20 seconds.
Brutal.
Sorry.
All right.
Let's do it.
The Alex Jones Show.
There is a war on for your mind.
I mean, I'm not even worthy to be bringing you information this powerful, and I hope
that you pay attention to what we cover here minute by minute because I've had chills since
last night.
This just confirms everything else we've already researched.
A Rockefeller study envisions future dictatorship controlled by elite, millions being killed,
mandatory quarantines, checkpoints, the end of the family, everything that's in the other
documents, but this dovetails with all the other Rockefeller Foundation documents about
the GMO food to sterilize you and force vaccines and the hell we're already living in.
This is going to continue to intensify until we take our governments back from these eugenics
madmen.
But that story is up on prisonplanet.com.
The question is, will you have the courage to really do the research yourself?
Because I don't want you to just sit here and hear me make these claims.
These people are so arrogant that they write policy papers, so many of them that they're
producing these policy papers and reports and white papers so fast that you could never
read them all.
It is an open conspiracy against you and your family.
I pray to God.
I pray to my Heavenly Father Jesus Christ every night to give me strength and the will
to be able to face this harm and to give me the strength to carry on because I know why
a lot of you don't want to look at this information and just want to comment on the YouTube videos
or on message boards that I'm a liar.
I know why because it's scary.
You're not going to be able to go to the ball games anymore.
You're not going to be able to just go out and get drunk with your friends.
You're not going to be able to just go out and enjoy yourself all the time.
The only chance we've got of beating the scientific dictatorship, this creeping death that takes
its time to incrementally enslave you mentally, psychologically, physically, spiritually,
the only way to defeat it is for the rank and file of this planet to realize that you
have a choice to make on what your destiny is going to be.
Once you face this information, once you consciously admitted it to yourself, it will take over
your life.
It should take over your life.
I mean, what else?
What else could it do?
We've got to get past the artificial stigma that the control corporate media has been
putting out for decades ahead of their open unveiling of planetary dictatorship.
They all talk about how we need a police state to carry this out.
Canada and the United States are going to work in lockstep, display the seriousness
of our commitment at both home and abroad.
One loser draw, you need to choose a sign.
InfoWars, tomorrow's news today.
Winter Sun Plus is the highest grade vitamin B3 you're going to find with vitamin K for
your immune system for overall well being.
There is an ad at the end.
Dan, you son of a bitch.
You knew there was an ad at the end.
Of course.
So when I heard that video, the first thing that stuck out to me was the quick cuts.
That seems strange to me, and it made me suspect that Alex in 2010 might not have been talking
about exactly what he wants people in 2021 to think he was talking about.
Yeah, I mean, you leave some things out, some details here and there.
Nobody needs to know.
The second thing that caught my ear was how vague and almost formulaic this coverage of
the Rockefeller document was back in 2010.
Was this really as deep as Alex got into the document that supposedly demonstrates and
outlines the globalists' evil plans?
Is this in any way believable, that if he considered this document to be anything even
close to that, that he wasn't able to find a clip of him that has more oomph than what
we just heard?
That was soft.
Yeah, that was a big load of nothing.
Yeah.
This all didn't sit right with me.
This was apparently a video that shocked the world.
This is supposed to be Alex dropping the mic and proving that he was always on the operation
lockstep tip, and thus you should totally listen to him about everything he's saying
now because it's all going to come true in the future.
That's the underlying argument that's being made by this video, and it felt dishonest
to me.
Surprise.
Yeah.
I wanted to understand the larger context, so I went back to this, and let me spoil this
a little bit.
My suspicions were not unfounded.
To give some background about what was going on around this time, if you're listening to
Alex's show, the only real-world actual headline is that the Deepwater Horizon oil spill was
ongoing.
And BP had announced the day prior to this episode that they had successfully capped
the spill, which represented significant progress towards resolving the whole situation.
Sure, sure, sure.
Alex also mentions a car bombing in Mexico that was carried out by cartels, but he doesn't
really dwell on the story much.
Outside of that, I'm not sure we get much else in the way of news.
You know who else predicted a pandemic in 2010?
That would be the CDC when they made a plan for how to deal with a pandemic that wasn't
really important until, say, a certain time period whenever it was ignored, and hopefully...
Yeah.
If I'm not much mistaken, the CDC constantly predicts...
It's basically their job.
To plan for things that are going to happen.
So here we get to...
We're starting here on July 16th, 2010, which is the day that all that is taken from for
Alex's very moodily scored...
So here's the beginning of the show, Alex dropping his lead story.
And I have all the vital stacks of news and information here in front of me that we're
going to be covering.
BP claims for the first time in 80 plus days that they have stopped the leak.
And I pray that they're not lying, because they've said this at least three times that
I can remember in the last 87 plus days.
So we'll be breaking that down.
That alone is weird to me.
First of all, his lead story is the BP oil spill on the day that he's supposedly breaking
these documents.
Yeah, well, I mean, the eventual destruction of the family and quarantines and killing
of all the people, that's second rate.
But the other thing that I think is super weird about that clip is the way that Alex
seems to be willing to give BP the benefit of the doubt about whether or not they'd sealed
the leak.
Well, I mean, BP's leak happening makes oil prices go down, right?
And he prefers oil.
Alex has sources, he has documents, he knows everything, he's kind of psychic.
He doesn't will see it.
That is fair.
He doesn't do that.
Very weird.
I certainly hope that this oil company isn't lying.
He accuses everyone of lying.
Well, come on.
You gotta give BP the benefit of the doubt.
That was weird as hell.
British petroleum is one word away from British Israelism, Dan, and that's basically what
he's going for.
So Alex does get to the Rockefeller document pretty quick.
It is the second headline that he's got, although I'm not sure he's read it.
I'm not sure he knows much about it.
I was here in the office last night when Aaron Dykes and I were doing research for the full
spectrum dominance eugenics film that we are working on that deals with chemtrails and
other issues.
And we have come across so much more information than our awareness of the globalist master
plan is growing exponentially.
Don't think that you ever know everything.
The more we learn, the more horrified we get to discover that things are far worse than
we originally thought.
So I sent the Rockefeller Foundation document over to Paul Watson.
He wrote a story about it this morning and just everything we talk about here, the magnitude
is off the chart.
I mean, I'm not even worthy to be bringing you information this powerful.
And I hope that you pay attention to what we cover here minute by minute because I've
had chills since last night.
This just confirms everything else we've already researched.
But Rockefeller study envisions future dictatorship controlled by elite, millions being killed,
mandatory quarantines, checkpoints, the end of the family, everything that's in the other
documents.
But this dovetails with all the other Rockefeller Foundation documents about the GMO food to
sterilize you and the forced vaccines and the hell we're already living in.
That's just going to continue to intensify until we take our governments back from these
eugenics madmen.
But that story is up on prison planet dot com.
This is about as deep as he gets.
That's not much.
Well, it's up on prison planet dot com, Dan.
Paul wrote a story.
Fixed it.
Alex is just reading off a headline from an article that Paul Joseph Watson wrote.
And everything that in the present day Alex is trying to pass off as his prediction is
actually just him reading from Paul's outrageously bad opinion piece.
Oh, no, Dan.
He was the one who told Paul that he needed to write an article about something.
But then it was Aaron Dyke who found it.
Well, you know.
That line, quote, global pandemics that kill millions, mandatory quarantines, checkpoints,
biometric ID cards, and a world of top down government control that's in Alex's sizzle
reel in the present.
That's just the first line of Paul's article.
So if anything, Alex should be saying that Paul predicted all the stuff that's happening
now and Alex read it and then took credit for it.
Yeah, I don't think Alex will be doing that.
Nope.
And that being said, Paul's article is not a prediction of anything.
It's just the same kind of trash coverage of this Rockefeller document that we've seen
11 years later just happening in 2010 and being quickly forgotten, even by the people
who pushed it as a conspiracy.
The article lays out that this is a scenario, you know, it admits that, that this is a scenario
that's being depicted in the document titled Scenarios for the Future of Technology and
International Development.
And Paul even notes that it's one of four scenarios that are included in the document.
Okay.
He then describes the scenario titled Lockstep in exhaustive detail, ignoring the other scenarios
or the point of the document at all.
Don't worry about it.
The conclusion of this article is absolutely unearned and completely unsupported by the
underlying evidence.
Sure.
Quote, the Rockefeller study is not a warning against preventing the kind of tyranny contained
in the scenario from unfolding.
It's a blueprint for how globalists want to exploit global crises like bioterror attacks
and pandemics in order to completely destroy society and rebuild it under a new world order
in their image.
It's crystal clear from reading the Lockstep scenario that the oppressive society portrayed
in the study is not presented as an admonishment of how governments would cynically seize upon
a pandemic to set up a police state and empower themselves as dictators.
It's a ringing endorsement that this approach would be the correct thing to do.
Dan, I've been holding my hand up.
You have.
You have me?
Yes, Jordan.
I have a quick question.
Why?
Because Paul thinks so.
Oh, okay.
Well, now that I've got that.
He said it is not a document predicting or like meant to prevent or warning.
But then he just said, because it's not, he didn't say why.
No, of course not.
These conclusions are not sensible to arrive at from reading the document unless you went
into it with those conclusions already in mind and you were just looking for anything
you could find to justify your narratives.
That entire blurb that I read you there from Paul's article, it's completely dismissible
by just reminding yourself that everything he's saying is his opinion.
It's not fact and it's not even coherent analysis.
The real tell here is how it's a completely ignoring the other three scenarios in the
document.
How come the conspiracy isn't that the globalists are secretly trying to reveal that they're
trying to usher in a world depicted by the clever together scenario where quote, pharmaceutical
giants release thousands of drug compounds shown to be effective against diseases like
malaria to the public domain as part of an open innovation agenda.
They also opened their archives of research and development on neglected diseases deemed
not commercially viable, offering seed funding to scientists who wanted to carry the research
forward.
Why isn't that the conspiracy that's in the document?
I will argue because in that world, zinc sales are down.
Yeah.
This scenario isn't used or even mentioned because it doesn't depict the kind of vibe
that Alex has spent his career making his audience scared about.
The four scenarios in this document are equally likely, as is a completely different future
that wasn't captured by the two variable exercise of this study, but the only one that matters
to Infowars is the one that paints the dystopian hellscape they make money by convincing listeners
is right around the corner.
If Alex and Paul wanted to fear monger about this document responsibly, they have an obligation
to answer one very basic question, which they refuse to in the past or in the present, which
is what is different about the lockstep scenario that makes it the globalist secret plan, whereas
the other three aren't.
Well, it's in the other d- because GMOs?
Sure.
Vac- vaccines, Dan.
They're gonna- cows?
It seems kind of like an arbitrary choice that you make, because that's the one that
appeals to you and you think is profitable.
Yeah, probably.
That would make sense.
Profit motive does seem to encompass most of all the things we talk about.
So they're gonna kill us.
Sure.
That's basically-
Yeah, that sounds about right.
It's always been.
Yeah.
DNA has been altered to also cause sterilization.
I mean, they're hitting us on so many fronts, and I've got all the government reports admitting
that the births, year by year, they're studying that human DNA is being damaged at a level
never before seen.
We are being mutated, and many of us that are able to even think and operate today,
our children, their children, and the children after them are gonna be deformed monsters
who are literally drooling basket cases.
Sure.
But of course, that will never even get to that point.
They plan to exterminate all of us long before then.
Oh, that's nice of them.
It's just an absolute fact.
And why do we have to sit here and fight with each other?
Government bureaucrats, police, military, everybody?
I mean, we're all in this together.
It's a tiny elite, less than 6,000 globalists in their own analysis that rule the planet.
And look, I'm gonna get into all the news coming up in your phone calls today.
It's just, this is so horrible.
They're collapsing the economy so they can take control of us through the government
healthcare system and soft kill us.
Ooh, oh boy.
Took a turn.
Well, this is like, this reminds me of the Heaven's Gate cult now, just on account of
like, I'm worried that we, like that argument, sure, we don't want them to kill all of us,
but on the other hand, if we all killed ourselves, that would take away their satisfaction, right?
Yeah, that would stick it to the devil.
Yeah, they'd be really bummed about that.
Yeah, also this 6,000, why doesn't the devil just give more peeps?
Oh no, you can only really devil it up with 6,000 at a time.
Is the devil behind this or not at this point in 2010?
Because it doesn't feel like it, it feels like it's an administrative plan.
Fair, fair, fair.
But I will say that we do know that the globalist plans are ten years behind, and here we are,
ten years later.
It just has the vibe of like, definitely being a mortal plan.
A little bit, yeah, yeah a little bit.
Different vibe.
What's the devil get out of this?
I don't know.
Anyway, Aaron Dykes was the one who found the document and brought it to Alex's attention
so he sent it across the pond.
Which is why Alex is a psychic who predicted everything now.
Yes.
Now, here's a little bit about Aaron Dykes and how he found his way to Infowars.
There are so many of these reports that Aaron Dykes only ate it by coffee.
What?
Many days will not sleep and I have to make him go home after two days of being up here.
This is somebody I hired right out of the University of Texas five years ago who didn't
really believe in what I was doing, who didn't really buy what I was saying and kind of laughed
when I hired him.
That's exactly who I wanted to hire.
I wanted him to see it.
And he'd gone to, you know, the UT public relations school, you know, he had very good
grades.
When he graduated, he was very intelligent.
And I said, you are going to see the dark side.
Hire me, you coward.
Wow.
If you really want someone who doesn't believe you, I have got a candidate for the position.
And that's me.
I don't think, I don't think Alex could afford me at this point, but no, no, no, no, no.
I do like that idea of like, I wanted to find somebody.
I want the most skeptical person.
I want somebody who thinks they can see through all of my bullshit.
And then I'm going to show them the truth.
Which is that we make a lot of money here and you can make some too.
Integrity is for losers.
I hired him out of public relations school because journalism school was not where I
find people to work at Infowars.
Nope.
Usually contests is how I find people.
So Alex, Alex is like, there's so much proof, man, or just so much proof of things.
These people are so arrogant that they write policy papers.
So many of them that they're producing these policy papers and reports and white papers
so fast, so fast, so furious that you could never read them all.
A group of just two or three people here in my office that research this, we could never
read them all.
It is warehouses full of it.
It is an open conspiracy against you and your family.
If there are in fact warehouses full of the proof of Alex's conspiracy theories, then
I would suggest he start by producing one piece of that proof because everything he's
pointed to so far in my experience has been bullshit.
John P. Holdren's eco science book doesn't advocate sterilizing people through adding
stuff to the water.
This Rockefeller document doesn't lay out a master plan to bring in a dictatorship through
a pandemic.
The Club of Rome's publications don't prove that they made up climate change.
Every single specific I've ever heard Alex mention doesn't say what he claims it does.
There is a warehouse.
It's just a warehouse that's full of books and publications that Alex has never read
or can't understand, and he's just using them as props to justify and support his flimsy
facade of dumb theories.
I'm going to argue that rather than a warehouse, maybe five gigs of a Google Drive.
Maybe.
No, because he used to print everything out.
It's physical.
Well, that's fair.
That's fair.
It's got to be a filing cabinet or two.
I hope they have a shredder.
That's how important the stuff they print out is.
We got to get rid of this the moment Alex prints out a tweet.
I can't be caught with this.
No, no, no.
Too dangerous.
Too many stacks.
So as I was listening to this episode, I heard one of the parts of Alex's 2021 prediction
montage clip that shocked the world, and I noticed something really suspicious about
how his words were presented.
Here's how this appears in the overly dramatic current day clip.
I pray to God.
I pray to my Heavenly Father, Jesus Christ, every night to give me the strength and the
will to be able to face this harm and to give me the strength to carry on, because I know
why a lot of you don't want to look at this information and just want to comment on the
YouTube videos or on message boards, and I'm a liar.
I know why, because it's scary.
You're not going to be able to go to the ball games anymore.
You're not going to be able to just go out and get drunk with your friends.
You're not going to be able to just go out and enjoy yourself all the time.
That sounds kind of prophetic.
Alex is saying that we won't be able to go to ball games or get drunk with our friends
at the bar, and that's exactly like what happened because of coronavirus safety measures.
The intention of this clip is to give the audience that impression, that Alex is predicting
social lockdown, which, if you haven't forgotten, is kind of the title of this video.
Sure.
So, there's a huge problem, though, and there's a slight edit that whoever made this clip
did that changes the entire meaning of Alex's words.
Do you mean when he said that they were going to nuke us and that's why we couldn't go to
ball games anymore?
No, that's from another show.
Gotcha.
I pray to God.
I pray to my Heavenly Father Jesus Christ every night to give me the strength and the
will to be able to face this horror and to give me the strength to carry on, because
I know why a lot of you don't want to look at this information and just want to comment
on the YouTube videos or on message boards that I'm a liar.
I know why, because it's scary.
And if you admit this to yourself, you're not going to be able to go to the ball games
anymore.
You're not going to be able to just go out and get drunk with your friends.
You're not going to be able to just, you know, go out and enjoy yourself all the time and
not spend some of your energy on resisting this shady, you lying piece of shit.
Shady as hell.
You motherfucking liar.
Yeah.
You are saying that if you are available to learn this information, that information will
so dominate you, you won't be able to go to ball games.
Motherfucking liar!
Liar!
I have a paragraph written, but I think you expressed it just about as well as I could.
Yeah, that was really shocking to me.
I was like, wow, what a difference a couple of words make.
Yeah, sure does.
Sure does make a big difference, doesn't it?
Really puts everything into it.
Put that back in your fucking sizzle reel, you son of a...
Yeah, it's not fair.
Fuck off.
The cutting out of those words completely alters the point of what Alex is saying, and
it makes those images of not being able to go to the ball game or bars anymore, you know,
it makes, when you cut it out, it seems like they're independent thoughts from everything
else that he's saying, as opposed to the then part of an if-then statement.
You got it.
This is intensely dishonest, and whoever edited this clip together took those words out because
they knew that in their original form, they don't really work to make Alex sound like
he made an amazing prediction.
But if you chop them off, it looks like he might have been onto something.
Using this cheesy score and making selective edits like this, the person who put this together
is able to transform something pretty meaningless and standard from Alex's show into something
that looks like a fairly specific prediction about stuff that would happen a decade later.
They do this because they know they can get away with it.
Anyone who's susceptible for falling for Alex's shit is probably not going to be the sort
of person who goes back to look at his 2010 episode to see if he was actually making a
prediction back then, so this is a safe game of exploitation and manipulation that Alex
is free to play, and man, it's just transparent.
Dan, frankly, at this point, I would argue, you're literally the only person who would
go back and find the episode that Alex said that and kick ass.
Well, I was curious.
Of course you are.
You know, because you hear that, it's like you can't go to the ball games anymore.
It's like, well, I mean, like, if you really did say that, I still don't think it means
anything.
No, it's not because he knows anything about it.
But it would be, yeah, you're right.
It would be interesting.
You're right, it would be interesting.
Going back and hearing that, I mean, I do it for your reaction.
That reaction is why I do it.
That's why you play the game.
I want to throw a baseball at him.
I want to throw a baseball right at his head.
Happy spring training of baseball to the brain.
Jesus Christ.
That is unacceptable behavior.
I was sitting alone in my room when I heard that, and I said, you asshole.
Do you know what the problem is?
He takes himself out of context in the clips.
That's the problem.
The problem is the Infowars media takes Alex Jones out of context.
Yeah, it's not fair.
So Alex gets to complaining about Obamacare and what have you, and he's like, hey, man,
they're going to try and tell you you can't eat foods and stuff, and oh, no, it's no good.
Tracking how much you weigh.
They're already doing that through the schools to then tax you if you're overweight.
They admit they're now going to do that and say what you can put in a child's Happy Meal.
Oh, it's okay for McDonald's to put silicone in the food.
That's CNN, a petrochemical, extremely poisonous, illegal in England and other countries, but
you can't put a toy in there.
See, it's all about control.
It's not so much that McDonald's puts silicone in their food, which is the impression that
Alex is trying to give the audience.
It's that McDonald's uses silicone in the preparation of their food.
You can find this information on McDonald's own website, that they use dimethyl polysiloxane
in the oil that they use to fry French fries.
What a great place to hide that information.
Right on their website.
No one would ever look there.
So the reason for this is because it's a food-grade anti-foaming agent, which prevents the oil
from bubbling up and burning employees.
Anyone who's worked in fast food knows that getting that oil on you is no joke, and with
the high incidence of younger employees at places like McDonald's, it's really important
as a safety measure to do what you can to limit the possibility of people getting oil
all over themselves.
Totally.
It sucks.
I'm putting a little oil on myself back in my fry-making days.
Yeah.
Aw, it hurts so fucking bad.
Alex can't prove that this chemical is dangerous to people.
And actually, interestingly, in 2018, MLive reported that, quote, scientists at Yokohama
National University in Japan say that a chemical added to the oil to cook McDonald's French
fries could help cure baldness in humans.
That's right.
Some early-stage testing has shown that dimethyl polysiloxane was used to, quote, aid the growth
of black hair on the back and scalp of mice.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
So, Alex, it's his own fault he's losing his hair.
Of course, because people are kind of dumb, after this news broke, these Japanese scientists
had to come out and clarify that eating McDonald's fries would not help you grow back hair.
It doesn't do that.
Of course not.
It's not the same.
Yeah.
Their lead researcher, Junji Fukada, told writers, quote, no matter how many fried potatoes
you eat, you'll never grow more hair.
That's a total misunderstanding that's gone viral.
It's so sad that scientists have to take time out of their day to say stuff like that.
Oh, boy.
So, Alex does stuff like this all the time.
He'll say something like, McDonald's puts silicone in their food, and then do nothing
more to examine the claim or help his audience understand what it even means.
If you just listened to Alex, you'd be, you know, it would be equally easy to conclude
that McDonald's is using this chemical in the oil as an anti-foaming agent as it would
be to believe that their Big Macs are half breast implant.
Right.
Right, right, right.
It just leaves you just treading water.
Yeah.
I mean, the worst part of that is we are a little bit conditioned so much to that type
of processed food that there's, it's almost borderline reasonable to be like, yeah, I
can see McDonald's putting silicone in their food.
I mean, it is.
We get so much, I'm not saying that it's a good idea or that I, you know, all that stuff,
but it is.
And I'm not, I'm not blanket defending use of all kinds of chemicals and stuff.
No, of course not.
It's a very different conversation from like what you're just sort of out of nowhere brain
would pull up if you're thinking about silicone, you're thinking of like plastic, basically,
as opposed to something that is a food grade anti-foaming agent for the oil.
No, he's, he's taking advantage of the fact that evil shady corporations are tend to tend
to be evil and shady.
And he's taking advantage of the fact that his audience does not demand any kind of specificity
out of them.
Why would they?
Yeah.
Why not BP?
Sure.
Why not?
This is so weird.
Coming up also BP says they've stopped the oil leak in the Gulf of Mexico, but we've
got screenshots of their cameras down there and it looks like there may be some hanky
panky going on, but we are looking into it right now and working on that.
But if this is true, praise God, this is certainly wonderful news.
Why are you still taking a wait and see approach?
You claim to have evidence that indicates there's hanky panky going on and you're still
trusting an oil company.
He's got money.
He's got money in oil.
I don't know.
He's got to have something behind it.
I don't know if it's that.
I just think it, I don't, I don't know, but it's weird.
That's very weird.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, we've seen some screenshots that show something weird is happening, but
you know, I think in this one situation I'm going to last the corporation.
I'm pretty sure that escape pod is filled with nobody.
There's nobody in there.
We don't need to fire a laser to blow up that escape pod.
Isn't this company that, uh, you know, spilled millions of tons of oil into the water.
They tell us that it's all good, but I saw some evidence.
There might be some goofing around, you know, might be some chicanery down there to say
that this, this massive oil spill, this ecological disaster, I'm going to just go ahead and trust
that they're, they're all, they're above board up to human hair.
We all make mistakes.
So one of the things I think is pretty interesting about going back to this time frame is like
when Alex says he's going to go to calls a lot of the time he does, like it's, it, it
seems more consistent that he'll get to calls and he'll take some calls and then jump back
to just doing the show and then take some more calls.
It has more of the feel of like an actual radio show back then.
And so he goes to some calls as opposed to maybe somebody who's abused, uh, amphetamines
for a few years.
Yeah.
So this first caller brings up that like, Hey, you know, finding out about all this
stuff about the evil folks who run the world and all that kind of makes it tough for me
to be happy.
Alex does not seem concerned.
You hit on a talking point that, that, uh, not a lot of times people will bring up and
what you had mentioned this morning earlier before, uh, I got through to talk to you was
about how once you obtain this information and the truth, basically how much it does
change your outlook on how you value your life.
And then I can honestly say it, my life hasn't been the same.
And sometimes I, you know, and I, I might even be asking for some advice here, buddy,
but sometimes it's really hard to find some balance and to try to even maintain a reasonable
amount of what I got given right by the constitution that, uh, you know, that just, you know, my
right to be happy.
Well, listen, listen, listen, Tim, we got out of balance.
Thomas Jefferson, George Washington, Thomas Payne, Patrick Henry, they all said, you must
guard the jewel of Liberty.
You must do everything you can in its defense.
It is, you know, the, of the prime importance, even if you struggle to keep freedom, you're
probably going to lose it and, and, and you will go into bondage and the worst elements
of society will take over.
And so we've gotten out of balance as a society becoming decadent, fat and happy.
So the evil crept in.
Now we're going back into bondage.
The blessings of Liberty we're now losing.
And so, uh, what did Barry Goldwater say?
Extremism and defensive Liberty is no vice.
Uh, there, there is no such thing as being out of balance.
That's all folks.
And by my underwear, my antsy pants, um, yeah, I think that this caller is expressing that
like, Hey, this stuff is really like, you scare me a lot and it's not pleasant.
Hey, you've whipped me into a constant state of fear and my adrenaline is always pumping,
which makes me feel bad.
Yeah.
And Alex is like, you're fine.
Come on.
What are you doing?
Chill out.
They're going to kill all of us, but it's like a while.
So he wants to give this dude a little bit more kind of advice and a little bit of, uh,
like when I'm with my family, when I'm out there fishing with the kids, you know, like
I'm thinking about fighting the globalist, but I'm also enjoying this because that's
why I'm fighting the globalist.
That kind of thing.
He won't be able to go to ball games.
I mean, you can take your kids to ball games cause that's why you're fighting.
You got to integrate the enjoyment of family time with your passion to fight.
Not yet the devil soon to be the devil.
Right.
And then this caller flips the script and changes the game.
Okay.
What's interesting is 10 years ago, you know, I've been married for almost nine, but, but
you know, 10 years ago, even six, seven years ago, I would still see a beautiful woman in
a grocery store and lust.
I would still, uh, you know, uh, be, I have a lot of flesh and now almost all of that
is burned away.
I mean, I'm attracted to my wife, but still my drive states are fully survival, warn people
deal with this, you know, protect my children and anything else, Tim?
Yeah.
And just a couple of real quick things here is, uh, you know, uh, you were talking about,
you know, uh, what people look at as important to these days.
And when I crack open my Yahoo page, which is my homepage, uh, they have this thing called
trending now and you'll see stuff like Lindsay Lohan, American idol, uh, raw wrestling, dancing
the stars.
And then the sixth thing at the end of the very last article, guess what it was, BP oil
spill.
That's what kind of priorities our country has these days.
That's a great point is, uh, what is that trend you're looking at Google trends or what
is it?
No, you know, it's, uh, on my, on my Yahoo, uh, I don't have a Yahoo, I've meant to write
a story about that.
Uh, I'm gonna talk when we come back.
Great points, Tim.
God bless you.
No time.
I just had a thought.
All right.
Also, uh, Alex is a couple of years away from divorce at this point.
Yeah.
Um, so it's too bad that he had all the lust burned out of him by this point.
You know, the internet, like the way that he described that, that reminds me so much
of the way that Douglas Adams described the babble fish, whereas like finally everyone
in the universe was able to communicate with each other and that caused more and bloodier
wars than ever in the past, you know, where it's like, Oh no, maybe it was a bad idea.
Just like universal communication.
Yeah.
The internet is fucking, it's probably bad.
Well, I don't know.
I don't know if the internet is bad, but it does definitely at very least expose some
parts of our behaviors and our patterns that maybe we wouldn't have been aware of otherwise.
Yeah.
Um, certainly trolling, uh, becomes a bit more noticeable, shitty as hell.
Um, and then also like the phenomenon that this dude's talking about with like things
like American Idol, WWE wrestling, they're trending, whereas something like the BP oil
spill isn't.
And it's like, well, yeah, that's people's attention.
The internet is the opiate of the masses.
I don't know what to tell you.
I don't know.
We're trying to feel comforted.
We have Obama in the white house.
Everybody's still like, maybe we won't have an evil president.
It was good times.
So Alex had something trigger in his brain because of what that guy said about his Yahoo
feed.
And he has come up with a plan.
And you'll see how it's a news item.
Normally they kind of feedback loop it and feed into it when it's Lindsay Lohan, uh,
or when it's, uh, something like, uh, the scandal of Mel Gibson, the media hypes that,
Hey, look, you know, the number one trend is Facebook or Chubacombra or Mel Gibson or
Kelly Osborn.
And the BP oil spill is way down the line.
Unemployment extension 2010 is number 15 on Yahoo trends.
Are you for or against it?
That should be number one, lead and mercury in our children's juice drinks and chips and
food and soft drinks.
That's all admitted.
Your children are drinking this in mass.
That should be the top trend.
Now what if we actually gamed their corrupt system?
What if every listener of this show today and tomorrow and on Sunday and Monday typed
the Obama deception into Yahoo and into Google search engines?
What have you did it over and over and over and over and over and over and over again?
That would put the Obama deception links to the video for people to watch it for free.
That would put links to that at the top of Google and at the top of Yahoo and tens of
millions more would see it.
This guy's a goddamn genius.
If every one of my listeners would buy one share of stock in, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's Bill Cooper all over the place.
But in like a minute, Alex has laid out a case for his audience to do something completely
nonsensical to solve a non-existent problem.
He is a genius of marketing.
The supposed problem here is that the news about the BP oil spill is not higher than
on the internet trending list.
This is an outrage when the top trends are about trivial matters like celebrities or
cryptids.
You can easily see how this is an easy argument to get people to agree with.
The oil spill is probably more important than pop stories, but this isn't a problem.
It's just kind of a statement about what attracts people's attention.
The oil spill began three months prior, so headlines about it might not have been all
that exciting to people.
And just a few days before this, Lindsay Lohan had been sentenced to 90 days in jail for
violating her probation.
And I believe Mel Gibson was in the news for, yeah, that racist ass rant.
I remember, I remember that.
This was not the time he got pulled over.
Yeah.
This was the other time.
Yeah, it's good that he still has a career.
It's fine to say that the BP oil spill is maybe a larger story for more people, but
it's ridiculous to complain about the public paying attention to those stories.
They were pretty serious stories.
You think the BP oil spill should be higher.
Well, here's what we do tomorrow.
Make something else news.
Right.
So Alex lays out his supposed problem, which is caused by some vague idea about how the
algorithm searches work.
And then the solution is that everybody needs to search for the Obama deception to push
that movie to the top of all search engine results.
This makes no sense, but it feels like it does to Alex's audience because they've
been trained to equate promoting info wars with engaging in activism.
They've been conditioned to believe that it's possible that if the Obama deception gets
seen by millions more people, maybe it'll have an impact on getting people to pay more
attention to oil spills and less to celebrity gossip.
The sleight of hand you see in this clip is phenomenal, and it really represents the bleak
underbelly of what Alex's world is always about.
The only solutions that are ever really offered are those that directly profit Alex.
The solution to the collapsing economy is to buy gold from Alex's sponsor, Ted Anderson.
The solution to the coming societal collapse is to buy survival food from Alex's sponsor,
My Patriot Supply.
The solution to COVID-19 and every other health condition is just to use Alex's supplements.
The solution to people not paying enough attention to the Deepwater Horizon oil spill apparently
is to try and trick search engines into thinking Alex's movie is more popular than it actually
is, so it's fooled into recommending it to more people.
Yeah, that sounds correct.
It's evil.
And looking back on this, it's painfully transparent to see what Alex is doing.
It's very bad.
But I do have a hard time not recognizing that it is a great marketing strategy.
Ugh.
Yeah.
I also enjoyed that as Alex was talking, like as soon as he said the Obama deception the
first time, you rolled your eyes and just shook your head.
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah.
So that's his big plan.
And see, this is a serious plan.
He spends a half hour talking about it.
Really?
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay.
And like, hey, look.
Look.
Sure.
We'll do the Obama deception first.
And then later we can do it with other things.
Okay.
What if you all right now went to a search engine box.
Let's show people live on TV.
Radio listeners could just go to Google, go to Yahoo, go to the biggest search engines
and type in the Obama deception.
The Obama deception.
Type in the Obama deception.
This'll probably work.
It'll probably push it into the top trends, maybe even number one.
And the next week I can put out a viral video, say on genetic engineering, causing DNA damage.
We can create a simple term for people to search.
And then millions of new people because of that information warfare tool will see it.
I like this technique that is sort of like that Steve Martin, one for the studios, one
for me kind of movie thing.
It's like, all right, this first one is just going to be promoting my shit.
And then the second time I'll do it about some topic that we want to draw attention
to.
What I want to do is kind of a ladder attack, okay?
Just get my name trending first and then I'll put out content to go viral.
See?
It's great.
And to be clear, Alex has done this kind of thing earlier in his career as well with
Google search terms and stuff.
It's not a new strategy for him, but it is tremendously desperate and weird the way he's
acting.
This one's terrible.
Yeah, this one's bad.
Yeah.
So Alex won, right?
Sure.
When there was an even playing field, Alex won.
His stuff was the most popular.
Everybody knows it.
Shut up.
Everyone knows it.
Okay.
So the globalists cheated.
Oh, okay.
So now Alex has to cheat so they can't cheat.
Okay.
It's complicated, but I just had this clip because Alex is really accepting and admitting
that what he's doing is cheating.
We've won on the level playing field, so they cheat.
So before they start cheating this system, we need to game their system right now.
Yeah, we got to game it.
We got to cheat that system in order to make sure they can't cheat again.
We cheat first in order to stop their cheating.
No, because they cheated before the level playing field.
They cheated before the level playing field when he was the most popular radio show on
the planet.
Yes.
So I want to stress to you, and I hope that stammering really drove home the point.
He talks about this for a long time.
Oh, boy.
It's a long time.
So we're not going to listen to a ton more clips of it because he does jump off to another
topic and that is that Pearl Harbor was a false flag.
Okay.
And it's now declassified.
The US had broken the Japanese purple and blue code and knew exactly what they were
going to do weeks before.
It took weeks for that task force to steam from Japan into that area of the Pacific.
That's way across the Pacific.
If you look at the map, here's Japan, here's Hawaii, here's the West Coast of the United
States.
They had to come all the way and the aircraft and the US submarines and all the islands
we control, they all knew they were coming and they were ordered to stand down and die.
Whoa.
Can't prove any of that.
Ooh, that's a big one.
We've talked a bit about his Pearl Harbor conspiracies in the past, but I just wanted
to play that as just to represent that he spends a while on that topic.
Now he goes back to calls because he has made his point that everyone needs to get to typing
in their search engines.
Of course.
And he gets a call from a guy named Angel Eyes.
Okay.
Who scares me.
I'm listening.
Let's talk to Angel Eyes in Texas here on the air.
You got me.
How you doing, Bulldog?
Pretty good.
Okay.
You know, Angel Eyes is because I think my eyes see what other people don't.
You're freaking me out, Angel Eyes.
That's not good.
Sir?
How you doing, Bulldog?
All right.
Maybe if it's 3 a.m. at a bar and I don't want to go home, if somebody starts with,
I'm Angel Eyes because I think I can see, I'm like, hey, maybe I'm listening.
I'll ask one follow-up.
Any time before that.
I can always leave, man.
I think I'm going to start our episodes now with, hey, what's going on, Bulldog?
Yeah.
That's a little bit of a charming way to greet me.
Sure.
Angel Eyes has some interesting memories that he wants to try and run by, Alex.
Okay.
I called you about a month ago in regards to the interview with Chandra Levy's aunt
with Barbara Walters about Chandra called her a week before she disappeared and said
something big is fixing to happen in America and I can't tell you about it.
You put out the flag that if anybody had a recording of that, could they send it to you?
I doubt anybody would have it.
That was like 10 years ago that happened.
I wonder, could you find out who Chandra Levy's aunt is and interview her if she hasn't disappeared
or, you know, died mysteriously yet?
So you're saying you saw Chandra Levy, the intern that was killed right before 9-11.
You're saying that she said something big is about to happen, but I can't tell you.
And you're saying you saw her say that on what show?
On Barbara Walters, I believe it was Barbara Walters.
It may have been like Leslie Stahl or one of those global reporters, but...
Does not spare the details here.
So Chandra Levy's aunt is named Linda Zamsky and the interview that she gave back in 2001
and her statement about her niece's disappearance were widely reported at the time in every
outlet you can imagine.
It would be the easiest thing in the world for this caller to have just googled Chandra
Levy's aunt and found articles explaining this, which kind of illustrates where his
memory has failed him.
The aunt didn't say that Chandra had said that there was something big that was going
to happen in America, as Angel Eyes is reporting to Alex.
According to the Washington Post, quote, on April 29th, the day before Levy was last seen,
Levy left a message on Zamsky's voicemail.
Zamsky would never hear from her niece again.
Quote, hi, Linda, it's Chandra, my internship is over, Levy said in the message.
I'm planning on packing my bags in the next week or ten days, heading home for a while,
don't know what I'm going to do this summer, and I really have some big news or something
important to tell, call me.
The article goes on to say, quote, Zamsky said yesterday she did not know what Levy
was referring to, but added that the 24-year-old did not seem upset.
According to Zamsky, she was Chandra's confidant about her relationship with then-Representative
Gary Condit, so taken in its proper context, as delivered by Zamsky, you could use this
comment to speculate that maybe Chandra had some news about a change in her relationship
with Condit?
Sure.
But that's not the context that Angel Eyes is bringing this information to Alex in.
He's saying that the news that Chandra had for her aunt was something big was going to
happen in America, which seems to be him implying that she had foreknowledge about 9-11.
Hey auntie, just wanted to let you know, coming home soon, I'm not sure, I don't know what
I'm going to do for this summer, 9-11's about to happen, it's going to be a wild couple
of months.
I've seen this conspiracy floated online before, so it's not like a completely new idea to
me, but it's one idea that kind of relies on connecting random dots and misinterpreting
and misrepresenting Zamsky's comments.
It's kind of shocking to me, honestly, that Alex would hear this and kind of not know
what the guy's talking about.
It seems like this would be something that he would have covered, and I bet he has and
he's just forgotten.
Yeah, he just doesn't care because it didn't really have legs, yeah.
Probably.
So, this internet spamming, it works quick.
It starts working while Alex is still on air.
It totally works, okay.
I'm noticing that on Twitter and Facebook it is alive with the Obama deception.
Thousands and thousands of people are flooding Twitter and Facebook by posting the Obama
deception from YouTube or just the term the Obama deception.
People are also going to Google and Yahoo and typing in the Obama deception.
We're going to try to trend that to the top to show people the power of the alternative
media and to reach millions of new people with the film.
But we can't make future films if you don't purchase them from us.
Booyah!
This has been a lot.
Yeah.
This is a few more than I was hoping for.
Hey, look, this is all working out great but also you need to buy the films.
I got you in the door, now you got to buy the films also or else I can't make another
one for us to artificially promote.
This war isn't over until we defeat the globalists and we can't defeat the globalists so this
war isn't over until you have made me obscenely wealthy.
Yes.
Beyond obscenely wealthy.
So Alex goes back to calls and this one dude, he's wrong, I think about everything, sure.
Matt in DC, you're on the air.
Hi Alex.
First, I just wanted to say thank you for doing more than anybody else in the world
to fight against this new world order.
Okay, well that's more.
And secondly, I actually have to disagree with you when you say that you're not smarter
than average.
You're probably way above average when it comes to intelligence just based on your discernment.
Yeah, that was wrong too.
It's the duty of great men to lead.
Alex, most people go cross-eyed when they try to process the amount of input that you
do on a daily basis.
That's three for three.
And we need to know when you're going to step up and run for political office.
I mean, run for mayor of Austin or governor of Texas and you'll have millions of people
migrating just to go vote in that election.
Oh man, just the population of Texas would explode in order for people to come vote for
Alex to be their leader.
If you stand correctly, if Alex announces that he is going to run for mayor of Austin
within whatever length of time you must be a resident in order to vote.
I'm sure there's some requirements.
Yeah, there would have to be.
So millions of people are going to go to Austin.
Just to put Alex in office.
And then they'll all move away.
Oh, I guess they'll just stay in Austin and the place will get even weirder.
There'll be a new shirt that'll say, keep Austin weird, but not that weird.
Run away from how weird Austin is now.
Yeah.
Um, also as a cross-eyed American, I resent him saying people go cross-eyed taking in
all the information that you do because he doesn't take in any information.
Um, yeah, that's very frustrating.
So one time Alex was gonna run.
I don't know if you know this, he was going to run for office.
Oh yeah.
But there was a problem.
He was too busy filming guardians of the galaxy.
No, he was too popular.
Politics is such a dirty business.
One time I got talked into filing for state rep and I dropped out in a week because I
was getting so much support and it freaked me out and I was reading the rules.
They've written the rules where you can't follow the law and get elected legally in
the campaign rules.
That way they can selectively enforce against you.
Um, so at this point, and I don't really ever intend to run for political office.
Um, good, true.
At this point, I don't intend to do that.
Uh, I'm just here covering the news and the information.
I mean, we're reaching millions of people a day, millions of new people every week.
It's growing exponentially.
Why should we stop what's working?
I mean, if it ain't broke, don't fix it.
Well, I don't think you'd have to stop.
You could just do what you're doing and then have people come in and vote for you.
I mean, it's not that you're wrong.
I completely agree with everything you say.
Well, Austin is incredibly corrupt because we do have a hundred percent election fraud.
I've proven it in the paper when I've caught them back in 98 and again in 2000 I mean,
it's just total fraud.
That's why you can't vote them out and they're stealing everything.
This is probably one of the most corrupt cities in the country.
It's also the most wealthy per capita and that's why the bloodsuckers are here.
They are, they are looting the public.
Uh, so I mean, I can't even run for office here.
There's no elections in Austin.
What, what are you talking about?
That's what are you talking about?
Some world-class arguing right there.
Yeah, I got me.
So apparently Alex has been living in a land of lawlessness and complete 100% election
stolen-ness for 10 years at least.
Didn't bother him that much.
Apparently not.
No.
I'm confused as to why.
Oh, cause he's full of shit.
Oh, that would make sense.
Yeah, he's just talking shit.
I was going to say, I feel like I would probably be like, hmm, I don't want to live here any
longer.
Yeah, I would be scared.
Or it took me way little time with Laurie Lightfoot to be like, I don't want to live
here anymore.
I, or if like, if you really believe this revolutionary shit that Alex is talking about,
it really seems like he would be not a radio host, he'd be a terrorist.
He would be running a cell or something.
He would be advocating that people do something crazy like a storm the Capitol building.
If you've been living in a city where there's fraudulent elections for 10 years and there's
nothing real and all the leadership, you can't vote him out because it's all like, what recourse
do you have?
Just accept it?
I will say, having been to Austin, the barbecue is great.
Sure.
Is that worth an endlessly corrupt election?
No, certainly not.
Not with the Lions at Franklin's.
Yeah, that's fair.
So Alex is, I mean, what's really most important though is you guys gotta, you guys gotta hit
that Google button.
And we are having listeners today try to, I mean, BP is not even in the top 10 on Google
and Yahoo trends.
So we're trying to get the Obama deception done.
Millions of people every day go to the front pages of these sites.
They look at what the top stories are.
You're able to drive it to the top.
If you put the term, the Obama deception, the Obama deception, just go into Google and
type the Obama deception in, hit enter.
It'll bring up the results back out again, put your cursor on it, click it.
So it's a new search and just keep reentering it.
At least 15 times.
It'll take you a couple of minutes.
You don't have to type it in each time.
After you type it in, you hit search, then you put your cursor in there, click it.
So it thinks it's a new search or change one letter, you know, erase the end, put an end
back on it, but it's easier just to that guy.
Show them guys, guys, just show them how to Google, show them how to Google things repeatedly.
Show them how to press the search button again.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because again, Alex is making this very clear that BP, the oil spill, should be number one.
This is what we do about it.
You can do that hundreds of times, it'll guaranteed go to the top.
Now listen, many times I have had my videos already number one on the web and be the top
search, and it gets millions of new people to see them.
We're just artificially doing this here today, so there's not Lindsay Lohan and Mel Gibson.
I mean, the BP oil spill isn't even in the top 10.
That should be number one.
You mean you really just summed it up when you were yelling over his last clip, which
is if BP should be the number one trend, why are you doing this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Alex is doing this because he wants more traffic and more money to come into his business,
but he also knows that admitting that would look really bad.
He wants the outcome, but he doesn't want to have to ask for it, so he pretends that
his motives are noble, and that he's actually incensed that Lindsay Lohan is getting more
attention than the oil spill.
In reality, Alex is pissed off that Lindsay Lohan is getting more attention than him,
but being too obvious about it is bad for his branding, so he's pretending to be concerned
about how many people are paying attention to the oil spill.
I will say that- It's so transparent.
Yeah, if you go back and listen to our coverage of the Obama deception, I will say that I
completely lost my mind around the eight or nine hour mark, so were the last few minutes
of the Obama deception about a BP oil spill that wasn't to happen for a couple years?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
Okay.
Certainly, no.
So Alex is saying, get on there, type it in, hit enter.
Sure.
A caller has a better idea.
Okay.
For those people who sit down at the computer five or six times a day just to check their
stuff and then they get up and leave, they're probably not going to think about doing the
search for you.
There are, however, really, really simple to use add-ons for just about any browser
out there that can automatically do searches for them or refresh current searches that
they have.
Yeah, like Google will ask you, hey, do you want us to give you updates on this term?
Yeah, that and extensions.
Just for example, Google has one and I use it for this exact purpose called the reload
every.
No, that's Firefox.
Firefox has one called reload every, and it can set up a refresh for you randomly or every
one second or 10 seconds or 10 minutes or however often you want it to search for you.
And I've read about this, that the mainstream media has these to push Lindsay Lohan and
stuff.
They're already doing this themselves.
Correct.
So this is a tool that info warriors and patriots who just leave their computers on, that they
can install on their browsers that will help.
Do me a favor, send me a list of those and I'm going to send it to Watson and ask him
to do a blurb or I'll have Matt Ryan do it.
So what I'm going to do is I'm going to get a list together of bots we can use to artificially
inflate our traffic.
Yeah.
First, are you telling me that you want non-computer savvy people to start downloading add-ons
to their browser?
And bots?
Generally speaking, that does not work well.
No, no.
Seems irresponsible.
And yeah, this seems like we've- Second, they know what bot traffic looks
like.
Yeah.
It is not hard to figure out.
Also like you're on air.
You're planning this scam on air.
It's ridiculous.
All right.
We are going to go rob this bank and I know we are, we've already confirmed that we will
be robbing this bank.
How should we do it?
Well, I will tell you this, we're going to have to walk away fast.
Yes.
Ring, ring.
Oh, hello caller.
Yeah, have you heard of cars?
You can use them to get away.
Do you want to drive for us?
Do you specifically want to announce right now that you have committed to driving for
us?
Very strange, very strange.
Not good.
So Bob Chapman shows up.
Oh, great.
He's a broadcaster, Bob Chapman.
Yeah, the guy sucks.
But it's not really all that interesting.
He's boring even, Alex.
I'm going to shock you this time.
Don't buy gold.
No.
Nope.
It's all about buying gold.
Oh, I'm surprised.
You can get a copy, a hard copy or an email copy or you can get a free one year subscription
by getting a small gold coin.
Yeah, the fifth of an ounce, Frank.
Great deal.
That's from Midas Resources offering that.
So here's the point I want to make very clearly.
If you're like sort of expert on the economy and the radio show host and the guy who syndicates
the radio show who also runs a gold company are all intertwined in a bizarre business
relationship, don't get involved.
They might be untrustworthy.
It might be that if the forecaster recommends buying the exact amount of gold that I sell
perhaps this is not a good
Yeah.
And if the forecaster, like his business is doing a newsletter and you can get a free
year of it if you buy gold from the guy whose business might be affected by the forecasts
Well, if the forecasts are rosy, maybe people might buy more gold.
No, if they're not rosy, people buy more gold.
No, I mean the forecast about gold.
Yes.
Yeah.
He does forecast good things for gold.
Usually.
It's nonsense.
It's very irresponsible.
So you might have forgotten by now, but this was supposed to be about the Rockefeller document.
I do remember that.
So this is the last clip from the 16th.
Okay.
When I'm on Sunday, 4 to 6 p.m., I'm going to cover this in more detail, and I'm going
to produce a special video this weekend for viral release that will be out by tomorrow
that's going to deal with eugenics where I'm going to show you a bunch of food and
their labels and the different poisons that are in them.
But a key study that Aaron Dykes found, Rockefeller study, envisions food, future dictatorship
controlled by the elite.
And it gets into controlling food for the environment, total control, martial law, millions
dead, mandatory quarantines, checkpoints, biometric IDs to travel, to live.
Read what these monsters are planning for you.
And it's the same thing in hundreds of globalist documents like eco science.
It's about food now?
Mm-hmm.
I don't know what's going on.
So I heard that, and I was like, well, he's going to get into it on Sunday.
So we better check in on Sunday while we're here.
Okay.
All right.
So we're going to be covering also the July 18th, 2010 episode.
Oh, God.
I have to tell you this, Jordan.
I got to warn you in advance.
Alex comes in a little hot to the show on Sunday.
Okay.
He's got a head of steam.
All right.
Let me at him.
I am fired up today.
I'm going to try to control myself throughout the next two hours.
It is Sunday, the 18th day of July, 2010.
We're here six days a week, Monday through Friday, 11 a.m. to 2 p.m. Central, back Sundays
4 to 6 p.m.
We have a lot of news.
There's been a big truck bombing in Mexico, part of the drug war down there.
They claim now that they're four days into a successful cap.
I pray this is the truth.
BP has lied in the past, but let's cross our fingers and say a prayer.
These are the same headlines.
And why are you still just waiting, seeing with BP?
What is going on?
What is happening?
I don't know.
Okay.
It's very strange.
All right.
But these aren't the reasons Alex is mad.
Sure.
The reason he's mad is because the First Amendment is under attack.
Oh, of course.
I'm going to cover all the news today, but the attack on the First Amendment and free
speech globally is numero uno, the cybersecurity takeover, the open announcements that they
do want to censor the Web.
Friday a listener pointed out the top searches were Lindsay Lohan and Mel Gibson and not
even the BP oil spill.
And I pointed out that in the past, my films like Endgame, Terrorstorm, The Obama Deception
have been the number one search on the Web.
Just that made a lot more sense than it being Lindsay Lohan or the top search should be
depression because we're going into one.
So I said, why don't our users go out and Google the term The Obama Deception to make
it number one?
And Friday and Saturday it was number one, more than 20 newspapers and blogs wrote big
reviews of The Obama Deception, even though it's been out for a year and a half.
There are hundreds of versions of it up on YouTube and Google and other video sites,
but there was one version on a director's channel.
We don't have a director's channel.
That was only allowed at the beginning of YouTube and six years ago and people that
have them still have them.
And so there are several director channels that have posted it all in one part, not broken
up in 10 parts.
And the video had gotten 6.5 million views or it had 6,400,000 and change Friday.
By Saturday it had gotten 100,000 additional, well above 6.5 million, about to be 6.6 million.
Well that's well above 6.4 million.
And at that trend I've learned to be able to gauge YouTube, it probably would have had
another million views in a week or so because it was the number one search term.
People did a great job getting that out there, but more importantly, in the last few months
if you search the term Barack Obama or Obama or President Obama, not the number three link
had been like that for a year, the number one link on the world wide web on Google and
Yahoo was The Obama Deception and a link to that mega viral video with 6.5 million views
and growing.
No fucking way, no fucking way was the first link if you search for Obama, Alex's video.
Absolutely not.
If that is the case, it's only on Alex's browser based on his searches.
I don't know, I don't believe any of this, but it worked apparently.
Alex's plan worked, he got more traffic.
I would like to know more about the people who posted reviews.
I could only find one or two.
That doesn't surprise me.
And they weren't complimentary.
That also doesn't surprise me.
I would like to have an examination from a film student on that movie.
So not all news is rosy, I mean we got definitely more traffic, the plan paid off, we got the
money and ran, but unfortunately the feds might be on to them.
School kids type it in for a school report, college professors, politicians, news people,
whatever.
You type Obama or President Obama or Barack Obama and it was the number one link.
It was hacked and it was taken down off the director channel and it shows done by user.
That's what a hack is.
They go in and once it's deleted, it's gone.
The 6.5 million views is gone.
All the tens of thousands of websites that are linked to that video, it's a dead link
now.
And so of course, now when you type in Obama, it's the Obama girl or the White House, it's
not our video.
So that's why the establishment did this.
I have no doubt that it's an inside job from YouTube or Google, one of their employees.
I mean this thing was number one, they were panicking and remember this was the YouTube
presidency.
I mean you go to the White House YouTube site, their videos get like a thousand viewers.
My average video gets about a half mil.
And so they're concerned about this and this is sabotage, this is criminal, but we're not
going to just lay here and take it.
We come back, I've got a battle plan, a mission for you, if you choose to accept it, we'll
kick their ass.
Google my name more!
Yeah, as soon as I heard that, my first thought was, what do you want to bet that his plan
to deal with this fiasco somehow involves the audience doing more free advertising?
Yeah, yeah, I would probably argue that.
We'll see if that's the case.
So apparently, according to Alex, this website, this user's channel on YouTube got hacked
and they took down this and it must be an inside job.
It has to be an inside job.
Partially inspired by how jealous Obama is of how many views Alex gets.
Yeah, yep, yep, Obama, Obama.
President.
President Barack Obama.
Right.
The most well-known man on the planet.
Uh-huh.
Yep.
Jealous!
Widely, widely respected.
Jealous of Alex's star power.
Uh-huh.
His reach.
Yep.
Oh, boy.
Yeah, man, it's like people who get petty over download numbers, you know, or like YouTube
views.
Alex and Obama were beefing.
They had the White House YouTube channel and they weren't getting the same kind of traffic
that Alex was getting, so they're like, we gotta take him out, we gotta take him out.
I mean, I would say they thoroughly fucked up healthcare at this point, so maybe Obama
was like, look, I just gotta focus on anything else.
I can't believe I bungled this one, too.
Yeah, exactly.
So we'll get into this as we go along, but I want to get out in front of this in advance.
I don't believe that this even happened.
The most I believe is that there was a temporary tech glitch or something that's being blown
out of proportion, or conversely, I could believe that this is all made up.
Here are my reasons for having that position.
One, the video Alex is referring to on the Change the Channel YouTube channel is still
up and active in the year of Our Lord 2021.
That's an issue for me.
It still has the original publishing date, it didn't lose its view count, nor did any
of the comments disappear.
There's over 200,000 comments on it, so I couldn't go through all of them, but I was
able to find some from the time period of around 10 years ago, and none are saying,
hey, so glad to see this got put back up or anything.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The 200,000 comments thing, too, also is because there have been a couple people who have been
having a running argument for the last couple months in the comments, and it's not even
replies to comments, it's just individual comments that are responding to each other.
It's impossible to navigate, and they both sound stupid.
What a bunch of assholes.
So two, I was able to find some blogs covering the alleged takedown of this video, and none
of them can actually confirm that the video was taken down.
All of them rely entirely on claims that trace back to Alex himself, which seems sketchy.
Well, it just so happens that the evidence that Alex had, he lost, and the people who
could have confirmed it, they were already dead.
I'm sorry, Dan, it's true.
Three, I was able to find a forum thread on GameSpot about the claims that the video was
taken down as an attempt to silence Alex, and some of the posts are a little interesting.
The angry pelican comments, quote, I'm watching that video right now on YouTube.
It's not deleted.
Another user chimed in, quote, I have it on in the background, that KRS-One guy has a
good analogy.
There seems to be a lot of people who are confused that the link that was posted to
a supposedly deleted video page is in fact delivering them to a page that began playing
a shitty documentary about Obama.
So I believe that this is a continuation of the traffic bomb Alex began on his Friday
show, which he's now heightening on Sunday.
I can't say for certain that the video didn't have an error loading or something like that
at some point, but there's literally no part of my being that believes that hackers got
into a YouTube account and took down the Obama deception.
It's almost the most unbelievable thing I can imagine.
Well, look, now, Alex can prove it.
See, when he went to YouTube, the page opened up and it said you have internet connectivity
issues, which clearly means that the YouTube page was taken down.
Obviously.
Sure.
If you get if you get that kind of message, there's only one explanation.
So this is a federal crime.
When you type the name Obama or President Obama or Barack Obama in, it was the number
one link on Google and Yahoo.
That was before we had listeners promote the term the Obama deception to make it the number
one trend search Friday and Saturday.
A whole bunch of newspapers reported on the film Saturday someone hacked into the director's
channel, probably YouTube themselves, and deleted that film.
The Obama deception and my newest film, Police State for the Rise of FEMA.
Luckily, we were Twitter about it by my listeners and we're able to call the director who runs
the director channel to get him inside there to change the passcode before they took all
the videos down.
The point is, this is a serious federal crime.
The point is, this is a hack against this film.
This is an attack against everyone's free speech.
This is all bullshit.
But the other thing that I want to say, you don't want to take a little time to say this,
is that if YouTube had deleted the video, which I don't believe they did, I think they
would have been within their rights to do so.
Well.
Alex is clearly engaging in manipulative practices to artificially game their system.
He's openly discussing that as his plan.
There's even been conversation on a radio show of groups of people using bots to boost
Alex's view count.
I could easily see an argument being made that this is an abuse of the platform and
against the terms of service.
That said, YouTube didn't delete this video and there was no hack.
I just wanted to point out that even if this was real, I still wouldn't care.
It is a federal crime for YouTube to enforce its terms of service policies, Dan.
That's true.
Yep.
So Alex shot a video the night before.
On Saturday night, he, this is so serious that he had to shoot a video talking about
how this video got taken down.
Is he going to talk about how people should Google bomb in the video about how people
should Google bomb?
No, no, no.
This is so much more important.
This is about an assault on free speech.
My friends, there has been an assault on the first amendment and free speech.
The Obama deception has been erased, obliterated, censored, put into the memory hole.
Oh no.
Why is this important?
Obama deals with the first amendment and free speech, but this hack was illegal.
These people legal hacks and somehow got our passcode and deleted this film and other documentaries
I've made so that you don't have a right to watch it and make up your own mind.
So you don't have the right to watch it.
They're taking away your rights.
All right.
So it still hasn't been taken down though.
No, it's still up.
Yeah.
That's an issue.
You can still watch it now.
The present day is a problem.
Yeah.
And this was so funny.
Alex describes what it was like to experience this hack.
This is still from the video from the night before.
And I got-
It's not his YouTube channel though, right?
No, it's another guy.
It's another guy.
But they work together apparently.
Oh, okay.
But there's some sort of a working relationship.
All right.
And I got to say, this is where things reached a level of like bad movie slash farce.
Luckily, one of my webmasters happened to be writing a story about the fact that the
Obama deception was getting hundreds of thousands of views a day and was the number one trend
being searched on major search engines.
So within 15 minutes of him being removed, we were getting Twitter pings telling us it
was down.
So I called the director's channel who we work with and I said, hey, your site's being
hacked.
He drove in from a barbecue he was at, went in within an hour of this starting and was
watching someone live in the interface, deleting my films, deleting police day for the rise
of FEMA and the Obama deception, and thank God we could change the passcode before it
continued.
Saw a little guy creeping around inside the YouTube account.
There's the little gremlin that steals videos.
I see him.
He was eating the video, but he hadn't quite finished eating it yet.
Oh boy.
Yep.
Hmm.
That's something.
That's good days.
Yeah.
That's another, that's actually reason four.
I don't believe that happened, but I didn't want to spoil the fun.
So Alex has said that he has a way to fight back.
And so in this report that he's playing, he has the solution.
Here's the good news.
We can fight back.
And the destiny of this documentary is now in your hands.
You can do several things.
Number one, go find the links on YouTube, Google, and other sites where the video is
still posted and send that link out to everyone and tell them, this is a censored film.
This is a film that the establishment doesn't want you to see.
This is a number one film that was deleted sensors.
These criminals, these 21st century book burners, every time they attack freedom of speech and
creativity and expression that the American people and the people of the world are going
to strike back, send the links to the Obama deception out to everyone, you know, and go
to Google and Yahoo and other major search engines and the Obama deception every day
when you first log into your computer and let's keep it at the top of the trends chart.
Let's make it the number one search term in the world that it was.
Let's have the Obama deception rise from the ashes like a Phoenix carrying the light of
liberty and freedom.
It is up to all of you to carry this torch forward.
Wow.
Can I throw a baseball back in time?
I don't know.
Do I have the arm strength for that?
I don't think so.
I can reach 88 miles an hour.
I know that for a fact.
So you can see how Alex is doing the exact same thing here as he did on Friday, just
super heightened.
He's created a fake problem and he's made it emotionally resonant to the audience and
then he's made sure that they know the only way for them to really fight back is to do
more free promotional work for Alex and his websites.
Instead of appealing to the audience's understandable feeling that the oil spill was more important
than celebrity news, then co-opting that for his own benefit, this time Alex has made the
supposed deleting of his videos into an attack on the audience themselves and freedom.
This is psychopath level shit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So what you're saying is that you've manufactured this lie about the video being taken down
in order to convince your listeners to, one, share other versions of the same video, which
if the video were censored, Dan.
Right.
Well, it's censored on that one that had all the views.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
So we need to pump up the other views on the other ones, which if that is the point, those
will be taken down in the same way.
Right.
Yep.
And then we'll do it again.
All right.
Yep.
Okay.
So I remember hearing pretty regularly that the reason that Alex was embarking on this
was because he was offended that BP was not higher up on the trends, because that's an
important story, whereas Lindsay Lohan and Val Gibson, not important.
I think we may have lost sight of that particular detail.
No, we didn't.
Oh, okay.
No, but Alex is about to turn heel on BP.
Okay.
The establishment could not put up Friday and Saturday with the number one search trend
in the world, not being Lindsay Lohan or Mel Gibson or BP oil spill.
It was the Obama deception because of all of you out there getting the word out.
And the video that was the top link, and this has been going on for at least a month, when
you type in the name Obama and any variation thereof was this film.
So now BP oil spill is an example of something that the globalists wanted to trend over Alex,
as opposed to the reason he's doing this.
Uh-huh.
This is silly.
It's slippery.
He literally was saying that BP should be the top trend.
It should be the number one over Lindsay Lohan, and the problem with these globalists is they're
trying to make it number one over things like Lindsay Lohan and me.
Yeah.
Terrible.
Awful.
This is outrageous.
The leadership of the highest order that they're trying to make BP the number one story, Dan.
Which I was advocating for yesterday in order to justify making me the number one.
But now it's not about that.
It's bigger than that.
It's about me now.
So we're back to the regular show, not the video you'd shot the night before.
And this is where I think I would say this reaches its natural conclusion.
These censors aren't going to have their way, but let's not stop there.
Let's make the second search in case they've blacklisted and blacked out the entire term,
Obama deception.
In case these McCarthy-ites have done that, I want you to search the term infowars.com.
No www in front of it, just infowars.com, and just type it into your search engine over
and over again, and we'll see how they like it.
Yeah, we'll see how they like it.
This is naked.
Lying, manipulative piece of shit.
What?
How can you listen to that and not go, fuck you?
It's the kind of thing that I see.
I'm offended by how manipulative it is, and how if you were someone who took him seriously,
this would be a really tough thing to experience, because it's all fake.
But looking at it now from a ten years later perspective, it's hard not to laugh at how
embarrassingly clear this is of a charade he's putting on in order to try and gain more
traffic.
Yeah, it would probably not work if you just said, hey guys, I would like you to artificially
inflate my traffic so I can become more well-known.
No, but if you put on a pageant.
Oh, it's the government and the BPs and the lockstep and all of this stuff.
Look, celebrities are trending when it should be serious stories like BP, and so what we
need to do is we need to get my documentary about Obama to be the number one, so we do
that and then we pretend that it gets censored and now we're angry, so we do it more.
Then why didn't it work the first time?
I buy a new house.
Why didn't it work the first time?
So Alex now gets to what I would describe as the yelling phase.
I would like a gremlin to eat up all of his shows.
Now listen, I've made the film.
On the level playing field of ideas, I won the Super Bowl.
I kicked their hand in.
I sat up here and didn't visit with my children for months.
I worked seven days a week to make this documentary and fly all over the country and spend hundreds
of thousands of dollars to make it, and I gave it to you for free, and I kicked their
butt.
And now I need you to pay for it.
I need you to pay for it, take an action with it, and these scumbags don't like it.
Google tells me I can't sell a t-shirt with his stinkin' image on it.
They tell me I can't sell this video, and I put up with it.
We wrote an article about it six months ago, but left it at that, and now they won't even
let me give it out for free when they put their stinkin' ads on it, and I know they're
the ones that get it.
I think the problem with the t-shirt was like a copyright thing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um.
Because he steals just about everything.
And he doesn't seem to understand.
For someone who's really into property rights, intellectual property seems to be a complicated
pickle.
Not interested, though.
Intellectual is in the name, so not interested.
Yeah, so he spends a little bit of time freaking out and yelling, and like, I was blown away
listening to this, like how clear it is that it's just like, everything is driving towards
just like self-promotion.
I need all of you to be my street team.
I need you to do this.
Yep.
They let Obama and the Globalist and BP and all of them spew their propaganda on the web,
but I can't put my films out.
And they didn't even make up some hanky-panky, because every time they file false complaints
against me, I just file in federal court.
You know behind the scenes I've had to file in federal court no fewer than eight times
in the last year and a half to keep that stinkin' video up for you?
You know I've had to go in there and file against false copyright claims and tell people
put up or shut up, let's go to court.
Maybe real ones.
I've had to file in federal court so you can see what Barack Obama really is.
I am busting my butt here to bring you this information, and I'm not complaining.
My family and my children in this country are worth it.
I'm not gonna be a slave to a bunch of authoritarians, and this is authoritarian tyranny that this
country's going into.
And I know you understand that, and you're upset out there as listeners, so I'm gonna
beg you on my knees for all of our future.
Don't say it.
We caught them inside the interface deleting videos one after the other, and they weren't
able to get downfall the Republican, that director's account, two million views.
I want you, because that's basically part two of the Obama deception, and quite frankly
is even more powerful film, though this is the mega-viral.
I want you to get that video, I mean here's the homework if you choose to take this mission.
Search into the term over and over again, Obama Deception Censored.
Search the term Infowars.com, and search the term Fall of the Republic.
Fall of the Republic.
Yeah, so now he's promoting the sequel.
Oh man.
Oh boy.
Is this how movies should advertise from here on out?
Should we have more movies just being like, listen, this movie is coming out on January
21st, and you are going to love it.
But they don't want you to see it on January 21st, so what you all need to do to see this
movie is Google the name of this movie, and January 21st, because they're censoring it.
Or something.
I think it's an unethical ad campaign.
I don't know if it would be effective outside the context of a very trapped audience like
Alex has, but, hmm.
Isn't that what happened with the Snyder Cut or whatever?
I choose not to know anything about that.
That's smart.
Me neither.
I just know the words Snyder Cut.
I've seen it mentioned a couple times, and each time I'm like, I'm gonna go the other
way.
I just don't need any of that.
I know, I just like, uh, yeah.
So they took this down, right?
This documentary.
They have not proven that.
No.
I don't believe it either.
But they did it in order to keep it from you, because they're afraid.
I understand these trends.
It would have gotten a million in the next week, probably two million the next week.
They know we hit the zeitgeist.
They know we caused a chain reaction, and they went in, and they shut this video down
so you don't have access to it, and so you don't have a right to see it.
They're gonna decide what you get to see.
This is 21st century book burning, and then I've got stacks of news right here in front
of me.
I mean, here's one.
Feds Ignore Due Process, First Amendment, shut down thousands of blogs.
That should be the number one story.
3,000 blogs were shut down last week.
No judge, no jury, no nothing.
Vice President Biden and intellectual property enforcement coordinator Victoria Espinel gave
an order, and they've got quotes here.
The DMC takedown actions were a direct violation of the First Amendment under prior restraint,
however, explains law professor Wendy Seltzer.
Because the DMC takedowns are privately administered through ISPs, they have not received constitutional
scrutiny despite the high risk of error, Seltzer adds.
So this is the White House now issuing 73,000 takedown orders this week, mainly of blogs
critical of Barack Hussein Obama.
So Alex is talking about the blog platform Blogotry here, and there were some initial
theories that people were kicking around that the platform was taken down due to DMCA complaints,
but that was just purely speculation.
It came out a couple days later that the reason that the server that housed Blogotry kicked
it off and thus removed 73,000 or so blogs was that someone was using the server to host
an Al-Qaeda recruitment website, complete with a hit list and instructions on bomb making.
Blogotry was hosted on server's own by Burst.net, who got contacted by the FBI regarding this
terrorism stuff, and they decided to stop working with Blogotry.
Apparently there had been some past terms of service violations that are unspecified,
so they must have just decided that if they were allowing an Al-Qaeda site to stay up,
they may represent too much of a risk to stay on the servers.
Yeah, that's probably smart.
I'm not sure in the end what happened with all this, but as of July 21st, 2010, there
was an article on CNET about Burst.net's efforts to try to get the data from people's blogs
back to them, so they could have their blog, but they would not re-host Blogotry, so the
users would just have to find another platform to use.
You shouldn't lose all of your content or whatever, yeah.
And I think that to the extent that that was possible, they were saying that they were
going to find a way to make that happen.
Sure.
There's no indication that any of these affected blogs were critical of Obama, or if any were,
that it had anything to do with these actions.
Alex is just making that up, because it's a concurrent headline that can be used to
strengthen his Obama deception censorship pageant.
They are taking down 73,000 blogs, and no one's talking about it, which is why you need
to Google the Obama deception right now.
Also to be clear, that stuff about Biden and Victoria Espinal, that was an unrelated story
from June, where there was discussion about the massive economic costs of copyright infringement.
The Infowars story about the blogs being removed just kind of assumes that the reason that
they got taken down was copyright violations, so the whole angle is that, but it's not true.
And also, you can just tell, Alex is like, he doesn't even know how the story on Infowars
fits together.
Yeah.
He's just finding bits and pieces of it, and reading it.
Yeah, he's playing Mad Libs.
Yeah.
And using it in a way to justify whatever the story already is.
So look.
What?
The internet.
They're doing some censoring.
Sure.
But you know what would be hard to censor?
The internet?
The real world.
Oh.
Don't let them stop you.
Go low tech.
Get free links to it online, but also buy the high quality DVD with the expanded extras,
and make copies of this.
I mean, making 100 copies of this might cost you 50 bucks.
And give it out to everybody you know.
Air it on Access Television.
Show it to your local church.
Tell everybody you know the system doesn't want you to see the Obama deception.
Now this is the most viral film I've ever released, but this was part two, Fall of the
Republic.
Ooh, we got part two here.
This is absolutely 100% televangelist shit.
That is fucking...
Yeah.
Oh, yes, it may cost you a little bit of money, but you need to know that this is about the
law.
You can spread the word.
You need to get this out.
Spread the good word.
You need to make sure that you are converting people to the word of Christ.
Yeah.
This next clip is a little jarring.
I found his switch in tone a little bit weird.
They can't arrest all of us.
It's over.
We're done.
We're done rolling over.
We're done giving in.
I've got a deal right now on Infowars.com, and you click on both the shopping carts.
We've got two different shopping carts, whatever your choice is, where you can get four films
for $19.95.
I don't even make money on that because I put a free pocket constitution in every order.
Okay, with the cost of the film and everything else, that comes out to less than $5 per film.
If you get 10 films, it's $39.95.
That's very weird.
Wow.
That's...
It's over.
It's done.
It's fucking done.
We're all dead, and there's two for one sales right now.
I got a deal.
I got a deal, baby.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
So, Alex throws to break really, really passionate.
He's freaking me out a little bit, but the underlying message here is that the only thing
you need to do to break the will of the NWO, to destroy them, is support Alex's stuff and
give him free publicity.
That sounds right.
You print up an image of Obama as the Joker, and you say, Google Obama deception, and you
never stop, and you let these Nazi bloodsucking anti-American parasites that want to make
you and your family slaves know that we are standing up against them, and we are red-blooded,
and we are not slaves, and we are not bowing down to them.
I'm not bowing down.
I'm at the tip of the spear.
I get death threats every day, and you know what?
I am honored to be who I am.
I'm honored to just be an average person that stood up 15 years ago and said, I'm going
to defend the Republic.
I'm going to defend the family.
I'm going to defend the Second Amendment.
I'm going to fight against abortion.
I'm going to see what happens when I really take action, and we have laid waste to the
enemy.
If you simply unloose yourselves and become the leaders you are, we will sweep this scum
into the gutter.
We will defeat the New World Order.
We will crush the tyranny.
Second hour, straight ahead, stay with us!
Oof.
Oh, boy.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
That was a little much.
Oh, boy.
It sounds like on Thursday, a producer was like, uh, Alex, we are, look, DVD sales have
gone way down.
Yeah.
Way down.
And then you can hear, this is like, this is like after a comic has been on the road
for a year, and they bought 200 t-shirts, and they got 190 in the box.
Yep.
And they're like, I'm going to get a bath on this printing.
Yeah, this was a bad idea.
You know, I can't give these away.
Yeah.
Well, we better turn your family's continued existence into something that's conditional
on buying this shirt.
That'll get this shirt out.
Yep.
Yeah.
So, oh, God, just more of this.
The globalists tapped my phones, folks.
They know I'm real.
They know what we're doing is effective.
They have all these statistics, and I never really get up here and toot my horn.
And I just tell you, we're having a big effect, folks.
We're having a big effect.
And now they've gone in and hacked and taken down my film, The Obama Deception, the one
that had the biggest views and was the top link under the name Obama when you searched
his name.
You think the White House liked when they searched the name Barack Obama or President
Obama or Obama, that a video exposing him as a traitorous globalist was the number one
link in the last month or the number one search term in the last two days?
Let's not let them stop us.
Let's search the term, Fall of the Republic, my newest film on the globalist.
Let's search the term Police State for the Rise of FEMA that they also erased, Police
State for the Rise of FEMA.
Let's search the term Infowars.com.
Let's jam them all into there so we can't be stopped.
Stuart, Antonio, John, Mark, Doug, Jared, we're going to get to all of you.
It doesn't end.
It just keeps going.
This entire show is more or less just doubling down on this spamming organization.
We need to organize against Obama's policies and I don't know what any of them are and
sure we're about to take control of the Senate because the Democratic Party is shit, but
I'm going to have to say the only way to stop him is to make him feel bad when he Googles
his own name.
In my imagination.
So Alex takes a call from a guy and he's trying to pump him up about doing free street teamwork
for him.
We're hitting everybody right now is a test because the bottom fell out of Obama.
He is their front man, their messianic savior.
He was supposed to bring us into the world government and it isn't working, is it?
So we ought to be happy.
We ought to be happy and it just lets me know the effect we're having.
So what are we going to do about it, Antonio?
Are you going to fight in?
Are you going to send everybody the links to the Obama deceptions that are still online?
Are you going to make copies of the DVDs?
Are you going to go and search the term Infowars.com to drive it into the top of the trends?
Yeah, they're only making us mad to do it more.
Antonio, great job.
Anything else?
No, sir.
This caller is so close to recognizing the dynamic that's happening here.
When Alex asks if he's going to burn the DVDs and send out links and all sorts of free street
teamwork for Infowars, the caller says, quote, they're only making us mad to do it more.
Yep.
That's totally correct.
Except the imaginary globalists aren't the ones making him mad in order to get him to
post more links to Infowars.
Alex is doing that.
Yeah.
You didn't stop and think, will the globalists be mad about this or will Alex just be more
famous?
Yeah.
Hmm.
I might be wrong here.
Yeah.
This one could be on me.
You know what?
I'm going to stick around and I'm going to stay listening for the rest of my life.
You bet.
And I'm going to double down on sending out links to everybody who just erases them.
I could either engage in self-reflection or I can send out links.
Yeah.
And you know, I'm definitely going to keep sending these links to people who have long
ago put my shit filtered into the spam folder.
Oh yeah.
Forward, forward, forward, forward.
Nope.
So Alex gets another caller and this guy is weird.
He seems to be a fan of some financial broadcast and apparently people on this broadcast have
been wanting to have a debate with Alex about something.
Sure.
And Alex has been ducking them or something along those lines.
It's pretty unclear.
This past Saturday on the webcast from Financial Sense Online, Jim Poplava, who is the proprietor,
said that your office hasn't gotten back to him yet.
Well, here's another issue.
You know, I've done an hour and 36 minutes and spent about 30 seconds plugging the films.
We have sponsors and video and t-shirt and book sales at Fundus.
I'm sorry, what the fuck did you just say to me?
What the fuck did you just say to me?
I've been doing the week here as well and I turn down probably 10, 15 interviews a day.
I can't do them all physically and I know there's a lot of big sites that want to have
me on.
I've tried to recruit other people.
I've tried to find other hosts I could promote.
They usually turn into egomaniacs and have mental problems and they can't handle the
power and so I can't do it all as my problem.
Oh, they turn into egomaniacs.
Look, I just can't afford to advertise.
So you guys do it.
I don't understand what this is.
This isn't complicated.
No, I mean like you responded to exactly the point of that clip that made me angry.
God damn it.
He's like, I haven't plugged but like 30 seconds on this show or whatever.
It's like you have plugged the entire show.
You turned the show into you being mad and then plugging.
Yeah, the last two episodes of the show, the Friday and Sunday show, have been protracted
nonstop experimental long form advertising, immersive advertising.
It's outrageous.
I do think that there's a possibility that Alex doesn't like experience that as plugging
or whatever, but taken from like an external viewpoint, like that's all he's doing.
Yeah.
Everything.
That's it.
Yeah.
No, this is complaining about not getting enough views.
That's all this is.
Yep.
He's being mad that Mel Gibson's racism is more interesting than his.
Yeah.
Lindsay Lohan's more famous than him.
That's a struggle.
Yep.
So we have one last clip here and it's how the show ends on Sunday.
Okay.
Boy, it's familiar.
We're getting a lot of new stations, so we're on AM, shortwave, satellite, and the internet.
They're not going to shut us down easily.
We've got to stand up against these sensors.
They're testing us right now, seeing if they can get away with what they're doing.
Let's counter them by getting the Obama deception out to everyone and info wars.com out to everyone.
God bless you all.
It's the same.
It's just, it ends as it started.
It ends as it, it died as it lived that episode.
Like I'm, I'm baffled and also kind of tickled and confused because I went back trying to
find the coverage of the Rockefeller Duck.
Yeah.
The most important document of all time.
Yeah, with that, Alex was all over and the plan, the plan.
He revealed the whole plan, got the information out to everybody.
Now I might be cynical, I might be a little jaded by my time covering Alex, but I will
say that my experience of listening to these episodes was that it was about something else
altogether.
He barely cared at all about it.
Feels like he even told people not to worry about it so much.
Yeah.
He said, let's get that Obama deception out there.
I mean, here's the thing.
Okay.
So what we've recontextualized that dumb fuck video as is first off, he's a lying piece
of shit in the present.
And second, if he isn't a lying piece of shit, if he is claiming that he predicted this entire
thing, that he failed on a level so incomprehensible that I had to listen to four fucking hours
of him tell people to Google the Obama deception instead of him warning the free world that
we're all about to die.
I mean, you would think that if he had come into the possession of this plan document
that was like laid it all out there.
Yeah.
I would want details.
I think you'd spend more time on it than he did spend probably more time talking about
the BP situation and how let's hope they're telling the truth, which is not hard hitting
news.
Nope.
Yeah.
There's very little by way of the, and that's why the present day 2021 video about the coverage
of the Rockefeller document is so thin because he barely even touched the thing.
It was just another headline that he was able to roll with.
Paul wrote an article about it.
Alex could skim it and say some scary words and it could be used to help scare the audience
and brow beat them into a place where they'll Google things for him.
Here's what I'll say.
Fuck him.
And two, if you are listening to that and you do not immediately demand the knowledge
of what are the steps that the globalists are going to take in order to implement lock
step, how can we stop each of these individual steps in order to prevent lock step from happening?
And instead he just says, it's going to happen and the only way to stop it is to Google the
Obama deception.
Get the word out, which means promote my shit.
In this situation, not only is he not at all a hero for predicting this or anything along
those lines, he is, he is, he's aiding and abetting the globalists in this regard.
He's aiding and abetting the imaginary villains in his head.
Exactly.
Yep.
Jesus.
Yeah.
It was not what I expected.
I mean, in terms of, in a, in a way, yes, it was what you expected.
I expected something, yeah, I don't know what I expect.
You, you know, you expect the unexpected with Alex, but yeah, you didn't expect that.
No, I did not expect two episodes of Google talk.
What a piece of shit.
Yeah, he's the worst.
Yep.
Anyway, we'll be back on Friday, Jordan, but until then we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Really easy to sum up this episode because it doesn't really talk about the, not hard,
doesn't really talk about the Rockefeller document.
It just annoyed the shit out of you.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's that knowledge.
I'm just going to fight that.
Go to bed, Jordan.
Yeah, we're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook.
If you could, please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work right now.
We'll be back, but until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I'm a, how about you go Google strategic relocation.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Well, Alex, I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
Thanks for having me.