N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledgefight, knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys in knowledgefight.
Dan and Jordan, Knowledgefight, I need, I need money.
Andy and Kansas, Andy and, Andy, stop it, Andy and, Andy and Kansas, it's time to pray.
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan, I love your work.
Knowledgefight, N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com, I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledgefight, I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes, like to sit around, drink novelty beverages and talk a little
bit about Alex Jones.
Oh indeed we are Dan.
Jordan.
Dan!
Quick question for you.
Yep.
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today is something that I did not know existed and has come into my life
and I'm pretty excited about, and that is hot honey.
I had no idea.
No, refuse.
I was at the store.
Oh, what's the point?
It's hot.
I don't understand!
I was at the store, and I saw it on the shelf, and I thought, what the fuck is this?
I'd never heard of it before.
It is honey that's infused with chilis, and so it's spicy, it's so good.
It is so good, because it's like honey, it goes on things, it has that honey-ness to
it, but then also the heat.
It's great.
It is fantastic.
You can add honey to things, mustard, you can add honey to it, you can't have mustard
honey.
Uh-uh.
No.
Honey is honey, my friend.
Honey is honey.
I'll be right back.
I have strong rules, I have strong opinions about whether or not-
I don't know, man, I think you might come around if you try a little bit of that.
Alright, I probably will.
I really enjoy that.
It sounds incredible.
It's so good.
Yeah, I believe it.
And, you know, I've only had it on a bagel or two so far, but there's so many things
I want to explore putting it on.
Celine!
Celine, run!
Run, Celine!
Get out while you can!
Meow.
Come here.
Gotta put some honey on you.
What about you?
What's your bright spot?
Celine, my bright spot is also food related.
But okay, now this is going to seem simple, but have you ever had a really good pear,
Dan?
Yeah, I love pears.
Pears are the best, but pears have the shortest period, the shortest window of perfection.
True.
That is true.
They turn pretty quick.
You're always either eating a hard pear or you've waited too long and it's mush.
And yesterday I ate a pear at like the precise five minute window where it was perfect.
What kind of pear do you like?
Do you like an Anjou?
I like an Anjou pear.
Do you like a Bosc?
I'm not a Bosc pear guy.
Is that even a kind of pear?
I like it green.
I like it real green.
I don't like the brown pears.
Nuh-uh.
Don't get me into that.
I realized as I started to talk, I don't know other kinds of pears.
I don't even think Bosc is one of them.
No, Boscayot was a pear.
That's...
Yeah, I don't know pears.
Yeah, no.
I do love them though.
Incredible.
Yeah, and I always got a little bit of shade when I was younger, which I'm a little bit...
Shade?
Well, I'm a little bit peeved about this.
Sure.
I'm still actually a little bitter, a little raw, and I got to air my grievances.
Unlike pears.
My dad is a huge fan of Jelly Bellies.
And so the Jelly Bellies were often in the house, jelly beans with all kinds of flavors.
And of course, as you're a kid, people like the toasted marshmallow.
That's the kind of thing that people like.
They like all these candy kind of flavors.
My favorite was the juicy pear.
The juicy pear.
It was the best.
I thought it was really good, and I took a lot of shit for it.
You took a lot of shit.
Took a lot of shit.
A lot of shit.
To the point where I'm 36 years old.
It's been a long time for you to be remembering the Jelly Belly incident of 1994.
Ugh, dad likes pears.
Left some deep wounds.
Um, yeah, those pears are great.
Yeah, pears are amazing.
So, Jordan, today we've got an interesting episode to go over, a little bit different
than normal, and we'll get into why here in a second, but before we do, let's take a little
moment to say thank you to the folks who have signed up and are supporting the show.
Oh, that's a great idea.
So first, you're going to love this one.
I pooed it on Scalia's pillow.
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, American hero.
Next, Dan F. Great name, I know.
Thank you so much.
I'm a policy wonk.
You're now a policy wonk.
Thanks, Dan.
Next, Lingle Bingle.
Not a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Lingle Bingle.
Thank you.
Next, BB Star Stuff.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, BB Star Stuff.
Just two B's.
Just two B's?
Not the Better Business Bureau Star Stuff.
No.
Oh, okay.
Sorry.
Next, Zilla.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, Zilla.
Thank you.
Next, Amara.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you Amara.
Thank you, and City Bird.
Thank you so much.
And then finally, I got a special shout-out, a technocrat shout-out I'm gonna give out
to someone, this is a very special shout-out, Laura's baby needs to arrive now so she can
take maternity leave already!
Wait, hold on, I'm getting an update on this.
Hold on, I think we got that email just an hour ago, is there anything new coming up?
It turns out we have an update, congrats Laura on your baby policy wonk!
I'm a policy wonk!
Crikey mate, that's fantastic, have yourself a brew!
How's your 401k doing bro?
Alright, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this Watson, alright?
Let's just get down to business, we ain't making that money off that heroin, why you
pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large, I declare info war on you!
Congratulations Laura and baby policy wonk!
Yes, thank you very much to the both of you.
And Matt for no reason at all.
Exactly.
But also, thank you.
Thank you very much Matt.
So, before we get into today's episode, I just wanted to make a little bit of a correction
about our last episode.
Sure.
When I spoke, when I was talking about Stefan Molyneux giving that speech, I had said that
that was in New Zealand, and I kind of fucked that up, I conflated two things in my head,
that was actually in Melbourne, Australia, that he gave that speech.
And the reason that I got it mixed up was because when they went on this tour they had
intended to speak in New Zealand, and New Zealand said, fuck no.
Right, right, right.
And that was what I had mixed up in my head, and I apologize, I got that a little bit.
Yeah, it would be, yeah, that's a nice little bit of context to add to that, yeah, sure.
So that was in Australia.
Yeah.
Good on you New Zealand, tell Stefan Molyneux to go fuck himself as much as you like.
So Jordan, today, I felt like it had been a while since we checked in with present day
Alex Jones, and honestly, I was getting pretty happy to have had that break from his uninspired
ass broadcasting.
It's been nice.
I was actually kind of excited though, to get back into the mud and see what his dumb
ass was up to, but wouldn't you know it, I checked back in, and Owen Troyer has been
hosting Alex's show all this week, so there's no new episodes of Alex's stuff to go over.
Wow.
As it turns out, Alex has taken off for another workcation, this time heading up to Florida
to cover what he calls a mask rebellion that's taking place at a grocery store in the city
of Naples.
Okay.
The store is called Oak's Farm Seed to Table, and Alex may or may not be broadcasting many
special reports from live inside the store.
Here is a little clip.
As the state is so frickin' awesome.
Florida is awesome!
Yeah, Florida!
And Seed to Table, the great Oak Farms, give it up for all the great crew here, folks.
Yeah!
Everybody's shopping in this place.
It's awesome.
You can hear about like two people climbing in the background.
It's sad.
Yeah.
That's a long drop.
That's a long drop for Alex Jones.
Oh yeah.
I see you guys in southern Illinois at the American Legion where they're holding a mask
drive for no one.
Now if I play my cards right, I might be able to go to a car dealership opening and record
live.
Alright, wow.
Oh boy.
So the situation with this grocery store is actually kind of funny.
It's actually not in the city of Naples, technically, and if it were, it would not have a mask mandate
because the Naples city council decided against imposing one, preferring instead to just make
it a thing they strongly recommend.
However, this store is in North Naples, which is about five miles north of city limits,
and is subject to the jurisdiction of the county, in this case Collier County, who do
have a mask mandate in place.
As such, the store's owner, Alfie Oakes, has been waging a protracted campaign against
masks since he feels like this COVID-19 stuff is a hoax.
Sure.
I poked around this story a bit, and honestly, it's kind of cookie cutter.
It's a Republican business owner making a mini-celebrity of himself in the anti-mask
game, and there's not much more to it.
Everything is about what you'd expect, all the way down to him calling George Floyd a
quote disgraceful career criminal after he was killed, and saying that Black Lives Matter
is a hoax.
Alright.
That led to the Lee's County school district severing their contract with him, which prompted
Oakes to sue the school district for $50 million, claiming as all bigots do, that their free
speech had been violated.
Oh yes, of course.
I don't know what his contract with the school district said, but if they had a clause in
there about being able to terminate the contract for cause, I don't think this is a free speech
issue.
In fact, I would assume that since he's a staunch conservative, Alfie should be in favor
of the school district being able to practice free association.
Rules for others and not for me!
They shouldn't be forced to retain business ties with someone they're opposed to being
connected to?
Rules for others and not for me!
Anyway, I don't particularly care about Alfie Oakes, nor do I care too much about Alex's
very transparent attempt to vampirically feast on the attention Oakes is getting at the moment.
If Alex had done, like, a whole show from the grocery store, then you might be dealing
with an excited Dan.
But as it stands, this is just too little to get worked up about.
It's really funny to imagine, though, going into a Whole Foods or a Jewel and just trying
to get some produce and you hear a guy yelling about the UN trying to kill the children while
you're shopping.
Yeah, I can't get the image out of my head of Alex and Owen on Supermarket Sweep together,
and boy, that'd be great.
Get the turkey!
Grind the beans, Owen!
Fill it up with the meats!
Get the beans!
I don't feel like that would elevate my customer experience if Alex is broadcasting live.
Probably not.
So I set out to find an episode to make for the good people out there to enjoy, and as
luck would have it, while Alex has been in Florida, he paid a visit to a podcast in Miami
called Flagrant 2.
I watched this, thinking maybe it would be good to cover, and it's just embarrassing.
Is that a basketball podcast?
No, that's the Flagrant Ones.
That is a real podcast, the Flagrant Ones.
The guys from Hollywood Handbook and Carl Tarr.
Oh, okay.
They do a podcast called the Flagrant Ones.
Yeah, well, Flagrant 2 is the...
No, because they're talking about this being like flagrantly free speech, offensive, talking...
It's comics talking!
Oh my god.
It's comics talking, man.
Get out of here.
It's flagrant.
You're not funny if you're doing that.
I watched it, thinking maybe it would be good, like I said, but I got nothing.
Alex is so fucked up that it's not even fun.
The guy who's throwing hatchets on Christmas Eve at his own cameras in his own studio is
fun.
The guy who's trying, he's just trashed annoying Rob Do about the ways to learn and a crystal
skull covered in semen is fun.
Hilarious.
This is not fun.
It's sad.
There was a moment in the interview that Alex did a while back with Logan Paul where one
of Logan's friends commented to Alex that he had a quote heavy pour when he was getting
another glass of booze.
The tone wasn't like, hey, cool pour, man.
It had a touch of concern in it, like telling Alex to slow down.
This interview has the opposite vibe, where the hosts are laughing their asses off and
just celebrating how basically incoherent Alex is becoming.
Alex lies to the host's face about things like Sandy Hook and his position on reparations,
illustrating that these hosts do absolutely no show prep before interviewing propagandists.
At the end of the thing, one of the hosts has a list of questions for Alex, like, was
9-11 a part-time job, which should give you some sense of the value and comedic merit
of this show.
The interview was so bad that I don't even think that it rises to the level of deserving
criticism.
Like the only thing that I heard in it that I thought was interesting was Alex really
drunk trying to explain why we need to cut off all foreign aid.
Okay.
I'm like, wait, hold on.
Now we're back on all foreign aid now?
What did this happen?
Yeah.
Well, Ron Paul still lives in his drunken soul.
Yeah, right?
There's also a very, very just depressing stretch where Alex is really drunk and he
tries to call Rogan a few times.
He's like, let's get Rogan on the phone.
And Joe doesn't answer.
It's such a mess.
It's not worthwhile as an episode.
Brutal.
So I was trying to figure out like, what are we going to do?
And then I remember, oh, that's right.
There's another motherfucker I've been meaning to talk about.
Oh shit.
I haven't gotten a chance very often.
That motherfucker is named Harrison Smith.
Oh no, we're doing white nationalist happy hour with Harrison Smith in the mornings?
Host of the American journal.
Oh boy.
Harrison Smith.
He had caught my eye a while back because of, first of all, his gleeful, the Patriots
have taken over the Capitol.
We won guys.
We did it.
And then also just listening to some of his shows, they'll be like, this is pretty overt
shit man.
Yeah.
This is pretty, this is pretty a biggity.
And so I decided I'm going to get back in, see what he's been up to.
I didn't think that this was a possibility for a while cause he's been gone.
He just had a paternity leave.
Oh, he just had a baby.
Congratulations Harrison.
And he's been gone.
So Rob Dew had been hosting and Tom Papert had been hosting and boy, no good.
But now Harrison's back.
Do white nationalists have to scream like, take that great replacement every time they
have a kid?
Probably.
In the living room, whenever the kid comes out, they're like, it's breaching.
They have to be like, take that great replacement theory.
At very least they make a little fun jokes with their partners.
Won't replace this one.
All right.
Hey, here we go.
You don't love me anymore.
Okay.
Um, so we, uh, there's one particular reason that I decided to actually look at this particular
episode just March 10th and it turns out I fucked up.
So we're actually going to have to listen to another thing, but here is the beginning
of March 10th, still got some good fucking music.
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen, you're watching American general info wars.com band.video.
What a day full of news I have for you today.
And at the end of this program at around 10 30 central standard time, Alex Jones will
be taking over the broadcast from his outpost in the state of Florida, a grocery store.
Very excited to bring a lot of information to you to take your calls as well.
And we do have a new sale at info war store.com.
I'll give you that information very shortly, but first let us begin as we always do with
our daily dispatch.
Roll the stinger, please.
What he's got sound effects.
Wow.
We're doing got a fax machine getting in the headlights.
All right.
Okay.
So this is directed by Quentin Tarantino and there's a fax machine.
That's all I know.
William Fear bringing us in the king of the pan flute.
Still love it.
I don't care if that's the, if that's like intro music for like the beginning of the
show.
It's mellow as hell.
I think I pointed this out after our last time we talked about him, but I still enjoy
it.
Yeah, no, it's great.
But, uh, you know, isn't that the song that bill dies to and kill bill volume two or something?
So it's in kill bill, kill bill at least.
And that's why he knows the song.
Well, of course.
But, um, the thing I think is really interesting is like that, like beep, beep, beep, beep,
beep.
The thing is like, okay, you're, you're showing the barest bones, uh, attempt at craft.
Yeah.
And that's interesting because no one else really tries that is fair.
And then he just goes on to like read off headlines and I don't really share.
It's a very boring segment.
So, um, he, uh, at the beginning of this episode, he has a quite a pronouncement in today's
program.
I'll be laying out what I think is a rather convincing argument for the fact that we are
rapidly racing towards a conflict that I would call world war three, the battle lines are
being drawn.
And we're seeing a lot of posturing that portends great devastation in our future has to do
with China, Iran, and the Western powers aligning themselves against, uh, those, those bad countries.
We're the good guys.
The new development that is also a Harrison clearly hasn't gotten the memo according to
his anti communist buddies like Alex, world war three already happened.
The cold war was world war three and some even think that the Iraq war is turned into
world war four.
So if there's another one coming, Harrison should be calling it world war five.
I thought we were still fighting world war two since Nazis still seem to be the bad guys
in this case.
I think that him using world war three sounds a lot more exciting.
So I merely understand why Harrison would just go ahead and stick with that branding
scaremongering.
So not only does Alfie Oaks think that, uh, you know, George Floyd, you know, was a criminal
and blah, blah, blah, Harrison has some thoughts.
Meanwhile the election of, or the, uh, uh, trial rather of George Floyd continues to
move forward and, uh, more revelations are being made, uh, releasing of the autopsy report
has revealed massive amounts of drugs in his system and as they say, no injuries that would
lead to death.
In other words, Jeffrey Epstein may not have killed himself, but it looks like George Floyd
did.
This is nonsense.
There aren't revelations coming out about the case at this point because the trial was
still in the jury selection phase.
The coroner's report and autopsy information that the public has access to is the exact
same information we've had for like six months and it doesn't show what Harrison is claiming.
He's pretending that there's a new piece of information that's come out that verifies
his preexisting talking points because he knows that no one in the audience demands
better and they already believe that George Floyd's death is no big deal.
The Washington Post had an article about the upcoming trial on March 10th and here's what
they had to say, quote, when Chauvin's trial for his alleged role in Floyd's tragic death
begins, much of the argument will center instead on the autopsy details, most specifically
whether fentanyl and underlying health conditions, not the police officer's actions, stopped
Floyd's heart and lungs.
Seven experts in toxicology, cardiology, and illegal drug use consulted by the Washington
Post largely disagreed with that idea, most of them strenuously.
All but one said the autopsy findings and other court documents coupled with the well-known
chain of events that evening made death by fentanyl overdose unlikely to impossible.
And the other one was just Rudy Giuliani wearing a doctor's coat, right?
Experts who have weighed in on the matter are pretty clear that what happened to Floyd
doesn't resemble what happens in cases of opiate overdose, which is why no one on the
scene administered naloxone, which they did have it.
They had the drug that would be used in the case of an opiate.
They have to.
Yeah.
The overwhelming consensus is that though there were drugs in his system, drugs were
not the cause of George Floyd's death.
As the WAPO article points out, this defense is one that police use all the time when they
kill people.
Abuse all the time.
Yeah, it's what they did in the case of the Rodney King beating, when it was alleged that
King was on PCP, and that made him such a threat that it justified the police's actions.
Totally.
This is just something that they do, and this is Harrison Smith essentially just, you know,
taking defense arguments uncritically, and then also toeing the line for just sort of
like exactly what cops say all the time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it's weird how people are trying to litigate this, like the NFL tries to litigate what
a catch is, you know, like, oh, you got to get all the way, and you have to take one
step forward for it to be a catch, and you have to make a football move, whatever the
fuck it is, you know, and it's like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
George Floyd is dead because of Derek Chauvin and his buddies.
The end.
There's no, there's no, you can talk about how much, you know, it's like, did he murder
him?
Premeditated.
Did he do all that stuff?
But no, he was dead because of those guys.
The end.
And it appears that even if there were some sort of a, like, I'm not saying this is the
case, but if there, like this argument that is being made by Harrison were even true,
then you still have negligent homicide on the part of these cops who would have had
a responsibility to address the medical condition that was supposedly happening.
Cops are supposed to keep people alive now?
That's their job, Dan.
Protecting and serving?
I don't understand those words at all when applied to cops.
Cool.
So this show starts out a little bit slow.
I know Harrison has declared that World War III is upon us, and I gotta be honest, I didn't
make it to him explaining that if he did, because I got sidetracked.
Honestly, on Info Wars, World War III is a slow news day.
Yeah.
And this is, this is just like, there's like scattershot headlines until he goes to calls.
And here's another one of these, these little petty complaints he has.
This one's about Biden not giving enough press conferences.
Oh no.
You can only imagine if President Trump had dared to go 50 days without taking questions
from the press.
Can you imagine that?
I mean, they'd be impeaching him already for this.
In February 2020, it was reported that it had been over 300 days since Trump had had
a formal press briefing.
So Harrison can go ahead and shove that stupid tone of his up his own ass.
Yeah, I was going to say, go fuck yourself.
Yeah, to make matters worse, ABC News reported in September 2019 that not only had Trump
not done these press conferences, but it had been, quote, six months since a White House
press secretary last came to the podium in a briefing room to field questions from reporters.
Yeah, and if Biden had done that, that, wait, what?
I do think that Biden should face criticism for not having press conferences enough or
yet, since I think it would, you know, it's a helpful piece of moving forward.
And I directed the same criticism at Trump when he was doing the same thing, because
I think the transparency and availability to the public is a good thing to encourage
in our leadership.
Harrison and Infowars don't really have any underlying beliefs.
They just attack their predetermined enemies and glorify whoever they like at the moment,
regardless if they're doing the same things.
They'll pretend that their hero didn't actually do what the villain is now doing.
But worse, not long ago, because if they did acknowledge that, they'd have to explain why
it wasn't a big deal for them when Trump did the same thing that they're so upset Biden
is doing now.
And that would unravel the game.
It would really make things difficult if you had to have sort of like a consistent position
throughout your whole.
That would really fuck up the game.
Yeah, it would be tough.
Yeah, they'd be out of business.
You know what, maybe, maybe there's something to this not having press conferences.
Right.
Perhaps again, we can take another lesson from this, which is this is maybe what Trump
should have done.
Maybe they just cut off the press and you just do whatever the hell you want without
taking questions, without accepting criticism.
Harrison, you're in luck.
Harrison, I have got great news for you.
I've got great news.
You can get rid of the maybe you can get rid of the what if this is so dumb.
You are talking about a thing a man has done recently.
And if I recall, your network celebrated extensively.
Yeah.
So anyway, Trump is out of office.
But there's someone else who's in office that I think that Infowars is warming up to quite
a bit.
And that person is Marjorie Taylor Greene.
And with that, I'd like to go to another video here.
It's Marjorie Taylor Greene talking on the floor of the Congress yesterday talking about
House Resolution 8 and House Resolution 1446 gun control legislation.
So it's really cool to see them warming up to Marjorie Taylor Greene definitely wouldn't
have suspected that was the inevitable destination of the path that begins with hero worshipping
Ron Paul.
Yeah.
Anyway, HR 8 is about expanding background checks for people purchasing guns.
The other bill they're talking about is meant to close what's known as the Charleston loophole,
named after the 2015 shooting because it was how Dylan Roof was able to purchase the guns
that he used to kill nine people at the Emanuel African Methodist Episcopal Church.
He shouldn't have been able to pass a gun background check, but he did because of this
loophole.
See, when you go to buy a gun, your name is run through the National Instant Criminal
Background Check System, which should provide a yes or no result within minutes.
However, in some cases, the automated system runs into complications and can't make a determination.
In these cases, the FBI who run the system have three days to provide a yes or no to
the gun seller.
And if they fail to give a determination in that time, the seller gets to decide if they
sell the guns or not.
And you better believe they almost always do, because they're selling guns.
Yeah, I do appreciate that guns operate under the same laws as pumpkins that turn into carriages.
Yeah.
This bill that Harrison's complaining about would change that window from three days to
ten days to hopefully provide more oversight that would stop things like future Dylan Roofs
having easy access to guns.
Consider this stat from a report put out by the Center for American Progress, quote, in
2018, 4,240 background checks were denied nationwide after the three-day investigation
period elapsed.
In at least 3,960 of those cases, a gun was sold to the prohibited buyer at the discretion
of the dealer, requiring officers from the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms and
Explosives to attempt to retrieve these guns from individuals with a potentially dangerous
criminal history.
This loophole results in tons of people who shouldn't be allowed to have guns getting
guns, which poses a bit of a threat and also creates a ton of work and expense for the
ATF to try and correct the mistakes caused by a clearly too short window of time being
given for these background check systems to provide an answer.
I am really confused as to what situations require a gun so fast that we cannot wait
for the FBI to give a determination.
I mean, three days or ten days or a year, what do you need a gun for now?
If someone's barging into your house, you need a gun immediately, perhaps.
The background check delay isn't going to help you one way or another whether it exists
or not.
It doesn't seem like it.
No.
And if you miss out on hunting season this year, I feel like that's your fault.
You should have gone two weeks earlier.
You could have gone two weeks earlier.
Not a problem.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I think that both of these bills are completely sensible, so it's great to see Harrison try
to attack them by not discussing the bills in detail at all and relying on a video of
a QAnon weirdo in Congress to make his argument for him.
This is just pathetic.
It's all you need to do.
This is outrageously dumb.
I'm going to go to a recording I made of Marjorie Taylor Greene's remarks on the house floor.
She made a bit of a better argument than that.
Did she?
I think so.
Um, Harrison, uh, is, uh, wanting to go to calls, but there's not enough calls.
And I would suspect that this is because Rob Doo fucked up his show.
I need this phone line full.
We got empty spaces here.
I'm not used to seeing this.
I was hosting American Journal for a little over a month.
Full phone lines the whole time.
I go away for two weeks.
Take care of my new baby boy.
Come back.
Nobody's calling in.
This is unacceptable, folks.
I need your help.
I can't do this show by myself.
I need the info warriors calling in.
I suspect what we're going to learn about some of these callers, I have a very strong
theory about why calls might have dropped out whenever Harrison left and was on vacation.
Because Rob Doo was like, no Nazis, please.
Yes.
Yeah.
That was, that was, that sounds right.
I have a hunch.
That sounds right.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Could you please get rid of everybody who says code words for Jew?
I'm going to have to hang up.
The phone lines are empty.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
What happened?
Yup.
So we get to this first caller and I just think he's weird.
I think this is a weird dude.
And with that, we will go to our first call.
We have Andy in California wants to talk about the upcoming Passover.
Thanks for calling in Andy.
You're on the air.
Uh, hi.
Can you hear me?
All right.
I can hear you fine.
Thanks for calling in.
All right.
Thank you for having the show.
Um, yeah, this year I noticed that the Easter and Passover on the same day, April 4th, interesting.
No, it's not.
Yeah.
Harrison.
When you look at the book of Deuteronomy chapter 38, it talks about the blessing of God will
give you if you follow his ways and the second half of the chapter is, uh, all of the curses
that'll happen if you go after straight gods.
Right.
And, uh, sounds like a real shitty God to me, this star being, uh, not anything really
to do with God's law, uh, a Phoenician fertility goddess.
It's just kind of like slapped my face like, wow, maybe this is one of our chances to maybe
get it right.
Uh, before it gets any worse, because if you look at everything you guys talk about and
what we're looking at in the world today, uh, it fits those curses, uh, I mean, perfectly,
and it's not, uh, satanic organization or whatnot that are doing it.
It's it's, well, I mean, they might have a chain in it, but God definitely allows it
to happen.
So in case you want to learn something, uh, or Harrison, if you're listening, Easter and
Passover are both religious observances that don't involve specific dates on our calendars.
Christmas, for instance, like that's always observed on December 25th, because it's tied
to our calendar.
Easter and Passover, however, are both observed based on the lunar calendar, which results
in the holidays lining up with different dates every year, according to our Gregorian calendar.
Easter is always the first Sunday after the first full moon of spring and last you're
following the Eastern Orthodox tradition, which is an issue that's too complicated to
get into, because Harrison and this caller aren't even touching on that aspect of things.
Ah, I want to get into it now, because I've had a lot to, I've been quarreling with the
Eastern Orthodox about this for a long time, Dale.
Well, I'm going to leave you to that.
Passover is based on the Hebrew calendar, which in turn is lunar-based, and begins in
the middle of the Hebrew month of Nisan and lasts a week.
Typically, because of how these dates are determined, they'll end up being very close
to each other, and very often, Easter does fall within the week of Passover.
This year, Easter is on the last day of Passover, April 4th, which I guess this caller thinks
means something nefarious, I don't know.
It's very interesting, according to Harrison Smith.
This is Blood Moons all over again.
Yeah, it's 100% Blood Moons racist shit, what are we doing?
The more important aspect of this caller, I think, is how much he's internalized the
underlying message of a lot of Alex's rhetoric.
There are demons out there, sure, but the curses that are plaguing everyone are the
result of God letting this stuff happen, because you aren't good enough for him to protect.
This is the messaging of cults, and it's very present in Alex's content, with his regular
outbursts about how the world deserves to burn for things like allowing abortions.
Yeah.
It's ridiculous.
Yep, yep, if all of us don't act in perfect accord, well, all of us will be killed.
Look, God's going to lift his protection, and there you go, here come, here comes, and
it's your fault.
God operates under the same laws as, like, a teacher, and if you're a student who didn't
bring enough gum for the class, well, everybody gets punished.
Nobody gets any gum, and you all get sent to hell.
Everybody knows that that's the way God works.
Yeah, and conceivably, it's your fault, as an individual, because you didn't-
Should've brought more gum to the class.
Well, but what is bringing gum to the class a metaphor for, in this case?
Basically setting up a religiously ordered society?
Exactly.
Basically setting up a theocracy?
A theocracy, you should have overthrown the teacher, brutally deposed her and murdered
her, and then God would have showered you with all the gum in the world, Dan.
Yeah, it's a little bit worrying when you start to think about the ramifications of
internalizing the blame for God's wrath.
It is a little bit of a problem, yeah.
Gets you into trouble.
So, Harrison starts talking about how the pope, you know, that globalist pope?
I've heard of the globalist pope.
Cool pope.
He's been in jail for well over a year.
Yeah, according to expert sources, please.
But, Jordan, what about that pope that I've seen going around?
Fake pope.
You haven't seen anybody.
False flag pope.
You haven't seen shit.
Steve Porchenek arrested the pope like a year ago, but I guess the fake pope, somebody pretending
to be the pope recently, I guess in an interview had said that climate change is possibly going
to cause another flood.
Those comments are what they are.
And Christians took that very simply and calmly as him saying that there would be a regular
flood.
Harrison has decided that the pope is calling God a liar.
There we go!
I knew it!
He also came out and said that because of climate change, we face threat of a new flood
from God.
Now, I don't know, maybe I was just a child.
Maybe I misunderstood.
But it wasn't one of the key aspects of the flood that God promised never to do it again.
Wasn't that a promise God made, and is the pope calling God a liar?
Yeah, so the pope's calling God a liar.
Now we'll get into this here in a second, but something I think is really interesting
is that Harrison starts thinking about the flood.
Starts thinking about the flood story, and he gets a little bit weird with it.
The original reason that God flooded the earth was sexual immorality.
What does the pope have to say about that?
I'm pretty sure what he has to say about that is, don't worry about it.
It's fine.
Come on!
Free love, pope!
So this is interesting to me, because the flood in the Bible happens pretty early in
the book.
It happens pretty fast.
It's in Genesis chapter 6, so I decided I would go back and refresh my memory about
the lead-up to the flood, and see if it happened because people weren't fucking the way that
God wanted them to.
They weren't fucking right!
So Genesis 1 is the creation of the world, and then chapter 2 is about the making of
Adam and Eve.
Genesis 3 is about the fall of Adam and Eve, having eaten from the tree of knowledge, and
in retaliation, God made snakes all slithery.
That one was guest-written by C.S. Lewis.
A lot of people don't know that.
He created painful child-birthing in male-dominated relationship structures, and then he also
turned Adam into a farmer.
Yeah, it was really important to get the male-dominated social structures in right away, like, right
from the jump.
Yeah.
First chapter, men rule everything, moving on!
And it's gonna hurt when you give birth.
Yeah, and it's gonna hurt!
And it's your fault for eating that fucking apple later!
Genesis 4 deals with Cain killing Abel, and then there's a bunch of names in a family
tree.
Genesis 5 is a bunch more names and how long they lived, bridging the gap from Adam all
the way down to Noah.
Sure.
In Genesis 6, God gets a little bit tired of people and decides they shouldn't be living
so long.
In addition to that, he sees that quote, sons of God were marrying quote, daughters of humans,
which I guess is supposed to mean that angels were breeding with humans.
Strange that there aren't any lady angels wooing human dudes, but I'll get off my SJW
soapbox here.
Don't worry about it, Dan.
Come on, now.
Here in, uh, here's Genesis 6, verses 5 through 7.
Quote, the Lord saw how great the wickedness of the human race had become on earth, and
that every inclination of the thoughts of the human heart was only evil all the time.
The Lord regretted that he had made human beings on the earth, and his heart was deeply
troubled.
So the Lord said, I will wipe from the face of the earth the human race I have created,
and with them the animals and the birds and the creatures that move along the ground,
for I regret that I have made them.
Wait, hold on, God.
Real quick.
Just quick question, God.
Um, just, we're in the planning stages.
I can see that you're reacting emotionally.
And frankly, I think it's a little bit offensive of you to say that they're acting evil all
the time?
Sure.
I mean, come on, man.
Also, what did the birds do?
Birds are just hanging out!
Well, I mean, look, if you want to defend the birds, that's your business.
That's what I want to do?
I have a long-standing beef with birds.
Okay, that's fair.
Um, I'm not going to go to bat for them, but I am going to say that I was reading over
this, and it struck me how weird this is, that like, you know, it's a big decision to
create a race of humans.
The existence of all things.
It's very weird that God wouldn't see it coming, that he would regret doing it.
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
He was a young God at the time!
We were young, he was young, everybody makes mistakes, this is teenage God.
That seems something strange to fit into the conception of a God, is a regret over the
creation of humans.
Woof, man, those guys were shit!
I fucked that one up.
Whoops!
Yeah.
Whoops-a-doodle.
Very weird.
Yeah.
And, by the way, even if, like, God was justified in being disappointed by humans, is extermination
a rational solution to that problem?
After all, it was God that created humans, so wiping them out is really just him trying
to cover up his own mistakes?
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
Anyway, that brings us to Noah.
God liked Noah because he was unlike the rest of the people.
From Genesis 6-11, quote, Now the earth was corrupt in God's sight and was full of violence.
God saw how corrupt the earth had become, for all the people on earth had corrupted
their ways.
So God said to Noah, I am going to put an end to all people, for the earth is filled
with violence because of them.
Twice in three verses the complaint of violence is raised in relation to God's decision to
kill everyone off with the flood, and weirdly, sexual impropriety isn't brought up at all.
It is odd that God would care more about violence than sexual impropriety.
That seems so weird, Dan.
After Noah builds the ark and saves all the animals, the flood comes and they have to
live on that boat that's comically oversized for about a year.
Noah is 600 years old at that point.
When the flood ends, Noah gets off the boat and makes an altar to God, which pleases God.
In appreciation, God says, quote, Never again will I curse the ground because of humans,
even though every inclination of the human heart is evil from childhood.
And never again will I destroy all living creatures as I have done.
This story is fucked up, but the promise that God makes at the end of it doesn't preclude
God from causing the kind of flooding that we would see arise from climate change.
People aren't suggesting that we're going to end up in Waterworld or some shit, just
that there are a lot of places that will become uninhabitable, and this will lead to mass
displacement and likely a lot of death.
That's completely compatible with God's promise to never again destroy all living creatures.
Yeah.
Yep.
David Smith is a dumbfuck religious zealot who's trying to repurpose religious stories
to suit his extremist agenda.
In this case, his opposition to LGBTQ rights and access to reproductive health care.
It's a pathetic display, and honestly, it's important to recognize that this is not a
news show.
They aren't even really conspiracy theory shows at this point.
Nope.
They're extremist religious programming that's masquerading as something political or about
conspiracy in order to make them more interesting and attractive to an audience that would reject
them instantly if they were aware that the message they were being delivered and was
being pushed to them was religious in nature.
These guys on this podcast where they're all drunk, if they realized what was behind Alex's
rhetoric and his messaging and how it was really largely a religious message, I don't
think they would think this was as funny.
Hey, hey guys.
I know we've had a lot of fun, but just to remind you, the earth is only 10,000 years
old and your sinfulness is going to get you sent to hell forever.
Anyways, don't abort a baby.
Hey, I know I'm three quarters of the way through this bottle of Jameson, but I should
tell you I'm a conception of angels and demons and how very serious it is that I can see
them demons.
You know, when you read the biblical flood myth, you really start to think, was this
written by a dude, because I think it might have been.
It feels very dude written.
It's weird to go back and read it after a long time.
It had been quite a while since I had read the story directly from the source and it
was like, hmm, I don't know.
I don't know what it is about my brain, but I can pick out little things that I missed
when I was younger.
Like, oh, that's a weird detail.
Yeah.
Isn't it really kind of strange when you sit down and grapple with reality and where we
are as a society now and you look back and you're like, so are you telling me that I
was taught when I was a child that God just irrationally murdered everything and I'm like,
and that's the guy I need to worship until I die.
That part of the story is really underplayed.
Really not important.
I do think that there's still like some metaphorical value in terms of, you know, I don't know,
steadfastness and faithfulness.
Or just educational value in learning about how people explain disasters throughout history
in an oral tradition.
Anthropological kind of thing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I agree.
But I just think, I think it would be interesting if back in my Bible study groups or Sunday
school we'd discussed the ramifications of extermination.
Yeah.
And there are so many better flood myths too.
There were actual floods.
Everybody's got a flood myth that was around at the time.
There were some great ones.
The only explanation I remember is like, they're all bad.
Yep.
The people who died were bad.
100%.
That's what they, that's what they argued.
That's not cool.
Yeah, yeah.
No, from the jump in the Bible, it's like, well, listen, killing everything that's evil
is on the table, obviously.
Yeah.
So I think that Harrison believes on some level that the motivation behind the flood
on God's part was something to the effect of something related to LGBTQ rights.
He might be conflating the story of Sodom and Gomorrah.
So he weaves that in.
Of course he does.
Yeah, yeah.
And I think the reason that he's doing that is because he doesn't actually remember the
flood myth one.
Maybe not, but he does remember that the rainbow is the sign of God's covenant.
Everybody does.
And of course you look at the, you know, in Christian mythology, I guess you could call
it the rainbow was the sign from God as a promise that he would never flood the earth
again.
So just think about this, that you have God flooding the earth because of sexual immorality.
And then you have the symbol of this.
The symbol of his promise to never do it again has been co-opted by alternative sexual lifestyles.
Ooh.
Satanic to its very core, I have to say.
What?
It's as interesting as Easter and Passover happening on the same day, Dan.
Is he trying to say that people who have alternative...
The gay stole the rainbow.
Well, sure, but...
That's what he's saying.
Of course.
But beyond that, I think what he's saying is that people who have quote unquote alternative
lifestyles are immoral.
Yeah.
He is.
He is saying that it is immoral to be a lesbian or gay.
Anything other than straight.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's cool.
I mean, I guess, you know, just own that position then, Harrison.
It seems like that's what you want to say.
Yeah.
No, it seems like that is what you are saying.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's fucked up.
Just come out and say that you think everybody who's not straight should be put to the sword.
Yeah.
You know, like your God does.
I think Harrison might be only a little ways away from that.
Yeah, you're probably not wrong.
So we get another caller here, and this caller, like, I'm still reeling from this.
Okay.
This is a minute long.
Listen to the...
Mic down for this.
Okay.
All right.
Because this is confusing.
This is coming to Carlos in Texas.
Thanks so much for calling in, Carlos.
You are on the air, sir.
Yeah.
What's up, Harrison?
I want to congratulate you on your newborn child.
Thank you very much.
You're going to...
Yeah, no problem, man.
You're going to raise a great info warrior.
I've been listening since David Knight, and ever since you came out on the show, you've
been a great addition, bro.
They should have been had you on.
Thank you, man.
I appreciate that.
Yeah, man.
You do a great job.
Hope you keep it up.
Thank you.
I want to give a huge shout out.
Huge shout out.
I want to give a special extra strength formula.
Here I am sitting in a parking lot outside my university with a 5G tower beaming right
at me, and I'm ready to go for the day, dude.
I took these pills last night and had a great sleep.
And I'm ready to go for the day.
And not only that, I took some more this morning, and we're chilling, and we're ready to go
and start the day, man.
And that's it.
That's all I have to say.
Oh, that's awesome, man.
Yeah.
No problem.
Peace, bro.
Thank you very much.
That's Dr. Jones's Natural Extra Strength Kava Chill and a beautiful plug from Carlos
from Texas.
The whole call, the only reason he called in at all was to plug this product.
So wait.
So you're saying-
There wasn't anything else to the call.
So this guy is just like, man, my friends and I took this Infowars product, and we were
like, fuck yeah.
I got a good sleep last night.
Good call, guys.
Yeah.
And then I took some more, and I'm chilling.
I'm ready to start the day.
Ready to start the day.
I'm on campus.
There's a 5G tower.
It's not getting in my way.
Not a problem.
I've got to call Harrison.
I am chill.
I'm so chill.
I'm going to give Harrison a call.
Let him know I love David Knight, but listen, the White Nationalist Happy Hour is so better.
Harrison has to know how chill I am right now.
I'm so fucking chill.
I got to call Infowars.
That's nuts.
That is nuts.
And it doesn't sound like a plant because it did sound like that guy was just a little
bit high.
He sounded a bit high.
He sounded pretty damn high.
He sounded a bit chill.
He sounded fairly chill.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I think it could have been a plant, though.
I think it could have because it almost felt like he was bailing when he ended the call.
It felt like maybe there was something else, and he was like, ah, fuck it.
Yeah, whatever.
Why the fuck would you call into this show and just be like, hey, your product works?
I guess to let everybody know that it gets you high, man.
What a waste of time.
Anyway, we get to this next caller, and actually this caller starts by talking about-
It's like calling up your weed dealer and being like, man, this stuff did it.
Shit's good.
All right, that was a good call, guys.
I'm going to get out of here.
So this next caller, Jordan, I had got into this episode and I'd started listening to
it because I thought that this was the episode where Harrison interviews Stuart Rhodes.
Oh, shit.
And so I wanted to hear that.
And when this caller started up, he says, I want to talk about Stuart Rhodes' interview.
So I was like, ah, shit, I got the wrong day.
Yeah.
However, this caller then proceeds to really freak me out.
Okay.
Let's go now to Scott in Florida who has a comment about our guest from yesterday,
Stuart Rhodes, leader of the Oathkeeper, he was on for an hour or so breaking his media
silence to talk about some of the fallout from January 6th.
And a caller, Scott, from Florida has some comments about this.
Thanks for calling in, Scott.
Did you enjoy the interview or do you have some concerns about it?
What's your take here?
Yes.
Good morning, Mr. Smith, and congratulations on your child, your dad, and that's such an
awesome responsibility.
You know, I'd like to say this, Stuart Rhodes is a hero.
He's a hero and a patriot, a leader of the Oathkeepers.
I pray for him and his family that this evil government does not incarcerate him.
You know, you should have you should have a panel if you can do a show.
I don't know if you can do this, where you could get the leaders of the Oathkeepers,
the Proud Boys, the Boogaloo Boys, the Three Percenters, my favorite group, the John Birch
Society.
I haven't heard from the John Birch Society, if ever there was a group to get involved
with the takeover of communism, the United States is a John Birch Society, sovereign
citizens, West broke out this church.
Look, let's be honest.
Whoa.
OK, so this list spiraled.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, we're we're on the edge of being like, and also let's get Lex Luthor in there.
Bad guys from Captain Planet, like, come on, let's do the whole Legion of Doom.
Get him in there.
Come on, buddy.
Let's just go for all evil everywhere.
Yeah, exactly.
I mean, like, I get the idea of like, let's have a roundtable powwow with Stuart Rhodes,
maybe someone from the Proud Boys.
That seems like, OK, this is where your show is at now.
You add the John Birch Society and it's like, oh, you're harkening back to your roots.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Right, right, right, the Westboro Baptist Church.
No, what?
What?
Why?
Sovereign citizens.
Jesus, dude.
They don't even have a leader by rules.
Yeah.
What are we doing?
This is very weird.
When he said the Westboro Baptist Church, that was one like my like, oh, oh, oh, what's
going on here?
What are we doing?
And this caller, it was this is only the beginning of the trouble with that really was the beginning
of the trouble.
Oh, yes.
Oh, boy.
So this guy is going to put forth the theory or is the position that January 6th was the
beginning of the Second American Revolution.
OK.
And I hate to mike down you twice.
Oh, boy.
This is fast.
You're going to scream.
OK.
January 6th, 2021 is going to go on in American history is the second American beginning of
the Second American Revolution.
It's going to be the pinnacle of the beginning of it, because this is not over, Mr. Smith.
The American people are being persecuted by a Zionist occupied government.
And let me relate what that means when you've got an FBI that interrogates, threatens people
like you were saying yesterday, because they don't like their opinions.
They don't like their thought processes.
This smacks of a Zionist occupied government.
What I mean by that, I want to be vague.
I'm talking specifically about a government that is controlled by APAC, American Israel
Public Affairs Committee, a Federal Reserve that is the Rothschild bank, just mentioned
a moment ago, Linda Rothschild.
That doesn't surprise me talking about a capitalist world order.
International Jewry is at stake here, is involved here.
And I know what you said with me last time.
Well, let's stop.
It's not just I'm not talking about average Jews.
I'm talking about international Jews.
Oh, boy.
This is off the rails.
Wow.
I feel like I feel like when Rob Dues hosting, he knows to hang up on.
People who say Zionist occupied government.
I'm talking about a Zionist occupied government.
And let me be clear on what that means, sir.
I believe the moment you talk about a Zionist occupied government, you have been clear on
what that means.
Click.
Yes.
Yeah.
Here at Infowars, our branding is supposed to be that we're against that kind of stuff.
In order to support that kind of stuff, we have to be pretend to be against it.
Oh, boy.
International Jewry, my friend.
I have never heard that in a positive way.
Have you ever heard, like, it's national, let's celebrate the International Jewry Day.
No.
What was the name of that book that Ford put out during World War II?
The International Jew?
This is Nazi shit.
That is straight up Nazi shit.
Yeah.
And I would argue, buddy, just I mean, and look, I'm going to go out on a limb here and
I'm going to say that he's very mad at the FBI for choosing to go after people who don't
share his opinions now.
I get the feeling that he was a big fan of J. Edgar Hoover's FBI.
You know, I think he was probably a fan of the FBI murdering people who would say things
like Black Lives Matter and the like.
Sure.
Or when the tide was so anti-communist and trying to root out communist sympathizers
everywhere.
Yeah.
I'm willing to bet there would be a slightly different tone.
Now the thing is that this dude is fucking overt.
He doesn't give a shit.
He's putting it all out there.
He's talking about how it's the International Jews, not your regular everyday Jews.
Well, because he's so comfortable, you know, floating all this stuff, he kind of makes
clear something that we already know.
When Mr. Jones says globalist, I know exactly what he means.
I'm not pinning it on him.
I'll say it.
In my opinion, when I hear the word globalist, I think of the Rothschilds.
I think of the Protestant family.
I think of a cabal of international Jewry that is pushing forward this new world order,
which I call the Jew world order.
And I hate what's happening in America.
He laughed at that.
Harrison laughed at this guy saying the Jew world order.
Harrison is straight up a Nazi.
This is outrageous.
Harrison's a Nazi.
That's a real Nazi.
How is this happening on air?
That is a Nazi broadcast.
That's Nazis, that's Nazis doing Nazi shit.
And he's giving up the game a little bit that whenever I hear Alex say globalist, I know
what he's talking about.
Yeah.
I don't know if that made me, I have a weird reaction to that because part of that made
me feel like, well, good for you, buddy.
You understand what he's saying.
It's nice that he at least can read between the lines.
I don't know if many people can do that.
I think it's bad that he can and does and believes that it's okay to do that.
Well, the experience that I had was like thinking, no duh, but like, you know, I'm so, I'm so
dull or numb to the fact that like that is the code, that the characterization that Alex
uses the globalist rely so much on these archaic forms of antisemitic tropes.
Yeah, yeah.
And like, I get that and I know that and so it doesn't surprise me.
Although it is a little bit shocking to hear somebody just be like, come on, let's talk
honestly.
I know.
It is weird.
Yeah.
It's really weird.
It's strange because it does indicate that, I mean, this guy isn't the only person in
the audience who has a cognizant sort of self-awareness that that's what he thinks Alex is talking
about.
Well, yeah, obviously.
Everybody gets it.
Dude.
Why do you think we use the code word?
So we don't sound like this.
So we don't say it on the air.
Yeah, man.
God damn it, dude.
So this guy, he has some reading materials that he might want to promote to the audience
and Harrison lets him.
Is he a Pez dispenser?
Your listeners are confused and frightened and want some sanity on what's going on.
Please God, tell me what's going on.
Read a book called The Protocols.
There we go, he's the Pez dispenser.
That's a fortune.
No, it's not a fortune.
Sure, sure.
And you've made this point before, Scott.
And I know you've also mentioned that if you've talked to Scott before, you've called in a
few times.
Yes, I am.
By the way, I am Jewish.
That sounds like identity politics to me.
Great, great.
Sure.
I don't care.
I really don't care.
It does not make any of the things you're saying any better.
No, no, no, no, no.
Nope.
Don't care.
Wow.
I'm kind of back by that, like, oh, these guys know each other.
Yeah, that's real.
That makes me even more uncomfortable, where you're like, oh, yeah, yeah, oh, no, no, it's
this guy.
Of course I'm going to let him say that he hates all Jews.
Duh.
Of course I'm going to let him promote the protocols on my fucking show.
You've made this point before.
Hang up on this guy.
Yeah.
Jesus.
You know what point he's going to make.
Jesus Christ.
Anyway, Harrison, not one to shy away.
How is it that people are bitching about banning books and the protocol still isn't banned?
Yeah.
Dr. Seuss, far more dangerous.
Oh, so angry.
So Harrison doesn't really, like, push back too much on this guy.
I am Jewish.
Okay.
Yeah.
Let me just say, you know, it's interesting that you, you bring it up with Stuart Rhodes
because actually one of the things I was going to mention yesterday that I didn't get to
with Stuart Rhodes is the fact that the organizations who are actually advising the FBI on what
to do, I mean, you know, essentially you have the FBI and you would think that they would
be answerable only to politicians.
They would be taking directives from civilian oversight.
But in reality, what you see, and there's stories going back all the way to 2017, is
that it's organizations like the ADL and the SPLC that are actually directing the FBI.
Does that sound true to you, Harrison?
They're calling the ADL and SPLC Jewish organizations.
They're calling themselves that, right?
So you have an organization that is of, you know, of a certain ideology that is not claiming
to be for everybody.
It's the Anti-Defamation League.
It's a Jewish organization.
And yet they're the ones who are directing the FBI.
Now, there is a weird sort of disconnect in the American psyche where it's like, how do
we not see that that's weird and wrong?
That it's a private organization that I consider a hate group that has articles about me calling
me an anti-semite, calling me a homophobe, calling me a racist, calling me all sorts
of horrible things that are completely untrue and totally baseless.
Yeah, that's a little tough.
That's a little...
Completely baseless.
What did they do?
Listen to the previous 10 minutes?
How would they have known any of these things to claim if they had not listened to me speak
for the previous 10 minutes?
Yeah.
Wow.
Wowzers.
When you have a caller who's insinuating that international Jewry is a cabal that's trying
to push the Jew world order, and if anybody in the audience is afraid, they should just
read the protocols of the elders of Zion.
And then if you then respond with, hey, you know, the SPLC and ADL are Jewish organizations
and they run our FBI and they're a hate group that runs our FBI, they're like, hey buddy,
you are signing off on what this guy is saying.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You are not disagreeing with him.
This isn't a debate.
This isn't an airing of alternative ideas that you have.
You guys are just both fucking out there.
It is interesting the difference in reaction between, because I feel like now that they're
all just letting it out, just like, hey, we're Nazis as fuck, how are you guys doing?
I'm a Nazi, you're a Nazi, let's have a great old conversation about Nazi shit.
I can feel my guard being lowered a little bit because I'm not like, what is this supposed
to mean?
In what way are they trying to hide?
In what way are they trying to lie?
Yeah.
However, I have let my guard down there and put it up to fight because I would like to
fight them.
The moment you're just like, hey, we love being Nazis, I'm like, ah, then you're fair
game.
Right.
You know?
It's brutal.
Ah, I hate these guys.
It's a mess.
Ugh.
So Harrison does have one rebuttal that I would say he gives, and it's just to protect
the business.
It's just to protect the game.
He has to disagree that globalist means international Jewish person.
Sure, but he will admit that the ADL, the SBLC, and the FBI, as well as the government
He'll not only admit that, he will bring that to the conversation.
Yes, of course.
Okay.
And so I do disagree with you there where it's like, oh, globalist is just a code word.
It's not.
It's a certain thing.
It's a very particular thing that you can subscribe to whatever religion you are, and
it doesn't mean you subscribe to it if you're Jewish.
So I do disagree with you on certain points.
That's not even what that guy was saying.
Yeah, no, that's not even close.
He's responding to a false point in order to try and protect the Infowars use of globalist
as a dog whistle.
Yeah, no, you're just a Nazi, Harrison.
Yeah, it's unfortunate for you.
Yeah, for you, and for the existence of the rest of us.
And it's unfortunate for him because I don't listen to his show much, and then I dip in
and there's this.
It's like, I think you are going to be a lot of my media diet in the future.
Wow, just straight up Nazi shit.
Yeah.
God damn.
So I got through that call and listened to a little bit more, and I just started to get
bored.
And I'm so overwhelmed by that call and how overt and offensive it was.
And I'm like, nothing's going to be worse than that.
You can't.
I can't imagine that it would be worse than that.
Next caller.
And that caller had said that the Stuart Rhodes interview that I was looking for was on the
other day.
So I turned this episode off and went over to the Stuart Rhodes.
You didn't wait to see if somebody called in and said the Holocaust didn't happen and
that Jews are also responsible for all the problems in the world?
I don't think it was a caller.
That might have been a guest.
That could have been Harrison.
So I went to the interview with Stuart Rhodes because there was some news about him recently
related to the 6th.
Right, right, right.
That he was a super cool dude and that everybody loves him and I never wanted any violence
at all.
I wanted to check in on his response to it, and I thought it was interesting that it's
on the American Journal, but that's because Alex is deep in the grocery store.
So here we find the introduction to Stuart's interview and Harrison has some bad ideas.
This is also, I should say, this is from March 9th.
Again, you have to begrudgingly admire the ability of the mainstream media and the corrupt
establishment, their ability to manipulate the minds of the American people, especially
when it comes to an event like January 6th, 2021.
It was, of course, as more information is coming out, we know, essentially an inside
job.
The same way that 9-11 was an inside job, 1-6 was an inside job.
Flashback to our- The Patriots have taken the Capitol.
If anyone wants to listen to our coverage of January 6th, Harrison's tone was very different
on that actual day.
The Patriots have taken the Capitol.
This is him doing the, I don't know why the SPLC thinks we're racist.
It's a little bit, it's tough to take with a straight face, like I don't really believe
any sincerity here.
No, no, no, fuck Harrison.
So he gets talking about this, the January 6th protest, and he says something that is
categorically not true.
What was occurring there was the largest protest, I believe, in American history, the most number
of people ever to gather in a single place for a political movement, probably upwards
of a million, if I had to guess.
That's not true.
I believe is doing a heavy lifting job in that sense.
I believe that that was the biggest, well, yeah.
So Stewart comes in and here's what he has to say about all these people who were talking
a bunch of noise about how it was an insurrection.
Sure.
And they're going for your head, man.
I mean, what has it been like for you?
Well, it's been like something out of Orwell's 1984.
It's thought crime and face crime and all the things that we've seen in the past that's
been done to others is now being done, not just to me, but anybody else who was in DC.
It's ridiculous.
As you were saying earlier, there were no weapons.
No one brought guns.
What kind of an insurrection is that?
You know, frankly, it's an insult to the competence of American patriots that were there to allege
that was some planned insurrection.
So Stewart Rhodes is coming on the show to try to get out in front of some pretty damning
information that's just been released.
It's related to the U.S.'s case against Thomas Caldwell, an oathkeeper who was arrested related
to the storming of the Capitol.
Caldwell had made a motion to reconsider his detention, and this document that was filed
in the evening of March 8th was a response to that motion.
There's some interesting bits in here.
The first thing that's important to remember is that the charge this guy is facing is conspiracy
to, quote, stop delay and hinder Congress's certification of the Electoral College vote.
That's key, because the conspiracy wasn't to storm the building.
The storming of the building was, quote, an overt act in furtherance of the conspiracy,
regardless of when they formed the intent to take these actions.
The prosecution isn't claiming that anyone conspired to storm the Capitol, just that
they conspired to make it so Congress couldn't carry out its work.
This should scare the shit out of someone like Stewart Rhodes.
Yeah, because he did that.
The reason it should scare him is that this filing also reveals that the government is
in possession of logs from a signal chat titled, quote, DC op January 6th, 21, which was previously
undisclosed.
Caldwell himself has not been proven to have been in that chat, but Jessica Watkins, as
well as another unnamed person who were both oathkeepers who were arrested with Caldwell,
were in there, as were multiple, quote, regional oathkeeper leaders from multiple states across
the country and Stewart Rhodes.
Who would have guessed that the people who believe that the government is surveilling
them at all times, trying to constantly implant them with computer chips to track them, would
have absolutely no idea that the government could actually read these fucking conversations.
These chat logs clearly show that Stewart Rhodes was in contact with multiple people
associated with the oathkeepers who stormed the Capitol, and also establishes fairly well
that they were all involved in a plan to mess with the certification of the Electoral College
votes.
And based on the publicly available evidence, it looks like Stewart could get rolled up
in this conspiracy charge, should the government want to pursue that.
The full extent of the chats aren't disclosed, but Stewart did tell the group, quote, we
have several well-equipped, quick reaction forces outside DC.
There are many, many others from other groups who will be watching and waiting on the outside
in case of worst case scenarios.
Maybe these people didn't have weapons because they had a plan that involved heavily armed
backup teams.
Yeah, they didn't have weapons in the Capitol because we were keeping them outside of the
Capitol to use on people who tried to escape the Capitol, dummies!
Duh!
On January 3rd, Thomas Caldwell sent a message to a three-percenter group asking, quote,
how many people either in the militia or not, who are still supportive of our efforts to
save the Republic, have a boat on a trailer that could handle a Potomac crossing?
If we had someone standing by at a dock ramp, we could have our quick response team with
the heavy weapons standing by, quickly load them and ferry them across the river to our
waiting arms.
He then sent maps to people alleged to have been part of his response team.
Well, that doesn't sound good.
I wonder, and to be clear, I'm just spitballing here, I'm not being sarcastic or facetious
at all, I'm just curious, I wonder if this dude got the idea to use the Potomac from
listening to Alex's show.
On the December 31st episode of Alex's show, just days before Caldwell tried to get this
boat planned together, Alex had a caller on his show who suggested this.
Just wanted to touch bases with you with the March on D.C., or the occupation of D.C.
I think that you, I'm going to talk to all the Cajun Navy and all these people that did
boat parades for the past three to four months, we need to have every single one of those
people plug up the Potomac.
Because you know...
That is a genius idea, and can you get boats from a Potomac?
Well, I can set out some Facebook posts and stuff, but they definitely need to get boats
from a Potomac.
No, what I'm asking you is, I don't see a lot of boats from a Potomac.
I mean, boats can get on the Potomac, can't they?
Yeah, well, I'm sure they can, especially like the Cajun Navy, when the hurricanes come
in, they have to go in there and help get people out.
I agree, well, we need to see the Cajun Navy come in and then get on the ground with us,
but I totally agree.
We need to see...
Well, because I'm looking at it, if they tie up those boats, even if they try to shut down
those bridges, and that's a free, you can get into, I mean, that's a public area, tie
up those boats.
If they try to shut down those bridges, just imagine the info war army crossing the country.
And by the way, let me tell you what this is about.
It's about global government, it's about lockdowns, it's about control.
That's what the whole COVID hoax is about.
Alex changes the subject there a little bit.
It's not quite the same thing.
This caller is talking about clogging the river with the boats, whereas Caldwell wanted
to use them to ferry weapons, but there are some similarities in terms of what's being
suggested.
So clearly this caller doesn't mean that the entire river should be clogged up, but that
these boats should tie together and block the area off so info wars types could cross
the river in the event that the bridges were closed.
There's thematic similarities to what Caldwell was trying to achieve, but it's probably not
connected in any way.
I just thought it was really interesting that it was just a couple days before.
And maybe this is just kind of how these folks' minds work, you know, parallel thinking in
terms of like, well, all right, we could use the river.
Yeah, it does seem like these are plans that they cobbled together from half-remembered
war movies.
This sounds something like I remember from Bridge on the River Kwai.
We're going to go into the Potomac, I guess, I don't know.
Anyway, the point here is that Stuart Rhodes is going to have a really interesting year,
and it also makes a whole lot more sense why he was trying to promote Jessica Watkins'
legal defense fund after the 6th.
Yeah, that does make sense.
So Stuart, he has a bit of a lie here about the Signal messages that he's been sending.
Sure, sure, sure.
The only thing they've got is a message from me posted on our operational chat on Signal
saying, anybody who's not on a PSD come to the northeast corner of the Capitol, that's
where I was standing, I wanted to be there.
And my intent was to make sure that our guys stayed out of trouble.
This is a lie.
On January 6th, Stuart posted in that chat, quote, all I see Trump doing is complaining.
I see no intent by him to do anything, so the Patriots are taking it into their own
hands.
They've had enough.
Later, Stuart sent a message to regroup on the south side of the Capitol, not the northeast
side, as he's saying here on the show.
At 2.41, Stuart posted a photo of the southeast side of the Capitol captioned, quote, south
side of US Capitol, Patriots pounding on doors.
By that point, multiple people in the chat had entered the US Capitol.
Of course.
We'll see how this shakes out and everything, but Stuart is totally full of shit here.
It's outrageous.
That's fucked.
Yep.
That is fucked.
Now, it's interesting because Stuart has a little bit of a, eh, what are you gonna do,
kind of defense.
Sure.
Here.
What other defense do you have?
You've been caught red-handed.
Listen to this.
All right.
And let me give you something to think about while you're listening to this.
Okay.
He's telling the truth.
I will do my best.
Now, ask yourself, if he's telling the truth, is this okay?
Okay.
Because it's not.
And we had a situation with North Carolina, sadly, our North Carolina chapter had already
gone on a road, and it declared on a chat that I wasn't even on, they declared to other
guys in North Carolina that in DC on January the 6th, they were not gonna have anything
to do with National or take part in anything that National was doing, they were gonna do
their own thing.
And they had posted that on December 31st.
A member took a screenshot and sent it to me.
So there's that.
Right.
So...
North Carolina's gone rogue.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, look, guys.
It's what?
What?
So I built this organization entirely around right-wing violence.
And a super strong distrust of centralization.
Yep, yep.
And then, strangely enough, one chapter went rogue and decided that I had no control over
them.
One chapter essentially declared states rights.
Yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's cool.
Yeah.
I've created these heavily armed mini-armies.
And, hey, oh, they don't want to cooperate with me.
Oh, that's trouble.
Yeah.
It turns out, I accidentally created warlords.
My bad, guys.
My bad.
I created roving bands of warlords.
Really a huge mistake on my part.
Oops.
That would be one of the reasons why people don't like what you do.
Yeah.
And people have been pointing out stuff like this.
Oh, okay.
So you guys were talking about the warlord problem.
No, no, no.
Now I see what you were talking about.
Oh, you were saying that if I create this loosely connected group of armies, what of
them might go rogue?
Oh, crazy.
You know what's strange about lionizing a leaderless resistance?
It seems that they don't want to follow my leadership for some reason.
Yeah, I mean, if this is true and, like, let's say that the North Carolina crew was responsible
for everything, I still think Stuart should get sued.
Yeah, I think you still created the whole shebang.
You don't just get to say, like, whoops, my group went rogue.
Hey, hey, no, no, no.
Look, it happens.
Yeah.
Yeah, no.
Anyway.
I'm off the hook because they went rogue, see?
No accountability there.
In this next clip, Stuart misrepresents what the government's argument is, and keep in
mind that the charge that this Oathkeeper is facing is related to conspiracy to obstruct
and interfere with the Congress's electoral vote.
They're trying to say that because we said the election was stolen, this was very dangerous
about this, anyone who said the election was stolen and then encouraged people to go to
DC, and then, like we did, encouraged Trump to invoke the Insurrection Act, and we said
that if he does, we're willing to serve as the militia if he calls us in the service,
which is a perfectly constitutional and legal act by the president.
He declares an insurrection and calls us up under federal law as the militia to call us
in the service.
He has every right and authority to do so.
They're trying to make that a crime.
They're trying to allege that that-
No, they're not.
No.
That's not at all what they're doing.
If so, you would already be in prison.
Yeah.
I mean, anybody could say, come to DC, anybody could say, come be a part of this protest.
You can't, you can't conspire to interfere with Congress's business.
Well, there's that.
Well, you actually can.
Yeah.
As long as you don't do anything.
Right.
You can conspire unless you make an overt act towards furtherance of the conspiracy.
See, here's what my defense would be.
My defense would be, it was a nonviolent protest.
Now the problem with that defense is that it wasn't.
So that kind of changes your, yeah.
You know, like if nothing had happened and they were levying this charge to stop the
vote, you could have been like, see, nothing happened.
We didn't do anything.
We didn't go anywhere.
It was just a protest.
Let's say no one breached the Capitol.
No one breached the Capitol.
And they just had a protest outside.
Just a regular old protest.
Then nothing would be happening.
Nothing would happen.
No.
Nobody's-
You know why?
The problem is what happened after the thing.
If Congress's ability to carry out the vote wouldn't have been impeded.
No.
No, no, no.
So it wouldn't have been a crime.
Right.
It would have been just a regular protest.
If overt acts weren't taken to further the conspiracy, the conspiracy wouldn't be prosecuted.
Yeah.
I think they're mistaking that they think we're criminalizing the first part where you're
like, hey, we don't like this thing.
Let's all get together and be like, no.
Whenever our problem was the second part when they were like, let's go kill people.
That was my problem with it.
I don't like the combination of it, but it's the second part that's a legal problem.
Yeah.
That's the one that's coming back to bite you in the ass.
So it turns out that because of what's happening and the prosecution of these people for storming
the Capitol and all this, it turns out there's no more Constitution.
Oh.
That we are now living in a post-Constitution America.
Right.
And the act they take just makes that clearer and clearer to more Americans.
You are not going to get justice at the hands of this so-called justice department as you
call it, the injustice department.
Nice.
Get them.
I don't know.
I mean, this is one of those things that's so fucking dramatic.
Yeah.
This is again, the, just the drama nonsense of these people we're in a post-Constitution
America.
Well, Hey, I mean, if you're in a post-Constitution America, guess what?
You don't have the right to own guns.
Yeah.
So.
So we can take those real quick.
I got bad news.
Bummer.
You're gonna have to quarter some soldiers.
We're living in a post-Constitution.
Fuck off.
Grow up.
And the thing that makes it even more silly.
Cosplaying cowards.
Well, the thing that makes it even more silly is that Harrison agrees with him that we're
living in a post-Constitution America.
And then he plays a clip of Marjorie Taylor Greene talking about defending the second
amendment.
Well, today representative Marjorie Taylor Greene, Congresswoman rose to speak against
HR 8, which is a national gun at registration and HR 1 4 4 6, which is a permanent firearm
waiting list.
So the Democrats are coming after our constitutionally guaranteed rights one after the other.
And there's no sense of them slowing down, only increasing their speed.
They're not constitutionally protected anymore.
According to you, there's no constitution.
We're post-Constitution.
What are you talking about?
You guys gotta adjust your fucking rhetoric.
If you're gonna say we're living in a post-Constitutional America, don't fucking talk to me about the
Constitution then.
Which one?
Fuck your second amendment if it's post-Constitution.
None of you have fucking read it to begin with!
Fair enough.
And that's all good and well.
But, like, uh, okay.
I mean, if it's, like, it's Thunderdome then.
It's, like, what are you...
Yeah.
Come, fucking, let's do this then.
It's, if we're living, if you really sincerely believe...
Mad Max me.
Let's go.
If you sincerely believe that the Constitution no longer applies, we're in a post-Constitution
America, and you're not just saying that to be a dramatic weirdo, then it should implicate
a whole bunch of your other beliefs.
Yeah, totally.
And you should no longer be talking about protecting the second amendment because if
there is no Constitution there's no amendments to the Constitution.
No, no, there's only the amendments.
I guess you probably should stop complaining about free speech.
Well, don't worry about that too much.
That's not guaranteed.
No, not anymore.
If it's the post-Constitution America.
No.
No, and if you're gonna say post-Constitutional America, then essentially what you're saying
is if we want the Constitution back, we're going to have to overthrow the fucking United
States government.
Yes, and write a new one or whatever.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Or re-establish the old one, but either way, ultimately, you are saying we need to overthrow
the United States government.
And the way we're gonna do that, according to Stewart, is purging the GOP.
See, there we go.
It's disgusting to watch all these so-called Republican leaders throw everyone at the Capitol
under the bus, condemn them all, and agree with the Democrats.
This was an insurrection and all this nonsense.
We have got to purge the Republican Party, and it has to start at the bottom up.
You gotta purge out all the rhinos, all the cowards or traitors that dominate the GOP.
Oh, they're gone.
It is full, infested with both of those, both traitors and cowards.
You gotta purge them out and put real patriots in there, like Mrs. Green, and you gotta get
more of that.
You gotta get more Marjorie Taylor Greens in there.
Do not, do not, for one second, do not, Stewart Rhodes, for one second, say that someone else
is a coward.
For one second.
One, you're going on this show lying about the shit that you did on the 6th.
If you were not a coward, Stewart fucking coward-ass Rhodes, then you would have turned
yourself in, you would have claimed that this whole thing is bullshit, and you would have
said, I'm going to stand and fight these fucking charges because I'm not a coward.
And instead, you went on a radio show, not even a good one, you went on a shitty radio
show to say, ooh, I didn't do any, no, no, no, no, no.
They're going to blame me for stuff that I had nothing to do with.
I'm not involved in the, they went rogue.
The North Carolina guys went rogue.
I'm not, we need to get rid of cowards and traitors because the North Carolina guys went
rogue.
The North Carolina guys went rogue and did all the things that we constantly talk about
doing.
No one is a bigger coward than Stewart Rhodes.
No, no, no, no.
That fucking coward.
No, no, no.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Marco Rubio.
Oh, that's fair.
That's fair.
Mainline Republicans.
We need to vote him out and get more Marjorie Taylor Greene's in.
We need to get rid of cowards.
Now, whoa, whoa, whoa, the federal government did, I didn't do anything, oh, no, no, I will
never take responsibility for any of my actions.
Of course not.
It also insinuates that even if that goes through, it might, it's not going to really
work, but it might help.
What a fucking asshole.
Still thinks that violence probably is going to happen.
What an asshole.
So we get towards the end of this interview and Harrison gives us, you know, basically
like what this is mostly really actually about.
Yeah.
I want you to tell us, Stewart, what, like somebody who's listening right now, they see
what's going on and they're thinking, what do I do as soon as this program's over?
What do I do?
Of course, go to Infowarsstore.com.
You can go to Oathkeepers.org, but what can they do?
Who do they call?
Ghostbusters.
Yep.
All right.
I mean, it's more or less a 40 minute infomercial for, uh, for, uh, Stewart Rhodes feigning
ignorance and innocence and then also trying to get money.
Why not just tell Stewart to take some of that fucking chill, man?
If you're going to be dramatic about the post-constitutional America, we got some products that will chill
you the fuck down.
I will say-
Protect you from 5G and get you ready for your day.
Here's that it works.
It seemed to get that dude pretty high.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I mean, I have trouble sleeping sometimes.
Maybe I should, uh, I mean, no, I will not.
I want to make this clear.
I have gotten this question a couple of times and, uh, especially recently people have asked,
have I ever tried Alex's product?
Oh, good god no.
Fuck no.
And we haven't addressed this in a while.
No.
Nor would I ever.
No, no, no, no, no.
Other people do those videos.
You can watch them.
But for us, we're just going to be sad.
Yeah.
We're going to be like, ugh, this is disgusting.
Why would anybody do this to themselves?
It would be a real bummer.
And then we would be realizing that we were doing it.
And then we'd get so sad.
So we come to the end of this and one of the things that I really am pretty insistent on
in my own head is I'm going to be paying more attention to Harrison.
This dude is a real fucking problem.
This dude's a Nazi Nazi.
I mean, the kind of thing that is apparently acceptable conversation on his show is further
than most of the time that you see on Alex's show.
It's outrageous, the kind of things that you'll hear on here.
I did not think I would get to this point, but Harrison brought me here a lot faster
than I was expecting.
I miss David Knight.
Yeah.
Boring as hell.
Boring, but he wasn't a...
But he knew how to walk that line.
And honestly, I think that, not to be too explicit about my feelings about this, I honestly
think that this is revealing too much.
I think that this is actually an incredibly bad strategy on their part.
I think that this is bad for Infowars and as such, it appears to be a head poking up
and I'm going to play whack-a-mole with it.
I'm going to pay more attention to him because I think it's a soft exposed underbelly and
a fucking idiot who doesn't know how to play the game that Alex and Owen Troyer clearly
play better, where they can shut this stuff down.
They can give the appearance of signaling to these white nationalists and anti-Semites.
Listen, I love your call, but this isn't really the topic that we're going on right now.
Click next one.
Yes, absolutely.
Yep, totally.
Harrison clearly either doesn't have the desire or the ability or the smoothness to be able
to have all that in the package of his presentation.
And I think that through that we'll probably see a lot of really, really fucked up stuff.
Yeah, we, we, I used to joke about it that one of the reasons that it was edifying to
watch Alex Jones, one of the reasons that we do this show is because Alex was the weakest
link in the propaganda chain.
And now Harrison is the weakest link of Infowars.
Harrison is way weaker than him.
Harrison's not even a link.
Holy shit.
Harrison's a fucking flower, a dandelion, people twirled into a circle.
So we'll check back in on him from time to time, I'll be trying to pay attention, keep
up with him, as well as Alex.
Monday, hopefully Alex will be back from his grocery store adventure and we'll have a Alex
Jones episode.
That's something that's really funny, just to cleanse our-
Sorry, sorry guys.
We were going to do an Alex episode, but he was at the grocery store.
Just to cleanse our palates after this, we have Stuart Rhodes lying his ass off, Harrison
fielding calls from outright anti-Semite Nazi types.
And all the meanwhile, Alex.
Because the state is so frickin' awesome.
Florida is awesome!
Yeah, Florida!
And seed the table, the great old farms!
Give it up for all the great crew here, folks!
Yeah!
Everybody's shopping in this place, it's awesome.
Alex flew to Florida for three claps.
Everybody be shopping.
Hey, this seems like a great way to take a vacation while still pretending to work.
Yeah, and go pay Roger a visit, I'm sure.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, yeah.
Anyway, we'll be back on Monday, but until then Jordan, we have a website.
We do have a website, it's knowledgefight.com.
Yes, we are also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter, it's at knowledgefight.com, go to bed Jordan!
Yep, we're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook!
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work right now.
Yep, we'll be back, but until then, I'm Neo, I'm Leo, I'm DZX, Clark, I'm Daryl
Arundis, I am the prince of the pan flute.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan, I love your work.
I love you.