N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys.
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight.
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.
N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight.
opt- in Victory –
I am sweating.
N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes.
Let's sit around, drink novelty beverages, and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are, Dan.
Jordan.
Dan!
Quick question for you.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
I got an anti-bright spot.
Oh, you got an anti-bright spot?
Yes.
Okay.
Sort of a dark spot, or at least, like, you know, in the cheers and jeers parlance.
All right, all right.
This is a jeer.
But it's also kind of a bright spot because it's me expressing some of my drives towards
me.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes.
What's your bright spot today?
I had to make a run over to the, uh, the CVS, and I went inside and, uh...
Whoa, is this buzz marketing for CVS?
It's not.
Okay, good.
Remember, this is jeers.
I saw a new beverage product there.
Uh-huh.
It was Coca-Cola with coffee.
No.
Uh-uh.
It was my first instinct.
Nope.
Here's my second instinct.
Double no.
Yeah.
I doubled down, and I got it.
Yes, of course you did.
I was very excited.
Of course you did.
It is repulsive.
How could you possibly think that's a good idea?
I don't know.
I've been surprised by things in the past.
Sure, sure.
You know, that black cherry coffee seltzer is really good.
Yeah, that is really good.
Yeah, this one is not.
No.
This Coke is, uh, disgusting.
No, yeah, that's, that's the worst thing I've ever heard anyone do to coffee.
Yep.
Bad.
Yeah.
I thought you were putting some cream in there.
I was thinking about it.
No, and actually, I should be perfectly honest, I bought three varieties of it.
Because they had single cans.
Sure, sure.
So I bought the regular, the caramel, and the vanilla.
Oh, boy.
I haven't tried the other two.
Wait, they were all three coffee, though.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Coffee with...
It's a new line of Coke things.
Oh, my God, these monsters.
I got all three.
Have we not enough problems already, Dan?
I got all three because I was like, what if they're amazing?
And now I've tried one, and I just, I'm gonna stare at the other two for a while.
No, I'm not gonna, I'm not excited to drink those.
Uh, yeah, well, that could be a bonus episode.
Yeah, maybe.
Eh, we could do that.
You hear me be miserable drinking Coke?
That wouldn't bother me too much.
What's your bright spot?
My bright spot, Dan, is that on Saturday, I will be finishing my Final Fantasy VII riff
make project.
Fun!
It will be done.
I couldn't do it last night, or Wednesday night, so I'm gonna do a marathon on Saturday.
I'm almost at the end of the game.
I don't know how long it's gonna take.
Sure.
But it's gonna start at 11, and it's just gonna go until I finish the game.
And the Wonks can join you over on your Twitch channel?
You betcha.
You bet.
You can.
JB, home, something or other.
3209.
You betcha.
Yep.
You got it.
Uh, yeah, that should be fun.
Yeah.
I'm not gonna stop by.
You're not gonna stop by.
No, no, no.
Please, please, let's not get any...
Wait, what time are you...
No, like, maybe they're special guests.
No.
What time are you gonna start?
Probably 11.
Okay.
Yeah.
If you hear a rapping on your window at about 1130, that's me.
We'll see.
We'll see what happens.
It's me, and I'm day drunk.
Okay.
Now that might be fun.
Crashing in through your window.
I'd be fine with that.
Um, so Jordan, today we got an interesting episode.
We're gonna be talking about Wednesday and Thursday of this week.
That is March 17th and 18th, 20...
No, no, no!
Damn it!
This was a terrible idea that is only gotten worse.
I think it's over.
I think it's over because you technically won.
Now I'm too aware.
Yeah.
But you also won.
The whole thing was you weren't winning.
I would never win.
Yeah, the game got busted by you winning.
Yeah, well, naturally.
Hold on, what's that?
Is somebody at the door?
Oh, no.
Wait, how does this bit go?
I don't know.
This is how most bits...
That bit is now that we don't know how that bit works.
Yeah, that's fair.
Um, so it's an interesting little bit of time.
I think there's a couple of very important things that come up.
But actually, I'm kind of shocked by what doesn't come up.
And then we have one of Alex Jones' most spectacular flare-ups.
Okay.
Blow-ups on air in recent memory.
But before we get to today's episode, let's take a little moment and say hello and thank
you to some wonks.
Oh, that's nice.
So first, hi in Seattle.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Hello, hi in Seattle.
Thank you very much.
H-I-G-H.
H-I-G-O.
Oh, I was going to say.
Well, then get some sleep.
Yeah.
Or if it was H-I in Seattle, that could be like Frasier.
Hello, Seattle.
Next, Big Robbie D. Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Big Rob.
Thank you.
Next, Paul Joseph Fartson.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, PJ Fs.
And Cassie, thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Cassie.
And I'd like to give a happy birthday shout out, because fucking on the last episode,
I said we're going to do this monthly, and then I get a fucking email from somebody who's
asking to be a March birthday shout out.
I was saying at the end of March, we'd do April.
Oh, my God.
Oh, man.
We're not going to be able to do this.
No.
We'll never keep track of this properly.
Now, the bit of this is being unable to do the-
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's try and give everybody birthday shout outs, but never actually get to the names.
This isn't their fault.
Of course it's not.
I've got no problem with this person, and I hope they have a happy birthday.
Of course.
But clearly-
For your birthday, we get an existential crisis.
Clearly, I'm not meant to have an email address.
Anyway, happy birthday, and congratulations on becoming a technocrat to our beloved trans-dimensional
chocolate male vitality raptor out in Michigan.
Thank you so much, Dell.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate.
That's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
We got to go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why are you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much, Dell.
Yes, thank you very much, Dell.
Beloved trans-dimensional chocolate male vitality rapper and a funky homo sapien.
How could you not enjoy both of those people?
Yeah, totally.
So, Jordan, Wednesday and Thursday of this week, I was dreading this.
I was dreading doing the show because I had a sense that possibly Alex would talk about
the Atlanta shootings.
Yes.
At the spas in Atlanta, left eight dead.
No interest in doing that.
No, and I thought that would be really complicated because there's a lot of issues to unpack,
you know, both about the anti-sex worker ideas that are possibly motivating of the shooter
and also certainly the violence towards Asian Americans.
Anyone who created Fentanyl the Magic Dragon or whatever can shut the fuck up.
And I thought it would be really difficult with the information that we have available,
but both of those things are things that intersect with Alex's world in a kind of scary way.
Insofar as he is misogynist and anti-Asian.
Yes.
And I didn't want to deal with it.
And so I was worried and I get into it and he doesn't bring it up at all on Wednesday.
Not a surprise.
He makes a passing reference to being an incel on Thursday, but he doesn't really talk about
this incident at all.
And so if he does in the future, we'll talk about it.
But for now, I mean, my feeling is I'm looking to get more information as it becomes available
and I think it's a horrible tragedy.
Yeah.
And this is how Alex started his show on Wednesday.
So I think that might be a little bit tasteless.
Somebody, somebody tell me that there is, oh, racism against Asians is not high.
Go ahead and tell me that whenever this is just fucking available.
Nobody's stopping this.
Right.
You know?
And even if like, you know, even if anti-Asian sentiment wasn't what predominantly motivated
this shooter, even if that is the case, which I'm not saying is necessarily the case, but
even if that were the case, if you're Alex Jones doing Info Wars, I would think, hey,
why don't we put this off?
The next day you're starting your show with a fentanyl, the Chinese dragon, racist ass
character.
What are you going to say?
He's going to be like, oh, see, the shooter was motivated by misogyny.
So it's totally fine for me to disrespect the victims by being racist.
Yeah, it's, it's weird.
Yeah.
So Alex starts the show in earnest and he comes in and he's got, he's got some, some
big news.
I do not say this on air for dramatic effect.
I say it because it's the truth.
We've absolutely gone into the zeitgeist.
We are in, for lack of a better word, revelations.
And this morning I was out for a hike and at the blood pump within my brain and I just
had 30 minutes of complete and total clarity.
Is this going to be about wet ass pussy?
And then driving into the office, I recorded about a 20 minute breakdown of what I'm about
to lay out again, but it was very calm how I did it and very cogent.
And so I am going to have that put down to a video file with a few documents and a few
video clips, but I'm going to air it.
I'm going to air it at the bottom of the next hour in about an hour and 25 minutes.
It'll take two segments to air.
And I'm going to talk about it ahead of time, but everything I'm about to say is documented.
So, if you don't catch what he's saying, here's what's going on.
Okay.
He took a, he took a hike that morning.
Yes.
And he got some clarity up in his head.
Right.
Then driving to the studio on his phone, he recorded a 20 minute breakdown of whatever
vision he got while he was hiking.
Yeah, that sounded like what I was hearing and that made me deeply uncomfortable.
Now he's going to talk about this stuff and then play the report that is the recording
of him on his phone.
Right.
Oh God.
So he's got like a 30 minute conference call that he needs to get to.
So he recorded a nice little break for people.
Yeah, that might be.
That sounds like the most reasonable explanation for this.
Yeah, or he didn't have a guest to eat while that person was on air.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I need a snack about two hours in.
I'll play this 20 minute clip.
Yeah.
Um, so anyway, the, the long and short of this, I don't want to, I don't want to spoil
anything for you, but it turns out the globalists are planning, um, a false extinction in 2030,
I think.
Did you need to go on a hike to get there?
I don't know.
I honestly was looking at it and I'm like, that's kind of cute.
Like it's nine years away.
Sure.
That kind of implies to me that Alex wants to live.
Yeah, that does sound right.
He's putting it off pretty far into the future before it's like, Alex, come on, man.
He's protecting the game.
Yeah.
For nine years.
It's not next month.
It's not 2022.
Yeah.
It's 2030, man.
He'll be, he'll be probably retired by then.
Well, somebody will hopefully have forced him to retire by then at least.
That's kind of aspirational.
It's, it's really frustrating to me because he's in a sweet position as far as doomsday
cult leaders go, doomsday cult leaders go, you know, like other doomsday cult leaders,
you can only predict the end of the world a few times and be wrong before people kind
of get the gist here.
We're on, the world is going to end on this date, 2000?
It's happened a lot.
It happens all the time.
But get this.
What?
It's going to be fake.
It's going to be a false flag extinction.
I guess that's also comforting?
I guess.
Okay.
Yeah.
So anyway, that's what the, that's what Alex was calling on his phone to talk about.
Does it matter if the extinction is successful?
You really don't even need a false flag for it, right?
Right.
Yep.
Yeah.
Anyway, we'll get to that when we get to it.
The 50 people left are going to be like, yeah, that was definitely the alt-right guys.
We got him.
So Alex is going to get to that when he gets to it and we'll get to it when he gets to
it.
So he has to talk about that. He has to talk about how he's got high level sources.
Sure.
That give him really in depth, cool.
Are they at the top of a mountain?
Oh my God.
Yes.
And that's why.
That's why he took the hike.
And that's why they have access to such like current important information.
Naturally.
Because they're radiating at that high, high level frequency.
We just got to go up.
We're now entering the time.
In fact, we have entered the time where everything is just going to be out in the open now.
I have an article right here that a national talk show host sent me minutes before I went
live.
Tucker.
And the reason I mentioned that is not name dropping.
It's to point out that God has put me in the zeitgeist.
It's insane.
I can pick the phone up and call Trump.
I can pick the phone up and call Tucker Carlson.
I can pick the phone up and call General Flynn.
I can pick the phone up and call Joe Rogan.
I can pick the phone up and call basically anybody that's on the good guy side.
It's just an incredible responsibility.
Real quick, just a point of fact.
That podcast that he did, that flagrant two or whatever the fuck, the one in Miami where
they're fucking wasted.
That is actually video evidence that he can't just call Joe Rogan.
He tries multiple times, but Joe does not pick up.
It feels a little bit like how I can say, you know, I can pick up my phone and tweet
it anybody I want to right now.
Like that's the same level of, sure you have their number, but nobody's responding.
I remember back when I used to produce a comedy show, like we'd have people like Hannibal
Burress or Nick Thune would come through town and I would have their phone numbers because
I booked them on the show and like coordinating when they were going to arrive.
Yeah.
And I would sometimes be drunk and be like, I have Hannibal's number.
I'm never going to fucking call this guy.
Rude.
I have Dave Attell in my phone from when we worked together.
I'm never ever in a million years going to pretend that I can just call Dave Attell.
That's how it feels with Trump.
Yeah, exactly.
Yes.
I was just sent this before I went live.
Transgender activists makes argument for all children to be put on puberty blockers until
they can determine the identity.
Puberty blockers are toxic.
They kill a lot of people.
They cause massive depression.
So imagine we're going to put you into this system that basically sterilizes you if you're
a boy.
It makes you closer to a girl.
That's what these monsters are.
That's their end game.
That's their goal.
And no one's allowed to criticize them because it's a scientific takeover.
So leaving aside a lot of the finer points there.
This was a story from December.
So whoever Alex's cool media source is contacting him right before he got on air might be a
little bit behind the times.
Or maybe they don't exist.
And Alex just recently heard about this this morning, maybe one of his staffers found it.
The headline Alex is reading is word for word.
The headline from an article in the Washington Examiner from December 14th, 2020.
It has to do with something that was tweeted by a YouTuber named Zinnia Jones.
Zinnia was making what essentially amounts to a reducto ad absurdiam argument against
the notion that trans youth were incapable of giving informed consent to take puberty
blockers.
The tweet read, quote, if children cannot consent to puberty blockers, which pause any
permanent changes, even with the relevant professional evaluation, how can they consent
to the permanent and irreversible changes that come with their own puberty with no professional
evaluation whatsoever?
This was followed up with another tweet, quote, an inability to offer informed consent or
understand the long term consequences is actually an argument for putting every single cis and
trans person on puberty blockers until they acquire that ability.
Sure.
What this person was suggesting is pretty clear.
And Zinnia explained this when they were reached for comment by the Washington Examiner, quote,
I was not making an argument that all youth should be given puberty blockers.
This was not an actual proposal, and it's not something I advocate or endorse.
This was an argument that claims of trans youth's unreadiness to give consent to puberty
blockers, if followed consistently, lead to the conclusion that all youth are likewise
not ready for the experience of puberty itself.
Because that conclusion is absurd, again, that was not something that I advocated or
endorsed.
The argument that trans youth can't consent to puberty blockers is faulty.
That makes total sense, and the argument that's being made here is structurally fine.
But the argument isn't advancing that it's good to put all youth on puberty blockers,
as clearly stated in the article that Alex is citing.
It's an argument specifically designed to illustrate a counterexample that shows the
flaw in an already existing argument.
Zinnia's tweets were in response to the United Kingdom Supreme Court decision that, quote,
there will be enormous difficulties in a child under 16 understanding and weighing up this
information and deciding whether to consent to use of puberty blocking medication.
And the tweets really only make sense in light of that context, of that decision.
These tweets put forth what Zinnia, I believe in good faith, contends is an absurd implication
of the logic being used by the UK court.
Unfortunately from a purely logical standpoint, the argument put forth isn't super effective
in this case.
For Zinnia's argument to hold water, it would need to somehow illustrate how the proceeding
of a naturally occurring process and the intervention in that naturally occurring process require
the same level of consent, which is going to be difficult.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
They did, though, I do recall Zinnia saying that she wanted to eat the Irish and that
she did, or they did stand by that.
I know Alex is an expert in Swiftian satire.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They were like, we gotta just eat the fucking Irish, so.
And just to be totally clear, I support trans youth having access to puberty blockers.
The logic of Zinnia's argument just has a hole that could be easily exploited by people
arguing against it.
Of course.
Uh, but otherwise it's alright.
Anyway, Alex is mad about this three months later, and he's opening his show bragging
about how one of his super cool media friends brought it to his attention.
It's tomorrow's news today.
Yeah, I do like hearing about tweets from three months ago.
Yeah.
Those are my favorite news stories.
Also the whole thing there where Alex is saying that puberty blockers were linked to lots
of deaths, that seemed weird to me since that's not my understanding of it at all.
I looked into it and it turns out Alex is passing along, dun dun dun, fake news.
Oh no!
In September 2019, a bunch of right wing Christian sites began posting articles about how a drug
used as a puberty blocker for trans youth called Lupron had been linked to over 6,000
deaths.
This headline was flashy and it led to articles all over right wing media in places like Life
Site News and Daily Wire.
Ben Shapiro retweeted it and the claim went viral all over social media.
Of course.
The drug had been linked to over 6,000 deaths, but the problem is that Lupron is not just
a drug that's given to trans youth.
According to NBC News, quote, the thousands of people who die while taking these drugs
are likely the terminally ill cancer patients who receive hormone blockers to fight hormone
sensitive cancers, like prostate cancer, according to experts.
Oh, well that's hardly fair.
Right.
The underlying FDA data that was used by these blogs to show that there had been 6,370 deaths
over the past 40 years that were patients who were on Lupron.
That's all they were using.
From there, they just assumed that all these patients were trans youth as opposed to terminally
ill cancer patients and decided to create a duplicitous fraudulent anti-trans narrative
out of it.
I would bet anything that Alex just saw this headline back when it was being posted on
social media, he never thought to look into it or understand the matter further because
he's dumb and lazy.
You know, 50 years from now, I bet the Japanese will improve upon it and call it Lupron the
Third.
Come on.
Oh, you don't even get that reference at all, do you?
I don't know if I should pretend I get it or just like...
Okay, Lupron the Third.
So it's based off of Arsène Lupron, the famous French cat burglar.
There was an anime 50 years later in Japan called Lupron the Third.
Forgive me for not knowing my anime and famous French cat burglar history.
Why wouldn't you know that?
Then Miyazaki did Lupron the Third and it was incredible.
I'm sure it is.
It's a hole in my cultural awareness.
Well, don't worry about it.
A few people will get it and they will fucking shit.
The intensity of that look you gave me was really scary.
I knew you weren't going to get it.
I was so mad.
Very scary.
Oh well.
Anyway, Alex is just full of bad information already.
And so, you know, this clip like this kind of is a little funny.
The average Westerner has less attention span than a goldfish.
So they may have a native intelligence, but their subconscious brain and their conscious
brain have basically been merged where they're like jellyfish.
They're in a trance and the sleeper must awaken.
That's why when you tune into NPR or you listen to Politician, they talk very, very slowly
and they talk very, very softly and they don't want anyone on NPR that talks in an excited
voice because what does an excited voice do?
What does that do?
It wakes people up!
I would say that an excited voice like that actually distracts from the glaring holes
and the information being yelled.
Okay, there might be that.
So wait, if NPR gives me a show, I will immediately become the greatest left-wing commentator
there is in Alex's eyes.
I guess.
I mean, I think that there is a, you know, if you go back to stand up, there's a lot
of people who make up for like kind of iffy writing with overperforming.
Yeah, that would be me, Dan.
Literally word for word me.
Yeah.
I think that Alex's performance and his showmanship or whatever is designed in order to make up
for and distract people from the fact that he doesn't know anything.
He's just making all this shit up.
One could argue most people who scream are often doing that.
Yeah.
Lupron.
Lupon the third.
Anyway, this next clip, this is great, man.
This is where I live.
I like people who are happy.
I like it when people are happy.
Even people I dislike, like Alex, I'd rather everyone be happy because then positive vibes
are emanating out into the universe, right?
That's good.
Yeah.
That's a good mood because magic happened in his life.
Okay.
Did he take another hike?
He went on that hike.
Yes.
And he had an idea.
Right.
And then listen to what happened.
The staff, the crew, they're amazing.
All right.
We've all had dreams that come true.
We've all had nightmares that come true.
We've all had predictions and they come true.
We've all said, hey, let's visit grandma.
None of this is true.
Phone rings, grandma just died.
That actually happened with me.
This morning I cut an audio recording dealing with the globalist plan to have a staged end
of the world event on or around 2030.
And I'm totally sure of it.
I have the proof.
I'll show you coming up.
He doesn't.
And when I thought about it, I thought, I'll just put the graphic of the satellite footage
of the earth from orbit over that.
And I said, I'm going to have them do that as the background today.
And I swear on everything I am on my heart, on my soul, that when I walked into this building
this morning, I looked up and they were punching up this background of the satellite of the
earth.
We probably do this twice a year.
And I walked in here intending to do the headline globalist plan, the controlled end of the
world by 2030.
And I told my wife, as I walked out of the house, I said, I have just received the biggest
download I've ever gotten on the hike I had just done.
She said, what do you mean?
And I said, they're going to stage the end of the world in 2030.
And she didn't think I was crazy because she's seen me do this all the time.
Okay.
That's why, that's why.
Honey, I took a hike and it turns out that God downloaded into my brain that they're
going to fake the end of the world in 2030.
All right.
Could you pick up something to eat on the way home?
Would you like a little road sake?
You want to stop by Costco?
We're out of cereal.
Come on, Alex.
Yeah.
That's a little bit silly.
I want to hear him read the pale blue dot speech over that graphic.
Actually, that's what it is.
Everyone you've ever known lived on that pale blue dot.
And the globalist got a fake on extinction in 2030.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's how he was hiking.
And now he's decided this is the greatest thing in the world.
He figured out how he wanted to visualize it.
He comes into the studio, staff is already fucking with that image.
Oh man.
How is this?
Is synchronicity.
Blows your mind.
This is magic.
This is the universe, man.
Blows your mind.
Holy shit.
I don't care.
Wow.
You're cold hearted, man.
I am cold hearted.
Wow.
Sometimes.
To coincidences of all kinds.
You know, they say that, you know, you can never really know the people around you.
And I feel that now.
Yeah, clearly.
I cannot believe this has not penetrated your stone heart.
Dark.
I don't think ghosts are real.
What else do you got?
What else do you got, Alex?
I'm not doing dreams.
All right.
Well, put a pin in that for a little bit later.
Oh, we're going to keep doing dreams.
So in this next clip, we get to Alex responding to some big news.
And that is that Trump has come out in favor of vaccines for COVID-19.
Yes.
Yeah.
This has got to be a false flag.
Oh boy.
So maybe a breaking point.
But I knew Trump had globalist enemies and I knew that they hated him and I wanted to
fix things and I wanted to believe in it.
And I don't think Trump himself is a bad person.
I don't know people that know him very well, but he's limited and he's not this big giant
40 chess guy that everybody says he is.
He just goes with what he thinks is right and also is way too optimistic and buys too
much into science when it's globalist science and you know, all the stuff they gave him
the Randezevir and the rest of it and the gene therapies made him feel so great.
He's now on board with everything they did.
He has come out and gone on Fox News and endorsed these killer vaccines.
And after you've seen 25 countries in Europe ban it now and hundreds around the world and
all the deaths and all the problems that the only way to get through to Trump is to get
in his face about this.
I'm going to reach out to Trump.
I'm going to get a hold of him if I need to.
And I'm going to communicate with him here on air and I'm going to call the sun up.
Yeah, this sounds like you have a lot of access.
Yeah.
So Alex has been mad.
Trump just got all these drugs from people that made him feel good.
Yeah.
He's like vaccines man.
Come on.
I have a hard time believing that this conversation didn't happen where somebody is like, Trump,
we need you to endorse the vaccine.
It can save lives.
You have a lot of influence over people.
A lot of Republican men, almost half of them refuse to get vaccinated and him saying, I
can't do that.
I'm going to piss off my followers who want to kill people.
And then the other person coming back, here's a hundred grand and I'm saying deal.
Of course.
Yeah.
So he was on Fox.
I am for sale.
He was on Fox and Friends and he said, yeah, people should get the vaccines, your choice.
He got it.
Yeah.
And whatever, too little, too late.
But what I think is going on more is that I think Alex might realize that like Trump's
a dead end at this point and this would be a really good time to just be like, all right,
I don't care anymore.
Bail.
And so Alex has decided-
This is free money.
He's decided that unless Trump cuts it out with his vaccine stuff, that it's over.
Okay.
And I'm going to communicate with him here on air and I'm going to call his son up and
I'm just going to say, here's the evidence.
And if you continue to say, this is wonderful and this is good and there's quote, no problems,
you're a bad guy and I'm going to be against you.
So that's that.
I understand he wanted to reopen the economy.
He thought, okay, if it's just a vaccine, you know, you shouldn't be made to take any
dead, but if you want to get it, I'm like, well, that's still bad, but I understand what
he's doing.
I don't agree with it, but I see his perspective.
Now he's like, everybody needs to get it.
Uh oh.
So yeah, I think he sees an off ramp.
There's no hope of Trump really ever becoming president again.
There's no power there really.
The movement or whatever is so like splintered-
Fractured and hates each other.
Yeah.
There is a possibility of coalescing again, but it's not going to be around Trump.
And Trump Jr. is a fucking, uh, not option.
He's a non-runner, non-candidate.
I think they're running into the problem that a lot of would be monarchs run into, which
is that their children are stupid.
Incredibly so.
Right.
And that's why, that's okay if you're already a monarch.
Exactly.
Because then you can't stop the power going down.
You gotta go straight Caesar on this guy.
Yeah.
And so, you know, I think that Trump or Alex realizes that there's not a whole lot of value
in maintaining Trump.
There's value in maintaining like, I didn't make a huge mistake for the last two years,
but this is a line too far.
You know?
I think we may see that.
Yeah.
And he can carve out a- unfortunately I wouldn't be surprised if he could carve out a better
space for him moving forward by being the, oh, it's the crazy guy who's also anti-Trump
now.
Like, yeah.
I mean, he could have this whole time, probably.
But also, like, one of the things I think is interesting is he takes calls eventually
on this show and the next show, and like, no one cares.
No one is like, hey, what, what, uh, how you're talking bad about Trump.
Yeah.
They've all moved on too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He was just an avatar for their hatred and desire to kill, and that apparently can exist
without him.
So they realize they don't need him.
Yep.
They'll create another.
Anyway, Alex doesn't care that Trump patted him on the head.
Come back to the Alex Jones show.
All right.
I'm going to talk about Trump and really for me, what will become the last straw.
It doesn't mean that I won't say he's good on topics.
We should take over the Republican party, uh, and we need his energy.
And boy, he called up and congratulated my wife and we got married and all that great
stuff.
And boy, patted me on the head and told me I'm the greatest broadcaster and I'm going
to take over for rush Limbaugh and how wonderful.
I don't care about all that.
I only kept that clip because Alex, uh, is definitely not mad that Dan Bongino took over.
Not at all mad about that very insulting thing to him specifically.
Not even a little bit mad at all about Dan Bongino taking the spot that he considers
rightfully is.
I think it's great.
Yeah.
I think, you know what?
All these radio stations played me instead of rush anyway.
Yeah.
He's definitely not mad.
Um, so, uh, Alex has been, you know how like his media contacts reach out to him and told
them about this three month old tweet.
Yes.
Alex also has some information he's been trying to get out to his media contacts and what
do you know?
It's over a year old.
And I'm going to just tell you something here that when I say I don't feel worthy to cover
this, we cover so much huge news continually.
That's just critical for me and you and all of us to continually constantly realize how
huge this is huge because it's easy to get live on air and cover a lot of stuff cause
it's live.
But if I produce slick reports on this, it would get 10 times the views online would
actually change the world.
And an example is this.
I was given this over a month ago.
I didn't know about this.
I learned stuff all the time.
I finally have read, cause it took me a month off and on spending 30 minutes here, 20 minutes
there, 10 minutes here to read this entire folder.
And I've asked, uh, Greg Reese, one of our best researchers to do a report on this.
I've asked everybody else that has time, you know, stay up here late, whatever everyone
should do different reports on this because every time I read this, cause I probably read
this whole stack three times.
I probably looked at it 20 times, but just scanned through it.
Every time I look at this, I find new stuff because you know, you get mentally exhausted
when you're reading scientific documents and this is a small portion.
This is probably 150 pages or more on Crimson Contagion.
If you get mentally exhausted reading scientific papers, maybe you shouldn't be reading scientific
papers.
I don't, I don't know, um, Crimson Contagion we talked about in the last episode was covered
in a New York times, uh, article a year ago, quite old, Alex found out about a month ago
and has leisurely read through some stuff and now he's ready to, he doesn't actually
really get down into it.
He just complains, uh, about how his media friends don't want to cover it on Crimson
Contagion.
I did 10 minutes with Owen Schroyer yesterday.
That's in the Owen Schroyer section of Bandau video.
Um, and that's the first boil down I've done, but it is to say bombshell, we ought to call
this show bombshell because mainstream media is always bombshell, this bombshell, that
global exclusive, this global system that I don't want to be the global exclusive.
You're not.
I've actually sent this to the main talk show hosts in the country.
All of them.
Tucker.
I guess one of them is dead now.
Can't do that, but I've sent it to the other two guys and they're sending me stuff.
They're like, I'm busy.
You, you cover it and I, and I get it.
This is unbelievable.
I think that they're saying I'm busy.
You cover it because they know it came out a year ago.
So funny.
Right?
I mean, that has to be the explanation.
They know like this isn't news.
This is nothing.
No, you've got nothing.
We should call our show bombshell as we report after the New York Times.
Wow.
And you know, what's interesting too is I would bet that Tucker would have enough sense
to realize that like, you shouldn't be talking about this.
This looks bad for Trump.
Yeah.
This looks real bad.
And in order to spin it, you kind of need to exist within like a fully realized conspiracy
world.
You can't have a foot in reality.
You have to create a complete, uh, isolated space where you can pull off a, actually it
was the globalist plan.
Yeah.
And, and Tucker is trying to pretend he still lives in the shared reality we all live in.
Exactly.
Whereas Alex just like, he gave up on that illusion a long time ago.
Um, so yeah, we got to agenda 21.
You remember that?
Sure.
Agenda 2030 maybe.
Yeah.
Now there's agenda 2035.
Ooh, I like that.
And so there are servants of Satan and there are servants of the living God that built
this planet and gave us life.
And then there's the rest.
Next hour, I'm going to expose the next level of the enemy operation.
We were amongst the first to expose agenda 20, 21.
Whoops.
And now we're exposing agenda 2030.
But what comes after agenda 2030?
Deltron 3030.
For the first time ever, you're going to hear next hour about agenda 2035.
Featuring Dan the automator.
Yeah.
I was going to say.
If they have their way, there will be no humans as we are known today, left on earth in 14
years.
No more humans.
No more humans?
Nope.
Dan?
Yep.
Um, it's, it's complete nonsense.
And he just like, I love how he just makes up a new agenda name.
Yeah, sure.
Why not?
Agenda 2030.
Agenda 2035.
I think agenda 2030 is actually real.
I think that is the name of like a summit that they had.
Yeah, sure.
Fine.
But agenda 2035 I think is entirely Alex's own creation.
I like that.
He can create words and he can create agendas.
So one of his agendas is, um, you know, I've never watched any of the Freddy Krueger movies.
Sure.
Have you watched those movies?
Uh, I watched A Nightmare on Elm Street or two.
I know that they take place in the realm of dreams.
They do and you shouldn't fuck.
If you fuck in a nightmare, Freddy going to get you?
Freddy's going to get you.
So that's kind of, you know, it's in the, it's in the realm of dreams and nightmares
and Alex lives in that space too a lot.
You know, he has these visions when he's on hikes, um, and apparently I would think that
a lot of the stuff that he does, whether for good or bad, may be driven by subconscious
things that he might not understand.
Oh, I would argue that all subconscious things he does not understand.
So listen to this clip with that context in mind.
Okay.
This is about how if you get an abortion, uh, then you'll be fine with killing old people
and stuff.
Sure.
And then Alex starts talking about his own history of paying for abortions and he says
some stuff that makes me really uncomfortable.
And so Trump coming out and doing this for me is him crossing the Rubicon because this
is 2021 and there's a major pushback against this, but see, I predicted this.
It wasn't hard to predict.
It's how they work.
They say it's not a baby.
It's not a human Roe v Wade, 1973, tens of millions of women get an abortion.
Now they're going to defend it because they never want to admit they killed their baby.
They never want to admit it doubles or chances of uterine cancer, cervical cancer, ovarian
cancer, or more, more than double.
And some of the studies, they just know it's good.
And because they commit the crime against God, instead of repenting, you harden your
heart, you double down.
You don't get God to forgive you.
And now you're a servant of evil.
And now you're going to support euthanizing old people.
Now you're going to support keeping babies alive and sell their organs because once you're
on that track, you never look, look, folks, I'm not a hypocrite.
Why in God's name would you admit you paid for abortion?
That's horrible because I did it and I repented and I swore to God when I was like 17 years
old and refound God, that I would not do that again.
And I went years without even dating because man, I can look at a woman getting pregnant
back then.
I'm still fertile.
And, and, and then I got a pregnant, married her, hadn't had three children with her.
And then that's the way, you know, I will never do that again.
And I repented and I had that God forgave me.
And I, it's like King David did all these horrible things, but he didn't mean it.
He, his heart was real.
God judge his heart.
He was forgiven.
And it was so good.
You've had an abortion.
He wrote the book.
Repent.
Kind of painted himself in a positive light.
I still have nightmares seeing the children though.
God still shows me the children as they grow up and how beautiful they were.
And I had a big nightmare the other night.
Like I was holding this little baby in my hand.
I was like about an inch big.
It was my son.
It was this incredible son.
And this demonic wolf just came and said, you killed your child.
Just ate it right in front of me.
And I couldn't do anything.
And Satan looked right at me with those red eyes and said, I got your ass, but you don't
because Christ has delivered me and cleansed me of what I did.
And as long as I don't back down now, I will be with Christ forever.
And so Satan get behind me.
I don't listen to a damn thing you say, but that's what this comes down to.
Ladies and gentlemen, that is what this comes down to.
So he was holding his tadpole of a fetus, not even that, still borderline and ovum in
and of itself.
And then the devil ate it.
And the devil ate it in front of him.
And Alex said he has nightmares that God shows him these kids.
So apparently God is sending these nightmares where the devil eats his child in front of
him.
And somehow Alex is like, yeah, God's forgiven me, I've repented, everything's fine.
But God's torturing me in my dreams.
That's how you keep Alex in line, okay?
If you're God, you've chosen Alex to defeat the devil and you can't let the chosen one
stray from the path.
So you got to send him constant, terrifying, threatening nightmares to make sure he knows
you love him.
I look at this from a more, I don't know, materialist perspective, or like reality based.
Al, I can see your stone heart right now.
I kind of see this as a thing where Alex may feel tremendous amounts of guilt about things
that he, and his opposition to abortion and the demonicness of it, maybe a lot of it might
be a byproduct of how terrible he feels about himself.
Sure, sure.
More importantly, this is what I want to say.
This doesn't belong on air.
No.
This is not cool.
This isn't cool.
This is bad.
This isn't good for a news show.
This isn't good for an editorial show.
This isn't good as analysis of anything.
Real bad.
It maybe has a place as like mid-range televangelist.
I could see that.
Yeah.
I could see like local televangelist, not like one of the all national ones.
He doesn't have a private jet, but he can afford a tour bus.
Somewhere under the Jack Van Impe level.
Exactly.
Yeah.
I find this to be really bizarre that anybody would listen to this and just be like, man,
this guy gets it.
He's talking on air, rambling about how he has visions at night of his babies that he
paid for abortions, and then the devil eats them.
And Alex gets mad, and ugh, God.
It's hard to take a man seriously who says we've got big news to get into, and then later
on goes to be like, I had a dream, and let me tell it to you in exhausting detail.
Yeah, it was the devil eating my unborn child to punish me or taunt me, and God welcomed
that dream into my head as some kind of a...
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
Oh boy.
So I really got this fucking weird sense about him.
That is nuts.
And this is nuts.
Back home, Alex Jones, your host.
Coming up in the next two segments.
That key report on the globalist plan for a controlled end of the world in or around
the year 2030.
Learn what agenda 2035 is exclusively.
And I'm as serious as a heart attack.
People figure that out now.
People used to hear me say this stuff 25 years ago.
It's all come true.
I've studied their documents, all their information, fused it together.
I have a lot of contacts, a lot of sources, but I'm now above basically any of those sources
except for a few of the top globalist.
I'm one of the only people outside the top globalist leadership that actually have all
the contacts and all the info to see their complete master plan.
And again, I'm not bragging.
It's true.
And I literally cannot tell you more at that point.
Okay.
So only Alex and like King globalists actually know what's going on.
Nobody else in the world could even see through.
I'm listening to this.
I'm like, this is rank narcissism.
Oh yeah.
No.
This is a display of somebody having a breakdown of some kind.
This is not a well person existing in space.
No.
Generally speaking as a bipolar one, delusions of grandeur are usually a big sign that stuff
is going off.
He has delusions of grandeur on a semi-regular basis.
I don't even know if I would categorize it as like feeling manic because like there's
also this, this like, no, it'd be malignant narcissism.
Yeah.
It's a flare up though.
It's bad.
Yeah.
And truly, if I'm the globalist and I know this, you got to kill him.
I mean, there's no big deal.
It's not like whatever backlash you might get from killing him is going to be worse
than having him know your entire plan.
Yeah.
I mean like everybody, I mean the backlash isn't going to be worse.
Well, I mean like think about it.
The conspiracy world still believes that like the man killed Bill Cooper and it didn't unravel
any globalist plot.
Didn't even really bother anybody that much at all.
No.
They just say, hey, Bill Cooper was right and you know that because they killed him.
Yeah, exactly.
That is just what would happen if the globalist killed Alex and if he's the only person who
can see through everything and understand everything, it's not like anybody else.
Yeah.
And if I'm a globalist, even if I'm a pacifist globalist, you know, like I don't want to
solve my problems via murder.
This is a special circumstance.
You just got to do it.
Yeah.
I think that what you've done is provide a pretty decent argument for why there are no
globalists because if they were as demonic and as cutthroat and have been working on
a thousand year plan, like Alex seems to think, yeah, they would have literally no reason
to hold back.
Totally.
And even if you have the protection of God, the God you've got protection from is the
one sending you weird demon nightmares.
Yeah.
That's a weird kid.
No big deal.
Yeah.
So Alex gets down to business doing what he does best, which is reading headlines and
just saying, whoa, gotcha.
About them.
Yeah.
No analysis at all.
Okay.
Where should I start this segment ahead of this big report?
Let's do this.
Let's go ahead and just read headlines in the vaccine stack from today.
Overhead shot, please.
The crew found another article I didn't know of the New York times, right when they were
launching the COVID attack a year and three months ago, it's the end of humanity.
And maybe it's for the best New York times says, get rid of humans.
They're evil.
That's their religion.
This headline that Alex is reading on air is real, but it's in the New York times book
review section.
It's the title of a review of a novel novel by Guido Marcelli titled Despatio HG, which
was published in 1977.
The plot has to do with a suicidal man realizing that all the rest of the humanity has disappeared
and he's the last human around.
In humanity's absence, he waxes philosophical and also notices that nature is taking over
what was previously cities.
From the review quote, beneath the philosophical welter, a new world glitters with pre-lapsarian
strangeness, gangs of plump cats raid administrative lobbies, chamois goats prance along train
tracks, ibixes graze hotel lawns, a sort of one man utopia seems possible.
The phonies and strivers are gone.
The city's churches, banks, and military installations lie abandoned, an index of empire's ruin.
This is a work of fiction that was reviewed in the New York times book section and Alex
is trying to pass it off as some kind of news article or opinion piece.
This is beyond the kind of sloppiness that would get anyone fired anywhere else than
Infowars.
What the fuck is wrong with this shit?
Man, I've got a breaking news story for him.
This comes from the 90s and there was a piece published where a guy specifically said that
it was the end of the world as he knew it.
He felt fine.
And he felt fine.
I remember that.
Which is fucked up.
You know, when you think about it, it's the end of the world and this guy feels fine.
Do you know what that means?
Top globalist, Dan.
Undoubtedly.
Yeah.
I think he also predicted like, uh, uh, uh, there was like an eye of a hurricane and then
he listened to himself churn.
I can't remember the lyrics to that song.
Don't even worry.
It's been a long time.
So Jordan, uh, he's been teasing this, this, uh, report, uh, that he recorded in his car
on the way to the studio, which you were so shallow about his, his vision while he was
hiking.
Yes.
Um, so he's been teasing it a lot.
We keep hearing it.
Right.
And so after this, after reading a slew of headlines, he goes to break.
How far into the episode are we?
Mm, I'm not sure.
Maybe two hours.
Couple hours?
Yeah.
About halfway through?
About lunchtime.
So he's getting about hungry.
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, so he goes to eat lunch and I actually do know that he does that because he says
that.
Okay, good.
So he goes and they play a special report and as they're playing it, I'm listening to
it.
I'm like, this doesn't sound like what he was describing about, uh, agenda 2035 or any
of that stuff.
Is it quiet and cogent?
No, it's just an info or a special report.
So it, like it goes to commercial and then it comes back, mic down for this.
Okay.
This is a amazing freak out.
That I will actually tell you is edited out of the version of this that appears on band.video.
They cut this out.
All right.
There's a lot going on around here at the office and I know you as a listener are focused.
That's fine.
I appreciate that.
You heard me say we're going to air this 2035 report when we come back and I just went off
and had lunch, was getting ready for the report to come on and I saw something else come on
while I was eating lunch.
I was like, holy hell, what's that?
And so I ran back in there and they're like, oh, we didn't know you want to air this report.
So, so that was not a tactic to say coming back 2035.
And so you, the whole show, I'm like saying, it's coming up, it's coming up.
That wasn't a tactic to then, you know, leave you there in the lurch with what we just aired.
It's great.
Everything I do, I shoot in writing from now on, I should have a little computer that puts
a print out for the military does that.
And then it's like a buzz and I can just, cause Cruz, great Cruz, great.
Maybe I should just quit.
Maybe that seriously, I'm thinking about, I've kind of done my mission, haven't I?
Maybe I should just walk out of here and they do a better job and never see me again because
I can either cancel Dr. Francis Boyle coming on to talk about how this is a massive crime
against humanity, a biological weapons attack on humanity and the master plan and what they're
planning and what they're doing.
I had him for an hour, but I also said, I'm going to air this report because I came in
this morning and I said, you got till 1230 to get this report ready and add graphics
to it because we're going to air this.
And then I said, here's the articles I want at 1230 to put over this, this thing we're
going to air.
And then I promoted it and I promoted it and I promoted it and I promoted it and I'm not
even bitching.
I'm trying to understand why I'm the worst communicator.
Worse, do a better job.
Get your ass together now.
I'm serious.
I suck.
I can't get shit in the fricking killing everybody and everybody's in a trance.
All right, let's go to rebroadcast for a while.
We'll see if I can boil on.
I'm serious, man.
I'm two inches from walking out here forever.
Can't do this anymore, man.
We're in a damn war.
They're murdering everybody.
It's funny.
Well, I don't think it's funny here.
Let's hear governor Newsome.
Let's hear Trump one more time.
Tell us how great the vaccines are.
Oh boy, man.
So that sound you heard was him slapping himself.
Yeah.
I just like, this is at a certain point, this isn't a show anymore.
This is a guy breaking down.
Yeah.
I feel bad laughing about it, but I hate him.
And it's kind of funny.
It's hilarious.
Yeah.
Also, did it just occur to you to write out a fucking script or something, an outline?
Right.
Oh, that's what the military, no, that's what all good shows do.
Yeah.
That's called like producing.
It's called producing a show.
Yeah.
And so he has to give a little bit of an apology, obviously.
Obviously.
And he explains that, you know, maybe this is on him.
And yes, that was a real freak out on air earlier because it's normal when world government
is coming in and setting up global passports and basically forced inoculations and doing
it to newborn homeless babies.
And I'm not mad at the crew.
I wasn't clear about airing that report, I guess, to them.
And I want to boil for a whole hour, but I will air that report because it only fits
the fifth, fourth of this segment.
And then you've got John Rappaport coming on and that'll be really memed earlier of
me slapped myself in the face.
But I am mad at myself.
I wish I did a better job.
Yeah, me too.
I, man, I just love this as a bookend because the episode begins with him talking about
how great it was that the crew psychically knew the video that he wanted to play.
Yep.
Very beautiful.
He didn't even tell them he wanted to play.
You know what, Dan?
I'm going to tell you this right now.
My stone cold heart.
Yep.
Not wrong.
He said it on the show that we're premiering this report at a certain time.
Right.
And I guess the producers aren't listening to the show to get that report ready.
I suppose maybe we should have talked about this before the show started.
It's pretty remarkable.
Yeah.
I love it though.
Bananas.
Yep.
So he has Francis Boyle on and I don't care anymore about that guy.
Yeah.
Because, you know, you have this whole thing where it's like, okay, for months we're talking
about how the coronavirus itself is a bioweapon that Fauci made in this lab and now we're
going to be doing the vaccine as a bioweapon that Fauci made.
Yeah.
I'm tired.
This is boring.
Francis Doyle frustrates me.
Boyle.
Apologies.
Frustrates me because if you are named Francis Boyle, I assume you have been knighted.
I don't know why, but if your name is Francis Boyle, it better be Sir Francis Boyle.
Probably because Arthur Conan Doyle?
Probably.
Yeah.
But it does sound right.
It kind of does.
It does sound right.
Yeah.
So he makes the, what I'm going to call the Larry Nichols mistake and that is that he
gives Alex permission to give out his phone number on the website to help info warriors
with legal advice or to assist their lawyers because he's not licensed to practice in one
state.
But he'll advise their lawyers on how to help them not get vaccinated.
Good work.
I don't care.
Stupid Francis Boyle.
Yup.
Anyway, we jump to the 18th now because that interview goes and I thought it would be funny
not to cover his report that he had from his car because it's a zero.
Yeah.
That sounds right.
And there are honestly more pressing issues like this that Alex gets into at the beginning
of his March 18th show.
And all over the place, the leaders of the LGBT movements keep getting arrested for having
sex with 10 year olds and 11 year olds because the truth is it wasn't about gay marriage.
It was always about sex with your children because it's a satanic ritual to drain off
their energy, to drain off their innocence and drain off their future.
The only thing they like better is chopping your children up with a meat cleaver while
they rape them.
And I'm sorry to have to tell you that, but that's what the big boys do.
So this is a kind of moment that you might describe as a mask off a situation.
Yeah.
He doesn't pretend all that he wants that he's a libertarian and that he doesn't care
what people do in their bedroom.
But underneath all that belief is this, which is the classical trope of homophobic rhetoric.
Yep.
To put this in context, Alex has found a story about a judge in Wisconsin named Brett Blom,
who was arrested on suspicion of uploading child pornography to websites.
He apparently was a family court judge and had formerly been the president of an organization
called Cream City Foundation, which is a philanthropic organization advocating for members of the
LGBTQ plus community.
And in the past, that foundation had sponsored some drag queen story hour events.
So naturally this is being presented in right wing media as this guy being the head of drag
queen story hour.
What Alex is doing is engaging in selective coverage.
He makes a big deal out of every time that someone in a group of people he wants to attack
gets arrested for a horrible crime and he ignores the other instances where the perpetrator
is someone who's a member of a group that he doesn't want to portray as evil.
When there's a school shooting, it's just an individual doing a terrible thing.
And in those cases, Alex fully understands how bad it can be to engage in collective
blame for individual actions.
Most of his career is based on yelling about how gun owners will be blamed for things like
Sandy Hook or the Las Vegas shooting.
You have to resist that or else you get guns taken.
But when you get right down to it, Alex does the far worse version of ascribing collective
blame for the actions of individuals because he's doing it to malign and attack historically
marginalized groups of people.
Any immigrant committing a crime becomes proof that immigrants are all criminals and killers.
The crimes of any gay person becomes proof that the LGBTQ rights movement is secretly
about trying to have sex with kids.
I'm certain most of the listeners don't need this spelled out, but this is profoundly dangerous
because what it achieves is coupling the perception of criminality with an entire group of people
based on the actions of an individual who's a member of that group.
And this is just unacceptable.
No, that's, that's just so fucked.
Yeah.
It's just so fucked.
Ah, God.
It just doesn't end.
It just never ends.
No matter how much fucking violence we see on a daily basis, it is still a man out there
trying to get people attacked.
And it's just so fucked.
Yep.
Ugh.
So, um, we're not going to dwell too much on that, uh, because like a lot of that does
surround like a lot of the sort of gross stuff that Alex, uh, I don't, I don't, uh, respect
him to handle and I don't want to replay on our show, but I felt that that rose to a level
of like, okay, Alex is saying that the sort of LGBTQ rights movement and the push for
gay marriage was actually secretly about trying to have sex with kids.
And I think a moment like that does deserve a place on our show because it reveals something
that's under the surface of his, his, his, his worldview, his, his beliefs, and that's
fucked up.
It's a, he's, that's, that's where he's at.
Yep.
And it's a, it's even more explicit than whenever he was like LGBTQP or whatever it was where
he was trying to add that in there.
And it's just, it's just, yep.
Hate him.
Yep.
I hate him.
Yeah.
Alex is mad that, uh, Biden has said some tough words about Putin.
Sure.
Sure, sure, sure.
And I get the sense from listening to this episode, March 18th, that there's a, there's
a sense that Alex loves Putin.
Real pro the Monarch that he wishes would take over the United States.
I think he wishes Trump was more like Bolsonaro or Putin, quite frankly.
And I think he would rather one of them invade the United States.
He wanted a God King strong man and instead he got a God King grifter.
He got a front man for the mob.
Yeah, exactly.
And so now he's like, Oh, look at what could have been, we could have had a 30 year monstrosity
of a Russian rule.
Great.
And so I think he's going back to that.
Cool.
And so there he is up there not knowing what planet he's on and he's on national TV saying
that Russia is going to pay soon and that they're going to be coming after him and that
we're going to kill her with no soul.
And that's why Putin then said, you actually need to look in the mirror, but let's talk
about what Putin has done.
What Putin's really up to Putin slashed the Russian defense budget in the last eight years
over and over again, he pulled troops out of all these different places.
He launched a national organic drives and they want to supply the world organic food
and with cleaner fossil fuels, they have a program to promote marriage and Christianity
and they are decrying the Carnegie foundation, the Ford foundation, Rockefeller foundation,
the Soros foundations, and are saying they want to post human world and that Russia is
not for it.
And so the globalists are very, very upset because they had Russia for 80 plus years
in their demonic clutches.
It's so funny to me because like last weekend I was watching Alex's documentaries for some
prep on some stuff and I watched terror storm, I believe it was in terror storm.
They kind of blend together cause they're very repetitive, but he was talking about
how he had proven that Putin bombed those apartment buildings.
Yeah.
Well, I mean it's not hard.
I know.
But then like on the, on the Y2K episode that he did, he was talking about how Putin looks
like a demon.
He's going to seize power or I just, I don't know.
It's weird.
That doesn't, it doesn't mean anything.
It's just wherever the wind blows with my prejudices today.
Yep.
And then so long as you stick within the relative boundaries of those prejudices, I'll support
you forever.
But if you break away, like say you support vaccines, then you're fucking done.
Yeah.
And I think that he recognizes that Putin is a leader that would protect the things
that are important to him, which is sort of heteronormative, white, masculine-based society.
I mean, consider the treatment of the LGBTQ people in fucking Russia.
Yeah, of course.
So Alex, I like it when he gets a little heady.
But I like this even more.
If you read the Sumerian text, or the Egyptian hieroglyphs, or the Aztec hieroglyphs, or
the ancient Dead Sea Scrolls, it's a bunch of translations from 2000 plus years ago from
things 4,000, 5,000 years old.
It tells the same story.
We go to India, they have 6,000 year old hieroglyphs.
China, 6,000 year old stone carvings that tell the same story.
A story we'll talk about here in just one moment.
The story of Jesus.
But first, let's talk about keeping the broadcast on the air.
I want to thank you all for your support.
It's a symbiotic relationship.
You get great products at the same time, but it takes a lot of money to run this operation.
We have to have our own infrastructure, our own crews.
I love it.
I feel like he slapped me in the face three times.
All societies over the course of all history have told the same story, and I will explain
it to you after.
Let's talk about money real quick, because I need it.
That's the real story that's been told over and over again throughout history.
So Alex does a really, really long plug.
Fairly long plug.
I don't even know what's long anymore.
Listening to his show, my radar is skewed.
Time is meaningless.
But he has a bit of a plug, and then he gets into what I think maybe is what the Mesopotamians
were all about.
Okay.
All right, let me do this, because I can't in five minutes or six minutes do it justice
in this segment.
But when I start the next hour, I'm going to get into humanoid and what that means and
how many times I've told you about this, and I want to be very, very clear.
I didn't predict this.
They admitted to producing humanoids 50 years ago, 50 years ago.
Right about 50 years ago, humanoids were already created, and by the way, humanoids were taken
to term.
50 years ago?
There are humanoids, quite a few of them.
We don't know the actual numbers, but a lot of governments worked on them.
So when you see movies in the 80s about replicants, they already have them, but they're not supermen.
Most of them are mentally retarded, have horrible genetic disorders, and are just in hellish
situations.
Yeah, so we already, of course, know about the fish people with sad human eyes.
Yes, naturally.
And then now we have tons of replicants walking around.
Uh, yeah.
Apparently.
Why?
I don't know.
I was going to take this seriously.
This has to do with more stories about advancements that are being made in replacement organ kind
of technologies.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
Uh, I was going to take it seriously, but then he said this, and I'm like, I'm out.
And here's the promise that Joe Biden and Ted Turner and Bill Gates have been given
by the little nasty dudes giving them this technology.
You might have heard of them.
The Bible calls them demons, not of this world, not very friendly.
They're being promised life extension, but they first got to kill us and test on us.
And the truth is these torture us and mutate us and do horrible things to us because they
know what we grow into and what we do.
We're kept pure and come together as a species.
But that is not the case.
This is actually a giant genetic war on the planet and we've been set up for this.
So I just think you should get ready for that.
If there's a story about some scientific breakthrough or some kind of scientific story, just some
story that's going on, I find that interesting.
But I don't care to talk about it realistically when it's being presented to me as part of
a plot where Joe Biden is going to get life extension technology, which was promised by
a demon.
Right.
Well, they're nasty dudes, called demons in the Bible, but they're otherworldly.
They're just nasty dudes.
Are you a nasty enough dude to extend the president's life is a question that I believe
video games asked.
I certainly am not.
Yeah, I just don't...
Once this is the realm we're in, any real conversation doesn't matter.
Once it's aliens or demons, nah buddy, I'm out.
Also anytime he says pure, I don't want him to expand upon that.
We all know.
It's better if he leaves it alone.
Stay away from the...
He shouldn't be allowed to say the word pure.
It comes off his lips poorly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It doesn't sound good.
No.
This is pure OJ.
What does that mean?
Is it white inside?
What do you want?
But in terms of the purity that he's talking about, I think he means fully human.
I think he does.
Although I don't disagree with you.
No, he does.
He does.
I believe so.
Yeah.
People in his community have an unhealthy relationship with the term pure.
Yes.
But I think he's talking about all humans, not humanoids.
Right.
So at this point in the show, Alex goes to calls, and this is one of the more uncomfortable
and unpleasant set of calls that he's taken, because it has to do with the vaccine.
It's all Harrison Smith calling in?
Oh, no.
That would at least...
At least that wouldn't be this...
This is depressing.
I think this could get people killed.
Oh, that's not good.
Yeah.
Because they're talking about the vaccine stuff.
And Alex has some bad medical advice, and then he also just is acting weird with these
people.
He's one caller.
He calls in, and he's talking about how his dad got the vaccine and then died.
And Alex's response is a little weird.
He was in and out, and he knew that's what did it.
Yeah.
God almighty, Ralph, who do you blame?
I would blame Bill Gates and the media.
People say, oh, all these famous sports stars that died, they deserved it.
No, they did it.
They said, I want to protect people.
They were tough guys.
They did it because they were lied to.
They were actually heroes.
Your dad, I believe, meant well and was a hero at the end of the day.
But what about the people that did this on purpose, brother?
Yeah.
Bill Gates and the globalists.
And I would love to meet Bill Gates.
I'll tell you that.
That's weird.
That's a weird response to have when someone's telling you this story about their dad passing
away fairly recently for you to ask, who do you blame?
We have a term, literally very, very old term.
Yeah.
For the thing that he is asking the man to do, and we say it in a bad context.
What's that?
It's called a scapegoat, Dan.
Who do you blame is not a good question ever.
No, it's definitely not.
It's rude too.
Yeah.
I don't think that caller took it as rude, but it is.
Who do you want me to kill is another answer for it.
Your dad was murdered.
Who do you blame?
Well, the thing is, it's bizarre and it's pointless to any real conversation that you
want to have that would have public value, but it's important to understand this element
of why this is exactly what Alex would ask, because this is an intensely painful story
if it's true.
I'm not sure it's just somebody calling into Alex's show, but assuming that it is real,
that's fucking super hard.
Dude lost his dad recently, and even if the guy's in poor health, that's still really
hard.
Yeah.
The idea is to take feelings like the one this caller is experiencing and translate
them into feelings of anger and hate directed at the people Alex has decided are his enemies.
Now, he's talking specifically about Bill Gates and what have you, but make no mistake,
this exact sort of transmutation of pain into hate and anger is exactly what happens towards
the marginalized communities that Alex attacks and demonizes.
It's exactly the same.
It's witch shit.
Yeah.
It is witch shit.
Do you blame the witches?
Of course it's the witches.
It stopped raining.
Do you blame the witch?
No, that's God.
The demons make it rain and God makes it sunny.
Duh.
Okay.
God, I hate people.
Yeah.
Alex gets another call, and this guy was saying that his dad got a shot and then maybe had
some indications that he might have prostate cancer.
Here's how this goes.
So my dad is a medical doctor and he had the second round of the vaccine and now he just
received word that his PSA levels and his prostate are high, which obviously are an
indication of potential cancer, so now he has to have a biopsy on his prostate.
Well, they actually said that, sir.
They said when you...
So did he take the Pfizer or Moderna?
I want to say Pfizer, but I'm not 100% sure on that.
Yeah, it's the mRNA that anything that's already precancerous makes it basically go cancerous.
They admit that.
Wow.
So now they want a biopsy of his prostate.
Can he show them the literature saying that it makes hormone-based tissues swell up and
that they should not do any biopsies for six months?
Oh, I guess I was not aware of that.
I mean, I've tried to send him videos and stuff.
He just...
Yeah, guys, type in, doctors say don't be alarmed after mRNA vaccine if your glands,
uterus, prostate swell up.
Yeah, that's what it does, sir.
Okay.
Whether or not COVID-19 vaccines can cause the side effect of gland swelling, this is
so irresponsible of Alex.
If this caller's dad, who is a doctor, has reason to suspect he may have prostate cancer,
he needs to take appropriate steps to make sure one way or another, because the key to
treatment is early detection.
Alex's advice for him to avoid getting a biopsy and just assume it's probably a side effect
of the vaccine, even though the caller can't even remember which vaccine his dad got, that
could get people hurt.
Alex is misrepresenting a recent article from the Cleveland Clinic titled, quote, don't
be alarmed by this COVID-19 vaccine side effect that could be confused with breast cancer.
This deals with possible swelling of the lymph nodes under your arm as a side effect of the
COVID-19 vaccine, which is relevant because that's also a sign of breast cancer.
This has nothing to do with prostate swelling and Alex should be immediately taken off air
for offering this reckless medical advice to his audience and to his caller.
To be clear, this caller is probably going to be fine.
His dad seems to not believe this bullshit and he's a doctor, so I would imagine he's
taking appropriate actions to protect his own health.
My son sent me YouTube videos and I'm a doctor.
I think I'm gonna get a biopsy.
The problem is with listeners who hear this and think Alex knows anything, what if one
of them has a possible cancer symptom that they decide to overlook because Alex told
them it's just a vaccine side effect?
Legitimately, that has the potential to get people hurt.
If you have, God forbid, some kind of swelling or some kind of a symptom of cancer outside
of, even if it is the lymph nodes in your arm, you should probably make sure and go
talk to a doctor.
But if it's in some other area and you hear Alex being like, oh, we got all the literature,
you shouldn't get a biopsy for six months, that six months could be critical.
It's fucked up.
This is one of the instances of me being like very much, there should be a consequence for
this.
Yeah.
If there's a consequence for telling people to drink bleach, there should be a consequence
for telling people not to get a medical treatment or not to do, yeah, no, that's...
It's outrageous.
Yeah.
That is, it is just as bad to say like, hey, here's a cure for your problem as it is to
say, don't seek out medical attention because you should listen to me.
Yeah, you're fine.
Exactly.
Yeah, that's fucked.
Yeah.
So this next caller, this person actually kind of tickled me with their voice.
I enjoy this guy's voice.
Okay.
Hey Alex, what's up man?
Man, I'm just watching the new Holocaust, brother.
I hear you, man.
Hey man, I can't believe I'm talking to you.
Hold on.
I've been listening to you since I was six.
That depressed me.
Oh boy.
I like him calling him man over and over again.
Yeah, that is nice.
That's kind of...
Hey man.
I like his little twang.
He's doing all right.
Hey man, what's going on Alex?
Hey buddy.
Yeah.
I like it.
Listening since he was six.
No, that's not good.
You can't understand things at six.
The kind of topics that Alex is covering, you have no ability to gauge or to measure
... holy shit.
At a time whenever everyone is telling you that your dreams are not real, you are listening
to a man tell you about how his dreams are real.
That's not good.
And that's how you get political awareness.
Yeah, that's definitely not good.
No.
Oh boy.
Yeah, I mean, what is six?
Like, or yeah, what is... second grade?
What is that?
First grade, I think.
Yeah, that's not good.
I was playing, I remember I would finish my work early so I could play with dinosaurs.
And I remember nobody telling me that dinosaurs were actually put there by, oh wait, no, I
disagree.
I was told that dinosaurs were put there by God to test our faith when I was six.
So well, that didn't have any negative effects on me, Dan.
Six was the first year that I lived in Hawaii.
Like I was, the first grade, holy shit, I look, I think back on like, I didn't know
anything.
Nothing.
I imagine listening to Alex from that age.
I am going to, I'm going to listen to Alex while I work on my multiplication tables real
quick.
So I, okay, so three times four is 12 and 12 is the number of the Illuminati trying
to kill me.
This has meaning.
Yep.
Oh boy.
The teacher might be the devil.
She doesn't know shit.
She's the devil.
Yeah.
I think it would be tough to live that way.
And I mean like I would come home from school and I would do homework sometimes watching
TRL.
Yeah.
This guy's listening to Alex yell about the devil.
Also, he seems positively cheerful for someone who has absorbed all of Alex's bullshit.
Man.
And once you hear about what's happened in his life recently, you'll be even more surprised
that he's that chipper.
Oh wow.
I don't know, man.
And then, you know, just like this whole COVID, they're such liars, man, and my wife lost
my wife last year because I couldn't really get her proper medical attention genetic.
She had a genetic condition and had, and she had real bad CLPD and she would, you would
not go to the hospital because they wouldn't let me stay with her.
She wouldn't.
She would not stay.
Oh yeah.
That's the whole thing.
Not letting you go in cause the COVID so they can run a dictatorship inside there.
That's right.
And I wasn't going to let her stay without me because I knew if they got her in there
with her condition, she was probably done for.
Well, they would have got a fake PCR test and then innovated her for the money.
Yeah, I know it.
And so anyway, basically we just sit at home till she died.
Jesus.
I mean, that's so sad.
That's a person who...
Alex killed his wife.
I mean, not individually, but like that information's fear of like insisting that they're going
to kill you for the COVID money made it so she didn't get appropriate care and sat at
home and died.
If true.
Again, this is just somebody calling into Alex's show.
Yeah.
And he's calling and complimenting the guy who he's been listening to since he was six,
who got it deep into his head that you can't let your wife go without, wow.
This episode has a body count.
This is a, this is a body count.
Yeah.
It really is.
Hypothetical future and like- That's just so fucked up.
It is like, that's how fucked up your brain gets.
I would rather blame, I would rather lose my wife.
I would rather lose my wife and still believe that I am following the correct path than
I would confront reality and save my wife's life or whatever, you know, improve her life
materially.
I mean, the alternative was you think you have this paranoid delusion about this conspiracy
that she's going to die if she goes to the hospital while she did die by not going to
the hospital.
Yep.
I don't understand how this is a win.
It's not, it's so fucking sad.
Wow.
That is just so fucking sad.
Yep.
And it's so awful when these like human stories, if true, penetrate through Alex's show and
they aren't taken as seriously as they really are.
Like that's, that's profoundly messed up.
And you have this and it's like, okay, these are glimpses into some of these people's lives
who have been affected by Alex's content, presumably since they were six.
Yeah.
And, and at the same time, the show, the day prior was a complete freak out of him just
being emotionally unhinged, yelling about how he needs to quit because the staff won't
get his video out on time and how he has nightmares of the devil eating his unborn children.
Yeah.
Like it's, that's the same person who is being looked at as an expert by this guy who let
his wife die at home.
Here's what you get empathetically from him, a quieter, sorry, and then continuing to yell
as if, and as if you weren't listening to somebody tell you, Hey, you're responsible
for my wife's death.
Well, and what you're going to get is that sort of, Hey, sorry about that, but then you're
also going to get a doubling down and a reinforcing and a validating of the exact conspiracy nonsense
that led you and your wife to not getting appropriate care.
It's, it's terrifying.
This is straight up real cult leadership.
This is 100% a your wife died and it's because of everybody but the cult leader.
That's just so fucked.
She would have lived if they wouldn't have killed her at the hospital.
Okay.
You know what happened in my cult?
The cult leader was responsible for the death of a child as was his parents and everything
that they believed in.
And whenever that child died due to their lack of care, their denial of care and their
belief that caring for the child at a hospital or even considering medicine would be a sin.
That guy went to jail.
Yeah.
Everybody has the right to accept or refuse medical care.
And so like, I am not going to do that.
I'm not going to play that game.
Sure.
But when you are responding to misinformation or cult leadership and that is what is motivating
you.
Yeah.
It's a completely different thing.
No.
That is, that is a crime.
Yeah.
Yep.
No question in my mind.
So that's just, I feel like when I, this is the complicated, like difficult push and
pull of listening to this show.
It's like, I kind of feel bad about myself because I'll laugh at what's clearly a guy
freaking out and having an emotionally unbalanced day on the 17th and I'll feel bad.
Yeah.
And then I'll get to this and I'll be like, I don't feel bad.
How can, how can he, how can he deserve any consideration?
No.
None.
I, it's just a...
It's difficult to preserve your humanity when faced with such inhumanity.
Like just true psychopathy of, I just, I'm such a narcissist that I can hear this story
that I bear responsibility, at least partially, for the death of this man's wife.
And I'm just going to tell him that he was so great.
I have a strong sense that Alex would not have kept his wife at home.
No, his wife would be in a hospital immediately.
Very expensive one.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
No, it's, it's so, it's just such what you see.
And I, you know, you want to provide empathy for this because you are a human being and
you can't allow yourself to let empathy die.
It challenges me.
It's tough.
But when you get past a certain point, it's just like, fuck you.
It's hard.
Anyway, let's get that...
For good and forever.
Let's put that behind us and listen to Alex.
This is not, you belong to the city, but it is Alex doing some bumper music and rambling
about nonsense just to sort of cleanse our palette on the way out of this episode.
This is a little Daft Punk track from the Tron Legacy soundtrack.
All right, okay.
The grid, a digital frontier.
I tried to picture clusters of information as they moved through the computer.
What did they look like?
Ships, motorcycles.
Were the circuits like freeways?
And then one day I kept dreaming of a world I thought I'd never see.
And then one day, one day, I got in and you found out it was a off-world demonic inter-spatial
attack.
Bring down the species and the collaborators were working with Satan against God's plan
to bring us down.
One day, I got in and when you come at it from that perspective, it all makes sense
and you understand it all and the enemy finally respects you.
I'm sorry?
She sees you as an enemy soldier.
What?
They don't laugh when we talk about that.
They look back at us and say, that's right.
We chose the winner.
We're going to lose.
We both laughed.
I laughed significantly.
I would argue that I did not just laugh.
I went for it, buddy.
Yeah, I guess the enemy respects you once you...
I really don't think they do.
Those three imaginary king globalists that have the same understanding of the plan as
Alex, they have a lot of respect for him though.
That's probably true.
That sounds right.
Like Achilles and Hector eventually had a respect for each other, although I believe
that was after Hector was dead.
But you know, it's just like that.
Yeah, so Ezra Levant comes on the show towards the end of this episode and he's just complaining
that the US Navy hired researchers at the University of Arkansas to spy on him and his
website and then somehow somebody sold that report to Justin Trudeau.
I can't find...
I'm sorry, what?
I don't know.
Okay.
Well, this is more than an article on Rebel Media where the report is referred to as Canada
Election Cyber Forensics Analysis at the date October 10th, 2019.
The actual report isn't linked there, and I have no idea if it's real, so I was trying
to get to the bottom of it and I Googled it, and guess what the first thing that comes
up if you Google those words is?
Bullshit?
Is a page where Rebel Media is doing a donor drive called Cyber Intelligence Operation
Donation using this alleged report as the bait on the hook of a pledge drive.
Quote, unlike the CBC, we don't get a billion dollars a year, so if you can chip in to help
cover our costs and fight back against the lies, we would appreciate it.
I don't know if this is real or not, and Ezra Levant is a bigot and a career liar, so I'm
not even going to pretend to take him seriously until he produces the report.
Yeah.
I don't care.
Oh, man.
But he does say something kind of funny.
Well, you know what?
Where's the ACLU?
If it was the Young Turks or Jim Acosta or MSNBC or even Ellen or some of the leftists
on The View who were spied on, it would be top news.
You're Canadian.
Wait.
If it were Ellen, you're Canadian.
It's the ACLU.
Where's the ACLU?
Dan, where is the ACLU?
I mean that seriously.
Is there a physical location for the ACLU?
He was asking an honest question, Dan.
I don't know if the ACLU does work with people who aren't protected by American civil liberties.
It's the First Amendment rights of...
The ACLU isn't in Canada, are they?
They may, but I just do think that's funny.
That is very funny.
Putting them on blast.
Where is the ACLU?
If Ellen was spied upon to help her get elected Canada's Prime Minister, oh, she'd be pissed.
Probably a coincidence that right now Ezra Levant is in the middle of a defamation trial
for saying that somebody was involved in a terrorist attack if they weren't involved
in it.
Probably a coincidence.
It doesn't come up.
I'm surprised by that.
On Alex's interview.
Yeah, it doesn't come up.
It seems like that would be the first thing I would want to talk about.
Yeah.
Get out in front of that thing.
Nope.
He gets for $200,000.
I think that's a couple of new donors.
That'll do it.
Yeah, he's going to need a lot of new donors.
Yeah.
Let's see.
He's being sued.
According to Chalk's statement in the claim, that's the person who's suing him.
Sure.
Levant alleged during his February 25th, 2014 broadcast that Chalk was involved in a shooting
at an Edmonton nightclub in 1993 when Chalk was 19.
Chalk was acquitted of the 1993 charges in what he called a case of mistaken identity.
He vehemently denied any involvement in the shooting, saying he was at his parents' house
with friends and had absolutely no knowledge of what transpired.
Yeah, so I don't know.
I don't know how that trial's going to go.
I think he's going to win that lawsuit, buddy.
I think there's a reason that legitimate news outlets don't just print the first name they
can find.
I don't know how that's going to play out, but I do think it's a little bit of maybe
an Alex Jones money bomb type situation that's being... I don't know.
It'd be funny if he was like, where's the ACLU and they're representing the other guy.
That would be quite funny.
I would enjoy that an immense amount.
That dude's not an... I don't know if he's an American either.
Anyway, this episode's been a little bit of a bummer for me, T to B, top to bottom, but
it is over now.
Is that the new way we sign off?
Yes.
The episode is over now.
Well, I mean, such high highs of the freak out that got edited out of Alex's own show.
That's a bad one.
Again, try an outline.
One time.
Quite an amazing thing, too, to see.
There's a point when Alex says shit and I was like, wow, I've got to go find this on
the...
Of course.
It's gone.
Just gone.
From the banned on video version.
Oh, man.
So he's censoring himself, if you will.
It got banned from banned.
They cut that whole thing out and put the right video in where the wrong video was put.
What a bunch of liars.
Those motherfuckers.
That's bullshit.
Did it in post.
I'm furious.
Yeah.
So that was the fun.
And then 18th is so depressing.
And the other thing is the guests, I just don't care.
You had Francis Boyle on the first one.
Sir Francis Boyle.
Excuse me.
And then you had Duke, Ezra Levant on the other one, and neither of them were people
I care about much at all.
I mean, if they're going to bring something to the table that was interesting, maybe,
but they didn't.
Yeah.
And yeah.
I don't know.
I may, now that we've had two episodes back in the present, I grow weary of it.
May try and time travel for Monday.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There is a little bit of that.
Yeah, we'll see what happens.
Anyway, Jordan, we'll be back.
But until then, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yep.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledge underscore fight and I go to bed Jordan.
We're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook.
Will you tell us, right?
If you could, please find a local charity or a bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work.
Yep.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I'm the Juiciest Ice Cube.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.