N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys.
Dan and Jordan.
Knowledgefight.
Riddle her.
I need money.
Andy and Kansas.
Stop it.
It's time to pray.
Andy and Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a fish and color.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your room.
Knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledgefight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes that like to sit around, drink novelty beverages and talk just a little
bit about Alex Jones.
Oh indeed we are Dan.
Jordan.
I have a quick question for you.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today is another counter shout out.
Another counter shout out.
Counter bright spot.
A counter bright spot.
Aha.
An anti bright spot.
I could not resist the urge while I was sitting around in the house.
I saw those Coca Cola with coffee staring at me.
You did it again.
Then I tried the vanilla one.
I swear you learn better than anyone else in certain areas and in others you're simply
impossible.
I'm a glutton for punishment.
You are.
When it comes to weird packaged goods.
I've never had it before, it's like your guiding light whenever you're at a store.
Yeah but it also, it's a pretty specific space.
That's true.
Because if it was like Coca Cola now with octopus.
Right, right, right.
That's not going to do it.
It has to also intrigue you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I get ya.
And kind of a really like 13 year old kid might get excited by this kind of way.
Ooh it's a new type of Nerds.
That's my sweet spot.
Speaking of which they have those Nerds clusters.
They got the Nerds Ropes?
They got Nerds clusters.
No, Nerds Ropes came out like 15, 20 years ago.
Okay fine, fine.
We sold those at the movie theater I used to work out when I was like 17.
I'm sorry I'm not a snack nerd if you will Dan.
So I tried the vanilla one and I gotta say it was better.
Okay.
Still really bad.
All right, all right.
Still disgusting.
Okay.
But it was kind of like you know the vanilla masked some of the problems of the coffee.
Sure.
Let's add a fourth flavor in here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's throw, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's just keep tossing stuff in there.
Cherry vanilla coffee coke, let's see if we can fucking make this taste not atrocious.
It's like when somebody describes wine tea and they're like it's got an oaky finish and
there's hints of fruit in there and somebody's like well what if we just added all those
flavors into coke?
It'd be like a regular drink.
Yeah, yeah.
I say sommelier, I say nay.
Samala nay.
I'm gonna try the caramel one at some point.
Well, of course.
Naturally.
You're already a pot committed here.
This is-
That's in the fridge.
Yeah, it's there.
I'm gonna drink it at some point.
It's just a matter of how long and how many times will I stare at it before I try.
Yeah.
What's your Bright Spot?
My Bright Spot, Dan, is it happens to be a very beautiful day in Chicago and my partner
and I went and played tennis and wow, the outside is nice, Dan.
You remember the outside?
I've heard a, I've heard tale of it.
What were you doing?
You were doing it, you were, what do you do on the show again?
Uh, the work.
You were working on the-
Yeah, I was doing that part of it while you were enjoying the outdoors.
There is that.
It's great that you get to do that.
Wow, we also frequently have conversations about how much I love nature and how you think
it sucks to go away.
There is that, yes.
I'm a man of many contradictions, Dan.
Well, I'm glad you had fun playing big time ping pong.
Uh, yeah, it was great.
Big old ping pong?
Yeah, it's real big.
That was the original name.
Originally ping pong was called whiff waff in the United States, but before that tennis
was called great big whiff waff.
What's pickleball?
Uh, pickleball is-
Is that related to tennis?
Isn't it the one where it's got the whiffleball and there's holes in it and you do the thing
with the pickles?
I don't know.
I don't think pickles are actually involved.
I'm not sure that they're not.
I've heard that word said a lot and I don't know what it is.
I have heard pickleball as well.
Please don't send me messages about it, I'm going to look into it as soon as we stop recording.
We're going to need 3,000 messages.
So, Jordan, today we've got an interesting episode to go over.
We're going to be doing a little bit of a time travel adventure.
Come back in time or forward?
You ask that every time and we can't go forward, I've tried.
We are going back to 2010, the magical 11 year old time of 2010.
Sure, sure.
Things were so different.
Yeah, it's like the turn of the millennium, but instead of the Iraq war, we had more of
the Iraq war.
Sure, sure.
We had the midterms coming up.
We had the Mayan apocalypse on the horizon.
Sure, that's still to come.
Certainly.
Yeah, yeah.
A lot of interesting stuff happening.
So, I'm excited to dabble in on this, but before we get into that, let's take a little
moment to say thank you to some folks who have joined up and are now policy wonks.
That's a great idea.
So first, Dr. Yummy Feet, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, Dr. Yummy Feet.
Thank you.
Next, Brendan, the policy wonk.
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, Brendan, the policy wonk, policy wonk.
Thank you.
Kranthulus the 12th, conqueror of five empires, lord of the blood pits of Fentha, Fathna,
excuse me.
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, Fathna gets really pissed if you don't pronounce their name properly.
It's true.
Yeah, it's a brutal, brutal feeling.
But I'm known for my mispronunciations of locations.
That's true.
I'm sure the Fathnians will.
So it's on, hashtag, on brand.
Okay.
Next, Paranoid Lemming, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, Paranoid Lemming.
Thank you.
Thanks for the brain worms, Jon, much love from E, thank you so much, you are now a policy
wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
This might be connected.
What's that?
I do believe that these are both about the same person.
Okay, we have a policy wonk pile on.
So the next one is, Jon, I blame you for getting jokerfied, love rex, thank you so much, you
are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much to all of you.
I think Jon is maybe getting some people into the show.
Jon, you gotta get to, damn.
So thanks, Jon.
So Jordan, like I said, we're going back in time, and I've made this call on the show
before, and I think I did it at a time when we had a smaller audience than we do now,
and maybe this will have a little bit more reach, and so if anybody out there listening
has access to really old Alex Jones episodes, like late 90s, early 2000s, please reach out.
I would like to try and find a way to get my hands on stuff from like 95, 96, 97, and
if anybody has a line on those, I've tried a number of avenues and they all kind of reach
dead ends.
A lot of people have some tips.
Did you text him?
No.
Oh.
I have not, I've considered that a last option.
That assumes that you already have his number.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, Alex, you up?
Hey, Alex, what up?
You got those old episodes for me.
There are a number of paths that I've gone down that seemed like, oh, this'll work out.
It's kind of difficult.
I think there's some, the episodes exist somewhere.
I know that for sure, but it's very, very difficult to find them in any meaningful way.
You think the Smithsonian has them?
Got to.
Library of Congress?
Of course.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, somebody's got to.
So today, Jordan, I was trying to find a fun time travel thing to do and you know, it's
tough.
It's a challenge.
Yeah.
And you're a witch, so you have high standards.
My standards for witchcraft are real.
Yeah, exactly.
I got a message from a guy by the name of Kirby Ferguson, who does some videos on YouTube
and Kirby had just finished up a duo of videos about Joe Rogan and Alex's last interview
and sort of the, some of the techniques and the styles that are used in the conversation.
Sure.
And I really enjoyed watching that.
It was really a nice thing.
And so I started thinking like, let's find some Rogan.
Oh no.
So I went back to September 15th, 2010 and found.
Welcome ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome and thank you for joining us.
It's September 15th on this Wednesday, 2010 transmission.
I got a call last night, Joe Rogan host of Ultimate Fighting is in town and he was inviting
me tonight to see the UFC and I said, Hey, why don't you come in the studio and get his
view on politics and quote conspiracies.
So that is good, but that wouldn't be enough.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's not enough.
This is before the Joe Rogan experience, right?
Or like at the very beginning of it, maybe.
I would have a hard time knowing exactly when it started.
I know that he promotes Joe Rogan.net, which is his website.
That's where the Rogan experience was initially.
So I could see it maybe being in like its earliest stages.
At the very least, we know he does not have $100 million yet.
He certainly doesn't, but he does have a friend.
And Eddie Bravo is a jiu-jitsu master.
He's also going to be in studio with Joe today.
So we got an episode from 2010 with Alex, Eddie, and Joe Rogan in Alex's studio.
I thought this would be a fun little thing to glimpse back on scene.
Take a little bit of a load off from the present day nonsense, maybe be a little bit lighter.
This was back when Eddie Bravo was still a practicing doctor, I believe, right?
Doctor jiu-jitsu.
Yeah.
He is licensed.
He's a, boy, he's not made for FCC controlled things.
Oh yeah?
Why do you say that?
We'll get to it when we get to it.
So Alex is going to talk to them at the end of the show.
That's third hour business.
Sure, sure, sure.
So I was like, I wonder what's going on beforehand and what sort of show they're, you know, by
appearing on it and being advertised as guests on the show.
What are they basically endorsing?
What are they elevating?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What's going on?
Yeah.
And so we get to Alex talking about how back when his grandmas was around, you know, in
grandma's time it was offensive to see a belly button in I Dream of Jeannie, but now society
is collapsing.
Oh boy.
In fact, last night I was talking to my mom and she was discussing her grandmother back
in the sixties was over at their house and she saw I Dream of Jeannie and she was just
shocked by the fact that the woman's navel was visible.
And now, you know, you can make fun of people who are shocked by things like that, but civilizations
have been wild and decadent and crazy before and people figure out, hey, we better control
this to some level.
Put away the belly button.
Or it causes society to collapse because it's a slippery slope.
One belly button.
Now look at the culture.
It's the end of days.
People see millions and millions over their lifetimes of simulated murders and deaths
and torture.
And every time I go to a movie to analyze it, I'm not really a fan of really violent
films.
What?
It's because I realized how serious it is unless it's in a serious context.
I would have liked to been in the theater when the road came out a few years ago.
I saw it on DVD and was profoundly affected by it because I've studied so much history.
I know how accurate it was dealing with cannibalism and deprivation.
I never put the pieces together until that clip that Alex's entire idea of like everyone
becomes a cannibal within 15 days is just from the road.
Just Cormac McCarthy.
Straight up.
Yeah.
I wouldn't rely on Cormac McCarthy for the betterment of mankind in terms of thematic
elements.
But Alex pretends that that's like stuff from studies and so everyone becomes a cannibal
within 15 days.
Yeah.
No, I mean, that's just kind of like, yeah, there's a bunch of bad people who are cannibals
in the road.
I can see if they had made a movie of it, I could see Alex's Devil being based on the
Judge from Blood Meridian, but that was a book and it's hard to read even if you're
good at reading.
So, no.
It's just a post-apocalyptic fiction novel that's got turned into a movie that Alex is
pretending is real.
Yeah.
Viggo Mortensen, right?
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Vigo.
Yeah, it was a good Vigo film.
The historical examples of cannibalism have been in ritual context, which makes sense
because the amount of energy you'd need to exert to kill and eat a non-cooperative human
would not be worth whatever nutritional value you gain from it.
It would be smarter from a caloric perspective to eat just about anything else.
This is just another example of some supposedly researched position that Alex has got that
he's coming from a movie that he experienced as real.
I mean, you know, in many ways, I would argue that man is the most dangerous game.
Because it fights back and it's harder to trap.
Exactly.
Yeah, so if there's easier game, go for the easier game.
And that includes leaves and shit, man.
It's not hard.
It's true.
No.
And the other thing, too, is you will find a number of examples over history, of course,
of people who are in desperate situations who resort to cannibalism.
Of course, yes.
Honor party and such.
Sure.
Yeah.
A lot of those, what makes those sort of unique are isolation.
It's isolation that's really crucial for those, yeah.
It's a lack of other legitimate options.
Somebody who's lost at sea or something.
Right, right, right.
You might eat somebody.
Yeah.
If they were on, perhaps, a road, it would be far easier.
The problem for many of these people is that they are trapped in the middle of nowhere
with no hope of escape or anywhere.
If there's foliage and wildlife, it's substantially easier and better for everyone to not eat
people.
Yeah.
So much better to not eat people.
And you don't need to wait 15 days to figure out that.
Nope.
So dumb.
Oh, what a dumb dumb.
I'm not going to eat any of these goddamn fruits.
So Alex has this idea that, and he sort of touched on it in that last clip, and that
is this notion that fake violence on TV and seeing it makes you experience it the same
way you'd experience real violence.
Sure.
And I have some thoughts about this.
Oh, yeah.
As somebody who's shocked by images of violence and death, someone setting themselves on fire
or blowing their brains out, there's real footage of that out there on the web.
Back in Vietnam, people were shocked by the image of children who'd been napalmed with
their skin burned off.
People were shocked by the image of Vietnamese police blowing a man's head off in the street.
That's shocking.
But now people are like, big deal.
They laugh about it.
Not that...
And they think it's cute.
No.
And it's because A, they don't know history.
B, they don't have common sense.
And C, they haven't experienced trauma.
Wild.
And this has all been done by design so that when your neighbors are being abused by the
jackbooted thugs or when the CPS is taking your kids, even your own family isn't going
to be shocked by it and just accept that bad things happen because the mind sees all this
simulated violence on television as real.
And so it can't differentiate between fact...
Cut off at the break.
That clip is really key to me to the point where it's one of the only times I can remember
where I'm really disappointed he got cut off by the break.
He's kind of interested in where he was going.
Here Alex is lamenting how fake violence on TV is experienced by people as real violence
and that desensitizes them to seeing instances of real life violence.
I don't know how common that is necessarily as a phenomenon.
I bet there is some effect that it has.
But I know that I've seen plenty of horror movies in my life and I still pretty much
experience depiction of violence difference than I do actual violence.
Pro wrestling is a really good example of this.
I can watch people hit each other with chairs and send each other through tables but if
I were watching that being done for real I would not enjoy it.
Any time it appears that someone has actually hurt themselves in wrestling reality creeps
in and I become worried for the performer because it's possible to enjoy the narrative
depiction of combat and still remember that it's a performer performing.
Then there's stuff like the UFC where people are fighting for real and people are trying
to hurt each other.
This is still kind of ritualized violence where everyone watching understands that these
are two trained competitors who've agreed to fight each other under specific rules to
see who's better at the sport.
It's closer to real world violence but it's something that's formalized, professional,
and both parties have consented to what's going on in the contest.
And then there's movies.
Right.
Which are just totally fictional.
Those are fictional, yes.
Most people can tell the difference between these forms of displays of violence and experience
them differently, whether that different experience is conscious or subconscious.
It seems to me that Alex cannot, and he assumes that because that is his experience everyone
else must also not be able to differentiate between the two.
Now here's where this point gets important.
Because Alex can't tell the difference between fiction and reality, he can't also tell the
difference between reality and fiction.
In the same way that he thinks that a fictional movie like The Road depicts a legitimate realistic
cannibal future, he has a tendency to think very real things like the Sandy Hook shooting
were completely staged.
Alex pretends that exposure to fictitious violence has made everyone desensitized to
real world violence, and yet in my experience one of the major themes of his show is denying
the experiences of people who have experienced the effects of real world violence because
he thinks it's fake.
Yes.
I think that's an important dynamic to recognize.
Yeah, I mean there's that extra level of not just because, you know, he can't tell the
difference between reality and fiction, and so he assumes everybody else can't tell the
difference.
Yes, I do think that is a part of the dynamic.
But that like second level of, of course he can't also not assume that of everyone else,
because if he were to realize that other people can easily tell the difference between reality
and fiction, that would be an attack upon him personally, or it would tell him that
it's possible to tell the difference between reality and fiction.
Hmm.
You know, so the only way that he can maintain his psyche through this is by assuming that
not only can nobody else tell the difference between reality and fiction, but that he's
the only person who can tell you you can't tell the difference between reality and fiction.
Yeah, perhaps that is, that is true.
Yeah, he's a mess.
Yep.
That's a real bummer.
You know, Alex has another story that's going around, and this is, this is interesting to
me because, you know, he's above the political divide, right?
Sure.
The left-right paradigm is an illusion, and it's all meant to get us all mad at each other
and fighting for no reason.
Yeah.
Democrat, left, right, conservative, Republican, meaningless words.
All just infighting for no reason.
This seems weird.
This is 2010.
Mm-hmm.
Big story at Infowars.com by Kurt Nemo, Pennsylvania Homeland Security puts anti-tax protesters
on list of terror threats.
And we got same reports out of Texas six years ago, listing gun owners, veterans as the number
one threat.
But because it was Bush's administration doing it, conservative media wouldn't pick up on
it.
Now that it's Obama, meet the new boss, same as the old boss, like the Who song says.
It's like, oh my gosh, Obama wants to go after conservatives.
Folks, you've always been the enemy.
Again, I would watch conservative pundits on Fox and listen to them on the radio, read
from reports that I had.
They didn't tell you they were reading a report, but I'd read the reports.
We'd covered it here.
I knew they were reading federal demonization scripts.
Whoever's loading their teleprompter is a globalist.
I mean, they're getting a direct government propaganda feed.
We know they're bad.
It's open and shut.
So if you understand what he's saying, if you get to the root of what he's saying when
he's trying to make this argument that he's above this sort of left, right, new boss,
same as the old boss, he's saying that Obama is targeting conservatives in the same way
that the conservatives targeted conservatives.
The left isn't the target of any of this stuff.
It's they are always the victim of no matter what.
No matter what.
No matter who's in charge, the enemy of the globalists is these conservatives, like Alex's.
It's interesting.
It's only the far right white.
But it's interesting that he can articulate this idea of it doesn't matter who's in charge.
They're all the same.
But the thing that he's saying that they're all the same about is that they're all globalists
who hate super far right people like me.
Yeah.
I mean, essentially it's like, hey, we don't have any white nationalist candidates.
And then they got a white nationalist candidate and they were like, holy shit, this is what
we've been wanting the whole time.
Yeah.
And here in 2010, you're starting to see a little bit of the beginning of that materializing
into a possibility with the Tea Party being on the rise.
Yeah.
Again, because of whiteness.
It was a major driver.
Yeah.
Big deal.
And Coke money.
Yeah.
Not Coke head money.
Coke brother money.
Yes.
So in terms of that, there is something that's going on at this point in September.
And that is that Christine O'Donnell was running for the seat in Delaware in the Senate.
And there had been a little bit of squabbling.
Karl Rove had come out and he'd had an interview that was a little bit critical of O'Donnell.
And Alex is not happy about this.
Here is the New York Times today.
GOP leaders say Delaware upset hurts Senate hopefuls.
Now they basically said the same thing about Rand Paul.
They sent in Cheney to campaign against him.
They put all their money behind the Republican establishment pro bailout candidate.
They demonized him, just like the Democrats are now doing.
And he's widened his lead against the Democrat in the last few months since he won the primary
against the Republican.
But they said the same thing.
Oh, people extreme like him.
And they lied about what he really stood for.
He can't win.
And so they create this self-fulfilling prophecy of, oh, you can't vote for that candidate
because they can't win.
And now the Republicans are creating the hoax with the Democrats that all these different
real Tea Party candidates who actually, you know, are against the out of control spending,
the banker bailouts and the rest of it, that that that they're bad and that they can't
win.
And you need to go for establishment Republicans, the same Republicans that are for.
Banker bailouts, the same Republicans that under Bush four separate times tried to pass
amnesty, the same Republicans like Newt Gingrich, who want global carbon taxes and want world
government.
And the hoax intensifies.
I have the transcript here.
We're not going to play the entire clip, but it's up on info wars dot com and prison planet
dot com in an article that Paul Watson's written anti establishment fervor, a hammer blow to
the Washington elite.
But here's a transcript from Fox News from last night.
Karl Rove questions Christine O'Donnell's serious character problems.
And then I have the quotes here.
They're saying because it took 20 years for her to pay off her student loans, that that
is deceptive.
Again, the serious questions about how does she make her living?
Why did she mislead voters about her college education?
How come it took nearly two decades to pay her college bills?
I've seen numbers of upwards of half of many college students now not paying their loans
because they can't cancel them.
Right.
Yeah, that would make sense.
Yeah, you're on top of it, Alex.
You should absolutely cancel student loan debt.
I think that's Alex's position.
So first of all, fuck Karl Rove.
Yeah.
That being said, Rove was just protecting his brand there and everybody's brand.
It's not really anything more interesting than seeing conventional Democrats be resistant
to embrace AOC in the present.
There's just that tension.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Someone like O'Donnell in particular and the aesthetics of the Tea Party in general were
a vast departure from the type of politics that Rove excelled at for decades.
So that obviously would represent a threat to his position in the market, either as a
strategist or a commentator on Fox News.
Yeah, let's keep the depths of our evil quieter, guys.
That was Karl Rove's philosophy, I believe.
In the end, though, Rove was probably right.
Christine O'Donnell was unelectable.
She finished third in the GOP primary in 2006 after making some pretty offensive comments
about the LGBTQ community and lost the 2008 general election to Joe Biden, who was simultaneously
running for vice president.
She would follow this up by losing the 2010 general election after it came out that she
had, quote, dabbled in witchcraft in high school.
And then, more to the problem, released this ad.
I'm not a witch.
I'm nothing you've heard.
I'm you.
None of us are perfect, but none of us can be happy with what we see all around us.
Politicians who think spending, trading favors, and backroom deals are the ways to stay in
office.
I'll go to Washington and do what you do.
I'm Christine O'Donnell, and I approve this message.
I'm you.
I was really hoping she'd say I'm not a witch.
I wanted her to say I'm not a witch at the end.
Just to reiterate.
As a reminder?
I'm not a witch.
Just to double down on that?
Not a witch here.
Obviously, I don't care if someone messed around with some witch shit.
Some of the coolest people I know have spent some time in that water.
I don't care, but man, Republican voters sure do.
It's one thing to have dabbled in witchcraft in your past when you're trying to run for
office, but it's another thing to cut an ad that starts by saying I'm not a witch.
That's so goofy and embarrassing from a political strategy perspective that anyone who would
do that is someone you shouldn't trust to make good decisions.
It's either an indication of them having bad instincts or being surrounded by people who
have bad instincts, and neither is a good option.
This 2010 midterm and the Tea Party candidates that came into office with it were a warning
of the future we were heading toward.
It's not surprising to look back at 2010 and see Alex supporting someone like Christine
O'Donnell and then flash forward to today to see him backing Marjorie Taylor Greene.
Yeah.
This is what he does.
Yep.
The issues about O'Donnell's college history and loans probably sound like petty issues,
but the point Karl Rove was making was more that the way that O'Donnell was addressing
these questions about her history didn't come off as convincing.
For instance, as early as 2006, she claimed to be a graduate of Fairleigh Dickinson University,
but actually didn't complete her degree until September 2010.
The reason for the delay had first been claimed to be a student loan-related issue, like a
delay because of that, but then the story became that she had to finish an outstanding
elective course before she could get her degree.
Rove was expressing on Fox News that if she was going to win, she would have to be more
forthright.
And she said exactly that, quote, she can't get away with simply saying my answer is on
my website or it's puzzling to me why the IRS would file a lien for me when I didn't
pay my taxes in 2005.
I mean, she's got to be more honest than that.
If she does, she's got a shot to win, but it's got to be passionate and factual and
hard hitting.
Yeah.
You know, and I think the very, see, you should have somebody like me if you're going to cut
a political ad because if you open with I'm not a witch, the reasonable person's response
is that's just what a witch would say.
Right.
I know witches aren't real, but my first thought when she said I'm not a witch is like, oh,
that's a witch talking right there.
That's a witch.
I haven't seen a witch before.
And I think anybody with like just a little bit of political instincts or any awareness
of how the media cycle works is like, you're going to get piled on for that.
Yeah.
Leave it alone.
Don't say I'm not a witch.
Don't worry about it.
So easy to ignore.
Cut an ad about how compassionate you are and how you care about the needs of the people
of Delaware.
Don't open.
Don't get ahead of the witch story.
I got to get out in front of this witch thing.
If I don't do this, they'll think I'm a witch.
People think I'm still a witch.
I think that's, what's really funny about that is Christine O'Donnell's name immediately
popped up.
There was a space in my brain for it, but I wasn't 100% sure.
And then you said witch and I was like, oh yeah, I remember that.
I remember that witch doesn't really actually know all that much about her, but he's decided
to defend her just because he likes, who doesn't seem to like her.
Now.
I don't know this lady from the side of a barn, but the fact that the attacking her,
the fact that the system is demonizing her, the fact that they have the Republicans and
Democrats coming out against her, I mean, that tells you all you need to know.
So yeah, Alex is just like defiant basically, but you know what's funny is like, why isn't
Alex talking about how she's a witch?
He seems to hate witches.
He hates witches.
It's because that clip doesn't come out until two days after this episode.
Oh boy.
Not the clip that we played, but the information about her babbling about her being a witch.
Bill Maher plays that two days later.
Jesus.
It sets off the witch news cycle.
That's so funny.
Yeah.
So Alex gets around to playing the clip of Rove talking on Fox news.
And I think this is really interesting because Alex sets it up pretty poorly.
And so let's go ahead and play a short clip of Karl Rove, you know, really demonizing
this poor lady and just repeating that talking point over and over again that she has serious
character problems and then when you actually go find out what those character problems
are, he just uses that term when you actually find out what they are.
It took her 20 years to pay off her student loans and she had an $11,000 lien on her from
the IRS.
No due process.
They just slapped it on her.
Here it is.
You know what?
If you vote for cap and tax and you have an opponent that says they wouldn't, then they
have a choice.
They have an option.
So I think it was, it was very substantive, very based on issues, very based on the voting
record of one and the promise voting record of another.
You know, again, you're making my case.
This was about Mike Castle's bad votes.
It does conservatives little good to support candidates who at the end of the day, while
they may be conservative in their public statements, do not events, the characteristics of rectitude
and truthfulness and sincerity and character that the voters are looking for.
She doesn't show rectitude.
This was a guy up there high and mighty saying, I tell you who has rectitude.
I tell you who is morally good.
I tell you, you know, who you could vote for and who you can't.
I'm the grand Puba.
I'm the high priest.
I'm going to tell you Republicans what you can and can't do your need to stay on the
Karl Rove reservation because I am morally of high rectitude.
This is the guy lying about WMDs.
So what you have is Alex introduces this clip in a way that the clip doesn't actually reflect
what he's saying.
And Karl Rove is actually making a fair point in terms of the context of this conversation.
That is there's some kind of non forthrightness that's going on and that is not great.
Yeah.
And so in order for Alex to deal with the clip that's played, he attacks the messenger.
He's just, and look, fuck Karl Rove.
I don't care.
But saying fuck him and saying he lied about weapons of mass destruction doesn't deal with
the issue that he brings up.
Totally.
Yeah.
That just point.
Oh, Oh my God.
You're all liars.
What a shock.
If I were a snarky debate kid online, I would say that is a, uh, Ooh, this is a person of
the tech.
This is not.
We don't even bother.
And I have scored a point or whatever.
But that's, that's what you can do whenever, I mean it, the audience enjoys it.
I think you even kind of enjoy it.
Enjoy what?
Just piling on Karl Rove.
Oh, fuck that guy.
Yeah.
All right.
I don't know.
I don't have any skin in that game.
I just, I just like to see, uh, any, any shit piled on Karl Rove is a good day for me.
Sure.
Yeah.
So in this next clip, we see Alex doing something we saw recently on a, on another, I believe
time travel episode that we did, we saw him pretending to discover the strategy of Google
bombing.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
And so he's going to start a Google bomb.
Okay.
Of course.
So we're going to have a new search term today.
We haven't done this in a week or so.
We're gonna have a new search term.
We're going to make number one today.
This is the first search search term we've done.
Every time it's become number one, Google search the term Gates, death panels, Gates,
death panels with an S Gates, death panels.
Just search those three words in Google, in Yahoo, in every major search engine, do it
over and over again and send the story out to everyone and click on the story and it's
already the number one link.
If you type in Bill Gates, death panels on Google news, it's our story is already number
one.
This is Paul Watson's article from yesterday.
And so, uh, we're going to push this out as the number one search term and then hundreds
of newspapers and blogs as you've seen, we'll then go click on our story to find out what
it's about.
They'll research it.
They'll write about it.
It'll cause another chain reaction.
So Bill Gates is who we're going after today.
And for the next 11 years.
Wow.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's interesting to think about like the 11 years intermediate, the like different
careers.
Alex and Bill Gates have had.
Yeah.
They've gone on separate paths.
There was, there was a moment where they could have come together, you know, things really
diverged.
Yeah.
You know, it's one of those, uh, uh, I took the path less trod, you know, that kind of
thing.
Yep.
Yeah.
So Alex takes calls.
Um, and a lot of it ends up being about vaccines.
Sure.
And a caller, right?
Of course it is because you're a witch, Dan.
So this caller is, uh, his kid is, uh, scheduled to be vaccinated.
Sure.
And Alex has a, has a way to, is a, he has a bad metaphor.
That's kind of what I was thinking.
I just wanted to, to thank you for what you do.
Uh, you're my hero.
Uh, first of all, I just want to say that I'm really nervous.
I apologize.
Um, I have a two month old son.
Uh, he's our, our first child and he's about to get his shots.
Uh, he's scheduled to get in this week, uh, for the vaccines and stuff like that.
Um, and I really,
You know, that's kind of like Jews were scheduled to get on trains and go to Dachau and Auschwitz.
And he's like, Oh, it's your scheduling.
It's your time to ride the carousel and Logan's run.
Um, uh, I mean, just cause they say it's scheduled.
I mean, did they take his blood at birth for the Pentagon database?
Uh, I think so.
I'm not real sure.
I mean, if he was born in a hospital, they did, but I mean, so,
Oh boy.
Yeah.
So that's the tone that he's coming at this caller with.
The caller's just saying that, uh, the child is scheduled to have some vaccinations.
He's like, Oh, like, uh, like Jewish people in the world war II going on trains.
They were scheduled.
You know, I really like not having measles.
Uh, and I, I think I re my childhood was better from not having measles.
What about all the polio you had?
I, I, it felt great to not have polio.
And of course you died of the whooping cough.
Right.
Yeah.
It was a struggle.
That was tough.
We did make it through that as a, as a unit.
Uh, I think that's great.
But 17 of your siblings died of tetanus.
Doesn't it seem like that should be an easier sell?
Yeah.
Like, Hey, you know how we don't have polio?
That's because of the vaccines.
So just think Alex thinks it's cause of hand washing or something.
That really bothers me.
It really bothers me because of fucking witches and people being good for a while or whatever.
It's more or less about witches.
Bums me out.
Yep.
So, uh, but it's important to see the, the way this tone works.
So he starts out the call and the guy just says that his kid is scheduled and Alex immediately
compares it to trains and the Holocaust, then he, he, he tries to sort of play reasonable
a little bit, but going back to vaccines, uh, to decision you have to make, uh, the
Japanese, it's gotta be more than a decade ago, made a rule, no vaccination until age
two, because they found completely that this stuff causes neurological problems, autoimmune
problems, but it's much worse when a little bitty baby has all these shots going in them.
By the time they grow up and get bigger and get some cognitive development, it won't stunt
them as much.
So now Alex is trying to play that, Hey, everybody's got to make their own decision and then immediately
jumps to this story about Japan, which is a complete lie.
Yeah.
In 1994, Japan amended a law that they had, uh, they had a law that made vaccines mandatory
and they amended this making instead quote, it was more of a civic duty than a strict
legal obligation.
According to the AFP, uh, the world health organization stats from 2018 reflect a vaccination
rate of 99% for tetanus, diphtheria and pertussis in one year old Japanese children and 97%
for the same age group with the polio vaccine.
Alex is just making shit up to demonize vaccination, but it's important to pay attention to that
way that he's trying to frame things.
Yeah.
You know, it's the, the, the caller brings this up, he compares it to the Holocaust.
Hey, everybody's got to make their own decision, but also here's a lie about Japanese people.
Okay.
So if 99%, 97% of Japanese babies, then we can look back and see if his numbers make
sense 25 years later or whatever it is.
And uh, they don't.
So can't we be done then?
Well, we can't because Alex is now- But I want to be done with anti-vax.
No, because Alex has said that everybody needs to make up their own mind.
Oh, but what if we have the proof of concept from Japan?
Everybody's got to, well, look, everybody's got to make up their own mind with the caller.
And so this caller is still on the line.
This is fucked up.
This is not what you do when you want someone to make up their own mind.
Does that answer your question?
Yeah.
I really, really appreciate that.
I appreciate your time.
Uh, I guess I'm just not going to do it.
I mean, I mean, um, but when it becomes old enough to go to school, I mean, would that,
would that be a problem?
Yes.
They are criminals.
They are hardcore criminals.
Again, they lie to you and say, it's the law.
He must take the shots.
They lied to you and said, there wasn't mercury until we forced it out in the open.
And now they say, okay, mercury is there.
It's good for you.
Then they're going to lie when he goes in school and say, it's the law.
Your child can't be in the school without shots.
And you say, I know you've got the waiver.
It's not even a law, but it's a waiver to a non-law.
I know you've got a waiver that I'm supposed to fill out.
So they make a list of you, but courts have even shown you can eat and not even do that.
And then they'll lie to you again, cause they're getting money.
When they hit your kid with a weapon from the feds, that that's tied to the federal
money they're given.
Uh, they have quotas.
They've got to get 97% or more vaccinated.
They don't get their money.
Then then the school nurse or the principal is going to lie and say, there's no such thing.
And then you can already have Googled your state.
You're calling from Tennessee, Tennessee vaccine waiver, conscientious objector, religious
objector.
So really principal or assistant principal, here's the waiver for Tennessee.
You lied to me and see, you'll know you're there with a hardcore liar.
Again, lying trash, an entire government and corporate system trained to lie.
And these teachers take their kids and inject them with the mercury too.
And they love the fact that in many schools, a third of the schools now special ed, and
there's just giant warehouses of children wearing football helmets, literally because
they bumped their heads on the walls and in wheelchairs and in diapers and they put taser,
taser, uh, belts around them in the public schools.
Now when they don't mind, they zap them and they love it.
They just love all of it.
And soon the whole school will be in the corner drooling.
And by that point they can just start euthanizing everyone.
They are just savagely chemically hurting us as bad as they can so they can submit,
make us submit and then just come in and have the helicopters fly over and spray the nerve
gas and kill everybody.
They're just getting everybody ready for that.
Okay.
That's hardcore truth, buddy.
Listen, those are criminals when they lie to you and, and, and, and try to force those
vaccines.
You understand that?
Yeah, I do.
Okay.
I appreciate your call.
I mean, it's hitting the game, ladies and gentlemen, everybody's got to make up their
own mind.
Everybody's got to make up your own mind.
I mean, they're trying to murder you in your fucking bed.
You coward.
They're trying to kill you in their life.
But everybody's got to make up their own mind about, look, everybody's got their own choice
to make between getting murdered in their own bed and being a heroic patriot who gives
me money.
It's a simple choice.
Yeah.
Joe Rogan's on this episode of this show.
Maybe we should never have expected all that much from him.
That would have made sense.
We get another caller and this is, this is just for good clean fun.
This is a little bit of parsley.
Okay.
This dude's asking about a JFK documentary if Alex has seen it.
And then we find that Alex doesn't know a very important bit of trivia about JFK.
Now he fancies himself kind of like a, you know, a guy who knows a lot about the conspiracy.
Sure.
He's a conspiracy guy.
It's kind of rough that he doesn't know this bit of, it's kind of a big one, right?
Incredible.
Deep, deep.
You should watch it.
It's revealing.
Even some of the attorneys that were defending, um, uh, the guy who took over JFK's position.
Now I can't remember his name, uh, when he, when they assassinated him.
Who is a, who is the next person, the vice president who took over, I can't remember
his name now.
Uh, well it was, uh, it was Robert Kennedy.
What?
Yeah.
And well, of course he was the attorney general, um, who was JFK's vice president.
Um, boy, I'm having a moment here.
I should know that.
Yeah, you should.
Yeah.
You should fucking know who LB goddamn Jay is.
This is a big part of the conspiracy.
He's the reason.
Oh my God.
He's LBJ is probably one of the biggest reasons that Alex hates the left anyways because of
LBJ that we got the civil rights act through there.
So I mean, not because of him, he fought tooth and nail for a long time, but it was a part
of the history.
Yeah.
That's weird.
Alex does eventually remember LBJ and then he tries to pretend that he just couldn't
come up with Humphrey who was LBJ's vice president.
Wow.
Wow, buddy.
Wow, dude.
That's brutal.
I understand if you take like a little bit of a second, but like that's too long.
Yeah.
Especially for LBJ, who's kind of a big figure in American history.
And a big figure in JFK assassination conspiracy theories.
Totally.
In fact, one of the many people suspected of JFK's murder.
Yeah.
Definitely.
Weird.
So now we get to the point of the episode where we get the introduction of Joseph Rogan
and Edward Bravo.
Oh boy.
It's interesting.
They have a different vibe back then.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
Maybe not.
Joe's definitely high.
Wow.
It's high as hell.
That's nice.
That's good to know.
But this is really awkward.
It's really, really awkward.
Well, it's good having you here and it was good seeing you last night.
There's so much to talk about.
Obviously, Joe Rogan of NewsRadio, Fear Factor, The Man Show, the list goes on and on, UFC
Ultimate Fighting Championship.
You've been doing that pretty much since the start, haven't you?
I started working for the UFC in 1997.
I was the post-fight interviewer.
So 13 years.
Yeah.
It's been a long time.
In fact, I remember like in 99 talking to you and you're like, man, this UFC is going
to be huge.
And I never even heard of it.
It's going to be bigger than the NFL.
Yeah.
Everybody was like, what are you talking about?
You're crazy.
Yeah.
It's now look at it's giant.
And it's in Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Right here.
You know, when I was with Ventura last week, one of the guys from the company that does
stuff for UFC was there and he was going to interview Brock Lesnar right after that when
he was on the shoot with us.
And so old Brock's back bigger than ever, huh?
Yeah.
That was great.
It's not as electric as some of this present day stuff.
And I think it's because Alex is sober.
I think there is a markedly different chemistry.
They might need something to grease the wheels on this.
There might need to be some grease on these wheels.
That's possible.
Holy shit.
This is not what I expected because it's chemistry.
There's a chemical missing, if you will.
Yeah.
Ethanol.
Alex is sitting here with Eddie and Joe.
All of the human elements are there for the record setting most listened to podcast ever
in human history.
Hundreds of millions of people have listened to it.
And then the sequel that set the world on fire.
On fire.
And it is just trash.
You gotta be drunk.
So bad.
You gotta be in Rogan's house and you gotta be a half of a fifth through.
Yeah.
I think there's some funny stuff to get into.
And I think one really gigantic lie that Alex tells that I think is interesting.
But this is a case of me getting hoisted on my own petard.
I legitimately thought it would be fun.
Yep.
And it's kind of...
It's kind of a dud.
Well, no.
It's not.
It's a fine interview for the most part.
Sure.
Like, Rogan's high.
Well, yeah.
Like, Alex is talking about, like, oh, we were talking last night.
You told me something really interesting.
And it's clearly that Rogan was, like, trying to spitball.
Maybe he was working on a joke or something.
Sure.
And Alex takes it as, like, a real point.
Oh, no.
Last night, you were really making a lot of points that I thought were right on.
Let's get into the red button.
The red button.
You were talking about how if there's a red button, they're gonna hit it.
Well, you know, what I was saying is that I believe that all human behavior is natural.
Just like I believe that all animal behavior is natural.
Bees make beehives and ants make anthills.
These are all natural things.
Humans are far more complex, but we don't think of ourselves as being natural, that
we're moving in a natural direction.
And I think that human beings and human society, especially with technology, I think we create
technology and innovation.
That's what we're here for.
And it's very possible that what human beings are here for is to make some new reality,
make some new technological innovation that's gonna change the world.
And it could be a big bang machine.
It could be a time machine.
It could be just some incredible discovery, something that they're going to invent eventually.
I mean, if they keep going with things like the Large Hadron Collider, they're not gonna
stop there.
They're gonna use whatever findings that they get from the Large Hadron Collider if it doesn't
blow up the world.
And they're gonna try the next thing.
Well, what happens now?
The goal is blow up the world.
Well, I don't know what the goal is.
I mean, that's just the joke.
The joke is that we're here to make the big bang machine and that there's a reset button
that gets pressed every 15 billion years and that these intelligent monkeys get to a point
where they break down matter and try to figure out what is at the center of the universe.
And they press that button and it restarts all over again.
I mean, who knows?
Just speculation.
Wow.
Heavy, man.
Heavy.
It's some good shit, man.
It's some good shit.
I think Douglas Adams put it better that if the question and the answer were ever known
then the universe would be destroyed and replaced by something weirder.
It was a lot simpler and a lot more quick.
But I mean, that kind of a thing is like, yeah, I could imagine getting high with someone
like a lot of the people I knew in college and having almost identical conversations
to that.
Yeah, 100%.
There's nothing wrong with that.
That's fine.
No.
We've moved on to simulation theory now.
It's the same basic thing.
But that's a fine place for Joe to exist.
Yeah.
Because he's like, okay, he's the older brother who's into weed, but maybe you've only stolen
a few beers at this point in your development down the opening your mind spectrum.
And that can be useful in people's lives.
That can open up your brain to new vistas.
Yeah, yeah.
It's like Val Kilmer in Real Genius.
It's just not that deep.
And then it's also clearly, you can tell that Joe was talking about this as some kind of
like an idea that has the structure of a Rogan bit.
It has the structure of something you could see him doing on stage.
And Alex is like, yeah, man, you know, it is an interesting idea that humans are trying
to make open.
They're trying to kill us all.
That's just how we're supposed to do it.
It's again, not being able to parse out the like reality and sort of.
Yeah.
You can't have jokes if you don't realize the transgression over reality.
That's why his humor is so terrible.
So Alex now gets to trying to plug some Eddie Bravo's jujitsu business.
Guys, both of you, fire out your websites.
Joe Rogan dot net, 10th Planet JJ dot com, 10th Planet JJ jujitsu dot com.
Man, I see your 10th Planet shirts and stuff everywhere.
I mean, I'm really I'm all over the country.
I'll see people wearing 10th Planet stuff or talking really incredible.
Well, how many how many gems do you have?
Twenty five, I think, you know, something like that.
Well, aren't you one of the best known jujitsu teachers?
He won't toot his own horn, so I'll say yes.
He's one of the most innovative and important jujitsu instructors in the country.
Sounds like B.S. because he's my best friend, but it really is true.
He's one of the most important.
He's just smokes a lot of weed and comes up with crazy jujitsu moves.
And it turns out they work.
And I'm I'm also known as a conspiracy theorist freak.
So that's right. He and he's more of a conspiracy theorist freak than me.
Eddie sounds like kind of fun.
Yeah, I'm a freak.
I'm a conspiracy freak, man.
That's what I'm here.
But he also has to introduce that, like to the proceeding as just the energy is off.
Yeah, it seems like Eddie or Alex should have just been like, let's do some conspiracy theories.
That's what we're here for. Well, Eddie tries.
Yeah, Eddie tries to push in that direction.
That's right. But Alex can't because Eddie is a no one to him,
whereas he's got to talk to Joe, the the big star or whatever.
It's less that. And I think it's more that like he's not fucked up and he doesn't want to.
That's fair. I just think it's that he's not fucked up.
It might get too weird.
Yeah. Although I just looked it up.
It turns out that Rogan's podcast has started by this point.
OK. Started in December 2009.
So he's almost a year in the Rogan experience at this point.
Yeah. So Alex is they get to talking about Eddie wants to know about the troops
and the like drug trade with opium in Afghanistan.
All right. OK, OK, OK.
One of his one of his like is like, how do they make money on that?
How do they make money selling drugs?
Sure. How does the actual process work?
OK, OK, OK.
And we never do get an answer on it.
Well, naturally.
But this next clip, I think, is fascinating because it is the behavior that you see on the Joe Rogan experience
whenever Alex is a guest being, you know, carried out by Joe 11 years prior.
It's flowing out and the U.S. troops protect the opium.
They put this on the news because if they don't, Al Qaeda will get the money.
And no, no, no, I'm serious.
I mean, I played a clip of Fox News or all those things, how patriotic it is to grow opium.
But you think I'm joking?
Come on, guys, cue it up.
Oh, let's see this.
You're only here for an hour because you've got to go see it at the way ends at two thirty.
Yes, but I have to see that.
So he calls him on it.
Yeah, he calls Alex on this.
Show me this video then.
So they start playing the clip.
But Joe and Eddie don't have headphones.
Alex, but how does how do the Americans get paid for the opium is what I'm saying?
How does that work?
It gets the OK.
Nineteen ninety nine.
Rivera. Yep.
Can we hear him?
Yeah, you guys would have to have headphones on.
Look, I just played it yesterday during the break.
I'll play it for you.
How's that sound?
Sounds OK.
And listeners have seen it.
Exactly.
Word for word.
Well, there's a shill.
Is your show.
I don't know.
He was the guy who introduced the he was the one who had the Zapruder film first on television.
The word is he knows all about this stuff.
But yeah, at Fox News, he didn't really get into it.
What did he say?
He goes, I'm out here with the colonel and they're out here helping them grow the opium
and the colonel's like, that's right.
We're going the seeds and the fertilizer.
What?
Here's the actual clip that Alex is talking about.
That is the principal crop that is being grown here.
The Taliban lend the farmers the money.
They are indebted to the Taliban.
They have to grow the opium.
Now the Marines in their success are, in a sense, a victim of their success, because
now the population is you know, they have these opium fields and we are tolerating it.
We are tolerating the cultivation of the opium because we know that if we were to destroy
it now, the population would turn against the Marines and it would be a real security
risk.
Let me introduce Lieutenant Colonel Brian Christmas.
He's the commanding officer of the 3rd Battalion, 6 Marines.
Really a wonderful group of Marines here.
I know that you care deeply about this this contradiction, the fact that here you have
one of the best fighting forces in the world ever mounted.
And in a sense, you're watching as this opium is being grown.
I know it grinds at your gut.
How do you deal with it?
What are you doing about it?
Well, frankly, this is a part of the culture.
So while it might grind in my gut, it's what they do.
We provide them security, we're providing them resources, and we're providing them alternatives.
The alternatives are different crops to grow.
They're getting the seed and the fertilizer to do it.
So when Alex says the guy is talking about giving them seed and fertilizer, he's talking
about alternative crops that they can grow instead of poppy, but that just taking all
of their poppy or destroying the fields wouldn't be productive to the mission that he's trying
to undertake.
So Alex goes to commercial and he shows Joe this clip.
Presumably Joe's seen it, and he's either too dumb or Alex showed him a completely edited
version of it.
Well, that is a fascinating piece of video footage with Geraldo Rivera in the poppy for
with the soldiers talking about the poppy fields and how they're protecting them and
providing them fertilizer and helping them grow it.
Yeah.
I mean, that's incredible.
It's outrageous.
If you go and actually watch this, like the context of it is really clear.
So you think that, you know, we were at the market and everywhere we go, they're selling
these little devices.
Take a shot of this, Greg.
They're hand-carved.
These are the little devices they use to scrape the opium sap off the plant.
And I watched as you bought every one that was for sale because you care so deeply.
Why'd you do that?
I want them off the street.
The idea is that we don't want to harvest the poppy.
We want to, you know, hopefully turn the poppy over and put some wheat, cotton, watermelon,
cucumber.
It's all great stuff they grow out here.
We just want to see that come to fruition and the poppy just to go away.
It's completely counter to the context that Alex is describing it in, and it's also counter
to the context that Joe has been convinced of.
We want to see the poppy go away is a very hard sentence to avoid when your argument
is, they're helping them grow it to kill Americans.
And when Alex says specifically they're giving them the seed and the fertilizer, and when
you look at that clip, it's specifically seed and fertilizer in the context of other crops
they can grow instead.
So this behavior is so consistent throughout Joe Rogan's career with Alex that I just don't,
I can't believe that it's not, I don't know what to think about it.
He can't stop himself from being like, yeah, he's too credulous towards a guy who has been
lying to him since they met.
Yeah.
And it's wild.
It doesn't feel like it's believable.
No it's not.
It's not believable.
It's hard to, it's, I can't square the idea that he is not in on it in some fashion.
Yes.
It's not unfathomable.
You can't not be at least a little bit in on it.
This level of being duped, but like it's pathological.
Like it would have to show up in all of his other relationships too.
Totally.
No, no, no.
Everybody has to either be taking advantage of him or he's in on it in some way.
But honestly, I don't think that that's too unbelievable.
No, that's not.
I mean, look at the people he's had on his show in the past.
You have that Dave Seaman guy who's a big Pizzagate dude.
You had Dave Rubin was on a bunch, Steven Crowder.
Did the Molyneux on there one time?
Molyneux?
Couple times.
I think a couple times.
It's brutal.
Yeah.
And so I think that there is a decent chance that maybe he is pathologically gullible.
He's just too gullible.
But then you'd think it would show up in his relationships with people like the closer
folks.
Like Anari Shafir.
Sure.
Or Tom Segura.
Or Bert Kreischer.
Yeah, but I mean that's why comics hang around with other comics.
We don't know what you normal people are doing.
We don't know what's going on with you guys.
You could say anything.
We're just trying to write bits, man.
I'm just trying to write bits.
I guess you've got to kind of take comedians out of the entire conversation because that's
a whole other world.
Because we're just a different, yeah, it's just weird.
Yeah I find it difficult to believe that that's true though because it would be something
that I think he would need to get therapy with or like he couldn't have made it to the
point he's at now if he falls for this kind of shit on a regular basis.
Oh and because I also don't understand what is so special about Alex that requires him
to make excuses for decades.
I don't know, it does seem like he has like a weird appeal to authority like hack in him
where if you just say something so confidently and you have like a group of people who tell
Joe that you're actually a very smart person and then you just say something confidently,
Joe's like, wow, a lot of people have to believe this so it must be true.
Because Dan Hope thinks he's cool.
Yeah exactly, like it does seem like there's that just, oh okay, well I heard this was
cool and this guy is, I'm told this guy is super smart so I have to at least engage with
it and then it's too easy to...
It's just remarkable to me to see the exact same dynamic though that happened in these
present day podcast appearances being done to Rogan in 2010.
This lying about the context of something, Joe calls him on it and then there's evidence
proffered but whether the evidence that's given is selectively edited to the point where
it only shows what Alex wants him to see or he sees it and accepts Alex's framing of it
despite the clear context that's to the contrary, whatever it is, he's not equipped to deal
with the sort of people he's associating with clearly.
And now of course it's got to be 10 million times as hard because if you confront that
reality now then you have to be like, okay, well for the past 30 years this guy I have
thought was my friend has been a complete piece of shit liar to me.
Yeah it's almost like, you know, you get that Nigerian prince email.
Yeah and you're like, man, you know, I just...
You respond and then you give him $1,000 and then he wants five.
I don't want to be the stupid guy, I'm not going to be the stupid guy who doesn't, yeah.
It's almost like Joe's pot committed on not calling out Alex at this point.
It does seem like it, yeah.
Anyway.
Oh boy, sorry Joe.
Did you ever, I don't know if this is a sort of experience that I had or if it's more universal
but we had a bunch of National Geographics in the house.
Tons of magazines in National Geographic because they're educational, they're glossy.
So as a kid I would read tons of things about forests and various animals.
I would have liked that.
I barely got dinosaurs and National Geographic was too believed in evolution for my household
at the time.
Well did you know that Nat Geo is putting out a lot of cover-ups?
I did not know that Nat Geo is covering, okay, okay.
Putting out a lot of cover-ups on the chemtrail issue.
I'm here for it.
You know what it is?
Nat Geo puts out these, something with Nat Geo is connected with the government because
you watch anything...
No, no, no, National Geographic, you've all heard about how record numbers of missionaries
turn out to be CIA.
Really?
Yeah, and record numbers of Peace Corps.
What?
Record to what?
Compared to what?
No, National Geographic is a eugenics organization and they are one of the highest level CIA
fronts.
Really?
I'm just going to say that a lot of people will say this is Malarkey, a very good friend
of mine.
His father is in the CIA.
Cool.
Okay, my buddy's dad is in the CIA, so obviously Nat Geo is a fucking record, record compared
to what?
Sure, it's meaningless.
But it's never substantiated how National Geographic is a eugenics front and a high-level
CIA operation.
Sure, of the highest level.
Just throwing that out there, and then, well, you guys are going to say this is Malarkey.
But my buddy's dad is in the CIA, enough said.
Joe Biden stole Malarkey from Rogan.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what he gave him $100 million for.
That's true.
So, there's some conspiracies that, you know, Eddie Bravo doesn't seem to be on the earth
is flat tip.
At least not yet.
Right.
And that actually comes to a point I want to make.
And that is that...
The earth is flat.
We've been trying to get to this for a while.
Yes.
Okay, I've been waiting for it.
Finally.
I knew it was going to come sooner or later.
No.
I've been waiting for it.
I've been waiting for it for years.
I was interested to see if you'd go back and you'd see the same conspiracies that he's
into in the present being floated in 2010.
Sure, yeah.
Because if the earth is flat now, it was no less flat then.
And it's not like these ideas weren't spiraling around in places on the internet.
It's not like it's a recent phenomenon.
Sure, sure.
So, I was going back and I'm like, it's incredible there's not any flat earth stuff.
And part of the reason is that that wasn't that popular in 2010.
It wasn't a meme yet.
On the internet.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And this is something that's important to understand about conspiracy theorists.
They think that they're independent thinkers.
Yeah.
And they think that they're like, oh, really?
Really digging into stuff.
Red pill, man.
They are the biggest fucking followers in the world.
Easy.
These things are popular and then they get into them and then nothing ever happens and
something else will become popular.
Yeah.
Like the Sandy Hook truth or whenever that was popular.
Totally.
No, it's a fashionable, it's a fashion thing.
Conspiracy theories are fashion.
And some things are aesthetically important to retain along the way.
Of course.
Much like, I may not listen to the boss tones anymore but I'll still be a boss tones fan
until I die.
Sure.
He's gonna be a 9-11 truther until he dies.
Of course.
But it's maybe not the most primary thing to talk about all the time.
You can't spend your life listening to the boss tones.
No.
And you can't spend your life always talking about 9-11 conspiracies.
Exactly.
Yeah, you gotta move on.
There's going to be a piece of each of our histories and I just, I found that fascinating
that it was like, well, yeah, of course.
Yeah.
You're into what you're into at the time.
Totally.
And it turns out something that he's into at the time is that Hurricane Katrina might
have been fake.
Oh boy.
What do you think about the conspiracy theories about a Katrina being a controlled hurricane?
How the way it...
Multiple top meteorologists said it had two eyes for a while, it just sat there, it didn't
act like a normal hurricane, and I've had the father of weather weapons on who was flying
into cyclones that are over 200 miles an hour in the 40s, Ben Livingston, and this is all
declassified.
This is like AP.
And, well, we're going to break, but to make a long story short...
We're going to break already?
Yeah.
In 1967, it's a regular radio clock.
There's like long segments, short segments.
In 1967, Stanford Research Institute and the Naval Weapons Laboratory certified they can
create and control hurricanes as easy as, kiss my hand, we'll be right back.
So it was a weather weapon hurricane?
I suppose?
We don't get back to this.
Why would we?
It was or it wasn't, and it is.
So it was.
Cool.
Yeah.
What are the implications of that?
Well, let's see.
If Katrina was a controlled hurricane, sent by whom would be the first question.
That is an important first question.
We would assume the American government, I suppose, or a foreign power.
Right.
All right.
So then the question would follow why, why specifically where it was attacked.
So then you got to say that it's a race-based bioweapon, I would assume.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Anyway, another conspiracy that gets floated when they come back from break is that the
movie Machete is meant to start a race war.
Okay.
So you believe that the movie Machete with Danny Trejo is by the government designed
to fuel a race war?
He's a superhero Mexican home Depot guy.
Just beat that out.
I'm sorry.
I totally okay.
But just, just, just, just, okay.
We took care of that.
Are we good?
Did we take?
Yeah, we did.
Okay.
I feel like it got out.
No, it didn't.
Okay.
Stop guys.
Come on.
Sorry guys.
Alex is not drunk.
Did we just racial slur?
I think so.
I think we just racial slurred.
Yes.
It's like, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wow.
Um, but Eddie Bravo does explain that he is a Mexican individual and so, right.
Uh, but it's certainly not a, I mean, this is on the radio.
Yeah.
I wouldn't put that one out there.
I wouldn't put your business out like that.
At the time.
Apparently they had a little bit better a delay situation.
It seems like whoever was on the button on the red button there, boom, I'm there.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
Big bang machine.
They had actual adults working for him instead of hiring teens up the street.
Yeah.
So at this point now we have Alex sober trying to deal with doing a show that has FCC rules
with two guys who are high and one of them is clearly a lunatic.
Insane and unable to deal with the FCC.
Yeah.
So he has been shamed.
Eddie has been shamed a little bit.
Sure.
And so he recedes into the background while Joe complains about the governor of Arizona.
How hilarious is that dumb lady that's running Arizona that Jan, whatever the hell her name
is?
Who's the, who's the governor of Arizona?
Well, well, yeah, that was a little Jan Brewer.
Yeah.
That lady is so dumb.
Have you ever seen her on TV?
Oh my God.
When she was on the debate and she just paused, she didn't know what to say.
She paused for like 10 solid seconds, said nothing.
She makes up stuff about people getting their heads cut off over in Arizona that Mexicans
are coming over here and cutting people's heads off.
And then they're like, where are these bodies?
Like, what are you talking about?
Wow.
It sounds like Alex present day.
Yeah.
Wow.
I don't think Joe should be allowed to call anybody dumb.
No.
Yeah.
It's, it's tough to hear.
Yeah, buddy.
Um, but yeah, it's, it's interesting cause Alex then has to sort of rebut a little bit
because he is also quite xenophobic.
Yeah.
He's trying to be, yeah, you're cutting in on my racism here, buddy.
And the governor is a Republican.
Right.
And he's like, you know, there is the need to have sort of at least a little bit of a
pushback.
Yeah.
Um, and then Eddie gets back in the mix.
Sure.
He tries again.
Element of chaos.
Let me, let me just say something.
I'm not a big fan and Joe knows this.
I hate super movie.
Eddie Bravo.
Come on man.
We're on the radio.
I'm sorry.
I can't bring him with me anymore.
This is ridiculous.
He's not a professional.
I hate superhero movies.
I hate super, I'm a Mexican, El Machete wasn't the greatest plot ever.
So he's trying to get back to Machete.
Yeah.
Is that what we were doing?
So he doesn't like superhero movies.
Uh huh.
Something got bleeped.
Yeah.
Okay.
Now as Eddie goes on, I think he's making actually a fairly decent point.
And that is, you know, when I, as somebody of Mexican descent, uh, heritage, I see Spider-Man.
I can't identify with Spider-Man.
Sure.
I don't identify with Batman.
This rich asshole with all his gadgets.
Of course not.
I don't, uh, I don't see myself in these, these heroes and for me maybe Machete is somebody
that I can see as, and Alex is like, nah, nah, nah, he's not nice enough to white people.
Oh boy.
You know, as a Mexican, you can't relate to Spider-Man.
That's a white nerd who, you know, and then, and then, uh, um, wait, as Mexican people,
we have nothing.
Now we have something, you know, Superman, a white guy from another galaxy.
Now we have El Machete, you know, for me, I've felt like, why couldn't it be a Mexican
scientist who, you know, who becomes the incredible Hulk or something.
The Mexican superhero hacks up gringos.
Pull up with an axe.
That's ridiculous.
Yeah.
He's a Mexican long hair.
Well, let me tell you something.
Let me tell you something.
The Mexicans I know that warned me about this film that run the production.
They didn't like the stereotype of Mexicans as working at home Depot and wanting to kill
gringos.
I like that.
Oh, well, this has been an insane interview, Eddie Bravo, you, you just really ruined the
whole cause.
Did we get another racial slur burped out?
No, I don't think so.
I think it was just awkward silence.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
It makes a fine point.
For the most part.
I mean, I think that's an acceptable point and I think Alex's point is essentially just,
I don't know.
Whoa.
We can't be having superheroes who aren't nice to white people.
Let's calm it down.
Oh, a superhero who doesn't like white people.
Then what would be the point of superheroes?
Yup.
Oh boy.
So we get a really big revelation on this episode.
What's that?
That Superman helped defeat the KKK's expansion efforts in his radio serials?
No.
Oh, okay.
The mainstream media, the MSM failed to pick up on this, what could be the largest story
of our times.
Okay.
And that is that Alex Jones knows how to mind control birds.
I've even tried this with birds around my house and things.
If I come out and even put in my mind the intent, like I'm going to kill that bird without
even having a weapon, the bird flies off.
But if you're just being out nice and friendly, you know, the birds just sit there, almost
land on your hand.
They're all, I've got all these tame swallows around my house.
So it's almost like there's something telepathic they pick up on the intent.
Someone is going to take this clip and use it and say, Alex Jones uses mind control on
birds.
They probably will.
I have fulfilled the prophecy.
Alex Jones uses mind control on birds.
I just had to play it to the bed.
You had to do it.
You couldn't not do it.
Yeah.
It had to be done.
I was a little bored.
Yeah.
At this point, like things are kind of starting to fall apart a little bit.
I can sense that.
I think Eddie and Joe's patience and their high is like, kind of like, I want to have
fun.
It's abating.
I want out of here.
Alex isn't having fun.
Whenever Eddie starts trying to talk in his, like just the normal way he socially communicates,
he ends up saying things that he can't say on the radio.
Yeah.
It's like when you go visit your friend at work, you're not allowed to be like, oh, hey,
we're at this hardware store.
Let me drop some racial slurs.
Yeah.
You can't do it.
And so it's the last clips here.
Is it possible?
Is it, you would know, is it possible to create a bomb that makes everybody gay?
Was that possible?
Probably not.
Okay.
Oh boy.
Probably not.
And this is where like sort of questions are coming a little faster.
Yeah.
Can we make a gay bomb?
Probably not.
Yeah.
Are you disappointed in Charlie Sheen?
Are we doing lightning round?
A little bit.
Okay.
When Charlie Sheen choked his wife, were you like, damn, you're messing up the cause.
Like I had you on the program.
You were looking good.
Charlie Sheen calling for full disclosure on nine one one and then he's got to go and
well, he needs a vaccine for that.
Is that what it is?
That would make me look, I'm not going to get into that whole story.
I'm not going to get into that whole story, but all I wanted to know is does this ever
wear on you?
I mean, you're constantly dealing with negative stuff by the way.
Charlie's a good guy.
He is a good guy.
Okay.
Charlie's good guy, but also chokes his wife.
Hey Joe, I'm going to go with one.
It says a lot about you and Alex that your first thought of Alex's reaction was, how
is Alex going to take this as personally hurting him as opposed to giving a shit about the
fact that, uh, let me, let me actually clarify that even more.
He's saying, how is this going to affect the cause that Alex is pretending to be so passionately
fighting for?
How is Charlie Sheen's personal transgressions going to hurt Alex's crusade against imaginary
windmills?
Now here's where things turned for me.
I mean, I feel like that's super dark.
That's that's a real dark clip that just happened right there.
Oh, you know, Ooh, I have bad news.
It's going to get more dark.
Yeah.
Oh, but that one was really dark.
That's like, um, sort of violence trigger warning maybe for this next clip where Joe
goes next, by the way, Charlie's a good guy.
I use a good guy.
I'm a fan.
Platoon was an awesome movie.
I'm a fan of Charlie Sheen.
Have you ever, some chicks need to be choked.
How about that?
Some of them get a little mouthy and you want to get out to them and know who's paying the
rent here.
All right.
Freak.
Is it illegal to choke a girl?
Yes.
I'm kidding.
I don't choke anybody.
I don't choke girls, especially unless they want it.
And then it's free.
Okay.
That's enough.
Yeesh.
That's dark.
Yeah.
Significantly darker than I was expecting.
I mean, you know, I guess what you'd call it is the sort of like playful misogyny of
2010.
This, uh, yeah.
Wow.
I suppose you could, I, wow, it is, it is like, it's really, it, you know, when you
go back and you watch a nineties movie, like when you rewatch trading places, I rewatch
that and you're like, well, you could get away with a lot of shit there, but then you
think it's 2010 and you couldn't get away with that.
That's too recent.
No, you could get away with that shit in 2010 for sure.
Yeah.
It's wild.
I, I, I, Jesus.
It's not a joke.
No, it's not.
He thinks it's a joke, but even if it, you know, even if it is a joke, it's not like,
it's not a well-constructed joke.
It's not, it's not a new thought.
It's really just playing on the edge of sometimes domestic violence is warranted honeymooners
level shit.
That's what we're talking about here.
Yeah.
Yes.
In the 1950s, Jackie Gleason can be like, Oh, I'm going to hit you.
Like, yeah, but no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah.
It's very, it's very strange.
But one of the things that I think is even more strange is that Alex can sense the like
responsibility he has as a host, which he has completely abdicated in present days.
Gone.
He's he has, he feels some responsibility to be like, come on, man, come on.
That would be interesting to hear today.
Would he just be like, yeah, no, right.
Like who's that?
Yes.
He would have to.
Right.
Cause he had, he does not give a shit.
No.
God damn.
Yeah.
It is kind of interesting.
He had some semblance in 2010 of something that was precluding him and stopping him from
going into that.
Maybe it's a possibility of like, the audience was more family audience at that time.
Could be.
Maybe there was more of a puritanical streak to the people who had listened to him on the
radio and shortwave, which was the most of his audience as the internet and the supplement
lines came in.
Maybe he didn't have to keep such a pretend air of, uh, Hey, this kind of conversation
doesn't fly here, gentlemen.
I imagine getting kicked off of social media and stuff.
Probably that was much later though.
I think he'd given up some of that, uh, Oh, even back at like 2014.
I bet he would let Joe Rogan riff a little bit more, even if it was getting into territories
that was seemingly advocating for, even if it's facetiously advocating for, sometimes
women deserve to be choked.
Yeah.
Like it's, uh, yeah, it's weird.
This is a real misogynist episode for Joe.
I wouldn't, if I were Joe, I wouldn't look back on this episode, calling Jan Brewer dumb
and then, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The critique of the Arizona governor, if in a vacuum, could be seen as like things that
this politician did were dumb.
Sure.
You could view them outside of like unnecessarily misogynistic stuff.
It's tough to, when like, I just wish that conversation.
To be clear, Jan Brewer, not a good governor.
Yeah.
I wish that that conversation wasn't there.
We could not have that.
I wish it was.
Cause then it could just be like, Oh, isn't it funny Eddie thinks that Katrina was fake
and he keeps saying slurs on air and he keeps getting bleeped.
Yeah.
So anyway, uh, this gets a little bit uncomfortable and uh, they, they, you know, they have to
come towards the end here and uh, Joe has to be like, Alex, you're fun.
You're fun to hang out with, man.
Okay, sure.
Saying that, you know, you're a, you're a fun guy to hang around with and people always
say, man, you're friends with Alex Jones.
Is that a bummer?
And I'm like, no man, Alex Jones is a cool guy.
We have a good time.
Last night we went to Fogo to chow, we had some delicious meat.
It was awesome.
We had a great time.
Then we went out to the comedy club and we went out to dinner afterwards.
We hung out.
I had a lot of laughs.
There was no doom and gloom and you know, it was like, man, hanging out with Alex Jones
must be a bummer.
You know, the dude's always talking about the end of the world and vaccines robbing
your soul.
And no, you're, you're fun.
I mean, he's been defensive about hanging out with Alex for over a decade.
Yeah, man.
You got to ask yourself why.
Yeah.
Why would that be?
Yup.
Why is it that people think, hey, that guy you keep vouching for bad news over the course
of a decade, constantly having people be like, don't do that.
Yeah.
I mean, that is though, that is such comedy.
That is such like the way that it's worked for so long in comedy of just like, yeah,
there's a little bit of permissiveness.
It's totally like, oh yeah, yeah, no, no, no, I know, I've heard he's a fucking monster,
but he's always been cool to me.
I haven't seen that behavior.
Exactly.
So, so I totally, so that means he can't be a violent misogynist racist.
Yeah.
I wouldn't listen to his show to see what happened right before I came on.
Oh, that'd be a terrible idea.
No.
That's office behavior.
That's not fun.
Yeah.
Also, there's another funny thing.
They're talking about Brock Lesnar and he had like diverticulitis and they were talking
about how like it was because he just ate meat before.
Sure.
And that's not good.
That's bad.
And that's really funny to me because Joe would later have Jordan Peterson on his podcast
advocating his all meat diet.
Jesus.
Jesus Christ.
I hate these people.
I hate these people so much.
Yep.
Yeah.
I mean it has to be, it could also be, I could see it being this where it's like Joe discounts
anything that happens on the show.
He's just like, yeah, Alex does his show and it's all bullshit.
It's entertainment for, and nothing he says matters on the show.
It only matters what he says whenever he's off air, when he's a person.
Does it matter what he says on your show, Joe?
Exactly.
Because it's the same, a lot of it is the same.
You would think.
There's overlap.
Yeah.
And then just like, maybe it is, look, I get it.
If Joe and Alex are super good friends and Joe knows for a fact that Alex is full of
shit and is blah, blah, blah, blah, it's all made up shit, he's still a friend that is
directly responsible for so much evil happening.
Yeah, no.
Even if you think he's faking it.
Yeah.
It's almost worse.
It's not almost.
It may be worse.
It's worse.
Yeah.
I think you could have a debate on that.
It's more malicious.
Yeah.
Emptier.
Signing off on it, whether it's real or you know it's fake, is ethically both bad.
No, it's not good at all.
Yeah.
There's no way out for Joe.
There's no redemption for that whatsoever.
No.
It's just been over a decade of negligence on his part, not recognizing the cancerous
and toxic influence of this guy that he just has fun at a steakhouse with.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's a pathetic lack of responsibility on his part.
Yeah.
It's interesting to me that we've seen it on Joe's show whenever we've talked about
these present ones.
Mm-hmm.
I didn't think it went like that exact same behavior.
It's the same things.
It's annoying to me the way that you'll hear in these interviews in the present that's
like, ah, we put on those Bush masks.
Yeah.
And they have that same story that they tell that sort of solidifies their friendship and
their connection, and that's annoying.
Yeah.
But it's even more annoying to go back to the past in 2010 and see the inability to
fact check claims Alex has made that you instinctually think aren't correct, and then at the same
time be like, ah, you're fun, making excuses for misinformation and complete fraud based
on like, we have fun.
Yeah.
And I think I find it viscerally fucked up to go back nearly, like a decade, and see
no change, like no growth, and if anything, regression.
Yes.
I would say regression.
That's fucked.
Yeah.
That really fucks with my head.
You know, because in my time period, I think we can go back through our show and see just
pretty consistent like, there's growth, there's change, there's something.
Yeah, there's some missteps here and there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We fuck up, we grow, we move on, and we're, yeah, we do what we can, but to be stasis,
to just be that, and then get worse.
I see Joe kind of worse because I think he's gotten more entrenched in these positions
of like, hey, Alex is a fun guy, why does everyone not want me to hang out with him?
Totally.
And if he's so consistently being lied to by Alex, Alex showing him either fraudulent
or misrepresented proof of his claims, he's just gotten deeper and deeper in those holes.
Yeah.
I think Eddie seems more delightful at this point.
I agree.
There's something about him that just is delightful and good-
No, I get it.
There's a nature about him that kind of, I enjoy it when he chimes in with like a, I'm
a conspiracy freak.
No, I get it.
I get it.
I appreciate John.
I appreciate the problem.
He has a self-awareness too of himself back then.
Yeah.
Like I'm a conspiracy freak.
He introduces himself as such.
He's a recognition that some of the things that he's saying are probably dumb.
Yeah.
He's articulating important things about representation and media.
I don't know.
It's just, it's weird.
All of these people are doing worse now.
Yeah.
Eddie seems so, he's just a guy who's like, I know everybody's laughing at me and I've
accepted that and I'm cool with it because I've still got me.
I've still got my stuff and I'm respected in the field where I'm meant to be respected
at.
Yeah.
And if you laugh at me whenever I say some stupid conspiracy theories, yeah, man, conspiracy
theories are stupid.
You should laugh.
Then a couple of years later, my best friend has a hundred million dollars.
A hundred million dollars.
Hey, maybe I start taking this a little bit more seriously.
Maybe too seriously.
Yeah.
Oh boy.
Anyway, we have one last clip.
Okay.
About Y2K, which is an interesting, interesting, uh, Alex's question, uh, his answer, uh, is,
uh, O'Donnell Ian in its non forthrightness.
Okay.
Alex, I got a question about the Y2K you were saying.
I was listening to old tapes and you were saying, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I did nine hours of radio on Y2K on the Genesis network.
You notice that before a question was even asked, Alex goes into defensive mode.
Yeah.
And my best friend runs in on my wife and she says, they're on ABC news saying a missile
was launched from Russia.
Ooh.
Now it's his wife's fault.
Yeah.
So I run back out there and ABC news is saying a missile has been fired for Russia.
So I said, I don't know what it means, but a missile has been fired for Russia.
Then they come back and say, Oh, it was just a scud.
We have to have the Russians here at NORAD and it was like some kind of drill or something.
And then I went on a guy named Michael Trudeau show that day and made jokes about it.
So people took nine hours and edited nine hours.
Part of it, me joking around, like Joe was saying earlier, like nuclear plants were blowing
up.
Yeah, no, it's not true.
No, no.
What they did is they just took pieces and I got to have an AP article saying, well,
six plants are going offline.
And then an hour later they'd say it wasn't true.
They were doing that to create fear.
Like, like I didn't believe in Y2K at first, then the, then the Pentagon said it was going
to be real.
Then I started believing it.
And then right before they said, Oh, we never said that.
It was a psyop.
Oh, Ooh.
What?
Okay.
What did you, I don't know.
I feel like even those excuses are contradictory nonsense.
Yeah.
No, it was my wife who told me, but I didn't believe it.
And so it's her fault.
But also when the Pentagon said it, I was like, well, obviously it's true.
I didn't believe that because it's their fault.
I was the mainstream media did the thing and that's it.
And that's their fault.
None of this is my fault at all.
I was on air for nine air, uh, nine hours and they've taken everything out of context.
Totally.
They've misrepresented.
I've been smeared.
I have been smeared, sir.
Simultaneously.
I was reporting on things that were a hundred percent accurate because the media was trying
to create fear about Y2K reporting on these media stories that were designed to make fear,
but then they retracted those stores.
Wait, w w w which is it?
It's both neither and everything all at once.
Such horseshit.
Yup.
Anyway.
What an asshole.
Yup.
Um, this is an interesting glimpse.
Couldn't you just one time be like, Oh yeah, I fucked up on that one.
It's not even, it wouldn't even have to be.
No explanation.
No.
Just like, yeah, that one's on me.
My bad.
I think it's too embarrassing.
It has to be.
Yeah.
Because I love the second episode.
Yeah, that's true.
And looking at the Y2K episode of his show.
And I think, I think some of the stuff that he was doing was like, it's really too far.
Yeah.
He was saying that like bases were being set up at an Austin airport for people to be around.
Everyone's out of gas.
Yup.
The gas stations are out of food.
It went hard.
Yeah.
I remember.
I think owning that is too hard to do.
So you have to create a defensive straw man about like what actually happened and then
people like Eddie will just give you a pass.
Yeah, that's true.
You gotta go to commercial anyway.
Yeah, that's fair.
That's fair.
You hear the music.
Yeah.
Run out the clock on this answer and then Eddie will drop it.
Or we'll get to commercial and I'll be like, Eddie, that is not a fair question to ask
me on air.
Hey, don't ask me that question.
Yeah.
You know we're playing a game here.
It's stupid.
Yeah.
And now you're making me feel bad.
Stop it.
Eddie, you're high and having fun.
I am not.
So we get to the end of this and I think this is an interesting glimpse back if only for
this dynamic is so different and so similar.
Yeah.
It's similar in the ways that you hate and it's different in the ways that you miss.
Yup.
It's not fun in the way that these present day interviews are because Alex is fucked
up.
Right, right.
Yeah.
It's nonsensical.
Yeah, Alex is more willing to like keep the ramble going, keep the riff going long enough
to where he hangs himself with too much rope, like that kind of thing.
Yeah.
Whereas on this show he's trying to cut stuff off before he looks too stupid.
He's trying to protect the business.
Yup.
So anyway, we'll be back to the present for our next episode or you know, probably.
But until then, Jordan, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
We are also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledgefight.com.
Now go to Ben Jordan.
Yeah.
We're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook.
And if you could, please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work right now.
Yup.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX.
Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I am not a witch.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.