N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledgefight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
saying we are the bad guys, knowledgefight
Dan and Jordan, knowledgefight
Riddle her, riddle her, riddle her
I need, I need money
Andy and Kansas, Andy and Kansas
Stop it, Andy and Kansas, Andy and Kansas
Andy, Andy, it's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding us
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan
I love your room
knowledgefight
knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to knowledgefight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're a couple dudes, like to sit around, drink novelty beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are Dan
Jordan
Dan
Quick question for you
What's up
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today is, I'd like to thank a wonk out there named Pat
who got in touch and helped me find some old Alex Jones episodes
I'm still on the hunt for more
But it's one of the first times that a tip has actually paid off
and I've got some interesting stuff
I like it
to look at, so I really appreciate that
That's good news
It definitely, especially as like the modern day, it's kind of like
I mean, spoiler alert, basically I'm really underselling the episode we're about to do
Sure, sure, sure, sure
And I don't enjoy listening to it nearly as much as I probably would some kind of like
way deep in the past intellectual exercise
Yeah
Kind of thing
So you got home movies is what you're saying
Clips of Alex playing baseball at 12
Nah
It's gonna be great
Unless it's a variant of baseball
that is all about anti-communist heroes of his
John Birchball I believe is what it's called
Birchball
Yeah, Birchball
Yeah, so that's my bright spot, how about you?
My bright spot, Dan, is I found a TV show called Wellington Paranormal
that's made by the same guys that did What We Do in the Shadows
Jermaine Clement and Taika Waititi
It's fantastic, it's really good, it's like an X-Files that's super understated
in that New Zealand way where it's like they're trying to give a ticket to a werewolf
like that kind of situation where they're just
That sounds fun
Oblivious to the absolute insanity going on around them
It's just like, no, we're just trying to do our jobs
I can dig that
Yeah, it's really, really funny
It's in that great vein of the mockumentary kind of stuff
It's great
I hate these kinds of moments because I hear that and I'm like,
that sounds good, I probably enjoy that
You'll never see it
Exactly
The second moment is like, I'm never gonna watch that
I'm never gonna watch that shit
Oh well, maybe one day
Someday I'll get to New Zealand
Then I'll watch it
Yeah, we'll see it on the local TV
You know, Jordan, I gotta say, I feel like it's been too long
It feels like too long in between episodes
What, between Mondays and Fridays?
Yeah, it really does
Okay
It just feels like too long
You are
I'm itching to be back in this seat
You're utterly incapable of doing anything but 12 episodes per week
Yeah
If you could, I would just
I feel like we're getting back together and it's been forever
It's surprising that it has been a while
Especially considering, I think we watched a movie together on Tuesday
Yeah
Like, yeah
Yeah, Monday
Whatever
Anyway, we're back in the saddle
Indeed
And today we'll be going over March 23rd and 24th, 2021 Blackjack
Blackjack, oh god dammit
And this is Tuesday and Wednesday
Okay
Of this here week
Alright
And there's something interesting that's going on, man
Beginning of this week, Alex was gone again
Okay
He was out of studio again doing something on the East Coast
Okay, okay
Something mysterious
He's trying to get out of Texas slowly and then it keeps pulling him back in like the Twilight Zone kind of situation
He apparently recorded a video of himself at the Skull and Bones
Sure
Which I applaud
Yeah
Going back to his roots
No, absolutely
That's the kind of thing he should be moving back towards
Why not?
Yes
Yeah
Certainly better than literal devil stuff
Yeah, I'm on Team Fuck the Skull and Crossbones
I don't like Yale or whatever it is, fine
At the same time, as I expressed to you, I'm going to be furious if I have to do more episodes about where Geronimo's bones are
Yeah, I'm not going to be stoked about that one, that's true
I don't want to hear it
Ah, yeah
Anyway, he is back on the 23rd and I would say not better than ever
And we'll get down to talking about that in a little stretch of time
But before we do, let's take a little moment, Jordan, to say thank you to some folks who are now policy wonks
Oh, that's a great idea
So first, globalist big Dr. B, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, BDB
Thank you
Next, Jay in Maine, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Jay
Thank you
Next, you are now a policy wonk, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, you are now a policy wonk
Tongue twister
Oh, boy
Next, Lord Cakewagon, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much Lord Cakewagon
And Muffin pants, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, Muffin pants
Also, Baby Goblin, what's going on? You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, Runc
Did you know that Baby Goblin was made a Lord between now and when they sent that in so that's Lord Baby Goblin
I did not realize that. 40% of all Wonks are Lords. I did not realize there was this honorific. Yeah, it's a weird thing that happens.
Hmm. Yeah, and then also that reminded me that when we were doing our zipping up the mailbag
One of the things we forgot was that goblin. Oh, I know! That got sent, it was sitting right next to you. I brought it from my place
I was so gentle with it. I was holding it at the palm of my hand like can't let anything bad happen to it. Very, very delicate. And then I didn't get to show anybody.
And that was from Cameron, and so thank you so much Cameron. You are now a technocrat. Yes, thank you very much.
And Drew Desedue, thank you so much. You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk. Crikey mate, that's fantastic. Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
Alright, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this Watson, alright? Let's just get down to business. We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good? My neck is freakishly large. I declare info war on you.
Thank you to y'all. Yes, thank you very much.
So yeah, I would say that this stretch of time is bad. And there was actually a bit more in it that I felt it was offensively bad.
Like, it felt more like I don't want to do this. Which type? We have many different types of bad on this show.
We have the incompetent kind, we have the uninspired kind, we have the horrific evil kind.
What type of bad are we talking about? We can't even use the word bad anymore. Yeah, that's true.
It's tough to exactly pigeonhole it, but it just feels like generalized incitement.
And it's kind of a generalized boring incitement. That's not good.
That largely has to do around white fears and immigrants, there's a lot of that.
And I questioned on a certain level while I was listening to these, is this even worth it?
Does this rise to the level of paying attention to it? Because it's pretty much just fucking gross most of the time.
Well that's not good. No, it's not.
It's not even super bad, it's just real gross.
Anyway, here's an out of context drop from today's show.
These people are evil. And when I say they're not even physically ugly, it's that they're not real.
Like when you see a mannequin or you see, like I say, plastic fruit, you know it's plastic fruit no matter how good it is, no matter how fake it is.
You look at it and you go, that's fake. You just know.
And you look at them and you go, that's not normal. That's not normal.
Look at Brian Stelter, that's not normal. That's an enemy. That's the enemy.
God Blaggit? God Blaggit. God Blaggit? Blaggit!
He screams to God himself, how dare you make me kill my son Blaggit?
I heard that and I was like, all I want to do now for the rest of my life is hide plastic fruit around Alex.
I was going to say, that sounds like a man who has tried to eat plastic fruit. 100%.
I just want to get him on camera eating plastic fruit.
It's like somebody who goes out of the way to all of a sudden be like, you know, I've never tripped going upstairs embarrassingly.
It's never happened to me. I've seen tons of people do it before, but not me!
So Alex is late to work on the 23rd and it's because his plane was delayed.
And so he recorded himself prior to this so you'd have something to play in the beginning of the show.
I'm Alex Jones, your host, and as we speak, I'm about to arrive at the studio and complete the transmission live.
But I'm coming to you from earlier today in the space-time continuum as major news and information breaks.
We're about to premiere this amazing report that only you can share with others and defeat the globalists.
This is seriously a mission. We are seriously on the cutting edge of this fight.
This goddamn anti-communist Smokey the Bear.
Only you can stop the globalists.
Okay, we gotta get, we gotta get, I want video surveillance footage of him recording that in a weird bathroom somewhere.
Right, and trying to eat the fake fruit that's on the counter.
Actually, I don't want that surveillance. Never mind. Yeah.
So, you know, here's some of the stuff he's covering in his pre-recorded shit.
Okay.
Now the incredible news is Project Veritas has done it yet again.
They just had a major court ruling where a judge said the New York Times printed lies about them, that they were fake news, that that was a known fraud and that the New York Times lied.
Project Veritas did not win that lawsuit.
The headline that Alex is lying about here have to do with a New York Supreme Court judge determining that Veritas's defamation suit against the Times can move forward.
A couple articles in the Times referred to some Veritas videos as deceptive, but the judge felt that this was more opinion than it was straight up reporting of news.
This kind of ruling honestly just seems like a parody where a liar is getting the court to force journalists to strictly adhere to rules that they themselves think are jokes.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Anyway, the game here for Project Veritas isn't actually to win the case or anything like that.
It's about the media circus they can drum up along the way while simultaneously trying to make other outlets scared to critically cover their work.
That's what's going on here.
Yeah, there should be a consultancy for dumb old judges who are like, well, I guess we have to take these people as good faith actors because of the legal system.
And we could just be like, hey, no, you guys probably should have charged them with a federal crime a few years ago.
So no, fuck these guys.
So Alex still hasn't shown up at this point and it's getting to be like a ways into the show.
And so Owen's got to break in with some big news.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are live inside the Infowars world headquarters here.
Owen Troyer sitting in studio.
We're going to go back to Alex Jones here shortly.
He's going to be joining us live here shortly as well.
But I had to break in and report some of the latest that we know of the Boulder, Colorado shooter.
Obviously his name, Ahmad Al Isa.
It's now coming out.
He was an Islamic State sympathizer, so an Islamicist.
He was a immigrant from Syria.
I don't know if I can find any evidence that he was an Islamic State sympathizer outside of wild conjecture being made by the guy who runs Jihad Watch.
Yeah, I was going to say, all we've got there is Owen read the name and he was like, well, obviously this is a terrorist.
And the thing that I find really interesting is even like within the last week, you can see how news is dealt with differently.
When there was those shootings at the spas in Atlanta, Alex didn't even talk about it.
And then the next day it was like, ah, incel weirdo, or whatever.
And then just moved on.
Maybe touched the story for a second on the second day.
When it's this, break into coverage.
Owen Troyer's got to come into studio to break in to give you the latest.
Kind of see what's going on here.
This is something that should fill people with great shame.
And the only way they can survive this long is by having that part of their brain removed at some point in their lives.
Because that is disgusting.
Just on a really deep human level, just disgusting.
Because it proves beyond reasonable doubt that they are choosing which stories maliciously.
Not because of any kind of newsworthiness purely by malice.
Yeah.
I mean, I think it's demonstrated throughout the most of my career.
I mean, you can't even, there's no middle ground on that whatsoever.
No, it's pretty tough.
Yeah.
So Owen knows, I mean he's been around long enough at Infowars that he knows the game.
He knows exactly what they do in these cases of shootings.
Sure. Gun control is common.
Well, of course. But also, psych meds, got to talk about that.
Got to portray him as the other side.
Sure.
He was a leftist, bro.
Of course.
He was, it seems maybe a paranoid schizophrenic.
So who knows what kind of pharmaceutical drugs he had been prescribed potentially for those mental problems.
And then we also have a lot of his social media activity before it was deleted.
Before it was deleted, showing that he was an anti-Trumper.
He was a leftist, liberal progressive.
He was one of those that pushed the leftist narrative to a T.
So, I mean, they do have some screenshots of what appear to be his social media.
Sure.
And I mean, some of those descriptions are slightly fair.
He had some post that they showed that were critical of Trump, but like,
Cool.
I don't know how much, like, it doesn't seem like it has anything to do with,
at least they haven't demonstrated at all that it has anything to do with what happened.
So Alex plays audio of the shooting.
No.
And I think it's incredibly exploitative and I'm not going to play that here,
but I'm going to play what he has afterwards.
Okay.
This is his, something he had prerecorded also.
His name was Eric Talley, a 51-year-old father of seven who was a patriot and who really loved human life.
And that everybody that knew him said was just an amazing person.
And he died heroically, helping stop some type of insane demonic psycho
that went into a King's Super grocery store in Boulder, Colorado,
and shot and killed 10 people, including this police officer.
He's the only name we know right now.
This is tragic and I'm not, you know, not going to diminish anything,
but the way Alex is behaving around this is really exploitative.
That's really the only way I can put it.
And then when Owen starts talking about what the solution to these problems are,
it kind of runs counter to the way Alex in his prerecorded stuff is trying to build this up.
Look, here's the deal.
Mass shootings in this country are really a rare occurrence
and they would be even more rare if we had citizens with guns stopping them.
But they know the police take at least two minutes to get to the scene
so they know they can fire off at least a magazine or two full of rounds
of innocent people killing people and get away with it
because they never get stopped until the cops show up.
One person, one citizen, one good citizen with a gun
could have saved lives in that Colorado grocery store.
And so there's this whole notion like, oh, you just want it to be like,
blah, blah, blah, everybody with a pistol on their head, blah, blah, blah.
No, that's not how I want it. That's not how I want it at all.
I want white people to have guns.
One crazy guy, one bad guy with a gun to kill ten people,
all it would have taken was one good guy with a gun in that store to stop it.
The problem is that one of the people who was killed was a cop
who was responding who had a gun.
Oh, they didn't give him the gun that day.
I mean, it's not like this disproves any possibility
of someone disrupting an active shooting or anything like that,
but the notion that they have that this is a magic, pardon the expression,
a magic bullet to stop situations like this is just, it's just ludicrous.
Yeah, in order to stop mass shootings, we need to get one good guy with a gun
to either assume people are going to be a mass shooter
and just start killing before anyone is a mass shooter
or get to the point where they're killing people after one or two killings.
So it's not a mass shooting. It's just four or five people dead.
I don't think you're solving a goddamn thing.
Yeah, interject into the center of an active shooting
and deputize yourself to shoot out with somebody who...
I don't think this is a good solution,
and I think that InfoWar's own reporting is a little bit convoluted on this front.
Anyway, Owen has a belief that most people won't ever be really affected by mass shootings,
and I mean, that's a little offensive, but everyone will be affected by liberal policies.
Oh, that'll happen.
Most people listening to this broadcast will probably never be directly impacted by a mass shooting.
Let's pray to God that continues.
But almost everybody listening to this podcast,
almost everybody listening to this radio show,
almost everybody watching this right now
is going to be negatively impacted by Democrat liberal policies
just like everyone in that grocery store was.
That's the real threat.
And now the liberal lefties are going so out of control.
Their minds are so warped. Their minds are so bent, propagandized.
They've become dangers to society.
So this individual was a danger to society.
He came in with a gun. He killed people.
Well, most of these liberals may not have a gun, but they're dangers to society.
Their policies will kill you.
Their policies will kill freedom in the West.
So the only policies really that he could be really talking about are...
Have to be gun control, right?
Well, that's one possibility.
Disarming people who could be the good person with a gun who can carry out murder against a murderer.
Or it's immigration-related, because this guy came from Syria a number of years back.
And so that would be the leftist policy that he's attacking there.
They're letting people who do these mass shootings in.
Sure, sure, sure, sure, sure.
And either way, it's dumb.
But it's also just... it's disappointing.
Yeah, I mean, it's hard to just... it's not far apart.
It's hard to be like, oh, it's liberals letting people in a week after it's not liberals letting people in.
You know, it's like, maybe there's a larger problem.
Maybe there's one that should be dealt with.
And maybe we should deal with it in a way that makes sense.
And unfortunately...
Or we could issue everybody guns. Do you want a gun, Dan?
No.
Oh, are you sure?
Not at the moment.
On the hip?
Nah, I'm alright for right now.
Okay, fine.
I like how you're like, would you like an appetizer?
Would you like a gun?
I'm okay.
Are you sure?
I also think that Owen's not the best prism to be looking at this through.
He's very milquetoast, but also clearly pretty extreme.
Yeah, no, he's got a psychopathic energy of the banality of evil going on about him.
Alex is more sort of interesting, and Harrison Smith is more of a straight-up bigot.
Yeah, Harrison Smith just says, don't let brown people in, and if they are in, shoot them with guns.
But being boring about it, which is terrifying.
So thankfully, Owen is done at this point, and Alex shows back up.
You know what he was doing? He was on a secret mission.
Well, I was on a secret mission in Connecticut.
I bet we'll find out what it is.
It was yesterday, but that's part of it.
But I am back in Austin, just landed about 30 minutes ago, rushed here to the studio.
Flight was a little bit delayed, or I would have been here from the start of the broadcast.
So we don't know. We don't get to find out what this secret mission was to Connecticut.
We don't get to find out what it is?
No.
What about the video we have of it out there?
Well, I mean, he went to the Skull and Bones.
Sure.
But that wasn't his main trip.
Oh, okay.
His main trip was, I would guess, if I had to bet anything, it would be lawyer-related.
It was in Connecticut.
Does he have any possible reason? There's no secret mission I could think of to go to Connecticut.
Boy, you know, there's a lot of reasons to go to Connecticut if you're Alex Jones.
At the drop of a hat.
I would argue he has more reasons to go to Connecticut than just about anybody else alive.
He has one very specific reason to go to Connecticut.
He is locked into Connecticut.
I would guess it had something to do with maybe like Discovery or something to do with the Sandy Hook case.
I mean, like, I can't imagine it being unrelated to that case.
Yeah, it would be hard. It would be hard.
When he said he was going to the East Coast, I was like, smells like Sandy Hook something.
But, you know, I don't know. There's a lot of places he could go on the East Coast.
Sure, sure.
When he said it's Connecticut, he's either, it's either Sandy Hook case related or he went to Stanford and he's trying to get a job with Vince McMahon.
Ah, that's possible. I'm not going to say no to that.
Yeah, that's the only other possibility.
Maybe he's enrolling in UConn. He wants to be a Husky, Dan. I went there for a semester.
Hey, maybe he's following your footsteps.
Yeah, he's always wanted to be me.
So, Trump, you know, this narrative gets really interesting with Alex at this point.
He's like, Obama, bad camps for immigrants and migrants coming over.
Bad.
Trump cleaned it all up.
Good.
Everything is good. Now, bad again.
How is it bad so fast?
It went bad really fast.
It seems like it's too fast.
Well, it's because Biden had a clip that Alex keeps playing where he's saying that he wants people to surge in whenever he becomes president.
Sure.
And what he's talking about is people applying for refugee status that were disallowed from being able to apply for refugee status during the Trump administration because he would just not.
We took four refugees during the entire Trump administration. Biden's like, can we have more than four?
That's not accurate, but also the ceiling was dropped quite a bit.
Yes, I was being perhaps embellishing.
And the only way to apply for asylum in the United States as a refugee, you have to be in the United States.
So when the Trump administration would stop people from making it into consulates or on the border, that was what he's talking about.
So Alex is pretending that Biden was like, everybody over the wall.
And so anyway, it's bad now. The camps are back to bad.
Sure.
Remember all the nice facilities Trump built with the water fountains in each area?
And they said, oh, you're drinking out of toilets. And AOC went and cried in front of a fence in a parking lot.
Well, she's not crying now because she's a monster and an exploiter for the most powerful, rich, tax exempt billionaires on the planet.
Ladies and gentlemen, AOC literally came out immediately against Biden, having migrant facilities open for children.
She tweeted, quote, This is not OK. Never has been OK. Never will be OK, no matter the administration or party.
Alex is making up that AOC doesn't oppose the things that Biden's administration is doing at the border because that's too complicated of a story for him to tell his audience.
The listeners are used to very simplistic good versus evil characterizations of people.
So to introduce the idea that AOC was against the treatment of migrants under Trump and is still opposed to the same types of treatment under Biden,
that represents a threat to the characters that Alex has painted.
Yeah, it really fucks things up whenever your enemy, I suppose, of Alex's has ideological consistency.
And ideological differences between the people Alex wants to pretend are all working for the fucking devil.
Yeah, that's that's that's what I'm saying.
He could have picked plenty of Democrats who are like, well, we're Democrats in the White House now.
We don't need to worry about. Yeah, that's that's not an unpopular opinion.
Yeah, but AOC is. Yeah. So I like most of this episode has been immigrant bashing at this point.
Like there is I have not, you know, cut out or I have not included a ton just because it's kind of standard, boring immigrant bashing that I just don't.
I don't know. He said a lot of this stuff before.
Yeah, he hates nonwhite people going into the country. We got it.
And then they're bringing in hard core people. Most of the, quote, Middle Eastern immigrants, the country, the refugees in the U.S., it's over 75 percent that are men.
Look, the numbers up in Europe. Again, look it up. Eighty five to 90 percent are men, military age men.
Yeah, there's this tweet, Ahmed Al Isa, why refugees and immigrants are good for America.
So he's trying to connect that to the the boulder shooting.
And it kind of makes a little clearer what what Owen's line of thought probably was.
Like I said, this episode is almost impossible to listen to. There's no real substance going on.
And it's mostly Alex just rambling nonsense to make his listeners afraid of immigrants.
According to the Pew Research numbers put out in August 2020, Alex is completely full of shit.
One thing he probably doesn't even know is that, quote, among all refugees admitted in fiscal year 2019, 4,900 are Muslims and 23,800 are Christian.
That's 16 percent Muslim and 79 percent Christian. That's super different than the picture Alex tends to paint, which is weird.
It's kind of weird. Yeah.
Also, according to the statistics from the Department of Homeland Security regarding refugee arrivals in 2019,
there's just no way to pretend that everyone coming in are military aged men. For one, 49 percent of arrivals in 2019 were women.
Secondly, 12 percent of all arrivals were aged 45 or older.
But then again, I have no idea what Alex would consider military aged.
Finally, the thing that Alex is mostly banking on here is that 43.2 percent of arrivals were between the ages of zero and 17.
That's a pretty wide age gap, so using the same number, Alex could try to make you scared of refugee teens,
and someone else could explain to you that a lot of these people are children.
Issues related to immigration and refugee resettlement are super important in the real world, but they aren't important when dealing with Alex.
He isn't living in reality and making an argument for policy.
He's decided that he hates immigration and the U.S. becoming less white, and he's making up shit to justify it.
None of this stuff is real, and it's just an appeal to fear, and it's boring.
Yeah, and it's really, really fucked up on the back of a racist, misogynist mass shooting.
Like, okay, whoa, we gotta hold off on being racist towards Asian for a little bit, so we can't not be racist,
so we're gonna switch targets to just blanket immigration.
How many fucking years are we gonna do this?
It's not like this is a new thing for some white motherfucking asshole to start screaming that all immigrants are evil.
We do it all the goddamn time.
You mean Alex, not the shooters.
No, I don't mean, yeah, I mean Alex, but I mean, like, it goes back, you can read newspaper articles from 1790 where it's like,
now we gotta close our fucking borders.
Right, right.
You know, it's like, we're just not gonna deal with it.
And the maligned groups can change, but the mentality stays the same.
And every time it blends up in violence, it doesn't stop, and we could deal with it, but we just refuse to,
under some bullshit banner of, just like Project Veritas being allowed to go with their fucking lawsuit,
I'm just, these guys are not good faith actors.
Yeah, probably not.
But you know who you should go to for information and ideas about immigration?
The Health Ranger?
Someone in Europe who has a great track record.
Oh no.
Someone who might be the head of Hungary.
More bonds come out from Eastern Europe and said it's forbidden to say so in Europe, but this is organized invasion.
95% of the immigrants are military age men.
Yeah, that's some of the boatloads come in that are 95% military age men.
Hell, some are 100%, but the numbers we've gotten are 85, 95%.
It's on, ladies and gentlemen.
And when they're on video, they're like, I'm here to rape, I'm here to kill, I'm here to burn, and they just start burning cities, raping.
Holy shit.
That seems extra.
Yeah, and I don't know about appealing to Viktor Orban as your guy.
I don't know if that's a great citation, seeing as he's made assisting refugees a criminal act.
Yeah, I would say, boy, it seems like he's like, you know what, that chow chess cue had some good policies.
I'm not saying he's a good guy, but when it comes to immigration, you want the chow and you get the chess cue, okay?
Yeah, it's strange.
Well, I mean, it's not strange at all. It's very transparent.
No. Anyway, if Biden, you know, after these shootings that have happened, if he wants to take a guns, turns out Alex and his friends are going to be more deadly than the Viet Cong.
Okay.
So let me tell you where this is going to end.
If Joe Biden tries to take the guns, it's going to wipe out law enforcement and a lot of military to the cause of civil war that'll make the Vietnamese resistance in Vietnam look tame.
And then if they were even successful to break the back of the country and get most people to do it, it will then create a giant underground and lawlessness.
You'll have such bad police involved. They'll all be corrupt that you will be worse than Mexico.
We will be a completely failed state with kidnappings, murders, beheadings, hundreds of thousands dead every few years, just like we basically are becoming.
Because the Tower of Babel can be every AI globalist takeover that's killing everybody that wants a post human world.
Okay. Yeah, I don't know. I'm not sure exactly what he's trying to intimate.
Like, is it that if Biden puts in better background check regulations for guns, that everybody will be murdered on the street?
Or is it that he and his friends will start guerrilla warfare?
I think he's just imagining Red Dawn. That's what he's talking about. He's talking about joining the Wolverines, going up in the mountains and running the Swamp Fox 2.0.
Yeah, 1776 2.0. No! That's over with. 1764 2.0, Dan.
It seems like a little, I don't know, it doesn't make me feel all that comfortable.
You know, it's going back to a lot of the ideas that were more popular within some of these militia right wing communities earlier on.
You know, the books like Unintended Consequences, those kinds of ideas that it's just, it's not great to see them popping up again.
Things feel a lot more volatile right now.
Yeah, on the other hand, they are a bunch of cosplaying cowards that give up at the first hint of actual resistance.
So there's, you know, it is a little bit heartening for me to look back on the 6th and remember that when push comes to shove, Alex will say that it was never his idea and it was all the liberals' fault in the end.
So I'm not too worried about guerrilla warfare from these assholes.
Hey, you know all those people who are out there doing the Red Dawn thing? That's just Antifa.
No, that was, I was saying, Antifa, they're Red Dawning us because of the double Red Dawn proposition.
Okay.
Yeah.
So the, oh boy, this isn't good.
Yeah, I'll just tell you that. There's a good set up for this clip.
Okay.
This isn't good.
Not good.
So let me explain how this works.
They collapse the third world.
Sure.
They flood us with Africans, military age men, Europe particularly.
That doesn't sound right.
And then, yeah, I mean, you're in a town of 500 Germans.
They put 2,000 military age men, black men from a poor country there with no jobs at refugee center.
They start raping and robbing you, some of them.
Now you hate black people.
Now you want to annihilate them.
And see, that's how the globalists are going to make us join them in the extermination of the third world.
That's coming next.
I don't know if I would be susceptible to that sort of plan that the globalists would have because I see other solutions to problems.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm confused.
I'm not entirely sure if there are these towns with 500 people and 2,000 immigrants come into it, all men with no jobs or whatever.
But let's assume that is the situation.
Sure.
I feel like there could be some other sort of structural ways that we could deal with the issue.
Hey, let's put some government works projects together, get these people employed.
Let's get some jobs.
Sure.
Let's get some maintenance.
I know this from the United States and Chicago specific.
Every bridge needs a little bit of work.
That's true. That is true.
Bridges are scary.
They are deteriorating quick.
Yes.
So let's get the government involved and inject a little bit of money. Everybody has a job.
That does make sense.
No, no, Alex is determined that this is how they're going to trick you into wanting to annihilate a population.
Yeah, I really feel like maybe you don't need, or maybe, I feel like maybe you're manufacturing reasons to do what you already want to do.
Maybe.
That's what I would, that would be my instant reaction to this.
Maybe you want to feel blameless about having those feelings already, and so you're creating excuses.
I'm just going to go out on a limb here, and I'm going to say that that would probably become a national news story.
Maybe a global news story. If Germany's government, Merkel is just like,
yeah, we're going to put 2,000 only military-aged men in with this small, tiny town of 500 people,
and then they're going to murder everyone.
Right.
And they'd be like, at the very least, this would call for a special session of Congress, right?
Yeah.
At least one.
So one of the things that I think is really interesting is that Alex plays a lot of games with what he believes is going on.
Sure.
You know, like he'll say that the globalists believe that they're talking to an extra-dimensional being.
I'm not saying I believe that.
No, no, no, he doesn't believe that.
I'm saying that that's what they believe. I'm just here warning you what they believe.
He does follow that up usually with, now it's obviously true.
Well, yeah, but just to be totally clear here, Alex is expressing that he literally believes he's fighting the biblical devil.
I was going to say, yeah. There we go.
And at the end of the day, they want to get everybody, because again, they make some of the elite white people think,
oh, you're going to be part of the club. No. Now they admit it's a post-human world, whatever this is running things.
And I believe the Bible, it's the devil, does not want any humans.
The Bible tells us the devil comes to destroy God's creation.
So Alex believes he's fighting the Christian biblical literal devil.
Question.
Yeah.
For Alex's theology.
Uh-huh.
All right. So the devil wants to destroy all humans.
Mm-hmm.
Okay. What happens to their souls?
Do they still get heaven and hellified or is he going for all the souls in heaven and hell too?
That's a great question.
And if so, how is he going to pull that one off?
Ooh.
Finally, should he succeed in killing all the humans, then what?
Or let's go another direction.
Uh-huh.
Let's say Alex is successful in vanquishing the devil.
Okay. What does he do? Who takes over stewardship of hell?
Right.
Yeah. All those people are just hanging out?
That's going to be chaos.
That's going to be, yeah, that's really going to fuck up the infrastructure of hell currently.
Right. And then how does that reshape theology for the future?
Doesn't it?
It's like, okay, so we-
You have to rewrite the entire Bible.
There needs to be a new Bible.
There has to be an entirely new Bible.
A lot of it is probably going to be based on stuff from our show.
The animals of Alex Jones.
You have the Old Testament, you have the New Testament, and the Jones Testament.
Yeah, because it nullifies almost all of the prophecies.
Like the revelations is, you don't even talk about God defeating the devil or a thousand years of Jesus' reign.
It's just more like Alex did it.
That's the end of revelations is, hey man, it was a good thing God gave us Alex fucking Jones.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Sure.
The last verse of the Bible is, I'm not bragging, but we did it guys.
Just one mission. No Bible at all. Just a mission accomplished banner. That's it.
Yeah, I don't really quite understand what, I don't know.
I just think it's really important to recognize that whenever he says stuff like,
I'm not saying that I believe this stuff, it's what they believe.
Of course.
That's him trying to hold onto some thread of respectability and credibility with people who would call him nuts.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's like, I'm fighting the devil.
Yeah, that's tough.
Everybody needs to recognize that.
That's really tough.
You need to recognize he thinks it's the devil.
I know.
It is a little bit like how they, all the articles about Roger Stone are always conspicuously like,
he was a lobbyist and he was close to Trump's inner circle and they never mentioned that he hosted a show on Infowars for two years.
That is a news outlet whose editorial position is staunchly anti-devil.
Yes, 100% anti-communism, anti-devil.
Roger Stone absolutely, I guarantee, said that the basic problem is the devil.
Probably. I don't know if he ever believed it.
I doubt it. I don't know if he believes anything.
Yeah, I think that it would be interesting to have that be what the public conversation is.
Totally.
It's not like he's a free speech crusader.
No.
He's not a Trump fan. He's a guy who thinks he's fighting the devil.
Totally.
And he's also super racist.
Yes.
But there are interesting things that he tries to get, he's taken some calls here on the show,
and he has this conversation that he has with the caller about taking these racist feelings you have and then redirecting them at the globalists.
That's nice.
No.
2024, really a massive political expression is needed.
Well, everything the enemy does is divide us.
And look, I'm tribal, I got red blood, don't you think I see all this and get mad at groups?
Then I go, that's my animal side.
I had that programming to survive in the old times against the group attacking me, but the enemy is using that against us.
And we have to still defend ourselves against groups or whatever, but we have to be aware of the larger plan.
That's the only way to defeat this.
This is an alien attack.
I don't go off UFOs or any of that.
I mean, it's alien.
The whole thing is rewrite humans, bring in world government.
Also, UFOs are real.
They want to kill everybody.
They try to kill us all.
UFOs are realer than the devil.
Well, I don't care if they were just killing the Africans, I'm against it.
But the truth is, they're killing everybody.
Does that make sense?
Not totally.
But the point that he's trying to make is essentially that he has this old timey racist programming that's inside him.
And you've got to take that and direct it towards the globalists.
And it's like, well, no, you should rise above it.
Maybe wrestle with it.
Wrestle with those feelings as opposed to just hate someone else.
It has to be evolution itself that makes him racist.
It can't possibly be cultural.
I actually don't think that he was talking about caveman days.
Where it's like a group.
I think he was talking about when he was in high school.
Because he constantly talks about how black people would beat him up in high school.
Sure, sure.
He talks about that all the time.
That's true.
I think he's talking about youth.
What an asshole.
I think it's so ironic now, with all the reports that we have from very credible sources and the government releasing shit,
that it's like, look, we see UFOs all the time.
I've got to be honest with you.
We see UFOs all the goddamn time.
Here are tapes of navy pilots.
Here's video. Here's everything.
And Alex is like, whoa, whoa, whoa, I don't believe in UFOs.
It's the devil we're fighting.
I'm fighting a demon.
It's the devil.
Right.
At the same time, still, the functioning letter in UFO is U.
Of course.
And, you know, let's get some more, let's make those IFOs.
Sure, sure, sure, sure. I see what you're saying.
So Alex takes another call, and this guy, he seems to be worried that the FBI is following his social media.
And Alex's response to it is a little bit weird.
Hey, Alex.
So I just want to preface this message with what Paul said in first collagens, because it's kind of scary, what I'm going to say.
He said that the powers of darkness were defeated on the cross.
And that is the, that is our only hope right now.
Look, I had the FBI show up at my house.
I have a TikTok account and Snapchat, and I basically preach the gospel on there.
And I went into the vaccine.
I'm kind of nervous on this phone call, to be honest with you, because...
It's okay, sir.
The FBI is the run by the Chinese now, and it's run by the Globals.
They just, they're told just to come out and intimidate you.
It's all, there's nothing to be afraid of.
That does relax me.
That's okay.
That's a wildly, oh, man, I'm so relaxed.
Yeah.
I was worried about the FBI, but that was the American government's FBI.
Now that I know they're controlled by the Chinese, and the Chinese just tell them to go rough people up a little bit.
I don't know what to believe about this caller.
He sounds a little skittish and a little weird.
Sure, a little bit.
I don't believe that the FBI, I don't know if I believe the FBI showed up at his house.
If they did, I believe that he's posting more on that account than he's letting on.
It does sound like maybe the FBI wouldn't just walk around at the behest of the Chinese government to scare him a little bit because of his TikTok.
Whatever the reality or non-reality of this one visit is, I'm guessing there's not going to be a follow-up visit, and they're not listening to him call into Alex's show.
I would say so.
There's some delusional paranoia that's going on here, and Alex is doing a great disservice to his listener by being like, oh, don't worry about it.
Don't worry about it.
It's just the FBI working for the Chinese.
Come on.
That is the way, like, to deal with delusional paranoia, he's like, we're not going to deal with the delusion whatsoever.
We're going to deal with the paranoia.
I'm going to try and make you calm down.
Of course the delusion is true.
I'm going to make you calm down, but also make it way worse.
Like, whatever you're worried about, so much worse.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, what are you doing?
Oh, you're starving.
A nuclear bomb's coming.
Oh, you're worried about one government?
You're worried about law enforcement?
Guess what?
The new government's talking about.
Now it's everybody.
Oh, also, and the new world order.
And the European government is trying to hire Africans to kill your entire town.
And also they're working with the spider leadership and the raptors.
All run by the literal devil.
Does the devil want to destroy aliens?
Alex hasn't weighed in on that, man.
He doesn't get into UFO stuff.
I just want to know.
I'm just adding that in there?
Silly, silly UFO stuff.
Okay, so Alex gets another call, and this guy makes an interesting point, and that is
that China isn't communist.
There is that.
Which is an interesting problem for Alex, because he constantly calls them the chai
comms and yells about communist China.
Yeah, there's a problem.
Uh oh.
I read China's not a communist country, nor at all a socialist country, but a primitive
crony capitalist country economically and a totalitarian dictatorship politically.
Now that's it.
China is a giant slave colony of the globalist.
We used to leverage out the whole planet and let them economically through economic warfare
and take over.
Here's what's going to happen.
Oh, we're not going to.
We've got one more 11 minute segment.
Okay.
We're not going to bother with that.
Not going to engage.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Crony capitalism and totalitarian government, which we absolutely have nothing resembling
here.
He rephrased this in a way that works for me, which is it's a testing ground for the
globalists and then we'll move on and I won't have to deal with how I am full of shit.
And he might as well just like neiner, neiner, neiner.
I'm going to call him communist tomorrow.
Like, that might as well have been his response.
Yeah.
So he gets another call, and this guy has a story from a year ago that blows Alex's
mind because it helps him demonize Muslims.
Locally, in Knoxville a year ago, April 8th, we had a stabbing.
You can find it on the internet.
Three pilot, that's a gas station, three pilot employees killed in stabbing attack at Knoxville
I-40 truck stop.
And of course they got no coverage because it was a knife.
Well, and yes, and then they had an article on the front page of the local newspaper,
a rag, the Knoxville News Sentinel under the leadership of the editor, Joel Christopher.
I wouldn't wipe my rear end with it.
They gave a front page coverage to the mother of the stabbing stabber, and she said that
it was not possible that he could have done what he did.
So why are we not hearing about it?
What is the racial makeup?
He was of Middle Eastern descent.
Bingo.
Yeah.
If a Muslim doesn't think, well, who else wants to stab three women?
I mean, 90% of the time it's going to be a Muslim.
Let's just say it.
I'm on against all Muslims, but give me a break, man.
They got a thing about killing women.
Wow.
That's wild.
That's really wild.
In Altadena, California last week, two people were fatally stabbed on a Zoom call, and I've
not heard Alex bring that story up at all.
There's a news story out of Michigan where a 14-year-old girl spent months planning to
stab her friend in the woods because she, quote, wanted to see someone die.
You had to hear this reported on Infowars.
We could do this all day, but the point doesn't matter.
Stories are props for Alex, and this is a prop for him to demonize and foment hatred
towards Muslims.
I believe this caller is also conflating things.
The claims that I believe were in those articles, they weren't that the guy, he couldn't have
been the person at the stabbing.
They were that he couldn't have been involved in a previous stabbing in a town called Millington
that initially people thought might have been connected because he definitely wasn't in
that other town, and I think that he's just conflating things about the reporting being
like, it couldn't have been him.
Because why worry about details like that, Dan?
You've got a group of people to smear and hate for the rest of your life.
Yeah.
Cool.
So Alex is like, this is exciting, a year-old story about a stabbing at a gas station.
Hooray, let's talk about this forever.
And the media covered it up by putting it in the front page of the local newspaper.
And covered it up by, like, there's a bunch of stories you can find about it if you want.
Anyway, they decide to talk about it for quite a while.
And then, Alex, they went on to have follow-up articles on the front page of the local newspaper
rag, and they said that the people who stopped him, who killed him and stopped him from killing
people, were investigated and cleared of any wrongdoing.
Yeah, they had an article at Yale saying, should I be arrested for being at Yale?
Wow, I'm glad you call in and know about this.
We're pulling the articles up now.
So Islamic stabs and kills three women, because he hates, you know, seeing that I'm free.
And then the media calls him a victim.
Holy mackerel.
Bill, I gotta jump, and I'm glad you called.
Let us know about that.
Wow.
You can see here how Alex takes little pieces of inaccurate information that a caller has
passed along to him, and then he writes his own headlines about them.
He's decided, based on literally nothing, that this person who stabbed people at a pilot
station was motivated by his religious beliefs and because he was so mad about women being
free because he's a Muslim.
This is all completely made up and based on nothing other than Alex's intense hatred towards
people he sees as different from himself.
Also, this caller is once again fucking up details.
The articles in the paper after the stabbing incident were about whether or not the police
were justified in using deadly force against the stabber.
They had ordered him to drop his weapon eight times and the police killed him when he failed
to drop his weapon and he began to walk towards the police car.
The news articles that this guy is referring to were about the DA's determination that
it was a justified shooting, which isn't the same as being like, oh, was it right to...
Yeah.
Whatever.
Fucking assholes.
I'm noticing the length of time we're spending on this call versus the one that was like,
the Chinese are a crony capitalist country.
Let's move on.
It does seem like he moved on from that awful quick.
Oh wait, you got a story about someone who you think is a Muslim stabbing somebody?
I mean, considering...
A year ago, this is exciting.
Considering discovering that information about China, seeing as how China is his main boogeyman
really, that could shake his entire worldview.
So he should really spend more time thinking on that as opposed to this one, which confirms
his biases.
Also, I found a C-SPAN symposium that Alex did about 9-11 conspiracy theories in 2006.
And one of his arguments that he makes is that somehow the globalists are working against
China.
So in 2006, they were against each other.
Completely different cosmology of evil at that time.
Gotcha.
So, we're done with the 23rd here.
And a lot of the show seems to be really intensely anti-immigrant.
It's disgustingly anti-Muslim and boring, just sort of paint-by-numbers nonsense of
Alex's bullshit.
And then, you know, the show's just disgusting on the 24th.
Some, like, weird pedophile stuff.
Jesus.
It's all about hurting your children.
And as soon as you figure that out, these are demonic monsters the sooner we beat them.
They are a cult.
Most of them are pedophiles.
Mid-level Democrats and up are pedophiles.
Remember that.
You don't even get in the club unless you rape children.
So Alex is above the political divide.
Totally.
You know, the left-right paradigm is all an illusion to this guy.
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
But all mid-level Democrats and above.
What is a mid-level Democrat?
I was wondering the exact same thing.
What's the cut-off point for mid-level?
Well, it's gotta be any elected official, right?
I mean, I don't know.
Would you call a state rep mid-level?
Maybe.
Or, like, as an alderman in Chicago mid-level?
Mayor?
Small town mayor.
Small town...
Sheriff.
Constitutional sheriff.
No, those are high-level patriots.
What about Democratic constitutional...
I don't even know if that exists, yeah.
Yeah, I just find this unacceptable and stupid, and I don't have time for it.
No.
So we get to an interesting story.
And this is a story about, allegedly, Black Lives Matter kidnapped 100 people.
That just...
Okay.
You didn't hear about this?
You didn't hear about this this week?
Hold on one second.
Yeah.
Black Lives Matter as a whole...
Nah, just some people in Rochester.
Okay.
A group in Rochester, Black Lives Matter.
Kidnapped a bunch of people inside a grocery store.
A hundred people?
Yes.
Okay.
And Soros is apparently paying them to do this.
That sounds true.
It's about keeping us shut down, intimidating us.
You ask, why would somebody do something this over the top and this crazy?
They do it because they've been told by Soros to go do it, they're paid to do it, and they're
seeing how far they can push us.
And guess what?
We keep putting up with it so it's gonna get worse.
The article's up on infowars.com and newswars.com.
It's also from gatewaypundit.com.
BLM mob traps 100 customers inside grocery store.
We're shutting stuff down.
S down.
S-H, you know what, down.
And they kept them in there for a long time.
According to a reporter for WROC who's on the scene, the entire framing of this story
is completely fake and a racist lie being perpetuated by right wing media to attack
Black Lives Matter.
That does sound more likely.
Kayla Green, who was there, said, quote, Wegmans closed doors and customers were kept inside
temporarily but were let out soon after.
Protesters never entered the store.
Protesters are currently listening to music and eating pizza in the parking lot.
Nobody is, quote, trapped inside.
Yeah, I was gonna say, every one of these types of protests I've been to have been sometimes
overly incredibly kind.
Protesters were having a memorial demonstration on the anniversary of the day that Rochester
police arrested Daniel Prude, which ultimately led to his death.
But instead of discussing any of that reality, Alex just says that Soros is paying to agitate
the goodly white people of the country to make them feel bad and stay inside a grocery
store or something.
Yeah.
It's all nonsense.
It is kind of really a good example of that kind of going, you know, that propaganda method
of going at your enemy's strength instead of their weakness.
When he goes after, like, why would somebody do something so over the top and ridiculous?
Because they wouldn't.
This is too over the top and ridiculous.
Aha.
I will just cut past all of that by saying Soros.
See?
Done.
Now, I will say that this next clip worried me because it's even more over the top.
And it also made me think, Alex...
Black Lives Matter clowned Mount Everest and blew it up.
No, he starts acting like they committed criminal kidnapping.
Sure.
Now, let me show you under federal and state law.
This is Title five, offense against the person, chapter 20, kidnapping, unlawful restraint
and smuggling of persons.
And that's what OJ Simpson went to jail for over a decade for.
And these were folks he found out were counterfeiting his stuff and he was pissed at them.
I might say what he was right, but, you know, I kind of get it.
Are you defending OJ?
But he actually...
Are we defending OJ now?
It makes me worried he's going to OJ me.
Is that a thing?
Are we defending OJ?
Okay.
Alright.
So, anyway, this Black Lives Matter protest in Rochester kidnapped and wrongly arrested
these people.
Sure.
And hey, man, if Alex was there, he probably would have started swinging.
Aren't we in an occupied government?
Aren't laws meaningless now?
That was a week ago.
Sorry about that.
It was in service of a completely different conversation.
Sorry.
I forgot.
And it felt really good at the time.
Those are still real.
Yeah.
But if Alex was there, he would have started swinging on people, man, just started knocking
people out left and right.
And then, then the media, the media would have called it a race war.
So they go to a grocery store, a Wegmans grocery store, and trap an estimated 100 people in.
Some reports are this went on for at least an hour.
You know, what do you got to go home to your kids?
What was that?
An hour?
Some reports.
An hour.
I got to shoot my mouth off.
But if a couple of hundred people came and blocked me inside a grocery store and I had
to go somewhere, I can't help it.
I'm going to get violent.
And then it's going to be called a race war.
No, if some white people blocked me in a grocery store, I'm going to start kicking their ass.
I mean, brown people, I don't give a damn.
At a certain point, folks, this is out of control.
And if we put up with this, we'll put anything.
Huh.
See, that's what I'm saying.
I'm not worried about them starting a guerrilla warfare campaign because we're at the level
of, like, I'm not worried about Mark Wahlberg actually stopping 9-11.
Do you understand?
Like, you blustery asshole, I would punch them and like, shut the fuck up.
Yeah.
And this formulation, too, of like, because we keep putting up with it, like, so the solution
is to stop putting up with protest.
Right.
Right?
I mean, like, obviously that's the message that would be being sent.
We stamp out any and all protests, we destroy the first amendment.
Particularly ones that are central to, you know, non-straight, white, Christian, male-related
issues.
Stamp out all those protests because they're Soros instigated.
Of course.
Yeah, I don't know, it doesn't seem great.
They do understand.
These people do understand.
Actually, never mind.
They don't.
No.
I should end every sentence.
They do understand.
Actually, I'm wrong.
Well, I think, I think the only explanation I could come up with for, like, to sort of
maintain the dignity of Alex's listeners is like, they have to just think he's telling
the truth.
Like, I can't imagine listening to this having a kernel of skepticism and maintaining any
illusion that he knows what he's talking about.
Dan, he brought it up.
If you covered this story and you went and found the, like, pictures of it, you found
the explanation for what was going on at this Wegmans and how Alex is for some reason imagining
people would call it a race war if he started fighting his way out of the store, you'd have
to just be like, okay, this is about you, man.
This isn't about reality.
This isn't about the story.
You're projecting everything.
All of those paper articles are written directly by Soros.
Did you know that 98% of all newspaper articles in the mainstream media were written directly
by George Soros?
Yep.
I read that in one of the 2% that isn't.
So I don't think that this is true.
But this is being praised on Facebook and Twitter as a good thing.
They just go randomly to a grocery store and there's black people, white people, you name
it inside, and block everybody in and start screaming at people.
And they surrounded the whole building and the emergency exits and wouldn't let people
out.
And look, I'm a man, so I'm, you know, still pretty tough at 47.
I'm still being intimidated and angry by this.
Imagine being a woman.
Imagine being an old person.
Imagine being some 80-year-old woman on her walker trying to get some food.
This is thug behavior.
It's criminal and it's disgusting.
And the police need to stop kissing the ass of these type of globalist thugs and need
to start arresting them for racketeering.
What?
Anyway, I'm not sure there's enough protesters there to surround a building.
Wegmans, they're not usually small stores.
They're usually fairly big.
And I've seen a bunch of pictures of the gathering.
It was not a giant mob.
Also, in reality, Wegmans closed the door to their store out of fear of the protesters.
So any decisions that Alex wants to complain about should be directed to Wegmans customer
corporate office or whatever the fuck.
The reason the protesters chose this location for their protest is that Wegmans uses uniformed
Rochester police officers for security.
And their protest was in part calling for the firing of the officers who were involved
in the Daniel Prude case.
It all makes total sense.
It's not random.
The reason they showed up there was not random.
And Alex is going to pretend that it's random in a very racist way.
And let's say what it is.
This is the equivalent of KKK.
This is a bunch of black people and white people.
And I guess it looks like there's some brown people there that are literally angry randomly
at random people at a grocery store.
And you see in the video, there's like an hour of it.
The old lady in the walker looks like she's about to have a heart attack.
And then she tries to get out the back and they yell at her.
So again, and this is just, this video is the beginning of it.
Hundreds of people surrounded the grocery store, all these big fat welfare queens.
And again, nothing is if you're fat, but man, all these people bitch about this country
sucks.
400 pounds, man.
You wouldn't last 10 minutes in Africa.
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Weird.
Wild.
Be a little too clear, Alex.
That's tough to back away from.
Yeah.
That's outrageous.
Yeah, yeah.
Whenever Alex is like, I'm not racist, show me the clip.
Well.
Wow.
Well, there's one of them.
Yep.
One of many, just on this episode, you flagrant racist.
Yeah.
That's, that's pretty, uh, it's pretty much, that's too explicit.
That's, that's too explicit.
It's yeah, it's pretty, pretty embarrassing.
Yeah.
Um, so yeah, I don't know.
The story's dumb.
Spends quite a bit of time on this, uh, this Wegmans grocery store, uh, story and a lot
of time talking about how M4s may be gone soon.
There's no protest about racial justice that's ever random.
No.
And not even that, but it's a daily occurrence.
And there's none that Alex will ever deem acceptable.
Yeah, of course not.
There's no version of it that Alex would ever, uh, see as like, oh, this is a productive
conversation.
This is something that's bringing attention to an important, blah, blah, blah.
Like you wouldn't, it just there, it doesn't exist.
Yeah.
Uh, it's, it would always be some kind of a Soros agitation in order to create division
in society and make white people feel bad.
Totally.
Yeah.
It's, it's, and that's what I was kind of talking about at the beginning of this episode
where everything is just kind of boring.
Yeah.
Like he's just, these are just Alex Jones tricks that he's doing.
Retreads.
Yeah.
A little bit.
It's just racism on autopilot, which is fucking boggling.
Yeah.
I was a little bit disappointed.
Um, I don't know, I just, I shouldn't expect anything.
Yeah.
But Infowars might be gone soon, man.
That's why we got to cherish this while we have it.
Yeah.
This is just like, these people cannot be at all introspective whatsoever if you can
have racism on autopilot this explicit, right?
Like at no point in time does he ever like sit down and go, did what I say come off as
super racist?
Well, it's, it's, it's interesting to me to imagine like a listener who's hearing like
particularly that last clip and he's talking about these welfare queens of 400 pounds.
Yeah.
And hearing that it'd be like, Ooh, that's weird.
But maybe you're somebody who's, you know, in inundated with shitty right wing media.
And that's just like, Hey, that's where we live.
I mean, then being like, why did you say you wouldn't last a day in Africa?
That's a weird one.
Yeah.
Why, why, why was that where you were adding, adding all of that is just strange.
Why?
I can't imagine being a listener and not being like, Oh, I get what he's saying.
Yeah.
It's black people.
But I mean, if you were a Reagan voter, you can't be mad about welfare queen at this point.
You know, I'm not sure Alex loves Reagan.
Yeah.
Well he loves using Reagan's racist talking points.
Sure.
The squid metaphor was maybe gone soon.
We've been hearing this for quite a while and I grow weary of it.
I'm running out of gas.
Now I probably wouldn't even play this cause he says like stuff about him being gone all
the time.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
Except he makes a squid metaphor that maybe goes too long and I find it interesting.
I like a good squid metaphor.
I'm not going to spend time getting into all the things they do to us.
I'm not going to say the things that they're doing that have an effect, the things that
deflect the things that don't have an effect because I'm not going to give the enemy any
idea of where to keep attacking.
But let me just tell you this, do not sit there and expect info wars to be here forever.
I've had a lot of classy family that had cancer and was dying and you just hear that that
member of the family's dead.
They were at work one week, totally nice, got their affairs in order.
So manly, so tough, so feminine, so tough that they just die and make no big deal about
it and donate their bodies of science and stuff like that.
I'm not as stoic as some of my ancestors.
I'd like to point out that I'm really glad that Alex did make that caveat that that's
not me.
Yeah.
I'm not that person who's stoic.
I'm going to go down, I'm going to go down whining.
I'm going to renounce God.
I'm going to sell my soul to Satan for one single longer second than I can handle it.
You're going to see me on a pink sweater.
Yeah, exactly.
I will do anything.
Yeah.
And I don't have cancer.
But America has cancer and this operation has a giant globalist squid attached to us
gnawing on our face.
Okay.
And I just let it sit there and gnaw and I know how far it can go till it gets to our
arteries and I'm, I'm laying eggs real fast escape pods too.
And we'll just see how they do getting caught in the whole underwater jet stream here and
what the, what they'll grow into and what they'll do.
Are you the squid and the person?
I'll grow a bunch of eggs to use that analogy if I'm a fish with a big thing attached to
me, eating me.
Um, so I need energy to be able to make sure that all those things that we're insuring
in the future continue on because that's the main mission and I've, and I've looked at
all the different possible future scenarios and, um, we're going to get eaten by a squid.
The globalists are so off the chart and so crazy now that there's a good chance that
they'll go ahead and just kill me and at a certain level, I kind of look forward to that
because in the big, great burden, atmospheres of pressure that I have to carry out this
mission will be gone.
Didn't he just say like when he got back from his last a weird vacation to Florida that
like all the weight had been lifted from him and he'd completed his mission.
Now he's like, Oh, I wish I was dead.
I had a good week where the burden wasn't there and now it's back and I really wish
the globalists would just fucking kill me.
Certainly had nothing to do with going to Connecticut.
Yeah, nothing in Connecticut made me feel like I want to die and that info Wars won't
be around forever.
Nothing in Connecticut would ever give me the impression that info Wars may be going
out of business.
I have to think that the metaphor here, the squid, I mean it's clunky metaphor, but the
squid is the, that's attached to info Wars is the Sandy Hook lawsuit.
He knows how far they can nibble before it hits the carotid.
That would be once his finances become public or they get discovery on a lot of this stuff.
People realize what kind of shit he's really into.
Yeah.
And yeah, then he fell apart with the I'm laying eggs because that could either be like
I'm trying to give money to other organizations or I'm hiding money in my dad's business.
That would make the most sense.
I don't know.
But anyway, he's got some more.
I love life.
I'll never commit suicide.
If they, if I die, it wasn't suicide.
I'm just saying I literally have no more fear.
I I've been through this so long.
I've done so much that I don't fear death.
I don't fear anything.
I may lose my whole family.
I may lose my children.
I mean, hell, the whole world's about to go.
I mean, you fear shadow all that matters is our souls, but you've got from me a total
commitment as strong as I can be.
I will fight.
And does that mean I'm going to go off the rails and act crazy?
Yeah, because I'm, I'm, I'm burnout folks.
I'm fried.
When you fight evil like this at a level like this, this long, you don't just care about
them.
You don't just not care about them killing you.
You don't just not care about you start getting to the point where there's no inhibition anymore.
Does that make sense?
No.
I give you my word that I will be as focused and hardcore as I can until the very end,
but I need financial support.
We know.
Yeah.
It's, it's, it's weird.
I would, I would pray that I would have all of my support dry up.
Uh, if I ever get to the point where I speak that modeling.
Yeah.
If I ever get that, like, uh, I, you know, just doing this at the level that I've done
it, I'm not afraid to die.
Dan, Dan, I won't let you go out like that.
Yeah.
But I will very much need you to check me if I ever start even getting close to that
level of blow harder.
We're going to get on a boat.
I'll take care of you.
Godfather style.
It'll be great.
This is embarrassing.
Yeah.
Um, yeah, that's not good.
So in a way there's squids out.
Squids.
I believe he's a fish in the metaphor.
I think that's how far I've gotten with the metaphor.
I think he's a fish being eaten by a squid.
I think he did say that.
I think he said, once he started to say that he was putting out eggs, he realized he had
to be something that laid eggs.
Yeah.
So now he had to...
The moment he said eggs, I think he thought he was the squid for a second.
Yeah.
And then...
This is the problem with Alex and protracted metaphors.
Yeah.
He's not good at metaphors.
Nah, it's a dicey game.
Yeah.
So Alex gets some bad news here on the 24th and that is that the ninth circuit has made
a ruling.
That's not good.
This is a big deal on the ninth circuit.
We'll be tracking that very, very closely.
That's just now breaking, overturning, um, concealed carry period.
This is just, you're like, Oh, the Supreme Court will overturn that.
Don't hold your breath folks, because we don't put pressure on them.
They don't fear the American people's political action.
They fear the mainstream media.
They fear the stacking of the court because nobody calls the bluff of the left.
And so the left is Buffalo-ing us, stampeding us.
It's only gonna get more crazy.
Go after him for fast and furious.
Get on the offense.
Go after him for the child smuggling across the border.
Do like Ted Cruz does, but almost everybody else sits there.
Don't do like Ted Cruz doesn't matter.
He's got guts.
And guts is enough.
Ladies and gentlemen, don't forget.
We got free shipping on the mega blowout sale.
Oh boy.
That was, that was clunky one.
Yup.
Yeah.
So go after them for fast and furious.
That'll do it.
You got them.
Man.
It's interesting how he pretends that they didn't have hearings on that.
Nobody ever calls the left's bluff, you know, like nobody's ever like, we refuse to sit
a Supreme Court justice until, yeah, nobody's ever been like, oh, we got to put pressure
on the Supreme Court by removing and replacing all of the, yeah, cool, cool guys.
Also this ninth court ruling, it has said, if I recall correctly, let me pull up the
exact wording of it, quote, there is no right to carry arms openly in public, nor is any
such right within the scope of the second amendment.
Yeah.
That's what the U.S. court judge J. Bybee said.
I would be hard pressed to find the wording within the second amendment that's like, yeah,
and carry them in the Wagner's.
No, like that, that is, you know, something that I would think that Alex would be like,
it's over.
Yeah.
That's the slippery slope.
Right.
And he's already said the Supreme Court isn't going to.
They're not going to help us at all.
Should this be at the point where now, like his, you know, Viet Cong thing from earlier?
I don't know.
There weren't any laws anymore anyways, Dan.
The entire government is unconstitutional.
Mm-hmm.
All right.
What are we going to do?
I don't know.
Let's take their guns away.
He doesn't really talk about this story as much as you would think based on the fact
that it should be.
The most important story that's ever happened.
He should go apoplectic.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He should lose his mind.
The Mayak report came out and he made such a stink about it for so long.
Yeah.
He talks to some weirdo who's got like a YouTube show for an hour about like trying to make
people afraid of stuff at the border.
And I didn't care because I got a little bit deeper into this next interview.
So I thought it was different and a little bit more interesting.
Okay.
And so what we have here is that Jim Hoft from Gateway Pundit, his brother, whose name
I refuse to learn, is on.
Jim Hoft's brother.
That's right.
That is his name.
To me it is.
Yeah.
He's on because he's got some news about COVID.
The historical had a lot of new information that just confirmed a lot of the older information.
It's a breaking exclusive, thegatewaypundit.com, location of origin of COVID-19 pandemic identified
between two of China's biological warfare facilities in Wuhan.
So this is apparently a situation where Jim Hoft's brothers learned that there was a cluster
of cases early of COVID-19 in an area that's geographically between the Wuhan Institute
of Virology and another lab in Wuhan.
And thus, put those pieces together, man.
Wait.
It was in between the two?
Yeah.
It was geographically in between the two.
Like on the street?
Yeah.
It was just on the street.
It was in a neighborhood.
Oh, okay.
See, what happened was, obviously, people were going back and forth between those labs.
Sure.
And they were coughing on people.
Right.
He's proved it.
So the place they stopped for gas is where the COVID outbreak started.
He's solved this case.
Oh, okay.
I gotta say, I gotta give it up to Jim Hoft's brother.
Well, Jim Hoft's brother really, Agatha Christie'd this one to completion.
I read the article on Gateway Ponder.
Initially, I was just gonna dismiss this and be like, oh, fuck yourself, Jim Hoft's brother.
But there's actually a really interesting piece in here that just demonstrates how these
people do their dirty work.
Well, congratulations, Jim Hoft's brother.
That area that's really, really dark where this signifies the most cases is between a
couple of biological warfare facilities.
Editorializing there a little bit, maybe.
He's describing a map where there is shaded clusters of where there were early instances
of COVID.
One is the entity that we've talked about for a long time, maybe for...
We started reporting on this Wuhan Institute of Virology back in April last year.
And where it looked like, yeah, this is what's going on.
Wuhan was released from there.
And then near that is another entity they're calling, that's labeled the Biological Preparations
Institute, BPI.
It's the yellow square on that map.
And between these two facilities is where they're saying the initial cases, the large
number of initial cases were first identified.
How far away?
Giving us more, I guess, more evidence that this thing wasn't just something that was
natural.
Is that more evidence?
That occurred in the food market, that red dot.
No, the large number of cases comes between the black star there and the yellow box.
So I've got some issues with this map.
It's actually, I found this very fascinating.
Is it the way that he's got a black box, a yellow square, and a red dot?
No, I mean, you got to have whatever as markers on a map.
Well, I'm fine with that.
My first issue is that there are four additional clusters of early cases that are nowhere near
either lab and at least 10 other reported infectors also outside the area that Jim Hoft's
brother is focusing on.
In theory, it would be just as easy to argue that someone got infected in one of those
other clusters and brought the condition back to the neighborhood that Hoft is focusing
on from the information that he's providing.
There's literally no way that he could prove otherwise.
You bring in multiple points of fact that would undermine his argument, but on the other
hand, have you considered, don't worry about it?
No, I have not considered that.
So the second major issue I have here is that the map is taken from a study in the International
Journal of Geo-Information, and it has to do with geographic data from a medical help-seeking
app called Weibo.
The data isn't meant to be used in the way that Jim's brother is using it.
It's misused data.
Only on one app?
Yeah, it's tracking the people who reached out for help through this app, which I think
there's value to, obviously, as data points, but it's not for this.
The third problem is that the map they're publishing on Gateway Pundit isn't the map
from that journal article, or at least it isn't the only one.
The map that's closest to theirs is the one that depicts Weibo help-seekers prior to January
18th, 2020.
Gateway Pundit doesn't include the subsequent maps depicting Weibo seekers from January
19th to 20th, which shows the distribution going way towards the areas nowhere near the
labs that they're focusing on, nor do they even bring up the map from January 21st to
22nd, which shows more of the same, shifting away from that hotspot that he decided to
cherry-pick data and just make his argument with.
Okay, so then in this case, here's what I've got for you.
Okay.
So, some dudes?
Shuffling dangerous COVID back from lab to lab.
They stop at a gas station, accidentally drop a vial, right?
It explodes.
That causes problems.
But that's a small outbreak.
It's just one vial.
So then they go to the other places, and that's where the big vials are tossed out of the
car.
I mean, it's an interesting plot for a book or something, but I don't think this supports
it.
I've written it down.
The final problem is that according to Google Maps, Jim Hough's brother has mislabeled the
map he published.
It appears that that yellow square that he's talking about to signify the Biological Preparations
Institute?
Sure.
That's actually the Biological Preparations Institute Marketing Center.
Well, they were trying to figure out how to advertise the pandemic, yeah, naturally.
The actual Wuhan Biological Preparations Institute is about 25 kilometers south of where they
have it marked on the map, and if you actually use the correct location, there are no clusters
right near it.
I swear to God, I want to throw baseballs at these people.
It's amazing.
Really hard.
Yeah, and it took a little while of looking at the map and asking myself questions about
like, what is this entity exactly?
Is this what they're saying it is?
And you know, it took a little while to unravel, but this is pretty basic stuff that they didn't
even consider, or they did consider and decided to lie about in service of making their argument.
This is that one situation of, what's the name of those places where there's the institute
and the university or whatever, and they keep mixing them up?
The Tavistock Institute?
Yes, the Tavistock Institute, and yeah, it's the same thing where they just keep mixing
up the dumb stuff and they're like, nobody's ever going to follow up on this except for
Dan.
Well, but I also, I would fully think that it's a very good chance that they just didn't
even check.
They just saw.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah.
They don't even bother.
Why would they?
Again, no one's going to follow up on this except Dan.
It's so sloppy and embarrassing that this is like Gateway Pundit's editorial, like that's
what's good enough to be put out as an exclusive and then come on Alex's show and ramble about
it.
And even problems that I was able to find with the way they were using that map from
the journal itself to what they were doing, even if they did have the right location,
there were problems.
Yeah.
And the fact that that is a different location than they're pretending it is makes it just
comical.
It's farce.
That's stupid.
Yeah.
So anyway, at that point I checked out.
You're like the Sigma-5 of propaganda.
Like, you know how Sigma-5 scientists are like, there's a one in a million chance that we're
not 100% correct on this.
You know, Sigma-3 is like one in a thousand or whatever.
There's a point in propaganda where it's like, well, only Dan's going to care about this.
So we're fine.
And he might not if he doesn't accidentally get curious about it.
Yeah, exactly.
If we fly this one by Dan, we're golden.
Yeah.
We can just make this boring enough.
I know.
Have Jim Hoff's brother talk about it.
Yeah.
Sigma-4 is Dan and some other people.
Sigma-3 is Dan and like the New York Times.
I don't know, man.
I unfortunately, you know, spent a little bit of time looking at that and it kind of
burned me out a tiny bit between the like sort of just very constant and boring racism
and immigrant bashing.
And then, you know, that I was just like, I'm out.
I'm out.
And unfortunately that made me miss Roger Stone.
He showed up in the fourth hour of the show.
I don't usually watch the fourth hour because I completely missed it.
Maybe we'll get it next week.
Who knows?
Probably not.
Roger Stone's boring.
He sucks.
Yeah.
He's boring now.
He doesn't do anything.
I think ever since he got that pardon, he's just not the same.
Just not the same, man.
Well, I mean, you know, I get it, right?
Like you've got all the adrenaline of like, am I going to go to jail?
Am I going to go to jail?
And then you get a pardon and you're like, well now what do I do?
It feels like the definition of once bitten, twice shy.
Yeah.
I'm not going to fuck around with needing a pardon again because I don't got a pardon
coming for the second one.
I will try and get attention to myself as best I can and maybe do some publicity stunt
things.
I need some money from people.
I'll be a shithead.
That'll be fine.
Yeah.
I'll have a good bone mow from time to time.
Sure.
Yeah.
I'll yell at Larry Klayman if I get a chance.
Not hard.
Not hard to do.
So yeah, I don't know.
I found this stretch.
When I said at the beginning of the show, I was like, is there even value in talking
about it?
Well, part of the reason is because I don't think a lot of it brings much new to the table.
True.
I think with Jim Hoff's brother and talking about some of the specific instances of things
he brings up, maybe there's a little bit, but his coverage of, for instance, the shooting
is all in service of anti Muslim rhetoric.
It's all in service of anti immigrant.
There's nothing there that you don't see in the aftermath of so many other tragic events.
If you look at Alex's coverage, there's just, and it kind of, I don't know.
It makes me sad that you can just still get away with the same tricks.
Yeah.
It is one of those things where sometimes we do an episode that I want in court as like,
this isn't a first amendment issue.
This is malice.
We can prove malice.
Listen to this shit.
Now you're going to have to listen to about, I think about a thousand hours of knowledge
fight at this point.
So strap in, but you'll get there and we'll get the conviction on this one.
We'll get it.
Anyway, Jordan, we'll be back.
Indeed.
We will, Dan.
But until then we have a website.
We have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yes.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledgefight.com.
And I go to bed Jordan.
We are also on Facebook.
And if you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work still.
Yep.
And until then I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I pledge on the altar of God to try to force Alex Jones to eat fake fruit.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.