I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying, we are the bad guys, knowledge
fight, knowledge fight, I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying, we are
the bad guys, knowledge fight, Dan and Jordan, knowledge fight, Rattle Earth, Rattle Earth,
Rattle Earth, need money, Rattle Earth, Rattle Earth, Andy and Kansas, Andy and, Andy, stop
it, Andy and Kansas, Andy and Kansas, Andy and, Andy, it's time to pray, Andy and Kansas,
you're on the air, thanks for holding us.
Hello Alex, I'm a person calling with your Japan, I love your word, knowledge fight,
knowledge fight, knowledgefight.com, I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight, I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes, like sit around, drink novelty beverages and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones.
Oh indeed we are, Dan.
Jordan.
Dan.
Quick question.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, Jordan, I think that one of the early bright spots when I moved
into this apartment was that I had a junk drawer.
Yes, that's true, yes.
And to check back up on that, I'd like to make my bright spot today that I had my first
real junk drawer moment.
Where you were like, what the fuck did I put in here?
No, I was like, of course I've got AA batteries.
Oh no, not the junk drawer batteries moment.
They've gotta be in there.
You never win.
I'm sure.
You never win the batteries moment.
So I was looking through the junk drawer and I found AAA batteries and no AA's it turns
out.
You are issued AAA's whenever you move in somewhere and nothing fits AAA's.
They always, like AAA's just come in a pack that's too big.
You don't need as many as you think you do.
Yeah, we'll give you 30 AAA's for one remote control.
Yeah, I was going through there, there's like pencils, pens.
I'm like, oh, I got a deck of cards in here.
How about that?
Yeah, why not?
Great.
It's your old timey Batman forever deck of cards.
You remember those?
It was a nice moment.
It really felt like it's complete.
You're home.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know if I feel home, but the drawer is fun.
That's fair enough.
How about you?
Dan, my bright spot today is my support structure.
My partner and you and the many people who helped me.
It has been a very difficult few days between me and my brain.
A week or so and not a good place to be.
Sometimes my brain has been downright abusive towards me.
Sure.
So it is nice to have these amazing people in my life.
Spoiler alert for the audience.
I didn't talk to you at all yesterday.
No, I know.
I don't know what I did.
You didn't do anything this year.
Look, I mean, our employee boss relationship, I feel is strong.
A rump.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So it is nice to have that.
It's a huge bright spot for me because there have been times
in my life where that support structure was not around and
I was teetering on a knife's edge.
So it is a huge bright spot.
Well, I love you, buddy, and I'm glad that you're feeling
better now.
A little bit better, I assume.
Let's do the show.
Okay.
And to sort of reverse the sort of, just because I'm
uncomfortable by you saying such positive things, you know,
you've really helped me a lot too as a support structure.
So thank you.
It's great.
It's nice to be able to be in that position.
Yeah, it's huge.
Yeah.
So Jordan, today we are going to, this is sort of like what
we're doing today is also even kind of like my support.
Okay.
Self support.
All right.
As Open Mic Eagle would say, what the fuck is self care?
This may be self care for me.
And we'll get to it here in a moment.
But before we do, we've got to take a little moment to say
hello and shout out to some new wonks.
So first, Jason B. also had a birthday recently.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Jason.
And happy birthday to you.
Also, BB.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
Also, BB just had a birthday recently.
Turned 20 years old.
How about that?
Oh, my God.
You're too young to listen to this show.
Do you remember being 20?
Oh, man.
I don't.
I mean, I literally don't.
Congratulations, BB.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, BB.
Next, Jared spelled J-A-R-O-D.
BS.
That's two initials, not bullshit.
That's Jared B to the S.
Yeah.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Jared.
Unclear when his birthday is.
If you are a policy wonk, please put your birthday in there just so we can give you
a happy birthday whether you like it or not.
Next, greetings from the city formerly known as Portland's anarchist jurisdiction.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Yeah.
All of you, I suppose.
Next, this is another person who had a birthday.
On the 23rd, just missed it.
Oh, that's close, though.
But happy birthday, Cillian.
You are now a policy wonk, as well as Janie, who is also now a policy wonk.
But I don't know what Janie's birthday is.
Anyway, Janie got in touch with us and wanted us to wish you a happy birthday, Cillian.
Policy wonkery all around.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much to all of you.
And while we're here, Killian Murphy, too.
I think he had a birthday sometime.
At some point.
Yeah.
And finally, Prop Comic Sans, thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Prop Comic Sans.
Good times.
Yes.
Now, Jordan, what we're doing today is...
I've got a question for you.
What's that?
Do you like apples?
Um...
So what do you think about them apples?
Okay.
All right.
Today, Jordan, what we got on our plate is I have found these old Alex Jones episodes.
I've found episodes dating back to 2003.
All right.
And I have...
So, how do you like them apples was relevant at the time, is what you're saying.
Well, it was still out of date.
It's a little bit late.
It's still out of date, but okay.
I found episodes going back to 2003, and I find Alex almost insufferable and very boring
in the present day.
Yeah.
I don't want to ignore him in the present day, but I also don't want to be doing a show
that is constantly just looking at him in the present day.
Yeah.
Because I find that to be dumb.
I think it's worthwhile as a sort of social thing.
Totally.
But as an intellectual exercise, I don't really care all that much about listening to a guy
constantly say he's fighting the devil.
Totally.
And then I'm supposed to take it seriously and be like, well, actually the devil started
as an idea.
Right.
I have no interest.
I imagine that the audience does get a little bit bored with, I didn't listen to the third
hour.
It was too boring.
So yeah.
And a lot of times I did listen to it and I just say, okay, who cares?
There's nothing in there.
Get the fuck out of here.
Yeah.
We will obviously still be talking about the present day, but for today I needed to go
back as far back as I could.
So today we are going to be talking about May 1st, 2003.
Ooh.
Is that when Christopher Lloyd guested?
No.
Christopher Lloyd, no guests on this episode.
No guests.
Okay.
This episode is amazing for a number of reasons.
There's a couple of things that blew my mind.
Okay.
I am convinced I'm a witch now.
All right.
And also I just, I, it's, it's a new day.
It's a new day from 20 years ago.
I find myself like getting these reinvigorations through like whenever I can find these old
time frames to look back on.
It really is recharging of my batteries and it's, it's, it's man.
I like it.
So Jordan, we start May 1st, 2003.
Do you remember 2003 much?
Do you remember what was going on in May?
No, I told you, I don't remember.
The Iraq war had just ended.
Oh boy.
Did we just mission accomplish?
That was that day.
You are a witch.
May 1st.
May 1st, 2003 was the day that George Bush landed on the, uh, the aircraft carrier with
the mission accomplished banner.
VI day as we all know it now.
Yes.
Victory was upon us.
Um, and so, Hey, here's Alex and the, we're going to find out a number of things.
Some of the things that are really interesting to me and I'm most excited to learn about
are things like how is Alex Jones's opposition to Bush and the Iraq war?
How does it exist when Bush is in office?
Right.
How can we look at that through the prism of history in the context of knowing how he
behaves in more generally as a pattern, how can we apply that to this source of material?
And so it's interesting anyway.
I believe you.
Did you know that the new world order has a plan?
It's how many years behind 18 years ago, it's coming into play.
Okay.
We are now following the exact model used by dictators to intensify their hold on population
on populations.
Whether it was bill Clinton or George W. Bush, the agenda of the new world order is spiraling
out of control.
Years ago, I read a Pensacola news journal article that is on info wars.com.
And one of our press releases about how during a red alert, you won't be able to leave your
house and have any rights.
You have a link to it in that story, the Marines took over the school and announced, this is
Marshall law.
Bill Clinton wants you to know what Marshall law is about.
I don't care.
Immediately.
I'm listening to this and I'm like, this dude is doing a voice.
Yeah.
I, I wanted to, I wanted to, he's performing.
This is so weird because I was, I was literally writing down, like, I don't know how to describe
it, but he sounds fatter.
I think it has something to do with the way he's filling up his arms with air.
I think he's doing a bit of a rush Limbaugh impression.
Oh yeah, totally.
And I think that rush Limbaugh has a sound better.
Yeah.
I, I, it's just, it's remarkable.
It sounds like a guy who thinks he's, you know, he knows he's doing radio totally.
And, uh, God, it just, it's refreshing.
Somebody trying.
It's amazing.
But apparently the, the globalist plan was falling apart back then to constantly falling
apart.
It's like when you're, it's like when you're on a ship, you're constantly rebuilding the
ship as you sail.
That's how it's always worked.
Is it?
Yeah.
Oh, I don't want to sail.
Don't sail.
It's really hard.
So I can't find the original article that Alex is talking about from the Pensacola news
journal, nor can I find articles about it on info wars and their archives.
However, I did find a geo cities level website that's copied and pasted what's supposedly
this article.
So I'm going to go off of that.
Okay.
Reading the article, you can tell that what was going on there was a situation where this
school called Hobbs middle school, it was part of a partnership with Whiting field,
Naval air station.
And, uh, the, uh, enlisted people coming to the school.
It was part of them volunteering to help teach for a day.
Yeah.
They did this very basic presentation as if the military was in charge of the school to
help the students better understand the issues that were facing the civilians in Kosovo at
the time, as is clearly laid out as being effective in the article quote, one of Whitfield
students, Julie McCool said the presence of the military personnel in her school made
the news she'd been watching from Yugoslavia seem a little more real.
Sure.
Which is great.
It achieves an impactful lesson for the students.
I mean, personally, I don't think any military should go anywhere near a middle school, but
that's, that's just me.
I mean, I assume that they weren't like, Hey, let's become fascist, but you know, what are
you going to do?
Right.
I mean, the idea of making the news real, uh, or helping the students understand it.
Totally.
There's a value to that.
If you were growing as far as like hitting the kids with the butt of a gun, then I'm
out.
Yeah.
I don't want to, I mean, I, yeah.
And I think that there also to sort of what you're saying, I think that, you know, I wouldn't
be in favor of things that are basically like PR work for the armed forces directed at schools.
That would kind of be a huge thing for me.
I don't like that.
I've been a Miyazaki fan for a long time and the military teaching children it's okay to
be in the military is a big deal.
I, from, from the article I, what I was getting from it is not so much that they were teaching,
uh, that it's cool to be in the military, but it still has the effect of rubbing off
and like maybe turning these people into icons that you look up to.
Totally.
Yeah.
I can also see though, like how this kind of an activity could be a really positive,
uh, as an educational tool for the students.
So I'm kind of, I don't really have a position on it.
On the one hand, it could have the effect of making these youths think that the army
is super cool, but on the other hand, it also has the potential to open up the students
to things they wouldn't have the chance to experience otherwise.
For instance, from this article quote, last year, students from Hobbs and SS Dixon primary
school communicated via email with a coast guard Lieutenant on a cruise bound for the
South Pole and had a video teleconference with their friend once she got there.
That could be a really neat opportunity for students to learn directly about all sorts
of things in a way that's much more real than reading about the South Pole in a book.
And that could be a positive thing.
Yeah, sure.
What's it like on the boat?
Have you ever seen a man die?
We have to keep rebuilding.
You've never seen a man die before.
I've seen two men die in my arms.
Also, it's important-
I don't know where that voice came from.
That was a weird voice.
Yeah, that was a weird voice.
My bad.
That's a 2003 voice.
Sorry about that.
Also, it's important to keep in mind that these are middle school students.
I would be opposed to this being done with an elementary school since I don't know how
well second graders could process any of this.
Totally.
That's how you get Alex Jones.
Yeah, but by middle school, the kids should be exactly at the point where this could be
a great experience for them.
They're not too young to process it and not too old to think that it's really dumb once
they're in high school.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
I think this is an article from March 1999, so it's nice to see that even in 2003, Alex
doesn't deal with new news.
I kind of was thinking it's 2003 and we're listening about Clinton and Kosovo, and while
I do think that that is a very important historical thing for us to learn, it's the Iraq War!
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
And if you're talking about militarization of police post 9-11, obviously, certainly
a topic worth conversing about, but if one of the things that you're leading the show
with is like the military coming into a school in Pensacola, like that was pre-9-11.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You just need to, there's better ways to do this.
You used to be able to just walk on a plane.
Whenever the military was at this school, you could walk onto a plane.
Yeah.
So that story from the past is being woven in with a new headline Alex has read about.
Now I have this article, Fox News.
Young Marines teach kids discipline integrity, and it turns out it's an anti-drug, anti-gun
program, and they teach the kids if they join the globalists they get to have guns, if not,
it's over.
It's all part of pure evil.
So this doesn't really relate at all.
No, it doesn't sound like it.
That four-year-old story was about a day when military, uh, volunteers, they created an
educational experience at a middle school.
This is more or less just a press release about a youth program run by former Marines.
The Young Marines is basically a more discipline-focused version of the Scouts, and it's run by the
Marine Corps League, which is a social organization for former Marines.
They basically put kids in boot camp-like conditions and have them eat MREs in order
to build strength and discipline.
From everything I can tell, it's definitely an anti-drug program, but I did not get the
sense that it's anti-gun.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I would have hated being in this group, and I think it seems kind of fucked up, but the
only way anyone's going to go to it is if they and their parents agree to take part
in it, so I'm not going to spend too much time complaining about their choices.
Yeah, you guys do what you do.
I don't have time for it.
The Iraq War is just going on.
It's frankly, the Iraq War is just beginning.
When that Mission Accomplished sign up was the beginning of the Iraq War.
No it did not.
That was way back when.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh man, we really thought we were going to get out of there, Dan.
I don't know if I thought that back then.
I absolutely did not.
I thought these guys were going to fuck everything up and we were all going to die.
So Alex is above the political divide, the left-right paradigm.
Sure.
All this stuff.
Talking about Clinton in 2003.
He's above the left-right paradigm.
48's Bush too.
True.
Now, here's where things get a little muddy.
Oh, I got news of conservative states gun-grabbing all across the country.
Wait until you hear about this, again, conservatism now is a byword for big government, no freedom,
condoms, abortion, everything.
Everything?
They are ultra-liberals, they are winning the war, destroying America because the liberals
learned how to dress up like conservatives.
It happened, folks, it happened.
It's pretty illuminating to me because it's really the core of Alex's fake presentation
of being above two-party shit.
He's presenting a position where the conservatives out there are actually secret liberals, which
is why the two parties don't matter, because they're both not far enough to the right.
Therefore they're actually the same thing.
That's what his being above the two-party system is.
Yeah, I'm above the two-party system because I want to destroy them and institute a theocracy.
What don't you understand?
It would be fine for Alex to just openly advocate that he feels alienated by politics because
he's way far to the right of anything that exists in polite society.
But even in 2003, he knows that's not going to appeal to a wide audience, so he plays
the game of being like, oh, the left and the right is a lie, and you know why?
If you actually are conservative, you've got to be an extremist to the right because these
really hardcore right-wing people are actually secret liberals.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That makes sense.
Great.
So, at this point, there was talk of the need for the provisional government in Iraq sorting
out how to set up a system there once we were to withdraw, which as we know from living
in 2021 didn't go great.
Well, it turns out that crony capitalism combined with colonialism does not work out well for
anyone.
Isn't that crazy?
U.S. reported to push for Iraqi government with Pentagon prevailing, and they are appointing
the members of the Ba'ath Party, the torture lords and others trained in the U.S. in the
80s and the 70s, all CIA, of course.
They are another easy victory for them.
They're going to be running things.
And we'll get to that for you as well.
I don't know how to read Alex's tone there.
I really don't know what, he's being facetious, or?
Yeah, I was going to say.
There's kind of a smugness to it more than a facetiousness.
I mean, they hadn't really announced de-Ba'athification at that time, did they?
That's what I'm talking about.
Did they?
No, no.
It's a couple weeks after this.
Oh yeah, that's what I was saying.
But yeah, that's exactly what I was thinking.
I was like, does Alex not know that that's a major thing that ends up happening?
And it's a major thing that ends up contributing to the massive destabilization in Iraq.
So is he being facetious in such a way that these idiots are trying to get rid of the
Ba'ath Party, or is he actually thinking that the Ba'ath Party is what's going to continue
going on?
Well, I think that based on the context that I've gleaned from listening to the rest of
this episode, I believe that Alex thinks that the CIA is running the Ba'ath Party and all
the people with Saddam and all this, like Saddam was allowed to get away to some island
somewhere.
Okay, okay.
How did that work out?
How did that prediction work out?
Didn't go great.
Didn't go great?
Didn't end up correct.
He was in a hole.
But he, Alex, I think he thinks that the Ba'ath Party loyalists and folks who the CIA were
trained up and all this will pretend that they weren't part of the Ba'ath Party or whatever,
and then they will become the people who are the puppets for the US within Iraq moving
forward.
Okay, so he didn't assume that the CIA would betray them like they always do?
I think that that's where he's going.
And that actually is one of the things that I, when I was listening to this, I'm like,
that's actually something I really want to track.
I'm interested to see how Alex's tone goes during the Ba'athification.
Yeah, that is interesting.
Because should he be for or against it?
I don't know.
That's a really good question.
That requires a nuance that Alex is absolutely incapable of now.
2003, Alex, I think is still incapable of it, but I'm interested to find out.
Because at this point, it seems like he's opposed based on this to the Ba'ath Party
members being allowed in the government.
Yes, right.
But then, based on his political ideology, he should be super against how the blanket
banning of Ba'ath Party members from all sorts of positions of influence went down.
Yeah.
It just seems like he can't possibly be for either.
What would, what could possibly, oh, oh, I know what could, the only thing that Alex
could be for is like, we forced all of them to believe in Jesus as their Lord and Savior
now.
I'm not coming at this with too much of a 2021 Alex Jones.
You're right, but I'm bitter and angry.
What am I supposed to do, Dan?
I understand, but we have to look at this through, like, obviously you can't have perfectly
naive eyes.
Sure.
But you have to, you have to look at this as like a different, a different time frame.
As a different person.
It's a different person.
Well, it's the same person.
And you'll see a lot of similarities.
Okay, well see, now this is why I'm bitter and angry.
Sure.
Yeah.
One of the things I noticed while I was listening to this is that he is definitely way more
doing a radio show and he goes to calls and then he'll get back to a story and then later
get back to some calls.
Like he jumps around like a lot of normal talk radio shows do.
It's a radio show.
And he, he's just doing a fucking rush impression.
Like this is outrageous.
You go to places where you can't go and buy a gun and have one in your house legally and
lawfully.
You got a lot of crime.
Crime!
Now that's a fact, ladies and gentlemen, that cannot be ignored or avoided.
And we know that when a state has a low threshold of gun control, where you have more liberty
and some semblance of a second amendment left, you have the lowest crime rates.
Because even a crackhead or junkie won't invade your home when you're there because they know
there's a 50-50 chance they're going to get killed.
So I just, I heard that and I was just like, this is just Alex doing an impression of right-wing
talk.
That's not Alex.
That's brutal.
Yeah.
And that sort of more guns is less crime kind of thing.
That's a talking point we've covered exhaustively because he talks about it all the time throughout
all of his career.
Yeah.
It's not true.
But when I was listening to this, I felt like I can see how someone would hear that and
believe it.
Yeah.
And it kind of intuitively makes sense that why, if I were a criminal, why would I risk
going somewhere where someone has a gun as opposed to somewhere where someone doesn't
have a gun?
Sure.
That makes intuitive sense.
And if you have someone like Alex saying this authoritatively and almost sort of mocking
the alternative, why wouldn't you just assume, why this guy knows what he's talking about?
It makes sense.
Yeah.
But you know, sometimes intuitive things are incorrect and this is one of them.
And I mean, it's the same way that people think about the death penalty of like, well,
if the consequence is so high, then that should act as a deterrent in the same, you know,
it's it makes sense to the macro where it's like, well, obviously we're not getting into
a nuclear war because of mutually assured destruction.
So that's a deterrent against doing that.
But they, you know, you're fucking hungry, man.
You know, like that's, that's a bigger deal than whether or not you're researching the
possibility that this home you need to do it, you know, like that kind of thing.
Yeah.
It doesn't make sense in the micro level.
No.
Yeah.
That's a, that's a good way to put it.
So, uh, George Bush, how would you describe his politics like on the spectrum of right
to left?
Um, ooh boy, I would put him in the, the, the like, not far right, not center, right.
That sweet spot of like, yeah, I want to kill everybody, but I want them to think I'm nice
while I do it.
Would you call him conservative?
Uh, compared to now?
Yes.
Well, you're wrong on all counts.
Oh, okay.
Bush isn't conservative.
His cabinet isn't conservative.
They are the most socialistic creatures ever seen in U S history, but they're just puppets
carrying out the agenda.
If you had Al Gore in office, things would be worse than it was under Clinton and whoever's
in office next, it's going to be worse than under George W because of their puppets, their
front man.
Yeah.
So he's a super socialist.
He's a super socialist.
He's the most socialistic creature in history and all of Bush's cabinet too.
Okay.
All right.
Uh, Oh boy, that's not good.
That cabinet.
See now that's, that's a cabinet filled with pure psychopaths.
That's the thing about George W. Bush.
I don't think he gave a shit.
I think he just filled this cabinet with a shit ton of psychopaths who wanted to murder.
Let's see if we can surround this team.
Just get it full of weirdos.
Yeah.
Four out of at least at least four of the people in George Bush's cabinet had personally
strangled a person, you know, like that kind of level of psychopathy excited to see the
2004 election happen.
Anyway, this next clip I think is, is, is wild because Alex is talking about how he
doesn't feel bad for Saddam, which obviously I guess that means that he doesn't feel bad
that Saddam's missing or out of power.
It's hard to feel bad for Saddam, but Alex, based on things he says later, I think he
thinks he's on an Island somewhere.
So I mean, obviously don't feel bad for him.
Well, I mean, it's not like Saddam was Napoleon where they're like, okay, we got to exile
you.
That's our solution to this problem.
And then Alex gives a voice to some stuff that I can actually get, you know, appreciate
that is that he feels bad for the citizens in Iraq, the people in the, on the ground
who are being affected by this stuff.
But if you pay attention to this, this, this is one of these indications that you can get
that Alex, even this empathetic kind of vibe that seems really grounded and decent is actually
rooted in just fervent anti-government sentiment.
Of course, Saddam is a bucket of trash, of course, he's evil.
The CIA hired him folks in 58 as a hit man, told him to invade Kuwait.
I mean, yeah, he's a bad guy, folks.
So I'm not sad for Saddam.
I am sad for the Iraqi people that are being mowed down in large piles by the hundreds.
If they dare to protest and one child throws a rock, I am sad for the US citizen, the young
college girl unarmed, run over by a bulldozer.
He then savagely backed back over her in the giant armored army bulldozer.
I am sad for the AP and Reuters cameramen that are being shot by Israeli snipers in
the head as they wear vests that say press.
I am sad for the police officers killed by their own SWAT team members.
I am sad for the people being shot down by corrupt cops and having guns planted on them.
I am sad, ladies and gentlemen, for the people being abused by government worldwide.
It's all in service of just strong anti-government positions.
Yeah, I don't see him caring as much now about the hundreds of millions that were slaughtered
by the United States government.
But you know, what are you going to do?
No, I can't expect him to continue caring about these people.
It's over after today.
Yeah, and that's part of the reason that I think it's really interesting, because he's
saying a lot of the things that are right, but it doesn't feel like it comes from a place
of any solid center to it.
It doesn't feel like it's based on intrinsic belief as much as it is on... well, I guess
it is, but the intrinsic belief is opposition to government.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm a little bit taken aback because it seems like I want to say that this is a slicker
show already.
A little bit.
I mean, that's because I was just completely out of control in the present day.
Exactly, but it's hard to like, oh, well, see, just because he's...
I would say it's almost more disingenuous by being a slicker show.
Yeah, I agree with that, and I think that that's part of the reason why I feel reinvigorated
by this, because I can see how someone would believe it.
I can see how someone listening to a clip like that could be like, yeah, this guy gets
it.
He does get it.
That is fucked up that US troops are killing civilians overseas.
That is fucked up.
And that is the way that Alex baits the hook to get people to fall into his anti-government
shit.
Totally.
No, it seems reasonable.
It's fascinating.
It's so disingenuous and so evil, just evil, you know, to hide your like, I'm a Joan Bircher
behind like, hey, it's wrong to kill civilians, because his answer is, yeah, it's wrong to
kill civilians until I want to.
You know, it's that kind of situation.
And he just leaves out that last part, which in the present day, he kind of leaves it in.
Yeah, he mostly leaves it in.
Yeah, he mostly leaves it in now.
So we'll get to a lot more of this like overt trickery, because I think you see some pretty
stark examples of it later on.
And actually, the John Birch Society comes up later in an interesting way.
But before we get there, Alex has another headline.
This is about Tom Ridge, Homeland Security, wanting to institute an ID system for livestock
due to a concern largely about the vulnerabilities within the food chain, the ability to know
if there's a diseased cattle somewhere that causes blah, blah, blah.
So Alex reads this headline, and apparently it's all about like more taxes or something.
Ridge favors national ID system for livestock.
Do you know how bad this is?
A whole layer of government bureaucracy in your life, harassing you, taxing you, oh yes,
a whole new bureaucracy knowing everything you've got.
Your cats, your dogs will be pigs, sheep, goats, cows, horses, a whole layer of tax.
You'll have a registration fee every year on your animal.
Why don't you keep the homeland and the food supply safe?
Seems to be mocking the idea of protecting the food supply.
Now that's interesting, because that does fit the tone of some of the rest of his coverage
throughout the show.
But what it doesn't fit is the tone of one of his commercials.
Are you prepared?
Seems that more terrorism on our soil is inevitable.
Chemical attacks, biological, nuclear, who knows for sure what dangers lie ahead for
America.
Recent articles have pointed to vulnerability in our agricultural industry.
An attack on our food supply would be devastating.
Jerry Guadetti from the ARC Institute has been alerting people to this very real possibility
for years.
Yeah, so it's so weird.
Okay, all right.
I can see how conflicting messages would cause problems for early listeners to the show.
I was listening to this and it seemed very bizarre.
It's like, okay, your editorial's out of sync with your advertising at this point.
That's why you're not raking in the cash.
That could be an issue.
Yeah.
That could be a problem.
Very weird.
Ted Anderson is still selling crap to his show.
That's a survival seed company, so obviously it would be in their best interest from an
advertising perspective to drum up the fears of the damage to the food chain and the food
supply.
Meanwhile, Alex has an interest politically in painting that as more government and more
taxes.
Of course.
They're going to tax your cat.
He says, loving ice.
So I don't know, man.
When you were in school, do you like playing games at recess?
Yeah.
Did you ever play foursquare?
Sure.
Foursquare was great.
No black magic, no cherry bombs.
No black magic.
If you threw a cherry bomb, you're out.
You're kicked out because then you have to chase after the ball.
I don't even remember what any of that means, but I remember exhaustive conversations.
There were a lot of rules.
That was the beginning of when you first find out about the kid who's like, oh no, he's
going to take his ball, isn't he?
He's going to take his ball.
Oh shit.
Now we don't know how.
Now we have nothing to play with.
I remembered the conversation of rules more than I remember foursquare itself.
Totally.
Well, here's the good news.
Foursquare is still legal.
However, dodge ball has been banned.
All over?
Maybe you haven't heard, but it's been on television.
I know schools right here in Texas, parents right here in Texas that have called in on
the show about it.
It's been in the news.
Dodge ball has been banned almost nationwide.
I remember our favorite game.
In fact, the girls, the, you know, the kids that weren't that big, the runts, everybody
loved dodge ball.
I mean, everybody would hooray to play it.
Everyone loved it.
And you know, if somebody didn't like it, that's the way sports are.
That's the way PE should be when you're six years old, seven year old, eight year old,
10, 12, usually play, I guess when you're about 10 or 12, they banned it.
And then I read a report about a month ago where they arrested kids, two or three of
them, criminal charges of assault because they would meet before school.
I remember doing stuff like this, but we would, we would wrestle, we would wrestle and knock
our teeth out and break our noses and the coaches would come around and go, you guys
watch it.
You're going to get hurt.
Do that on the mats with your head gear.
Get in here.
I'm giving you a SWAT.
You know, you'd, they'd take you to the nurse and fix your lip and you'd get a pop for wrestling
without head gear.
But the point is now the kids will secretly get behind the school with their dodge balls.
Just a little bit of freedom.
I can't find any stories about students getting arrested for pre-school hours, dodge ball
games.
That's such a, I hate those.
I hate that shit so much.
Like one, it seems silly now not to realize that dodge ball at that age is essentially
a way to facilitate bullying.
Yes.
It's like, I'm happy playing a dodge ball as an adult.
That makes perfect sense.
We all know the game.
We're all doing a great job as a kid.
You're just like so many guys just picked on the smallest, like Alex is like, everybody
loved to play the game.
He wasn't the runt.
Yeah.
I think it is a game that can get abusive and I understand people not wanting to play
it and they shouldn't be forced to play it.
Totally not.
But I guess if people want to play during recess, I don't, I don't believe, I can't,
I don't believe that it's been banned almost nationwide.
There aren't arrests happening if you play dodge ball, but I do think it's interesting
the different way that Alex is talking about his school days violence here in 2003, very
less dark, much less dark.
At no point in time did I hear him say he stomped a guy's guts out.
Yeah, no, if we take the present day understanding of Alex's former violent tendencies where
he murdered a couple people.
Yeah.
A little bit different.
It seems weird that he'd be sitting here in 2003 laughing whimsically about.
Come on.
We used to have little scrapes back in the day.
Now granted I murdered.
I did kill him.
I hate those fucking stories so much of like, Oh, when I grew up, we used to go out back
and we'd get hit with a switch if we got in trouble and we turned out fine.
And you're like, you guys are all legitimately insane.
Everything you believe is nonsense.
You did not turn out fine.
Do not tell me that story and then not connect it to your violent present.
And that's why they're banning dodge ball.
Of course.
Now, do you think anyone has been arrested for this is going to, this is, this is a trivia
question that is a very important, all right.
Do you think anyone's been arrested for musical chairs?
Yes, absolutely.
30 to 40 people at a time daily.
You've probably heard.
They're making a musical chairs.
You can't play musical chairs.
Now there haven't been a rest made for musical chairs for secretly playing dodge ball or
tag.
I forgot.
Tag too has been banned.
Tag you get arrested for playing tag.
Then why the hell did you bring?
Bring up tag!
You did!
Yeah, I know.
But why did you bring?
No arrests for musical chairs.
I would like statistics on that.
Does the FBI publish musical chairs related arrests?
Yeah, it's from the Bureau of Statistics.
Does the ATF also take care of that?
Yeah.
I don't know.
I mean, I feel like as I recall musical chairs can get a little bit physical, but it's not
supposed to.
Like if some kid is fighting with somebody over a chair, that's a behavioral issue.
Everybody goes, okay, well we gotta deal with this now.
This was unintended.
This is not part of the game.
So Alex is pretty deep into a conversation about what you can and can't do at schools
and how the government is cracking down.
Oh, that government.
Now they have gone too far.
Well here it is.
Banned on campus, boys talking to girls, World Net Daily, elementary students protest restriction
after showing public signs of affection, sixth grade girls protest, photo heralded news newspaper,
and it shows dozens of young sixth grade girls with signs saying, allow us to talk to boys.
Smiling, attack on the shoulder, could lead to criminal charges.
Okay, everything's criminal now.
So that's a good story.
How are we still doing this?
So this is a story out of Portland, a Peterson Elementary School in specific.
What happened was that there was a teacher at the school who witnessed some non-specified
public displays of affection at recess and decided as a preventative measure that they
needed to disallow girls and boys from talking during recess.
Obviously this is taking things a little bit far, but also Alex is completely blowing this
story out of proportion, pretending that if a boy talked to a girl he'd get arrested on
criminal charges.
That's totally made up, because I suspect even Alex knows that talking about this story
on the merits of it might come off as a little desperate in terms of trying to make your
audience outraged.
Little silly.
Honestly, he's missing the forest for the trees here, and there's a much, much better
story to be told.
That is the story of Sarah Maines and Hannah Guerrero, two 12-year-old girls at the school
who took issue with the rule that got made and protested against it.
Sarah and Hannah straight up formed a student committee, studied the school's rules, and
figured out the proper steps to get a complaint heard.
They got all the protesting student's parents to sign off on letting them demonstrate, then
held a protest to have their complaint heard.
Sarah's mother puts it so well in this article from the Herald and News, quote, I'm so proud
of my daughter.
The hardest part was to walk into that school after protesting like that.
She stood up for herself.
I think she learned something important.
It's heartwarming.
Yeah, it is nice to know that no matter what era we're in, it is a universal rule that
children are way better people than adults by a wide margin.
Also, the principal of the school said, quote, no disciplinary action would be taken against
the protesters, and he's willing to hear any complaints from students and parents.
What you basically have here is a situation where a teacher possibly and probably over-reacted
to something that they were right to be concerned about.
This led to an overly broad rule being put in place, which got students to become active
in opposition to it.
These kids learned how to appropriately and effectively have their voices heard, how to
present an argument through proper channels to power.
It's honestly an amazing story, and I'm so impressed by these kids.
Yeah, it really is an amazing story.
What a bunch of dicks.
This story that is really inspirational is absent from coverage in places like Infowars
because the story isn't real to Alex.
It's a prop, and for this to be an effective prop, he has to distort details to make it
something the government was doing to these kids, as opposed to an iffy administrative
decision.
It makes me kind of sad because the Infowars audience is deprived of hearing this story
about students getting involved in direct civic action solely because focusing on that
too much makes it clear that this whole thing about flirting becoming a criminal act is
complete bullshit, and that bullshit is how he keeps the audience engaged and outraged.
Well, I mean, the story is essentially a microcosm of the people taking on the government exactly
like Alex would want them to do theoretically, however, that would be bad for his audience
to actually take civic action to change things because then he would run out of money.
Yeah, the students who were protesting here didn't try and change the government by sending
money to a blowhard student in the class.
There wasn't one student in the class who yelled a whole bunch.
Yeah, exactly, and then they were like, I'll take care of it for you.
I'm the tip of the spear going against this teacher here.
Send me money.
If one student had written a pamphlet that it was selling, yeah, that would be who Alex
is.
Behold the teacher's horse.
Yeah, exactly.
Oh, she's just in it for the apples.
How does this still work?
I think that's why I'm a little depressed about going back to 2003 because how do adults
still get caught up in this bullshit?
Look at this.
It's the same story that we're hearing about now.
Yeah, it is.
It's the same story.
It's the same shit, and adults are still, at no point in time, are they like, oh, have
I heard this exact same thing 20 years ago and I'm fine?
Well, yeah, but I think that you forget.
The war on Christmas happens every year.
Sure, sure, that's true.
I think it's one of the evergreen things about-
The Iraq war happens every year.
I think it's one of the evergreen things about the right-wing media ecosystem.
These complaints that somehow all the kids are being softened at school or whatever,
it's just something that will never not elicit a reaction from that audience.
Yeah, no, of course, because if they were to hear that the kids weren't fighting at
all, they were learning, using their words, organizing, and then making a real change
in the world, that would not fit in with their, these kids are soft argument.
That would be difficult for them.
It would actually make you look like an idiot for fighting instead of learning and organizing
and making change.
Yeah, and those girls who started that protest, who got the committee going, studied the rules,
they accomplished what they set out to accomplish.
Yes, and they both grew up to be Michelle Obama.
That's one of the important lessons, I think, is being deprived from the audience, and I
think that's just unfair, but that's how it's supposed to be.
Anyway, Jordan, if you want to get more depressed about thinking about the past and the present,
and about how I'm a witch, I would ask you to put your mic down for this next clip.
The British government actually released foot and mouth.
In fact, two months before the outbreak, they had to admit, they had contacted people, the
agriculture departments in the counties, and said, get pyres ready, get lots of wood ready
to burn piles of dead animals.
They said, why, and they said, oh, well, you'll see, and then they admitted the foot and mouth
got released from porting down Bio Weapons Lab.
They said by accident, someone released it or someone stole it.
By the way, that's a level four Bio Weapons Lab that has stuff that'll kill specific races
of people, wipe out all whites, wipe out all blacks.
Just amazing.
So many similarities to the present.
Wow.
There's no truth to what Alex is saying, but interestingly, in the aftermath of the 2001
foot and mouth outbreak in the UK, there were a ton of rumors flying around about how it
started.
Subsequent investigations have shown that it started on a farm that was feeding its
livestock untreated waste, but that didn't stop theories from flying around in the days
immediately after the outbreak.
One of the popular theories was that there was a vial of this specific strain of foot
and mouth that had been stolen from or accidentally released from porting down, a biological lab
in England.
Sure.
This is an interesting story, and it follows essentially the same path as Alex's present
day theories about the novel coronavirus.
At various points in the early days of the 2020 outbreak, Alex has suggested that it
was intentionally or accidentally released from the Wuhan Institute of Virology, and
he's also discussed the use of race specific bio weapons to bolster his claims.
Jesus.
This is like looking into a funhouse mirror of the past.
This is so awful.
I'm trying to torture you with this.
I mean, because why would you...
Like, okay, I get that we're evil as a species or whatever, and people are going to do...
Just because something shouldn't exist doesn't mean it's not going to, right?
But you can't possibly think it's a good idea.
Even if you could make a race specific bio weapon, you can't think it's a good idea to
leave it anywhere.
You have to have that in a safe, inside of a safe, inside of another safe surrounded
by people who've lost their hands, who can't open it, like that kind of shit.
If you would ever endeavor to make something so stupid and destructive, you would have
to keep it in a parody of security.
Yeah.
It's something that's a hoax.
I mean, it's literally like you're one whoops away from all white people gone.
That's not okay.
Yeah.
And also race specific bio weapons are real.
It's bad.
So The Guardian looked at the various theories about the foot and mouth outbreak, and the
port and down one was one of the ones that got their attention.
Unfortunately for the conspiracy, they spoke to a representative at port and down who said,
quote, we have never worked on foot and mouth.
That doesn't sound like folks admitting that it was released from there, but yet Alex is
on air saying that it's been admitted.
It's about what they don't say.
That's weird.
It's really weird.
Kind of like how he always acts.
This Guardian article also discusses the revelation that months before the outbreak, people from
the Ministry of Agriculture were calling around getting quotes on the price of timber in order
to burn diseased animals.
That is true.
Yeah.
They're reporting this as them sneakily and cryptically telling farmers to prepare piers,
but that's about the level of accuracy you should expect from Alex.
Yeah.
It's kind of close to something that's real, but according to The Guardian, quote, Stratfordshire
Animal Health Office, part of the Ministry of Agriculture, rang around merchants in the
autumn asking for quotes for timber for piers as part of an animal contingency plan on how
to deal with swine fever and foot and mouth outbreaks.
This is a requirement of all EU countries.
It happens every year.
So it's not something that's suspicious at all, but Alex has built it into a foot and
mouth was intentionally released from a level four bioweapons lab.
Of course.
In order to...
Oh, boy.
That's a story that's more about how England was like, remember when we threw dead bodies
in the Thames and then there was disease?
We don't do that anymore.
It was a smart move on our part.
So another sort of mirror glimpse to the present and the past comes in this next clip.
Just stylistic, though, instead of content.
And I haven't even scratched the surface.
I've covered some of the important news.
The news is so insane today that I will cover all 100 articles.
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do it in the next two hours, and we're going to get to all your calls immediately
after this break.
That's just...
Wow.
He's always about to get to it.
If you say that, there should be a ticker that appears just by magic.
Like 100 stories?
It's a countdown clock.
It just appears.
Every day the show ends at 98.
If I had...
Got to two stories.
That's my wish.
My genie's wish is just like, I don't want money.
I don't want happiness.
I want purely just...
If you make a claim like, I'm going to do 100 things, a ticker appears.
The end.
So Alex does end up going to take some calls, and he gets a call from a guy, and the conversation
drifts into talking about the government tracking children via cell phone.
Sure.
Or tracking people by cell phone and then using the excuse that it's to protect the
kids.
Right?
Yeah.
And then Alex says something weird.
But now that they're announcing that we're about to be tracking you, the government says
that, oh, the police locally are watching the FEMA command center they built.
Now it's, oh, it's for the children.
See how they introduced it?
It's for the children.
It's for the criminals.
It's for the minority.
See, it's always for that other group.
Go ahead.
So that's interesting to me because that's right on the line.
That's right on the line.
It's always for a minority.
That's the kind of thing that if you were really uncharitable and ungenerous to him
you'd be like, okay, what minority groups are you talking about here?
Is that coded language?
But it's also, if you are charitable, you could be like, well, he's just saying that
groups that aren't the majority, so criminals are a minority of the population.
It's right there on the line.
It's always, and it's rich for you to be like, oh, see how they do that?
They say it's for the children.
And then the next breath is like, I only care about the millions of aborted babies.
It's about the aborted babies.
It's not about controlling women's actions at all.
Sure.
Yeah.
That's bad financial advice to give.
Although I will say that he's not saying this as just solid financial advice.
Sure.
There's an ethical component to it, but his audience would have missed out on some money
if they took this advice.
You've got to be preemptively down at your county commissioners, your state legislature,
calling Washington.
You've got to preemptively find out if any of the mutual funds you own, own speculative
tech stocks like Applied Digital.
If you've got Motorola, they're involved in the biochip.
IBM.
IBM is a, you know, so-called good stock.
Well, yeah, it's like buying a piece of Satan.
You need to go ahead and dump that stock.
It's up from where it was in 2003.
I would argue.
It's not hugely up, but you'd make a nice bit of money.
If you'd bought stock in it in 2003, you'd make maybe a good, more than 50% profit.
Not bad?
No.
But the reason that he wants you to get out of it is, apparently, IBM owns the Chinese
military.
I did not know that!
I would add an addendum to that.
IBM owns, or the Communist Chinese military, owns Applied Digital Solutions, their front
company.
They don't want to take the heat of being involved with this product, but they are the
owners.
You know, their financial statements, 2000, 2001.
I think 2002 is out yet, I haven't read it.
There's a Chinese plant that's being built for the implantator, ejector, and the chip
itself.
It's all part of hell on earth.
So yeah, apparently there's a Chinese plant that's being built to get the implantator
and the implants for the chip that they're going to put in everybody.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
And IBM owns the Chinese government's military.
That is an interesting way to diversify your business, your revenue streams.
Yeah, it's like, okay, well we did pretty good, but that almost suggests that the computer
thing was just a way for them to make enough money to buy the Chinese military.
It also introduces a lot of questions that I want answers to, like, has it been sold
since?
That's a good question.
Does IBM still own the Chinese military?
Also a good question.
What say does the Chinese government have about military decisions, do they have to
check with IBM?
Sure.
I think one of those shared office space companies wound up buying it, yeah, I think they wound
up buying it.
They don't have a solid business plan, so they were like, well we might as well buy
a military while we've got the cash.
Yeah.
So Alex takes another call, and this guy made me really sad.
I mean, I just can't sleep, I'm going to be honest with you, I spend probably about 15
hours a day studying, reviewing articles you put out.
That's because you're normal, you're sane, when you read about giant FEMA cams and execution
centers it upsets you.
I can't imagine reading for a number of hours about things that Alex suggests people read
and not realizing, oh, this guy's a dumb-dumb.
Oh, this is full of shit.
Yeah.
All of this is terrible.
I find that really difficult, I don't know what this guy is reading.
I don't think he is, I think he's probably reading message boards or something and calling
it research.
It almost seems like you would learn about how much bullshit it is by osmosis, just by
repetition of just like, I've heard this before, I've heard this before, I've heard this before,
this guy might be full of shit.
Wait, this doesn't say what Alex says.
Yeah.
Yeah, it just bums me out.
And I think it is indicative of how a lot of his listeners and how a lot of people who
get into this world, their experience of it is compulsive.
What he's describing is such a compulsive relationship with this information.
I read what you write 15 hours a day, because you're normal, man.
You're normal, bro.
Because you're a normal dude, that's how people react to the things that I say.
Yeah.
So Alex at this point needs to make a programming note.
Okay.
And that is actually kind of revealing in as much as he is clear, even in 2003, that
tragedies bring traffic.
I made a comment last weekend that after every time there's a terror event, the listenership
peaks, it spikes.
Well, obviously, all news, newspaper sales go up, radio listenership goes up for news
talk.
That always happens.
And I made the comment that right after the so-called Iraq war ended, that listenership
dropped.
And then that gets picked up, and another host says it, another host says it, and basically
it ends up we don't have any listeners.
That's ridiculous.
A little defensive.
Yeah.
But I think that this is interesting, because at this point he does understand that dynamic
of tragedies lead to more people viewing my shit.
Which is a lesson, obviously, he should have learned from 9-11, and he should know that
by now pretty well.
But I question whether he understands at this point fully that obsessing about the immediacy
of another tragedy happening soon will also spike his ratings.
I think he learns that pretty quickly, but it doesn't feel like it at this point.
It just feels like a radio show.
Yeah.
So he gets another caller, and this guy sent me down a nutso rabbit hole, insane, too much
of my time.
Okay.
I was wondering if I may take this opportunity to see if we can get any signatures on the
site that I talked to you before about, if you want to go ahead and announce it.
What site is that, Eric?
You've got a site signature.
Is that a petition?
Yeah.
It lists over about 300 grievances.
Oh, yeah, I read that.
You sent that to me.
Yeah, a lot of good grievances there.
What's the website address?
Redeclarationofindependence.com.
And then I would imagine it.com, yeah.
You bet.
2003 is an interesting time for followers of conspiracy culture and the communities
surrounding it.
In the present day, extremely far-right tendencies have almost entirely absorbed that space,
but it wasn't always like that.
So back then, I would be willing to bet that I'd probably agree with some of this caller's
suggested new grievances in his post about the government.
Okay.
Luckily, the Wayback Machine exists, and I was able to find this caller's redeclaration
of independence, and perhaps unsurprisingly, I did in fact find some common ground with
this guy.
Okay.
For instance, his first complaint reads, quote, we demand the abolishment of engaging our
military in unconstitutional activities, spreading them out as the police of the world while
leaving our borders wide open and unprotected.
I might have left out the part at the end about the borders, since it has nothing to
do with the main point of unconstitutional engagements of the military, but leaving that
aside, we agree that the government's got to stop this war stuff.
True.
A little bit later, we find even more agreement.
Quote, we demand the abolishment of all instances of murdering citizens completely within their
rights and destroying and refusing to disclose evidence in these crimes.
I would even expand that language to include non-citizen residents, but we're on the same
page.
Cop shouldn't be killing people.
Yeah.
It's important to remember that that's where those people were, and now they're at Blue
Lives Matter.
You know?
You don't know what this guy's up to.
Sure.
So this whole agreeing thing falls apart pretty quick, since it immediately dovetails into
complaints about UN treaties and calling for abolishing, quote, the post office, public
education, and Amtrak.
Oh, so we're Ron Pauling it.
A little bit.
Okay.
This document completely goes off the rails with words like treason starting to pop up
in all capital letters.
There.
That's where we get into trouble.
In all caps a word, you are, yeah.
Apparently part of the re-declaration of independence is charging any individual or
industry that traded with North Vietnam, China, Russia, Iraq, or any of their satellite countries
with treason.
This extends to literally everyone who worked in things like steel or petroleum industries,
but also to everyone who's been in elected office in Congress or the executive branch
or the Supreme Court dating back to the Korean War.
Yeah, you might as well just rewrite that to say, we got to clean house and get rid
of all these guys.
And past.
Let's, yeah, let's begin at the 16th century and we'll start over.
The document demands, quote, all who served in these political positions during any of
the times of armed conflict in question from the Korean War to this date be stripped of
any retirement or other compensation.
I'm guessing that's in addition to the treason charges.
What about people who supported the civil war?
The South, huh?
Do they get treason charges?
Yeah, it's before the federal reserves.
Okay, well, that's fair.
The thing is, this is nuts.
This document is nuts.
And it's hilarious for Alex to pretend that he's read it trying to humor this caller.
I'm certain that Alex didn't read it, but honestly, it's so much funnier to imagine
that he had and was still giving this guy a glowing review.
You see, here's how the new Declaration of Independence ends with a suggestion of what
they should do next, quote, we hereby petition for renewal of government removed entirely
from Washington D.C. and reconstituted in another region of the land.
And at least temporarily at first, during its beginnings, this new government for and
of the people will be situated and redeveloped from Austin, Texas, the birthplace of the
new people's house with an initial mailing address of bleep, I'll just bleep it out.
Okay, okay.
A new government will be birthed for the free world, led initially and temporarily by the
following patriots of this new age.
Alex Jones.
Names?
Oh, no.
Top of the list?
Yep.
Oh, shit.
Alex Jones, Eric Rainbolt, Mike Hansen, George Humphrey, Chris Athanas, Kevin Smith, and
Robert Dassey, in order to retain our original forefathers declaration of our God-given rights
and framework for the lasting legitimate republic promoting global freedom under God's laws,
not a select group of men's laws, and the complete dismantlement of all forms of tyranny
hereafter.
This wasn't that much farther after Mallrats, so I can see Kevin-
Wrong Kevin Smith.
What?
It's not the view askew, Kevin Smith.
This guy wants to overthrow the government, reconstitute it in Austin, and have Alex and
some of Alex's friends temporarily rule this new blossoming government.
That's amazing.
Yeah.
In case you don't know those names, Mike Hansen was Alex's longtime cameraman and producer.
Kevin Smith worked at Info Wars, and George Humphrey and Bob Dassey were regular Info
Wars guests.
The new Politburo is just employees of Info Wars.
Yeah, except for Chris Athanas, I don't know who that is, and Eric Rainbolt.
I was like, who the fuck is that?
And then I realized, it's this caller.
Well you're not gonna not insert yourself into the Politburo.
So if you Google the address that he lists as the temporary address of the new government
of America, you'll find that it's listed as the publishing address for a 2005 book titled
The Freemasonic Architecture of History, self-published by Eric Rainbolt.
It's Eric Rainbolt's house.
It's Eric Rainbolt's house, isn't it?
Well, hold on.
It's definitely the address of the publishing of this book that was written and self-published
by Eric Rainbolt.
Uh-huh.
He was also the proprietor of 911exposed.com.
The real mystery here, though, is that the name of the person listed as the owner of
that house doesn't match with Eric Rainbolt, so I felt like I was at a dead end, but my
curiosity was itching too strongly.
Was this caller the person who wrote the new Declaration of Independence, imagining
a new government forming at his house in Austin where he gets to rule alongside Alex?
It's really complicated, but I looked into the phone numbers and addresses listed for
the publishing endeavor, and I'm pretty certain that it is this dude.
It was actually written under Eric Thunderwater.
I found the phone number that's associated with it.
It's someone else's phone number, but also it's a house phone.
It's associated with someone named James Rainbolt.
But Eric Rainbolt has published multiple...
Still living with his dad.
No.
I don't know.
Maybe.
Okay, maybe.
Eric Rainbolt has written a couple of other books under the name Eric James Rainbolt.
So anyway, I'm pretty sure it's him.
All right.
Yeah, that would probably be him.
This is a stupid long road for me to wander down, but the reason I still think it's important
is because there are some fairly critical things that me and this guy would totally
agree about.
We would both want to end the Iraq War, and we both want greater oversight on police,
but it's pretty crucial to recognize that despite our differences, we aren't even close
to allies, nor could we ever be.
Ultimately, I want to create a world that operates better and more fairly for everyone.
And ultimately, this guy wants to be on Alex Jones' small council.
Yeah.
Also, this guy ended up with 75 signatures on his petition at the point of the last screenshot
in the Wayback Machine, available...
This date was from July 2010, so I'm not sure exposure on Alex's show did much to help that
petition.
I would argue that maybe...
75 signatures.
That's not good.
They might have read it and got to the part where it's like, what the fuck?
Alex is in charge of the government, along with the guy who wrote this?
Yeah.
The enemy of my enemy is not my friend if they also want to establish a fucking Game
of Thrones style, I'm the Hand of the King for Alex Jones situation.
Yeah, a bizarro religious extreme libertarian nonsense fantasy land where Alex and some
of his guests rule the roost.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't think so.
Yeah.
I don't think so anymore, but I will choose other people to work on that issue with.
Anyway, this was kind of what...
I was like, I'm sure that's this guy.
And then...
Let's talk to Eric in Texas.
Eric, you're on the air.
Go ahead, sir.
That was the beginning of the call.
It is Eric.
Oh, it is Eric.
Yeah.
Okay.
So anyway, Alex gets another call, and this guy is kind of interesting.
This fellow has a plan for dealing with some of the media that he doesn't like, folks like
Hannity.
Yeah.
These folks who are not conservative, apparently.
I'll make them put the lotion in the basket.
Nope.
We need to dig up dirt.
Okay.
You're listeners who are very intelligent and very capable people.
Many of them have, I'm sure, computers and know how to use them very well.
You can access a lot of public domain information.
It's all quite legal.
And I think that we should start a campaign of accessing as much public domain information
about all these suspect broadcast individuals as we can.
Case in point, I don't know if you or your listeners are aware, but Sean Hannity was
a troublemaking adolescent who came from a Long Island, New York community.
That's a very interesting thing.
Maybe that needs to be looked into further, and it tells you something about what the
real makeup of this man is.
Michael Savage, who you mentioned, the guy used to hang out in the late 50s in beatnik
bars in Greenwich Village, New York.
That's one of the major articles.
He's a beatnik communist.
That's invented.
So Michael Savage is a beatnik communist.
Wow.
Yeah.
All right.
Here's what we do, guys.
We got to blackmail Hannity and Michael Savage with their child records.
Yeah.
It's really interesting.
You think that that's a potent way to attack these figures on the right that you don't
like and apparently aren't on the right.
I found out public records that Sean Hannity got a D in his civics class.
Is that the type of person we want on the radio, Dan?
It is over for him.
He's hashtag canceled.
He's toast.
This is cancel culture.
Yeah.
That's literally what the right does.
Oh, man.
Anyway, I just think it's really weird to hear this kind of ploy being suggested by
this caller.
Yeah.
Alex being like, all right.
And then also the political framing is so important.
We have George Bush in all of his cabinet.
They're super socialists.
Sure.
You have Michael Savage as a beatnik commie.
These very right wing people are being presented as left.
Yeah.
So they're not even moderate.
Or maybe they're supposed to be the moderate left or whatever.
Sure.
Rhinos, if you will, Dan.
That was a big talking point in 2003 and ever and always forever.
But it makes it okay for whatever really, really hard right wing thing you want to be
like, oh, no, this is just actually normal conservatism.
Right.
Right, right, right.
I don't know about that.
Jesus.
Maybe sovereign citizenism is even just normal conservatism.
Sure.
Hello, Ida.
Yes.
Thank you for taking my call.
The reason I'm calling is I listen to you almost every day.
And I understand we've got 250 million of the happiest slaves in the world living in
this country.
And that's why they'll never revolt.
I have revolted.
I have been thrown in jail five times.
I am now looking at a year and a half in jail plus a $1,500 fine simply because I refuse
to go down the road without a driver's license.
Yeah.
And the federal law actually says that and the court really say that you don't have to
have a license for the generally accepted conveyance, but that's a horse and buggy still.
Hey, Alex, I've used every definition coming down the pike in court and the judge turns
around, the prosecutor objects and the judge turns around and he says it's okay to object.
I can't use it.
And the next thing I know I'm getting paraded off to jail.
You need to go ahead and appeal it up to a higher court.
But yeah, these courts, even federal judges have said are just rubber stamp kangaroo courts
now.
Oh yeah, for sure.
For sure.
You don't need a license for sure.
Your honor, objection, silly bullshit.
Sustained.
Yeah, this isn't true.
What Alex is saying isn't true.
They arrested me simply because I refuse to go down the road without a driver's license
is an interesting way of putting I've been driving without a driver's license and I don't
give a shit.
Also, Alex later in the call says, I've driven without a license for years, so I think they're
targeting you.
Yeah, that sounds right.
That sounds right.
It's weird.
But that's like a bedrock of sovereign citizen shit.
It's just a misunderstanding of rules.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Or almost like an oppositional defiance toward the concept of rules that aren't self-generated.
Yep.
Yeah.
So in the present day, Alex Jones loves one Tucker Carlson.
Sure.
He's got enough of him.
Loves the guy.
Yeah.
Didn't like him so much before.
Yeah, I was going to say.
Yeah.
Obviously we've heard he doesn't like Hannity.
He thinks that Michael Savage is a commie.
Coincidentally more important figures than him.
What do you think he thinks about Fox, Fox News?
Oh, I think he thinks that they are just a left-wing outlet giving out propaganda for
an Obama that hasn't even been elected to the Senate yet.
Do you think that the average Marine or Army that's on the ground today know what's going
on?
Do they even have any idea?
They just don't know.
No, they just have Fox, the ultra commie channel that calls itself conservative beamed into
them.
Oh, everybody loves you.
Oh, it's great.
Oh, you're the greatest heroes ever.
By the way, we're cutting all your benefits right now, but as so what, you know, that's
the system.
Ultra commie channel, Fox News.
We're cutting all your benefits right now is not a thing that is acceptable for Alex
to say in a negative way.
He should be like, yeah, they're cutting all your benefits because you don't deserve them.
You lazy pieces of shit.
You know what?
I quit this show.
I got to leave.
Ultra commie Fox News.
Yep.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
That wasn't quite what I expected.
I mean, it's, it's, it's all, it's a lot to see.
Like when I, when I first turned on the episode, I was like, I think I'm going to have like
some really subtle things to try and sift through.
Yeah.
Instead it's just like, Michael Savage is a commie, Fox News is ultra commie, everyone
are communists.
Like, oh wait, this is, this is great.
Yeah.
That's, that's so, cause we've talked about this for years of like, if you just abandoned
Trump, you could carve out that space of like, I don't trust Fox News.
They're a bunch of liberal commie bullshit, you know, like listen to that.
Like you, it's so easy.
You could just be like, oh, there's Biden's giving a speech on CNN and they're whining
about some nonsense five-year-old who's got a problem.
Perhaps the proof of the pudding is in the eating as it were.
That's true.
I mean, like look at where he was in his career in 2003 and look where he is now.
Like obviously signing up with Trump has massively exposed him.
It's gotten him a far greater space in the public sphere.
He's made, it's made him relevant to the point where people like at least jokingly make his
name trend.
True.
Sometimes.
Back then in 2003, he had like a position of defiance against the right and the left.
Right.
He could pretend that it was because he's above the divide, but it's really, he's extremely
far to the right.
Exactly.
But you can see the, it didn't work.
It didn't work.
No, that's true.
That's true.
You're not wrong.
I, but, but it, you know, I'm, I'm still of the opinion of like carving out that comfortable
space is so much better than being like, well, if I hitch my wagon to Trump's train, I can
become world famous.
Yes.
No, I think it would be healthier and better if he had carved out that space.
But clearly he lusts for the sun, like Icarus.
That's true.
That is true.
And maybe that's just, uh, he could never do that while maintaining whatever it is that
he's doing back then.
Yeah, it is.
It is one of those situations where were the actions and context completely different.
I would be like, man, I got to give it up to you for seeing an opportunity and shooting
your shot.
And it has not worked out for you, but within the context and his actions, uh, he's an idiot
and I hate him forever and I want to throw baseballs at him.
I don't know if you know this, but 2003, in addition to seeing the end of the Iraq war,
um, we also were, uh, in the middle of SARS.
Okay.
Now, some people may remember the COVID-19 is originally SARS coronavirus two, uh, the
sequel to, uh, what's going on in 2003 SARS.
Let's see how, let's see how we handled it differently.
Reuters money may be the root of all evil, but China is trying to make sure it won't
be a source of SARS.
Now they already have public service announcements here in this country of how quote cash is
dirty and how we need to get rid of it to the safe cashless society.
Well the central people's bank of China was putting more new cash into circulation and
holding used bank notes for 24 hours before putting it back on the people's hands.
The people's daily newspaper said on its website on Tuesday, the communist party mouthpiece
at some banks or even sterilizing grimy bills and showering them with ultraviolet radiation
trying to kill the SARS virus, which has killed 148 people and infected more than 3,300 in
China.
Like 300 globally, not even that many folks, this thing, millions die every year from flu.
This is nothing.
They can't even isolate the virus.
It's hysteria.
As the Toronto star said, it is a UN power grab.
I didn't say it.
Toronto starred in so weird to see how the past echoes with the present.
Like you can dip back into 2003 and hear Alex Alex making the exact same nonsense claims
about SARS that he would eventually make about the novel coronavirus.
It's remarkable, almost like the actual facts in front of him don't matter.
And the particular details of a story are just decorations on top of his underlying
preexisting reality denying narrative.
SARS was a big deal.
It was real and it was not a UN power grab.
At this point, scientists hadn't been able to concretely isolate the SARS virus, but
they did achieve that this same month, on March 22nd, 2003.
At this point when Alex is making the episode, it's only been a few weeks since China reported
the outbreak of cases to the World Health Organization, and the situation is very much
in its infancy.
The international community jumped into action and quickly identified and isolated the virus,
and cautionary steps were taken to prevent the spread.
Because of collaborative action, and probably somewhat because the right-wing conspiracy
movement hadn't grown to the size it has in the present day, only 774 people in the world
ended up dying during the outbreak between November 2002 and July 2003.
The Toronto Star article Alex is referencing is something I can't find, but I would bet
anything it was an editorial article presenting the opinion that Toronto's response to SARS
has been hysterical.
You can find some people still, you know, some existing websites that express that sentiment.
It's hard to say if people there overreacted, but the Greater Toronto Area saw the fourth
largest outbreak of SARS cases in the world, behind China, Hong Kong, and Taiwan, so it
really does kind of make sense that the matter there would be taken seriously in a way that
might look like hysteria, but if you didn't act that way, who knows what the end result
would have been.
You know, I've always been, like, especially, you know, obviously now when you're thinking
about it, but it always kind of, like, messed me up when people say, oh, you're reacting
hysterically to this virus, and it feels like the entire human race should be so hysterical
about viruses and bacteria, considering...
Especially really new ones.
Yeah, considering disease has killed almost all of us.
You know, like, we talk about, oh, I'm so scared of war and all that shit.
Of all the people who have ever lived, most of them have died because of some disease
or another.
And I think that...
Like, we should all be hysterical, you know, like, that's what I would say.
And I think that the conversation largely has been, like, in times when we're not dealing
with outbreaks and infections and stuff, people in medical communities talk about the unknown
unknowns.
Exactly.
About, you know, like, all the conversation about Disease X or whatever, about this thing
that we don't know about that we may have to deal with.
It's really a terrifying prospect, because you have to figure out how it spreads, what
its characteristics are, and while you're figuring that out, it's spreading.
Or it could be spreading, or it might be spreading faster than you think.
Yeah.
It's a terrifying thing.
I agree with you.
Like, almost levels of hysteria become more rational the more you think about it.
Yeah.
And I remember some people that I knew were going through some steps that I would say
were maybe a little bit further than I would have, even, at the beginning of dealing with
the 2020 situation, and I kind of was like, hey, you guys are going a little far with
this.
And their response was, you know, I'd rather do this and look stupid later than not do
it, and feel like, oh, I could have taken preventative measures.
And I think that that's a compelling argument, and I felt stupid afterwards.
Yeah.
And it's also just, but I mean, part of it is just the very fact that so many fucking
people don't not just not understand evolution, but believe in it entirely.
It's just like, you realize that if a virus spreads, it's going to reproduce billions
of times in a very short period of time, which exponentially increases the possibility of
mutation and adaptation to our measures against it.
Like it is not, it is a constant battle.
It is not a, like, even now, if we defeat COVID-19, to the extent that we would all
love it, if we don't completely eradicate it, it is going to mutate and it can come
back any time.
You know, like it's a real terrifying reality.
And most people are like, eh, it's probably witches.
Like that's where we are.
Yeah.
Or, you know, witches that work for the UN.
Totally.
It's a UN power grab.
Yeah, it's a UN power grab.
It always is.
Always.
And I think if, you know, I don't know, I guess if Trump was president and the conspiracy
community existed the way it does now in 2003, SARS might've been a much bigger problem.
Oh, totally.
Well, I mean, you think about...
It's weird to think about it.
You think about so many of the, you know, like you think about Ebola outbreaks.
You see, you think about those things that happened in the past that in retrospect you
realize were handled by people who understood and were serious about the problem instead
of actively exacerbating it.
And the people who are causing problems should be held responsible in the courts.
So what you gonna do?
Hey, you know, Alex, at this point, you know, he's getting towards, you know, the end of
the show.
You know, we're getting deep into it.
He still hasn't covered the news.
How many of those?
In the next hour, I'll get more into this and what life will be like under the new world
order.
We have covered about a third of it.
I'll have to just jam it all in calmly in the third hour.
I don't know what's been wrong with me this week, but I've been more fired up than usual.
Before I end this segment, you want to find out what really happened with 9-1-1.
You want to see all the information, the globalists admitting it, the documents, the news articles
in a professional package.
Get Road to Tyranny, get part two of That Matters a Terror, my two films.
That's the ad pivot back then.
There's no pills to sell, no wellness supplies.
Get my films.
Yeah, he's just trying to sell his documentaries.
I'm looking for exposure.
If you get three of them, price goes down by three films.
What about shipping?
Is shipping still expensive at the time?
I don't remember.
Could be free.
Probably prohibitive.
Yeah, might be.
So Alex has an epiphany when he comes back from the commercial, and this just made me
want to throw something.
I'm frankly starting to panic on air.
I'm going to be honest with you.
Stuff's getting so bad.
I see the plan coming together.
Now I know my analysis has been dead on all along.
Worse than I thought, frankly, and it's freaking me out.
I know the nature of the globalist, watching serial killer control freak demons build a
cage for humanity is very energizing, just energized to resist them.
I've asked God to make me a vessel to fight the New World Order, and sometimes I just
think there's too much.
I mean, I'm just too energized.
I've got all the information.
I know what they're doing.
I know what their plans are, what their operations are, and like my mouth, my speech centers
can not, I don't think, articulate the globalist program properly to you.
It's just horrible.
Anyone who listens to our show with any regularity has heard that speech.
It's one that Alex gives pretty frequently when he gets in a wistful, contemplative mood.
Yesterday he was confused, but today all the pieces have come together, and he's more certain
than ever that his analysis has been right all along, and it's worse than he thought.
That's an interesting experience to imagine having when something groundbreaking happens,
but to go back to a random episode of his show from 18 years ago and see him pretending
to have the same epiphany that he does regularly on his show nowadays, it's a little annoying.
Also, another reason I pulled this clip is because Alex makes a reference to God and
to demons, but I think you can tell how much different that feels than how he acts and
speaks in the present day.
To my ears, listening to this, it kind of comes off like a man who has religious inclinations
but isn't a zealot.
It feels like a person calling his enemies demons as a pejorative insult, not as a description
that's meant to be taken literally.
It's weird to think about, but maybe Alex meant it to be heard as literal all along,
and people were just giving him an unasked-for benefit of the doubt.
There's no way he could think demons were real, and they were just Democrats.
That seems crazy.
So we'll assume that he's being metaphorical in this sense.
I don't think that's the case, but it's fun to think about.
Like the possibility that, nah, he's been pretty upfront about it.
He's talking about demons.
Dan, I hate time travel episodes sometimes because you're like a Mr. Peabody who refuses
to let me get into the time machine.
You just make me watch a movie of the past, and you're like, oh yeah, if we used this
time machine, we could fix it all, but too bad, asshole, we're just gonna watch.
Well, that'd be a more interesting cartoon.
Ah, could be.
So Alex gets to another call, and boy, he has some pretty anti-immigrant sentiments
back in 2003.
Unsurprising.
You know, I have a lot of friends that are Mexicans, but I don't have too many immigrant
friends, but you kind of wonder how in the world they got their driver's license in the
first place.
Look it up.
You know, if they do have one, and they really do not have a driver's license because they
do not know the law.
They're there for big companies to work because they do work.
Yeah, and the big companies have said, these people are here to vote our rights away because
they don't even know what they're doing, and they can't speak any language, they're just
the tall what to do with their local bosses, local little bosses, barrio boss, who works
for the government, and they're here to deindustrialize and to give us cheap wages.
Don't arrest them, don't mess with them, and it happens.
You on the other hand are middle class and got some money, you're to be fed on, pushed
around, they're going to let you know to keep in line.
Okay Alex, you know what you're doing, that's for sure.
I would have the exact same response as that caller, you know what you're doing, Alex.
Yeah, you lying piece of shit, you know what you're doing.
Yeah, jeez.
This is the same show where just an hour ago we were told you do not need a driver's license.
Right, with that caller.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sovereign Citizen shit.
So there's a difference, I would say, between who gets to not have a driver's license and
who...
You're not meant to remember that.
Fair enough.
On that same show we had Alex talking, you know, I was talking about that, like, if you're
uncharitable you could hear him saying the minority, and you could hear that as him talking
about, you know, minorities, non-white folk in his mind, or you could look at it as like
criminals are a minority of the population and that's what he's talking about.
This is not the same thing.
Nope, nope.
That's not this.
This is explicit.
Yeah.
These guys aren't talking about undocumented immigrants or people who came here through
improper channels or people who overstayed a visa, they're just talking about the blanket
category of people who are immigrants, and this conversation is outrageously white nationalist
at its core.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This caller is puzzling over how immigrants managed to get driver's licenses, which is
a bit silly, and then Alex shoots the moon by arguing that immigrants are coming to be
controlled by, quote, barrio bosses and instructed to take, quote, our rights away.
You got it.
The coded language is almost comically transparent here, and this walks hand in hand with the
white nationalist ideas about the great replacement that get thrown around in more recent times.
This is the way that conversation was had back then, and it's basically indistinguishable
from white supremacist positions on immigration.
Yeah.
It's outrageous.
I just see like a six year old Harrison Smith being like, man, I want to be worse than that
someday.
I want to be more explicit about exactly what I know he is saying.
I want to take this game and push it a little farther.
Yeah, let's go a little bit further to the racist.
Oh boy.
So Alex, uh, he gets to, he has this big point that he keeps making and that is that he can
go on any show on any conservative, well, there's, there's a more to it.
Okay.
He could go on any show, conservative, liberal, normal, whatever, right in the middle center.
Who gives a shit?
He can go on any of these shows.
They can take 30 calls.
They all agree with him.
Of course.
They all agree with because he's so ideologically consistent and because everyone knows that
Bush did nine 11.
That's true.
So he gets, he ends up role playing a little bit as some callers that he's fantasizing
about talking to on these radio shows.
And then I can be on some other station and take 20 calls and then one guy will call and
he'll go, you're a liar, Bush isn't trying to take my guns and I'll go, well, actually
the bill numbers, that's 22 Republicans are supporting it.
And you're a line coming.
I tell you, you liberals come up with some plans to confuse us and get us off track.
George Bush would never, he's a Christian conservative and you've, and then the hustles
say, well, actually he is supporting that and the gal go, Oh, well I still don't like
this guy.
Get him off here.
I just want to turn my guns in.
I mean, they don't say that, but they say everything else up to that.
So they're in a delusional world and I can be on Pacifica radio or something with all
the, what you would call liberals and they're all calling in a green, making good points
admitting the Democrats are corrupt too because if you're not hypocritical, they'll wake up.
You got liberals calling in going, yeah, I see what you mean about owning guns.
It makes a lot of sense.
You know, the government's tyrannical.
Why should we give our guns up?
I'm going to realize what you're saying and I did hear Australia's crime rate exploded
once they took the guns and then one person will call in and go, I bet you're racist,
Mr. Jones.
Aren't you?
Yes.
New World Order is a code word for some type of racial group you're a member of.
And I go, no, actually the government's calling for New World Order and I'll go, wait a minute.
You work for the government, don't you work in intelligence or for the FBI or for the,
or do you work for some federal program where I work?
Does it matter?
I'll go, just answer the question.
Well, yes, I work for the government.
Well hey, whoa.
This was one of the moments in the show where I was like, this is kind of feeling like the
present.
This is imaginary nonsense.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This one's good.
So I've heard that narrative arc of these callers discussed by Alex throughout his career.
That's sort of, it's very normal.
These seem to be archetypes of callers that he's imagined arguing with that he uses as
examples for decades as dumb people he has to talk to.
These people are used as caricatures of straw man arguments presenting things that are valid
complaints about Alex.
He uses these imaginary dumb callers as puppets to introduce these ideas like that he's a
racist because then it's a lot easier to mock and discredit those ideas like that he's a
racist.
Yeah.
You can hear Alex essentially laying out that him arguing that the Republican Party is corrupt
is a way to get liberals who can admit that the Democrats are corrupt to wake up.
Yeah.
If you lie about him being hypocritical, they'll wake up and they won't know you're lying because
you're not a malicious figure yet.
This is a strategy and it's meant to make Alex look closer to the middle where this
hypothetical Democrat is.
The idea is for him to paint a picture where he and this liberal have more in common than
they think and they only don't think so that they're more in common because these two corrupt
political parties have told them that they're not similar.
This is not true.
Alex is light years to the right of the GOP.
So what he's actually doing is trying to pull disaffected people of either party towards
the extreme right.
For people already in the Republican Party, this could mean becoming extremely right wing.
For Democrats, this might mean becoming a jaded political nihilist, maybe embracing
the GOP or just not voting for Democratic candidates.
Ultimately, the political end result of the project Alex is engaging in is this.
It's always about dragging people to the right while pretending there is no right or left,
which serves the political interests of whichever viable political entity is furthest to the
right.
Yeah.
That's what he's doing.
I am above the left right divide, Dan.
They want to do all these taxes and things, and I just want to drink blood from the skulls
of my enemies.
What doesn't everybody get about that?
Wake up, people.
I'm above the left right divide.
Right.
I mean, if he was truly opposed to the left right divide or whatever, and someone was
like a Democrat and they were like, oh, you know what?
The Democratic Party does suck.
I'm going to start exploring further left options.
He should be just as into that, right?
I mean.
That's what I think.
Yeah.
Oh, no, he's not.
Because the socialists are...
There you go.
Well, I mean, George Bush is a socialist.
They're demons.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Everybody's a socialist at this point.
In the present day, he's a socialist of demons.
We're not sure about that.
That's fair.
Could be a metaphor in 2003.
Is he...
He's anti-Reagan at this point, too, right?
I haven't heard him bring up Reagan on this episode.
Oh, that's true.
I can't speak to that.
That's true.
Fair enough.
He doesn't like anybody, from what I can tell.
It does sound like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That is like, you look back and you're like, ooh, gross, conservative.
They were communists.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Which I can...
But you can totally see that kind of being attractive, especially at that time, whenever
you look at the fact that both political parties are like, war is great, and let's do it all
the time.
And you're like, what's the fucking point of having either of these political parties
if we're just going to wind up with a mission accomplished banner?
Right.
And I think that that is why something like Alex is super potent back then.
Totally, totally.
Because there are a lot of people who are right in the exact place that they need to
be to hear a message like that and get sent down a road they don't know they're going
down.
Yeah, yeah.
I would say it's hard to argue that, you know, Osama bin Laden didn't destroy an entire country
by himself.
It's kinda...
He had compatriots.
It's kinda a little...
No, he had tons of compatriots, of course, but it's a little bit like, you know, 9-11
really did defeat America.
Alex does talk a bit about 9-11 on this episode, but not in a way that I felt like this is
where we're gonna start picking into it.
Sure.
So as I look through the 2003 stuff, when he gets into more of it, I'll definitely...
We'll see some more 9-11.
Yeah, 9-11 will definitely be more of a topic than it has been in our show in the past.
But I can't talk about it today because Alex, as he's talking about these callers that he
gets on radio stations, he ends up talking about being on a show out in the UK, right?
And this...
He got a call from a warden, a jail guard, and this is when...
This is evidence that this show used to be a family show.
I was on in England, and big national show, the James Whale Show, and it covers the whole
country.
We're getting calls from Scotland, Ireland, wherever.
It's a big transmitter.
A couple transmitters.
Actually, there's a big one in London.
They can have like, you know, 500,000 watt AMs there.
And I'm on the show, and they take like 20 calls.
Everybody agrees with me.
And one guy calls in, and he goes, I'd love to get you in a jail cell.
I'd love to get you in there.
And well, actually, the guy's threatening me, saying, yeah, you're gonna be...
You're a traitor.
You're a idiot.
You're this and that.
Don't talk about how my queen's German, because I pointed out their royal family isn't even
there.
You know, it isn't even British.
And I said, wait a minute.
You work for the government, don't you?
He's like, yeah, I'd like to get you.
I'd like to get you.
And he hadn't even said yet that he was a jail guard.
I go, you're a jail guard, aren't you?
He goes, huh?
Huh?
I go, yeah, aren't you?
And he goes, yeah, I'd like to get you in the cell, and I'd like to urinate on you.
He's another word.
I said, oh, oh.
And the host was amazed.
He goes, how'd you know that?
I can just tell.
Family show.
I don't say piss on this show.
Not back then.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
We're gonna adhere to these FCC rules.
Yeah.
No piss.
I would say, I don't know, I haven't heard this radio interview, but I would guess that
either this caller was like, yeah, I'm a jail guard.
You did.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sure.
I'm a jail guard.
Fine.
Or this didn't happen, and Alex is imagining it.
Yes.
It's interesting, though, Alex goes to spending five minutes talking about how he knew this
guy was a jail guard.
He's like, he had this tone of his voice where he's saying, I want to get you locked up.
I want to get you locked up.
And people only have this tone when they really want to do it.
So I heard this guy's voice, and I knew that he either, either was a serial kidnapper or
a jail guard.
That was only two options.
Most people who are smart kidnappers just become jail guards, because then they can
do all that stuff, and it's legal.
That sounds right.
That makes intuitive sense.
And this is how I read this guy's voice and knew that he was a jail guard.
People who kidnap illegally just don't know what they're supposed to be doing, right?
They just haven't found the right kidnapping job.
It's a little annoying, but also kind of trivially fun.
Like Alex is just wasting his time.
It's such an annoying habit of so many people to tell you a story where somebody is acting
so over the top, unreasonably, that it's impossible to believe.
And you knew before he even started he was full of shit.
Yeah.
It's like, why am I here?
So Alex gets back to calls, and this caller unfortunately has a terrible story of being
canceled.
And I'm calling you today because my local FM talk station has banned me from asking
any questions concerning the Warren Commission because they say it was 40 years ago and it's
so full of holes that they deny its even existence.
It was all a big television drama, like when Ruby shot Oswald.
But you know-
Anybody who believes that Oswald acted alone, fine, I got a bridge, I want to sell you.
This is like my favorite thing.
I love going back to this time in the past, and the callers are fucking callers.
They're not like sycophant nonsense, I love your brain force now.
It's a weirdo who can't call the local FM station anymore because he talks too much
about the Warren Report.
I'm not allowed there anymore because I refuse to discuss anything but 50 year old news.
That's what I do here.
I love that.
That's a vibe I could listen to, like, I could listen to that forever.
I'm not allowed on C-SPAN anymore because I won't stop talking about Fort Sumter.
And it's bullshit, Alex, it's bullshit.
The cancel culture is out of control.
It's out of control.
They won't let me harangue them for no reason about Fort Sumter.
It's infuriating, Dan.
I love it.
Love it!
So he gets another call, and this guy brings up the John Birch Society, which I teased
would come up.
Alex believes that the John Birch Society is mostly good.
Yes.
He's pretending that so much of his ideology isn't based on people who were in and adjacent
to the John Birch Society.
Unrelated.
Unrelated to the John Birch Society.
Very good.
No.
Unrelated.
I learned everything separate from the John Birch Society.
I did my own research, I definitely wasn't raised in a household filled with John Birch
or literature.
It was mostly John Birch Society stuff and sci-fi that he thought was real.
That's mostly-
Wow!
That really does explain everything, doesn't it?
Not everything, but a lot of it.
It explains too much.
Yeah.
For a human.
So, this made me laugh so fucking hard.
If you get what he's talking about, don't yell it out.
Just let this play out.
There is an Oklahoma family who are begging oil and a bunch of other stuff who are actually
involved in the founding of the John Birch Society, but the John Birch Society overall
is good.
Certainly, early on, not the Birchers, but other conservative groups have been used by
the bankers.
They'll tell some good conservative military man, that guy's a communist, go take him out,
and they'll go do it and later take him out for plausible deniability.
So many of our troops over there in Iraq now really are risking their lives and living
in a third world cesspool bombed out stone age system because they really believe in
this country.
Yes, sir.
But it is evil.
Does that mean the troops are evil?
No.
It means they're ignorant.
Thanks for the call, Spencer.
I appreciate the call.
Yeah.
I should have gotten into that.
Man, I had an article, big mainstream article on that family, how they funded the John Birchers
and all the different things they do and how they are big supporters of Bush.
I need to dig that back up and cover that.
Hmm.
I wonder who he's talking about.
Is he talking about the Candyman?
No.
He's talking about Fred Koch.
Oh, that's who he's talking about.
Son of a bitch.
Yeah.
He's talking about the Koch family.
That's right.
They're in...
Oh my God.
I didn't think of them because of the Kansas thing.
Yeah.
They started in Kansas, but Fred Koch eventually, you know, he'd go on to help Hitler build
some oil refineries.
Well, sure.
And then he started a crude oil interest in Duncan, Oklahoma called Rock Island Oil and
Refining Company.
It's just amazing.
Like in 2003, hearing Alex like, oh yeah, I heard about this big family that they fund
to the John Birch Society and they support Bush.
He doesn't know the name.
He doesn't know anything about this.
Unreal.
He's bathed in John Birch Society nonsense and he doesn't know the name of Fred Koch.
So infuriating.
Yeah.
And then, you know, you think maybe if Citizens United had gone another way, none of us would
be able to instantly pull Koch brothers names.
Wouldn't that be lovely?
Yeah.
I don't know.
I don't know if that's true, but certainly it made it worse.
I think it's really interesting that like, I'm, you know, obviously I'm fascinated by
particularly that era of anti-communist propaganda and sort of ideology.
And so the John Birch Society is something that looms large and like obviously I've looked
into it a bit and I know about the first meetings and the people and like, yeah, obviously Fred
Koch was one of the founding members.
Like, it's weird to me to think that Alex came from a family that clearly was Bertie.
Maybe not full on members, but associates of members.
And he doesn't, he doesn't understand like who the, who some of these players are.
I mean, weren't they supposed to be cells that weren't necessarily connected to each
other originally.
So it's not like they had a hero worship of their founding members.
No, but you would know.
You would think.
You would hope.
But then again, Fred Koch didn't stay in it for all that long.
Yeah.
He was too busy with the Nazis.
He's got shit to do.
But then again, the Koch brothers were pretty involved with like Ron Paul.
Yeah, that's true.
I don't know.
It's weird.
It's weird that he would, he'd have this non-awareness.
What an ignorant asshole.
How dare he tell me that he knows anything.
It does feel like he's not feigning ignorance.
He does seem like he's frustrated that he doesn't know the name of this big Birch family.
It's strange.
Wild.
Anyway, he gets another call.
This is where we learned that Saddam Hussein may be on a beach.
Hey Alex, my name is Nick.
I was in the water about 22 years.
Just some full information about Saddam Hussein.
On the 14th of this past month, the Gulf News out of Dubai and the Iranian News Service
both reported that the U.S. reached an agreement with Russia for $5 million cash in credit
to get Saddam and 100 of his closest followers out.
This past Thursday on Univision, one broadcast in the middle of the day said that Saddam
Hussein had been spotted in Cuba with his family.
Sounds about right.
Okay.
All right.
Yep.
Sounds about right.
He's probably in Cuba.
Yep.
That makes sense.
You know what I would do?
Possible other explanation.
Someone who looks like Saddam Hussein was seen in Cuba.
You know what I would do if I was Saddam?
Get closer to the United States.
Good idea.
That's a good plan.
He'll never look.
I'll take a boat from North Korea to Maine.
We have one last clip here because Alex takes another call, and this person is into the
Birch Society, and so there's a little bit more conversation about that.
I think this is kind of interesting.
First, let me say something about the John Birch Society.
I was a member when I lived in Utah.
I'm not a member now, but I do get the magazine, and they put out wonderful information.
So you're still a member.
I was going over some old ones the other day that go back into 98, and here they were telling
about this threat of the World Trade Towers being bombed, and this is all a connection
with Saddam Hussein, Osama bin Laden, and on and on and on.
And how the government's going to blame that for it.
Right.
But the one thing I want to make clear, and this is for everybody, there's people that
say things about Alex Jones and put out information about Alex Jones or John Stattmiller or somebody
else.
And this is a ploy.
I remember back in the 50s and 60s, the Communist Party put out a propaganda.
Divide and conquer.
Right.
And the same thing with MacArthur.
I even hear conservatives talk about MacArthurism as though that was something evil.
No, McCarthy was right.
No, he wouldn't do what the human wanted, so he's bad, yeah.
McCarthy was right.
Well, McCarthy was right.
The KGB files got released five years ago, and it turned out it was twice as bad than
he thought.
But it was okay when he said it was, hold on, let me say something.
Hold on a second, ma'am.
It was okay, ma'am, ma'am, it was okay when he said that it was just communist.
When he figured out that, he said, wait, the army runs the communists, our army's giving
them nukes and funding them, boom, he was out of there like that.
Go ahead.
So Alex has made up a fun story to try and pretend that Joseph McCarthy was right and
his insane communist witch hunt, but that's all just bullshit.
Yeah.
Also, I love the moment there where he almost yells at her.
Yeah, yeah, that is nice.
That's a really polite, angry Alex.
Yeah, yeah, that's better than now.
Mm-hmm.
Fuck off!
Yeah.
Look!
Buy my shit!
I would assume that those issues of the John Birch Society magazine that the caller's referring
to, I think they have to do with the other time the World Trade Center was bombed back
in 1993.
You would think.
That has something to do with that.
I've noticed that a lot of conspiracy thinkers tend to ignore that that happened because
it helps make sense of why people would have been talking about terrorists attacking the
World Trade Center before 9-11.
Yeah, it would be like, oh, so this guy already tried it?
It would make sense for him to give it another go if he failed the first time.
Yeah.
They need for these conversations to be devoid of the context of the first bombing because
otherwise it's like, yeah, of course.
Yeah.
That's a reasonable explanation for this.
I find this really weird, because Alex is talking about, like, okay, so this caller's
saying that there's a John Birch Society magazine from, like, 1998, it's talking about bombing
of the World Trade Center, and Alex is like, yeah, and how the government will blame bin
Laden.
Yep.
That's supposed to be his prediction.
Yeah.
So wait, now he's saying that the John Birch Society stuff from 1998 was making that prediction
that he made in 2001 that also he stole from Bill Cooper.
Yes.
Yeah.
He doesn't seem to be so eager to take credit as some kind of a prophetic person in terms
of this at this point.
Yeah.
I would imagine the reason that he didn't make it to the four-year university was he
couldn't keep himself from plagiarizing anything and everything in his sight.
Yeah, it's possible.
It feels like more of an individual at this point, though.
I'll say that.
It does.
That is true.
Yeah.
I was not-
I mean, despite the Rush Limbaugh impression, they're very clear.
Yeah.
Well, I remember at that time, my dad had all the Limbaugh books and I was inundated
with right-wing talk news radio, and I wasn't hearing this shit.
That's for sure.
I definitely wasn't hearing this.
Some of this is a little weirder, but also I'm fascinated by how some of it is so one-to-one
similar to the present, the way he deals with SARS, the way he's saying that they intentionally
released foot and mouth from port and down.
It's hauntingly similar.
Those who learn to exploit in the past refuse to change anything so they can continue exploiting
in the future, Dan.
So I have one last question for you.
What do you think about apples?
They're pretty good.
So what do you think about them apples?
That's the real question.
I'm fascinated.
I'm loving the past, and I can't wait to keep listening to this.
Yeah.
I can't wait to see how, as the Iraq war is clearly not over, how Alex deals with that.
The 2004 election, it's just nuts.
We haven't done monthly investigations for a long time.
I feel like this might be open-ended.
This could be forever.
Yes.
But be not afraid.
I will still also be keeping up on the present day, and I promise on our next episode we
will check in and see what Alex is up to, whatever his dumb ass is talking about in
the present.
No kidding.
See if it mirrors this.
I know.
Somehow.
We'll see.
But anyway, we'll be back.
Until then, we have a website.
Indeed we do.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yep.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at Knowledge Underscore Fight and at Go To Bed Jordan.
Yep.
We're also on Facebook.
We are.
iTunes.
And if you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work right now.
Yep.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I am super socialist Paul Wolfowitz.
Cindy in Kansas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.
I love you too.