N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Damn and Jordan, I am sweating
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledgefight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Shang, we are the bad guys, knowledgefight
Damn and Jordan, knowledgefight
Rattle her, rattle her, rattle her
Need, I need money, rattle her, rattle her
Andy in Kansas, Andy in, Andy in, stop it
Andy in, Andy in Kansas, Andy in, Andy in, it's time to pray
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan
I love your work
knowledgefight
knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight, I'm Dan
Um, Jordan
We're a couple dudes, I can sit around, drink novelty beverages
and talk just a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh, indeed we are, Dan
Jordan
Dan
Quick question for you
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, it might be the same as yours and that is
Oh, I bet it's not
Okay, well in that case, thank you to the Godawful Movies podcast
Oh yeah, yeah
Our episode came out with them on Tuesday
and it was a lot of fun to see the response that people had
I think we have a lot of crossover between audiences
and it was so fun hanging out and talking about a dumb
Chuck Norris fighting demons movie
It was a blast
I was so terrified when we recorded that
that none of it would make sense
Like, the plot doesn't make sense if you watch the movie
and then hearing the five of us try and
piece it together, yeah, no, no
I've never done a podcast where you just like
break down the plot of a movie before
Yeah, yeah
And so for me, I was very self-conscious of like
there's no connective tissue here, this does not make sense
Oh, but everybody seemed to enjoy it, so thanks to them
and if you haven't checked that out, you should give it a whirl
Yes, very much so
I gave it a little bit of a listen and
they told us many times, you know, like
hey, I'm just trying to move along
don't worry about it if you keep talking and we're both like
man, if you don't literally tell us to shut up
we're gonna keep talking
We can't stop
No, I was literally listening to that like
I missed at least a half hour of stuff that I wanted to put in there
Yeah, yeah, I know, that's definitely true
There were more thoughts
Yeah, we could have done so much longer
Could have been like one of our Rogan episodes
At a certain point, I was half expecting them to leave
and just be like, hey, you guys finish it out
Yeah, we'll be back
Yeah, yeah
So what about you, what's your bright spot?
My bright spot, Dan, I will guarantee it's not the same as yours
because it is
Opening Day Baseball, baby!
Okay, yeah, that is different
Yeah, that's different
I was gonna say you could guarantee because you already know what mine is
Yeah, well, obviously
So that's a stupid bet for me to take at that point
Well
Congratulations on the sticks
Yeah, Opening Day Baseball
Don't congratulate me, it's not like I'm getting my cup of coffee this year
You enjoy watching these guys get out there and play the game America's past time
I do, I do
Um
You know, I think the Ricketts family should have been burnt at the stake for many reasons
but what they're doing to the Cubs is now at least number three on the list
Who's looking good this year? What teams are in, who are you keeping your eye on other than the Cubs?
Uh, other than the Cubs? Well, I mean, I'm looking at Los Angeles
The LA Angels because Shohei Otonori is my favorite baseball player
Sure
By far, he can throw a 98 mile an hour fastball
He can hit 500 foot dingers, Dan
It doesn't get better than that
How are the Expos looking?
The Expos are looking dead, uh, non-existent
Uh
The Expos are looking like a Blockbuster franchise right now, how do you feel?
Uh oh, I gotta call my booking, I made some bad bets
Uh, well, you'll get there in 1999
Um, who's that, uh, is Johnny Damon still around?
He looking good this year?
What else you got?
I don't know
I want, I want more names from you
Albert Pujols?
Uh, actually Albert Pujols is on the Angels and he is still around
All my buddies used to love, uh, Pujols because he was on the, of course, he was on the St. Louis
He was on the Cardinals, yeah
And he had that weird stance, he would stand there real weird
Still does, still does
One of the best hitters in the history of the game
Yeah, he's very good
He seems like a good guy too, from everything I can tell, right?
Uh, yeah, that's what I've heard
I don't know
He seems like a nice dude
Seems like a, I don't know
Nobody's ever been, like, gone out of their way to be like, hey Jordan, have you heard how much of an asshole Albert Pujols is?
How's, uh, how's Roberto Clemente looking this year?
Not as good as you might hope
I've got bad news for you, Dan
Oh, no
So, Jordan, um, today we got an interesting episode to go over
As I promised, we're back in the present day
Indeed
So today we're going to be talking about March 30th and 31st, 2021
Blackjack
So what do you think about them apples?
Oh, no
He's thinking about, nah, it's not going to work
That bit's not going to, that's not going to fly
No, but I do love that drop
I have to use it for something
No, it is good
I think you can tell me, you can use it whenever you have something
shitty to say to me instead
How do you like them apples?
Exactly
Alright, Blackjack
Anyway, it's interesting, couple of days, infuriating in many ways
Kind of bizarre in another way
There's something that I think is really interesting
that I think bears talking about
but it also, Alex's position on it almost doesn't matter
So this is my way of, as is tradition, underselling what we're about to talk about
Right, right, right, right
In advance, this doesn't matter
Nope
But before we get down to business, let's do something that does matter
which is name some new wonks
Oh, that's a good idea
So first, I'm Dan and it's 2020
One Blackjack, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Next, Knowledge Fighting God Awful Movies is my kink
Give me more please, sirs, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Thank you
Next, William K.W. III, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you, Billy Kay
Thank you
Next, Spider Leadership, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, Spider Leadership
Thank you
About time they started pulling their weight around here
Looking at you, mercantile dogs and archaeologist cats
Yeah
Next, I sold Dan weed, not guns, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Did I say that someone sold me guns?
Was there a possibility?
No one sold me guns
No, was this like an old friend of yours in high school?
Maybe
Who were like, you had the opportunity and in the left hand I have a gun
I don't
And in the right hand I have some weed, you can only choose one
I don't recall that, I know that I have bought weed from a lot of people over the course of my life
And I do know that there was one person that I knew
I don't think it's this person, because I have no, I don't know
But there was one person that I knew who shall go nameless
Who did sell me weed for a while
And then later I found out that he was also selling guns
Oh
But I didn't know that at the time
Well, I think we know it now
I don't think that that's this person, it would be bizarre if it was
That would be bizarre
But anyway, thank you so much, you're a policy wonk
Are there any people who have been with the same weed dealer for like 30 years?
You know, like some people who are like, I just only go to this one store for my, like I'm a Kohl's person
Do you have like a, I'm a Kohl person
I wouldn't be surprised
I mean, you know, I think you have a bond that's formed
I think Kohl's gets arrested less
And that disrupts relationships sometimes
Their loyalty program is a little bit better
So finally, I'd like to say thank you to somebody who is now a technocrat
Thank you so much, Neve C. You are now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
Crikey mate, that's fantastic, have yourself a brew
How's your 401k doing, bro?
Alright, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this Watson, alright?
Let's just get down to business
We ain't making that money off that heroin
Why are you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large
I declare info war on you
Thank you so much, Neve
Yes, thank you very much, so much
Yeah, so Jordan, today we have a fun out of context drop
Alex is violent towards animals
Sure
And this is right in that line
Sometimes you gotta hit a mule upside the head with a 2x4
Whoa
That doesn't sound true
Sometimes you have to, sometimes you are left with no choice
I would like more context on the situation where I have no choice but to hit it with a 2x4
Well, if this wasn't an out of context drop, I could give you the entire context
Because Alex spends about 10 fucking minutes on this show
Talking about how sometimes if there's like a cow that's being eaten by fire ants and it's pregnant
And you gotta get it to safety, you gotta hit it with stuff in order to get it to move
I was gonna go with pure zombie situation
But I will accept that if there is a cow being eaten by fire ants
You need to get this cow away from the fire ants
You gotta hit it with a board
Sure
And the liberals would tell you, no, don't hit it with a board
I'm still gonna go with maybe try getting rid of the fire ants first
Maybe try a hose
He spends probably two segments talking about that
That seems right
It's outrageous
Does he have enough time to get to the big news?
No
Oh, okay
So here we start on the 30th and I'm gonna give you a spoiler in advance
I turned this episode off
It got very boring
But here's how it starts
Wow, it is official mainstream news
That the COVID lockdowns are designed to make us live in our houses and be prisoners
To quote, save the earth from carbon
You know, Debo said it years ago
They had a plan a few months ago
They said how great the lockdowns are, have them permanently to save the earth
Have robots deliver us all our food, making us obsolete, depopulating
Sure
But now the Wall Street Journal, the New York Times, the Associated Press
Without me even looking today
Wait, what?
Just everywhere are saying
What?
We need to be prisoners and never leave our homes again
I mean, they are just going for full Stockholm syndrome
I was like, oh, wow
How could this not have turned out to be a banger of an episode, Dan?
I was like, wow, this is gonna be something he's really gonna need to substantiate
Without even looking, I saw these things that didn't happen
How amazing is that, Dan?
I think that one of the things about our show that I enjoy is that you'd hear something like that
And most people would be like, no, it didn't
Yeah
I'll dig into things, but today I just felt like, no, no
The media did not say, did not announce that they want you to be prisoners in your home
I'm fine, we've been over this territory so many times that this is just one I'm gonna be like, no
Absolutely not, go fuck yourself
Listen, I give you more than the benefit of the debt, and you have broken me, sir
I don't feel broken, I just don't care
I'm gonna choose my battles, and this is one I'm just gonna be like
Wise, that's wise
Tell me what you're talking about, and then maybe we'll get into it, but probably not
Because I know the only citation that he ends up giving in the first 40 minutes of the show
Is a fucking editorial that doesn't say what he says it says
There's a problem with that
So I don't care
Anyway, this is where we get really misogynistic
Sure
You heard him bring up Stockholm Syndrome there
I thought it was the moment he started speaking is when we get really misogynistic, but here we go
Whoo-nelly
They are just going for full Stockholm Syndrome takeover
Because they know at least 30% of the public, mainly women, will go under Stockholm Syndrome
Because it's so authoritarian, they can't believe it's actually happening
And they are going to submit to the tyranny, nothing against women
But it's known in every psychological study in Rome and Babylon that
When an army would take over the city
Most of the women within minutes would start fighting for the enemy
As soon as it was clear that the enemy had taken over
And they would rat out their husbands, rat out their children, help execute them
If they thought it was for the good of the community
That's why when the country is conquered or the place is conquered
You don't kill the women
That's why, who was the house slave in Rome?
In Africa, who were the house slaves?
Africans had as many slaves as anybody
You brought women in the house
You kept the men out in the fields
And that's the system
Wow, that's something else, man
I don't even know where that begins
Yeah, it's a lot of thoughts and a lot of them are dumb
Okay, okay, alright
So then, okay, okay?
Mm-hmm
Okay, Dan, we have historical records
Of so many cities that were conquered
We have psychological studies from Rome
Yes, we've got so many psychological studies, double blind studies
Rome did a lot of double blind studies back then
Whenever invading armies will show up
Women will immediately start fighting, within minutes
Start fighting for the enemy
Women are traitors
I'm confused as to whether or not he knows the
Severe number of underground, boy, I don't know
Resistance movements that were started, helmed
Almost like a locomotive, maybe, that went underground
I think there's one big one that it's hard to put back
So first thing to clear up, Stockholm Syndrome, as Alex understands it, isn't real
It's something that's depicted in dramatic movies a lot
But in terms of real life instances of someone exhibiting the signs of Stockholm Syndrome
It's exceedingly rare to find a real case
Yeah, what it really is, is that the cops are bad and reasonable people are like
Oh yeah, you guys are bad
And you can find some similarities to the behaviour within domestically violent situations
Some people will make those parallels, but that's not what we're talking about
That's not what the depiction of Stockholm Syndrome is
Second, the image of history that Alex is presenting is also not real
In movies, perhaps, invading groups don't kill women when they killed all the men in a particular town
But that's not how things have gone generally
No, they killed all the women, it wasn't hard
Always, but sometimes, a lot of the time
And the exception generally is when these invading groups would take the women as property
After conquering a particular group
And it wasn't because these women just decided it would be a good idea to join the other team
Oh shit, now it's time to be property!
Guys, it's time, woo!
Let's get enslaved!
Let's do it, concubine me, baby!
Also, it may be the case that most depictions of persons enslaved inside households in the media are often women
But that's also historically not something that was universal
For instance, William Wells Brown and Lewis Clark are both examples of enslaved persons in the American South
Who were men whose duties were in the house
Both of whom wrote books about their experience that Alex could learn from, if he'd like
Alex's understanding of history is based almost entirely on movies and vague feelings he's gotten about history from media
Literally nothing he's saying is based on reality at all, but it feels like it if you just kind of assume fiction and reality are the same
And that's all that's going on here, man, and it is grim, his vision of what, like, that's a painfully chauvinistic view of
Yeah, yeah, you know, and it's not like, you know, movies aren't entertaining and stuff
But I think the fact that most movies have been written by white men over the years has probably ruined a bit of our good historical interpretation
I think that might have something to do with his ridiculous beliefs
Could be, could be, could be, you know, but no, no, Aaron Zurgen's good, yeah, never mind
Alex has this deep historical knowledge, and I shouldn't be poo-pooing him so much because, like, I mean, he's got a stack of papers
I have a stack of just unbelievable COVID-19 news, but just look at this stack, ladies and gentlemen
Look at this that dovetails with it
Your radio listener, you can just search into anything I'm saying and pull it up, what the crew does
Look at this, AP, Dear Normal, were you really that great in the first place? By a Sophie Rosenbaum, this reads like the darkest satire ever written
So this is nonsense, and we'll get to this here in a second, but here is Alex sort of talking about the editorial a little bit
But it's real, and I'm gonna take the time out, even though this is four nightmare pages of evil, and I'm gonna read the damn thing on air, bottom of the hour
And it says, we're gonna lock you in your house, and you're gonna love it, and you're only gonna leave when we say you can, and it's not about the COVID, it's about the Earth
Doesn't say any of those things
That sounds right
This is an article that's an editorial presenting an opinion held by this writer
Alex is getting mad at an editorial and pretending that it somehow is the globalist admitting that they don't want anything to go back to normal, and it's all about climate, COVID's not even real
Furthermore, it was not addressed to Alex
No, it was addressed to Normal
Yeah, he's very abnormal
So Alex has nothing to do with this
If you read this editorial, it's not dark satire, and it's not advocating that we stay in lockdown forever
It's this writer expressing that as the world goes back to what we're looking at as normal, we run the risk of not living as ambitiously as we can
A better world is possible, and the urge for things to go back to some idea of normal might get in the way of achieving things that, you know, are good
From the article, quote, without normal, the path forward is more open, the opportunity is perhaps broader
What if there's a whole lot of amazing that stands to be lost if normal returns?
What if instead of banking on normalcy, we focused on that one-of-a-kind ability to adapt and evolve?
Maybe that's the way forward, instead of simply reconciling with what was and trying to recreate something that's already had its day
It's an interesting position that this author brings up, and it's not a unique perspective in terms of things that I've read, certainly
Yeah, yeah
But it's absolutely not what Alex is lying about, but it is a good headline for him to riff off of
Sure, yeah, yeah
But it's just nonsense, and if he's read it, this is embarrassing for him to be worked up about it
He has absolutely not read it
Yeah
Not a chance
Did he read it on air?
I don't know, probably, maybe after I turned it off
I told you, I turned off this episode
That's fair, that is fair
And part of the reason that I turned off this episode was, like, that misogyny at the beginning was pretty wild
That's astonishing
Yeah
But, because it's not a direct attack, you know, we're so used to misogyny being directed at women in the present
But to create a weird fictional, like, Adam and Eve story out of all women throughout history when being conquered
Well, all psychological studies have shown that within minutes they start fighting for the enemy
See, I feel like this is not true
This is just not true
What psychol-
Hmm, how would you even take that psychol-
Is there a psychologist that's in there on the ground, like, oh shit, somebody just got conquered, we gotta get there fast
Otherwise they're gonna turn before we've studied it properly
I don't know
But it was kind of interesting in a, you know, like, oh, you seem weird today
And I kind of got interested in, like, oh, is this gonna continue?
And it didn't, and it just became this aggressively long, protracted, boring stretch of immigrant bashing
Sure
In such a way that really, really is, like, unacceptable
Un-okay, yeah
And I'll play a little clip and then, you know, we'll sort of discuss why I needed to turn this off
And then we saw a Daily Caller report saying, oh, there are hundreds of illegals with their children and others
And unaccompanied children at the airport in South Texas
Loading onto planes with no ID
Loading onto planes with bags of cash and envelopes of cash
Controlled by the Democratic Party being sent all over the United States to disappear into God knows what
Encounterment of federal and state law, which Biden hadn't signed an executive order
They could be overturned by courts, they haven't changed the federal law
This is all lawlessness
So he goes on and just on and on, beating up and saying, like, just horrendous things
About anybody who may be an immigrant
And, you know, the effect of this isn't something that is positive
It's not something that's even interesting
This is just an incitement
Yeah
I think when he's talking about these people who are alleged to be undocumented folks
Who are being given bags of money and then sent to disappear into the-
That's only going to make the audience suspicious of everybody that they see
That they might deem to be possibly an immigrant who might have a bag of cash
And just disappeared in the middle of America
If he said-
It's irresponsible as hell
Yeah, if he said Jew, we'd just be like, oh, okay, cool, you're a Nazi, now stop speaking forever
Because that's what he's- he's doing that
He's Nazi-ing
It's not something that can really be interestingly discussed outside of rebuke
Yeah
It's not something that I have much to bring to the table other than, fuck this, this is unacceptable
We've talked a ton about, like, specific narratives and things that he deploys against, you know, immigrant populations and what have you
But this was just, like, it just should be turned off
Yeah
It's not even, like, I don't know how else to say it
We should have a drop that's just a big, like, stamp sound and then it says Protocols of the Elders of Zion
And then we just move on, like, yup, boom
And so there was one more thing that I heard, and this is, like, I was in that place
And I think I still needed something else to kick me over the, like, turn this off
And this is where I turned it off
And then the FBI announces two days ago they're waiving all background checks for the people at the facilities and the foster homes where they're sent
So they're coming in, no ID, not with their parents in many cases, as young as two years old
They're being put on buses and airplanes and flown to be picked up by random people and never to be seen again
But then separately you'll hear National Amber Alert, 12-year-old girl grabbed out of her backyard
Massive man hut shuts down two counties as they search the grid for the kidnapper
But then you've got massive death, massive numbers of dead women and children found by the thousands on the border
Look it up, and it's just, oh, that's not going to be a news item, that's not going to be a story
So here's the headline right here, out of town hall, FBI waives background check requirements for those housing unaccompanied minors
So Alex is talking about people at emergency intake centers, the FBI waived part of the background check that needs to be done for people working at those centers
He's lying about this story, but what he brings up is still an actual issue
And that's where also I feel really like I hate him, because this is a real issue
Yeah, yeah, yeah
And I'm not going to agree with him, but I'm also not going to disagree fully, but he is still lying
Right, right, right, right
So it's true that the FBI has waived fingerprint-based background checks for people who are being employed to work at emergency intake sites run by the Department of Health and Human Services
That is not a good thing, and I don't support that, but it is not what Alex is suggesting
This doesn't apply to people who are taking people into foster care, it's just for people who work at those sites who are quote
Supervised by federal employees or others who have passed fingerprint-based background checks
Again, not what I would say is a great idea, but it's not what Alex is saying
Also, Alex is claiming that they've waived all background checks for these individuals, which is not true
They still have to pass public records background checks, but they're not using fingerprinting
The reason to do this is to expedite the process, which makes some sense, but again, I would probably prefer that they err on the side of caution
Sure
I was really curious about this story, so I dug around a little more and I found this story in the Associated Press
Quote, US waived FBI checks on staff at growing teen migrant camp
That story was from November 2018 under Trump
Beyond the background checks waiver, Trump also reduced the access to mental health professionals for people at the camp, which was a mess
Even worse, in December 2018, the AP reported on news from an emergency detention center in Florida called Homestead
Where quote, the staff isn't being screened for child abuse and neglect at the Miami-based emergency detention center
Alex wasn't mad about any of these things because Trump's administration was doing it, and there was no ability to score points off it
He doesn't care about the well-being of immigrants, and when it's a Democrat president in charge
He just uses the mismanagement of immigration as a prop to attack his enemies
When his hero Trump is the one mistreating these people, Alex isn't okay with it, he supports it
And I don't want to bring these cases or these instances up of Trump and his administration doing this as a what about thing
I absolutely don't want to do that, and I'm not trying to score points on Alex
Wow, there's no point in, I mean, not, you know
I'm discussing my frustration with like, this is a problem and it's still a problem
It's not something that is okay now because Biden is in charge, we need better solutions to these things
Yeah, no, it's still monstrous
Yes, and the FBI background check thing, the aspect of it, I understand the explanation that's being given
I'm not sure that explanation is acceptable
Right
I don't know, but I would be, I would have that exact same response in Trump's instance and now
Yeah
And it's just offensive to see Alex spend half an hour demonizing immigrants in such a way
that it stands to potentially put people in danger and then to use them and mismanagement of
immigration intake centers like this as a prop for him to use to attack Democrats
No, I absolutely don't care what face or what party affiliation you have
If I am anywhere near those people, I was screaming their faces
This is the best you fucking have, this is what you're gonna do
Yeah
Fuck off
And so, you know, I just got kind of fed up and I turned it off
So now we'll jump to the 31st
Because I thought like, there's probably more interesting stuff to talk about
We've heard him talk about this kind of thing a lot
Sure
It's very kind of worn out territory for Alex
Totally
So there is some news and thankfully Alex has got some big bombshells on the 31st
Okay, all right
Working on the weekend like usual, down in the deep end like usual
Wow, we're in the center of the zeitgeist
I barely just slid into my chair here because we've got so many big breaking news stories
that we're working on right now that are so exclusive and so important
Big bombshells
Okay
So exclusive
Big old bombshells
So exclusive, so I assume, and when he says so exclusive
Uh huh
I put this story at between one and six years old
No, it's current
Okay
I can tell you I've talked to the highest levels of the media food chain about the congressman Matt
Gates situation, I've also talked to his good personal longtime friend and confidant Roger Stone
I have made a lot of phone calls and ascertained exactly what's going on with the whole Matt Gates
extortion deep state takeover, Roger Stone joins us coming up in the second hour today
and he's still getting all the details together right now but it definitely Matt Gates is telling
the truth
This is weird
Yeah, Roger Stone's coming on to talk about a sex trafficking incident he's definitely
never engaged in in his life before
It broke this weekend that the justice department began investigating representative Matt Gates
about the possibility that he had engaged in a sexual relationship with a 17 year old girl
and possibly had paid her to travel or paid to travel with her which would possibly constitute
sex trafficking
Yeah
Gates claims that this is part of an elaborate plan to extort him and as far as I'm concerned
I hate Matt Gates and I think he's a real piece of political shit but I need to see
more about this investigation before I can come to any conclusions on the matter
The claimed actions are too severe and I don't want to do a disservice to the alleged crime
by using an accusation to score points against a politician I don't like
Totally
According to the New York Times this investigation began under the Trump administration so it's
going to be hard to allege this is a plot from the left
Deep state
It's said that this has to do with a Florida politician who had been an ally of Gates's
named Joel Greenberg who is the former tax collector of Seminole County
This guy is currently facing charges quote including sex trafficking of a child and
financially supporting people in exchange for sex at least one of whom was an underage girl
We will see what happens with this as more information comes out but even if he's telling
the truth and this is all part of an extortion plot against him Matt Gates is still a pile
of garbage
Also like if it is an elaborate plan I really hope that whoever is doing this
extortion against him is arrested
Yeah
The thing that I don't want is neither of these things to get prosecuted
I am fine with whatever crime is handled here
Some crime is the problem
Something's up and you got
Yeah and I don't need an extra layer of crime to hate the shit out of Matt Gates
Right
If he's guilty of a crime then I hope he's prosecuted and taken care of
But I'm gonna hate him either way Dan
And we'll see
Also Roger might not be the best source of information for Alex on this one since he's
been photographed at Mar-a-Lago with Gates and Joel Greenberg
Come on what's a little sex trafficking between friends
And according to the Times websites run by Roger's associates had published articles
favorable about Greenberg's candidacy for tax collector
Shocking
This is a mess
The tangled web but we'll see
Anyway there's other news
We lost Rush Limbaugh not too long ago
Hooray
And oh no
We had another tragedy befall the right wing
Oh no
I've got so much to cover G. Gordon Liddy died a great guy
Great patriot, great talk show host, great American
Really?
The FBI was like him today we wouldn't be in this problem
That we're in with these communists and globalists we've got that
Yikes
Doesn't eulogize him much
Can't just mentions G. Gordon Liddy's dead wishes the FBI was more like him
Boo
Oooh big pass although I think maybe our problem is the FBI is a lot like him
Yep
Yeah
So Alex has one of his big narratives on this episode is that a lot of the prosecutions against
people who broke into the Capitol and stormed everywhere and what have you
A lot of them are falling apart
Oh that was years ago though the right wing has moved on from that we're talking about
culture war stuff Dan we don't need to worry about that because that happened years ago
Well we got to turn around and mop it up a little bit
Okay
And now the prosecutions are falling apart and there's a Politico article that Alex can't
seem to find that goes over this
I mean we are witnessing incredibly historic times you know in fact guys there's an Infowars
article about the case falling apart and feds shocked that they're gonna have to drop all
the cases but I actually want the Politico article that's linked in that I forgot to
tell you about that so give me that Politico article that they're gonna have to not get
jail times these people on the left's totally panicking because I can't find that now in
my stack and I just had it
People aren't panicking this Politico article does talk about how it might be a bad look
for you know Biden's administration to end up having to not prosecute or give plea deals
to a lot of the people who weren't the insiders they weren't the people who were you know
actually planning violence
So I understand that and I think that you know in terms of reality that kind of makes
sense and as somebody who isn't in favor of over incarceration I do understand that and
I kind of don't think it would be in society's greater interest to lock up everybody who
went into the Capitol in the same way that I think that you know drug offenders should
be released from prison
Right right I think I think that there should be less people in prison
Yeah I mean I ultimately functionally it's like when you're going after the fucking mafia
like cool you arrested a bunch of fucking low level meatheads who are going around looking
for protection money it doesn't matter it doesn't do anything we're not doing anything
to the people who fucking orchestrated it and incited it
So I kind of don't give a shit about these people at all
Well the people who you know might have just been along and went in I can completely understand
the idea of like getting probation or time served or something if you've been held without
bail yeah I don't know but I understand that and I think that maybe it would be unsatisfying
to some like folks who are trying to maybe run for office on retribution
Sure sure sure sure um but that doesn't mean that people who are like the people who planned
the the stuff like yeah yeah keepers and totally they're not gonna get like sentences
No you planned it yeah that's the part that's the people who are coordinating and like yeah
Stuart Rhodes's friends yeah they're still in deep shit
That's what I'm saying I just don't care about because all too all too many of those people
are really borderline just infected with this terrifying brain virus that has destroyed them
through right-wing propaganda since they were fucking six years old right yeah and Alex is
trying to pretend that this is everybody even all the oath keepers and stuff who had like
communications plans and no Alex's buddies are going down he's trying to pretend that like this
Politico article is about everybody sure and it's not it's mostly about people who are just like
what are you gonna do they just walked in yes it's trespassing yeah but what are you gonna give them
six months in prison for that is that right yeah that and and I think that that's a sensible
conversation to have sure in terms of like what what gives us the best outcome possible as a
society and well I mean as a society does giving somebody who uh you know passively stormed the
Capitol six months do anything for the problem probably not it could make things worse yeah it
doesn't like to act as a deterrent no and now I wish that we would treat all offenders with the
same kind of uh I think that's kind of the bigger issue yeah that is the problem is not uh the
treatment it's the unequal treatment beyond all recognition here here yeah yeah so apparently one
of Elon Musk's rockets blew up um but hey man still don't care about Elon Musk don't call it
a little bit you can't call him a loser because he's trying he is a loser though and this is this
is interesting Alex seems to be taking comments about Elon Musk a little personally another
SpaceX spaceship prototype explodes during high altitude flight test and the media is calling him
a loser as usual no uh the losers are the people that point their fingers at people that are doers
and say that we're the losers no you are the losers so Alex is lumping himself in with Elon
Musk and saying the people who criticize the doers like me and Elon Musk sure they're the losers no
what I want to do is put myself in the same sentence as somebody whose wealth is based
entirely upon apartheid Dan that's what I want to do people talk about how me and Elon Musk
are losers just because we exploited a population to make untold amounts of wealth and then the
moment it looked like it was going to go bad for us we ran away to the United States face
no punishment for our crimes whatsoever and then got even more wealthy based off of stock
manipulation for no fucking reason I mean to be fair like like Alex used to hang out with Bob
Chapman who made all his money on like that's what I'm saying you gotta defend people who
run apartheid scams lived in Rhodesia yeah exactly yeah oh boy yeah so we get to defending Matt
Gates now and it's interesting because the only way that Alex can ever do these things is like
revealing he himself committed a crime no just pointing to other people but he's built up as
villains totally okay let me break this down for you if congressman Matt Gates son of a big
successful billionaire wasn't well spoken wasn't pro-constitution didn't have courage wasn't a
fighter I would not give a damn about him he'd like an old shoe I'd throw it away and if any
evidence of him screwing kids came out I would absolutely come out against him and say he should
be put in prison but he's not just Scarborough found with a dead girl in his office with their
brains bashed out who then is a good globalist who gets a show on msnbc with the daughter of a
famous war criminal Zbigniew Brzezinski Mika yeah so there's like ah yeah he's not Joe Scarborough
let's lie about his his past yeah it's it's it's weird because I don't know what that has to do
with oh it doesn't have anything to do with this no no no it seems like that's the strategy is
just distract yeah red red sheet over here have the bowl the bowl that is the audience's attention
charge over there despite the fact that of his descriptions of people who would drink adrenochrome
the only difference so far in description between Gates and everybody else is just an R
next to his name yeah he's the son of a billionaire he's in the government he's but it's also like
he's a weird Republican exactly it's not just that he's a Republican he is weird yeah yeah
he's an asshole yep so Alex lies a little bit about the allegations uh and man it's one thing
for Alex to take insults against Elon Musk personally sure that's that's one thing right
Alex seems to be taking this a little personally that sounds right too trying to claim there were
women saying they were 25 years ago who were really 17 at a party that he was at is not enough
for me to turn against Gates especially when the Democratic party's doing this and especially
I'll reveal for the first time here I went to the FBI a few years ago when somebody tried to
extort me who I hadn't had sex with and I talked to the experts I said you got to go report it
I once said hey I'm being extorted here's the here's the text messages
they had five agents in the room I mean let me tell you try to extort my ass I know the FBI's
corrupt point is I go right to them so it's on record that you tried to set me up you tried to
let me tell you they got people they got the media will give people money to say anything
they paid people twenty thousand dollars to say I walked around the office and grabbed a goldfish
out of a fish tank at the office and ate it this is a reference to Josh Owen's article from 2019
in the New York Times in the article Josh doesn't allege that Alex ate a goldfish that's the fake
version of the claim that Alex uses as a straw man to not talk about the actual complaint
from the article quote once a co-worker stopped by the office with a pet fish he was taking home
to his niece it swam in circles in a small transparent bag when Alex saw the bag balanced
upright on a desk in the conference room he emptied into a garbage can I don't know if
Josh's claim is accurate or not but it's very clear that Alex is making this claim that Josh
was paid twenty thousand dollars by the New York Times to say this about Alex the reason Alex is
using the specific of quote eating a goldfish is so he's less likely to get in trouble if Josh were
to demand Alex prove that the Times paid him to say what he did Alex could then pretend he was
talking about a different claim made about him but it's very clear this narrative is the one
that he's built in response to Josh's article if I were Josh Owens I would probably threaten
to sue Alex for this yeah that'd be worthwhile yeah I don't know I don't know if Josh Owens is
a public figure I don't know what Alex has no ability to demonstrate that Josh got paid to lie
about him or to say anything about him this this seems like slander quite frankly and I think it's
clearly malicious in intent totally absolutely this person said something I don't like
and so I will say that they were paid to say it Alex saying hey how are you sounds malicious in
intent there's no middle ground so apparently Alex got extorted sure sure sure sure sure sure sure
he's he's defending Matt Gaetz a little bit like he's about to say what's next are we
going to investigate everybody who's did exactly what but not that I didn't do it
you know it's it's interesting the way that Alex decides to do this defense too because his defense
seems to be like hey man Gaetz likes to party that's what I was thinking it would be but I've
made some calls and uh what you're hearing about Gaetz is pure bull he doesn't even know if he
from wild parties he was at over the years if he doesn't know who this woman is um and I had the
same damn thing is that there's 30 people at it you don't even kiss anybody and then you got
somebody saying you give me a hundred thousand dollars or I'm gonna say what you did to me and
I'm like hey FBI will speed dial hey I'm coming in right now but I'm telling you man this is what
happens when you're successful and you're famous and it's crap you try to extort me
I'm gonna try to get the FBI arrest your ass because it's not true ladies and gentlemen
you're supposed to be talking about Matt Gaetz why do you keep talking about yourself you keep
talking about you an awful lot an awful lot also do not sell me on you being a tough guy
ever again I'm gonna call the FBI I've got them on speed dial also I'm a revolutionary who's
fighting against the American government well I think it's an interesting approach to be like
Matt Gaetz goes to wild parties and he doesn't remember who's gonna remember who you fucked
come on you go to the party you fuck it's not a names thing then it's really strange
I just I think that on the one hand it's a strange defense of something that I don't know if anybody
can know what the reality is about the investigation at this point at these parties
you go and then Matt Gaetz puts on his eyed wide shut mask and then you don't know who's there
it's weird but I think the reason that I'm most interested in it is it just keeps coming back to
Alex like he keeps bringing himself back up as like there's a proxy that he feels as almost as
if there's some sort of lingering guilt somewhere I don't know about that but I it's just weird it's
just weird anyway Alex wants to give Gaetz some advice there is so much more that we're going to
be discussing when we get into Matt Gaetz and we're going to use this to make it about the
Clintons and to make this about Bill Gaetz and the minute Matt Gaetz talks about Bill Gaetz
and the minute he talks about Epstein they're going to drop this like a hot hand grenade
I don't know I don't know if that's true um I do think later on Alex lays out like what he's saying
and it's like you know what Gaetz needs to be like talk about Bill Gaetz but you got the wrong Gaetz
ah you get it how fun who's the new Gaetz gate yeah and so Alex also even lays out that he's
like Bill Gaetz runs the media he controls all this sure if Matt Gaetz starts talking about
Bill Gaetz he'll call off the dogs oh boy what I am I am really excited to see just how fast and
how brutal the right wing machine will destroy Gaetz the moment he threatens the grift like the
whenever he was talking to Tucker on that interview and he's like you know you know
Tucker how you've done this too uh it's like uh oh man you're going to be destroyed if you think
that you're gonna get loyalty gates you are making the same mistake a lot of you idiots make yeah
you're gonna end up burning like the bridge with Tucker and you'll be left hanging out with Roger
and Alex yep oh yeah yeah it's gonna be brutal and it's gonna be fast yeah it's kind of convenient I
think I read a headline the other day that he like before all this came out that he was planning
on possibly retiring from congress yeah he's gonna make a move you know nothing interesting
is gonna happen in between that article and when he moves to Newsmax I'm sure of it OAN probably
okay um so in this next clip uh we get Alex bestowing uh the mantle of the future of the
GOP on somebody and you'd be hard-pressed and surprised to find out that it is not Matt Gaetz
oh okay after all of this oh surprising no we have a new leader okay so here he is Marjorie
Taylor Greene the future of the Republican party voted in 75 of the vote on vaccine passports
talking about Hillary's religion and Biden's religion being the mark of the beast I kind of
do agree with Alex though that she is the future of the GOP yeah she is absolutely going to be one
of their elder statesmen uh screeching into the atmosphere upon her babel tower as the rest of
the world burns around her Alex takes this to be like a a good thing whereas I would say it's a
cautionary statement to say that she's the future of the GOP I would I would argue that's that's
probably a correct assessment of the biggest problem any people have ever had so we get to
talking a little bit more about Ms. Greene uh and here's what Alex has to say they have a perfect
example of why they hate Marjorie Taylor Greene she's dumb she's a listener of this show she's
mean she saw her others and they're educated about how the world works and they can see it
themselves and they see the corporate communism how they've created monopolies for themselves
and now the big corporations want tyranny for all the rest of us and they're using
classical forms of tyranny with technocracy to dominate us now the republicans are told oh be
afraid of her stay away from her because if they adopt what she's saying when she won by 75
percentage points the highest record in years for a republican to be elected to congress the
past record was like 69 she topped that by six points what was she saying there's a new world
order a chai comm takeover corporate communism they're coming for your guns they're destroying
the border they're the enemy let's do something that's what you do when you're under attack
i definitely think Alex could be right that Marjorie Taylor Greene listens to info wars
of the times he said that about elected officials this is the first time i'm not gonna argue with
yeah no that sounds right that said Alex is completely making up everything he just said
about her election win first let's remember that she was running essentially unopposed since her
opponent had withdrawn from the race prior to the election Alex is claiming that she won by a record
margin because he wants to create the impression that she was just saying info wars stuff and that
stuff is so popular that it wins elections by record amounts so everyone should adopt the most
popular stuff which is info wars stuff this is something that he is pulling out of thin air
uh green won her race 74.7 percent to uh 25.3 percent she didn't win by 75 percentage points
as Alex is claiming he just doesn't know the actual details or doesn't care to be accurate
that's fine though since i think you could be generous and assume he just meant that she won
with 75 i would say that's probably what he's close enough and i don't expect him to actually
know what he's talking about or be accurate yeah what's more egregious is him trying to say that
the previous record for republican running for congress had just been 69 margin or the vote who
knows yeah either it's completely insane just in the 2020 election for the u.s house in florida's
second district neil dunn won a seat against independent kim o'connor by a 97.9 to 2.1
percent difference that's a margin of 95.8 percent far higher than margery taylor green's margin
that's like if he ran against a half-finished game of hangman green's official margin of victory was
49.4 percent which is the 18th highest margin of victory among republican house election winners
hey that's not bad hang your head high you know nothing wrong with that sure left it all out on
the field alex desperately craves uh being seen as smart and having a ton of information at his
disposal but in order to create that perception he generally just makes shit up knowing that no
one listening will even care he'll probably just believe him it's because he's a con man yeah that
would be why also just because it's fun in the 2018 election republican tom graves won the same
district seat that green did with 76.5 of the vote which is more than she got yeah his opponent
received 23.5 of the vote so that means his total vote and his margin of victory were both higher
than margery taylor green's were she's actually less popular than the previous republican who
won that house seat that is the future of the republican party and it's what you get when you
use infowars that would happen yeah yeah yeah we should kill half of the constituents is usually
less popular than you might expect half of the constituents are gonna have a problem with that
yeah the other half usually so uh we get back to defending matt gates and it just does seem to be
like dude parties man come on roger stone is gonna have the inside scoop i've got from my angles
my sources that talk to gates gates has been on the show but i haven't talked to him in years
and uh we got a pretty good picture of what happened and what's unfolding this is deep
state globalist extortion uh is he a playboy was he at some parties with wild girls years ago
um maybe he truthfully does not remember or does not know but this is extortion this is a dirty
trick okay this is not strong i i would say i would say that's uh that's a road to conviction
if that's your defense hey i got drunk and partied i don't remember yeah i would say
that i went into this episode like the the sort of the way that i explained it like i don't know
enough about this case i read the times article i read what the people who are you know the sources
who are familiar with the investigation sure uh we're saying and we'll wait and see what comes
out of this sure i don't know like yeah yeah yeah the more i listen to this episode the more i'm
like what are you doing this is a terrible defense if this is your damage control like spin that
spin that you're doing i gotta think he killed people at those parties like yeah yeah i don't i
feel like he's trying to soften the blow of something worse that's how it feels yeah and
i don't know if that's just because it's how alex like operates or or what look have you ever seen
the movie bachelor party he went to one donkey show so not that big a deal and that like this
is this is like don't don't let alex anywhere near the court if if this happens your honor
it doesn't matter if he doesn't remember your honor i uh would like to say well i made some
calls well i actually got some calls and i made some calls people that know gates well
some big big big people and they said no gates is a playboy gates doesn't like underage women gates
has never hid this that he's single and young uh and he's not even he doesn't even know if any of
this is true he doesn't didn't fly with some underage woman that's made up this is a shakedown
but the question is do they have some woman who can claim that well she was younger now she's you
know 20 something that she went out with him three years ago uh but but definitely he went to the fbi
definitely it's a shakedown um so you're saying that he might have dated a 17 year old a few years
ago that is kind of what he's saying isn't it it's not specifically what he's saying
oh can you call a character witness for the prosecution and tell him to defend
this is a mess man hey hey alex we want you to really defend the shit out of matt gates
that's how confident we are that you're right alex we're gonna put you as the prosecution
yeah that's how we're tying one hand behind our back alex hey look fucking dated a 17 year old
three years ago she's 20 now come on that's the same thing as being 20 back then it's matt he
doesn't remember what what in the god's name is holy shit let's see if roger can do better
what is the inside poo-poo
back i mean if you had to name the single most effective uh member of the house in terms of
fighting for the america first agenda it would have to be matt gates it's not insolent incidental
that right here on this show only weeks ago i mentioned him very realistically as a presidential
contender so this is a search and destroy mission i know matt gates to be a person of extraordinary
integrity he was a playboy coming from you that means a lot to a wonderful woman ginger who i've
met several times they're very much in love this is not the matt gates that i know this is a
cheap political trick this is an effort to derail his career folks don't know this but
matt gates his family is among the wealthiest families in florida therefore the yes that makes
it less suspicious blackmail is a very realistic one i'm getting so suspicious the more this goes
suspicious why are they doing this they don't have to they don't they don't their audience does not
demand it alex could have legitimately just said this is all bullshit hey matt gates is he's come
out on tucker and he said that he's being set up see let's move forward done now let's get to the
big news of the day why are they doing this i'm not going to give this story the time that they
want me to that's how integrity i spent over an hour on it yeah absolutely wow that broj ban
the only thing worse than having alex defend me in court would be having roger defend me in court
there's nothing wrong with it i'm roger stone i've done it all these two unsavory fucks like
being like yeah he's great makes me think this person is not great and i understand that maybe
that's that's a bias of mine yeah you know not everybody who's beloved by villains is a villain
is a villain themselves sure sure i mean if i was going to uh put money on it i mean i would say
that the fbi should get some text records and i would imagine the moment that new york time story
came out roger stone got a text saying i did it what do i do that would be the most likely
situation for me so um the the narrative now becomes with roger on board um that they're
they're trying to get rid of gates because he's the heir apparent to trump sure in the 2024
election basically the guy has enormous cojones he's got huge courage you know usually when you're
young and you first get to congress they tell you to to us oh yeah he has incredible charisma he's
super smart definitely they sense the alpha male they're scared yeah because he has many the same
traits as trump he's audacious he's bold he's a brawler they don't want to take another beating
like they took in 2016 so this is kind of what they're doing i think they see their neck i i
think the the sense that i get like it's still weird they're trying to brett kavanagh this
yeah perhaps but i think it's even more than that yeah i i think that they feel an absence of their
uh sort of i idol basically sure there isn't a figurehead uh for them to coalesce around and i
think that they're feeling the pressure of that there's a crunch that trump is absent in terms of
being there um you know they can still like say hey we're trump supporters he's still the real
president right right right but they still need somebody to be the face yeah it's the fall of
stalin they're all jockeying for position and i think that i the sense that i get from the
conversation they're having because they keep making reference to like off-air conversations
that they've had and the sense that i get is that alex really thinks that matt gates should be the
next person that gets the mantle of the weirdo conservative version god king wow um and so i
guess he's interpreting this as a preemptive attack on the part of the globalists again and
you know what i don't believe any of that's real and i don't believe that's true sure if alex does
believe that's true then it kind of does make sense why he would spend an hour on this story
yeah but still his defense is terrible no it's not good it's not good i mean ultimately his defense
is like why can't white men do whatever they want why can't why can't uh gates party yeah what whoa
what are you gonna judge him he's he's white and he's a man come on now you're you just let him do
what he wants to do also he's rich what are you gonna punish him for what if like i don't know
beto what if it came out that beto had dated a 17 year old how do you you know or are there
allegations of that how do you think alex will respond to that i mean we'd go ape shit yeah and
that's but that's the point of not giving a shit about what about ism we're not going to beat them
at what abouting no they're there they're it's like they're bread and butter no it's just kind
of something that can be a little bit funny to imagine how much you would freak out totally yeah
but hey look the reality is based on the claims that are being made um uh gates says that there
are tapes that prove his innocence that the fbi has okay and if that's the case then those should
be able to come out and you know resolve this whole thing fine i still hate you for all the
other shit you do yeah yeah roger demands the tapes most importantly let's hear the tapes we
need to hear the tape that's right the key is he went to the fbi they had a sting up they were
about to bust him yesterday somebody in the fbi leaked that info to the new york times for damage
control gates was about to have a devastating victory i think that's exactly right by retiring
from congress so the idea that they're presenting now is basically that there was this guy who by
the way matt gates said by name accused by name on tucker carlson's show yeah uh this guy who was
a former justice department official sure he's trying to extort uh uh gates and his family for
money sure there's the allegation that they'll come out with if he doesn't pay up or whatever
of course and so his dad had been wearing a wire in order to entrap this person as you do and
because they were just about to nail this uh this extortionist sure the new york times got leaked
this information right about the allegations that were the threat right to matt gates's extortion
and and to to be honest i don't i don't know if i believe all that it seems like a defense that's
being made and you know i if if that's the case it should be very easy to clear this up oh yeah
not hard at all it should be incredibly easy and then that person who used to work at the justice
department should go to prison yeah it's not hard no it's like it's like these people don't
understand that the that law if it's to function at all is to be applied equally otherwise it is
not law that is a struggle yeah so uh the new york times reporter who covered this story they
reached out to roger sent roger an email and i think part of that is because roger was hey roger
did he do it hey level with me hey buddy look this is off the record just tell me if he did it or not
hey raj uh we have a picture of you and hit him and greenberg at mar-a-lago and how say you follow
up question did you do it so roger got an email and he's got a response for the guy and this gets
alex really excited i actually got an email from michael schmidt the uh reporter at the new york
times that wrote this story today i'm going to be releasing my response because it is quite
extraordinary um they don't hold the new york times to the same standards they hold everybody
else to it is amazing linked to associated with is known to have spent time with that's killed by
association hold on hold on i want the exclusive can you pull up the email i want to hear your
response to the new york times uh yeah you'll get a chance to take a look at it i've got to
touch it up a little bit because the more i read it the angrier i get and then alex is like uh
yeah when you uh when you get a chance to touch that up could you uh go in the war room and uh
war room and talk about it yeah yeah roger's response is yeah if i'm awake
dude you're in florida it's not late does not give a shit anymore i go to bed at four yeah
you dinner at three and i'm in bed at four it's a good life it's not a bad life yeah so alex really
is thirsty for that uh that exclusive at what how many pictures with alleged or convicted sex
traffickers can you be in before people start look dude at a certain point you got to let that go
because they congregate at mar-a-lago yeah that's true you know if you go there there's probably a
picture of you with a perv now that's probably another thing we should put a red flag up about
right you know but i mean like it's not you know you go to you go to most easily cantina you're
going to get a picture taken sure it's going to be a home of skyman bility yes i get that yeah
that doesn't mean that you're a smuggler just because he took a picture of you with
right right you just like to hang out at the place where smugglers go and i get and i get that but
how many pictures do you get to be like look i get it one or two and then you see that picture
and you go oh that's not going to look good later on when you're at five then it's just too many
you sound like the fucking left guilt by association all over the place and it's not
good i'm just saying there's just too many of them anyway uh look on our first episode that we ever
did we learned that it was time to pray uh because benjamin netanyahu was the canary in the coal mine
was that what it was jesus five goddamn years later it's time to pray we're still praying i
have to tell you it is still time to pray yeah roger roger i know for real because i've talked
to you privately i see the tears in your eyes when we've been in person when you were saying
pray with me you start crying you were always a christian but you didn't let us pray none of us
are perfect god feels all get a little bit of partying here and there none of it was wrong
in god's eyes because you repented of it like king david but but let's pray we got a minute
and a half left to break but lead us in prayer for for congressman matt gates please right you've
got to imagine roger's like you motherfucker you son of a bitch how dare you you are getting you're
begging me to pray how dare you first off you're telling this bullshit about me crying while prayer
get the fuck out of here i think that's good for the all their images though i think i think that's
fine that's that's the version of the story that you'd want to know he's the penitent man who is
pardoned by your god king naturally yeah yeah that's what you do yeah and you go overboard
with it too yes rending his garments and beating his chest as is alex's sort of style yes uh but
yeah it i mean look it's rude to be like will you lead us in prayer i on my dumb conspiracy theory
show where we're saying that matt gates may have dated a 17 year old years ago but who knows he
doesn't remember his wild parties whatever i would be mad if you asked me to pray the day before
let alone five minutes on the spot yeah so i was like is roger gonna pray i want to hear it mic
down okay uh look i'm not i'm not the most articulate but i'll give it a try dear lord
those the you who created both heaven and earth yo you who stand for justice and hate injustice
please watch over matt gates in this struggle for his freedom he is a good man he is a godly man he
is an innocent man he is a man of great promise do not let the left wing hate machine that sought
to destroy me sought to destroy general flint now destroy this great american patriot oh man
and by the way that's another topic for you to come back we're trying to get flint to run we're
begging them on our knees okay weird okay all right man just go back to when like he was a
young operative working with like nixon yeah and be like hey in 2021 you're gonna be hanging out
with alex jones and praying on air he would have hit you with a two by four like you're a mule
yeah yeah he is a sad piece of shit this is wild just this is bad just like i don't understand why
this isn't something that like would have more media coverage like this this to me seems like
so bizarre roger stone preys on air i know but like like they roger stone still has to be a
big bad in the media he can't they can't just portray him as this sad i mean just real pathetic
a nonsense man i think also too as i as i say that out loud i think i kind of realize that were you
to cover something that way you might run the risk of offending people who are christian or religious
like the idea the it's not it's not mocking prayer no it's mocking the idea that one it's roger
stone two it's on alex jones's show uh it's more that and i think that that tone might not be able
to be properly conveyed so that makes sense the right wing machine would turn it into a massive
deal but i can't like if you are by any stretch and adherent to uh the the intent of the bible
um i would argue that that prayer is way more offensive to christians than any article being
like roger stone is an asshole don't let them do what they did to me yeah that that like not even
god is above the left right paradigm is that what we're doing not well he is your god is pathetic
and shitty that's what that's my alex's god is above the left right paradigm and that means that
he's super to the right super to the right yeah so alex at the end there was talking about how
we want to draft mike flinn uh general flint sure uh to run for president they talk about this a
little bit the him and him and roger are not quite on the same page let's draft uh general flint to
get going what do you think roger uh look i think i've made it as clear as i can that if the
president runs i'm for the president and he has the right to make that decision and he has the
luxury to make it in his own time but if the president doesn't run it's absolutely vital that
we have a candidate a man or a woman who really understands and supports and completely is
committed to hold on five more minutes exactly on flint we need a stand-in and i get you're being
delicate here we're not against trump if trump ain't gonna do it we have to fire up flint and
we were firing up gates behind the scenes we have to have them ready in case trump doesn't do it
look right back hey alex you dumb fuck uh trump pardon me i have loyalty to him for life i'm gonna
say trump yeah forever yeah forever we can have hypothetical uh conversations about anybody else
but you have to understand that i will always give a proviso that trump is technically still
president even if gates were president trump should be yeah yep yep but i mean it just becomes
all too apparent there the way that they're conversing that like we're looking for a stand-in
yeah yeah we need somebody to get uh the dumb dumbs as excited as trump did and it's not gonna
happen and matt gates is the kind of shithead who would wear a gas mask right and then get covid
right but they they just don't have any of it like it's it's very abundantly clear now that nobody
but trump has the stuff that the like total uh attributes that are necessary to pull off a trump
campaign you know like gates isn't going to be able to because he doesn't have that image of
being a successful billionaire he's kind of a piece of shit yeah he's an asshole yeah and he
can't pull off any kind of sexual impropriety scandal because he's too young and not enough
people want to back him in order to run interference for him so we're probably going to wind up with
trump is the republican candidate and it's going to be so sad and miserable for everybody so long
as the media learns any lessons from 2016 and 2020 so i imagine that we're gonna have trump in 2025
yep but it's okay dan if the democrats pull it together and govern effectively there's no way
that a right-wing uh let's move on so uh alex has uh he lets roger go and uh who very confusing um
very very very confusing i think i get generally what they're doing but it's still like
i can't imagine having any time to prepare and thinking like this is the defense that
we're gonna spend like half of the show on yeah that is bizarre have a better defense tomorrow
yeah that makes the most sense yeah be like hey we know these allegations are terrible and we're
gonna look into it and we'll have more rogers not available today he'll be on tomorrow to talk about
it yep roger could be asleep who knows who cares yep it just doesn't matter really silly take your
time um but uh alex has also built up this entire story about the uh everyone who stormed the
capital is getting off scot-free sure and the libs are really mad about it so stewart roads is on
along with his lawyer i was gonna say you better have a lawyer present um i don't know if this
lawyer is gonna be helpful stewart should have his lawyer next to him at all times his lawyer might
need a lawyer oh boy as an ex-prosecutor what do you think of the fiasco uh i actually is kind of
how it's been since the beginning i think thought that they were overreaching they seem to
have an agenda that they wanted everything to fit into but the facts just don't support that i don't
know if it was something they had planned because i believe that that event was funded somehow with
antifa but um i think they wanted patriots to act up more than what happened and then they have
continued to try to push a narrative that the facts don't fit into you were here over a month
ago that's what you said in the green room you weren't on air you said it looks staged we're not
sure yet but so stewart roads his lawyer that he brings along thinks antifa paid to do something
with the yeah yeah yeah i you know i think i think the past few years have really taken a lot of
shine off of uh the legal minds of our country this lawyer seems insane yeah i think most lawyers
now are starting to sound a lot more and more insane yeah yeah him and him and stewart alex
and stewart and this lawyer they they just talk about how like ah everybody on the right is good
of course yes yes we're all angels over here and everybody on the left drinks adrenochrome and it's
kind of dumb and it's not really all that interesting or or uh you know uh it doesn't
bring much to us but stewart does have a prediction that we've got to put on the record
so we can you know okay all right uh we're looking at the summer of rage they're speeding your time
table up that's why it's important for us to understand what's coming you should expect them
to decouple the dollar from the world currency and kill the dollar this summer and what you're
going to have to do is become strong this they want us divided and weak you got to unite to
become strong that means food and fuel and ammunition the clean water the ability to
self-sustain so you can resist the compulsory taking of the vaccine in order to eat and i
totally agree with you so yeah the dollar is going to be destroyed this summer look for that
everybody who believes that take your stuff and just go into the woods create a splinter society
and leave the rest of us alone or if you believe that take the dollar that still has some value
okay pay your internet bill sure download an episode of alex jones from last year saying
this year will be the summer of rage ah that might be too expensive download a couple years back when
he did it every year now 5g is how they get you now i'll go back to like years and years in the
past should say tomorrow they're going to devalue the dollar while he's conveniently selling gold
it helps it helps to sell gold it's outrageous i i mean we'll see oh no this summer oh man i'm
really worried i'm really worried so stewart's whole big thing is that the government is going
to starve everybody that's his uh that's his new thing um that he's pushing pretty hard it's going
to be tough to win votes on a platform of uh starve everyone but we'll see how they pull it
off dan counterpoint yeah here's a great uh here's a great uh electoral strategy okay hey do you miss
food here is food here is food yeah i will vote for food sir i think that's what stewart is trying
to uh trying to get uh trigger in people's minds anyway um yeah come to the end of this and it's
it's weird because you know i i think i think um obviously i'm more interested in non-present-day
alex jones he's very he's a very dumb uninteresting person but this this defense
of gates really did interest me in as much as like i hate matt gates and i'm not interested in piling
on him sure until we know more naturally alex his defense makes me suspicious it really makes me
think that alex knows something that we don't know and it's bad and it's real bad that's what
it makes me think it's hard to get any other impression obviously we don't know that now it's
good just be you know knee-jerk protect your own right kind of thing and and you know maybe there's
something and i would say that if this is his knee-jerk reaction that's probably just as
illuminating as if he does know something that we don't know because his knee-jerk reaction is like
come on sexual assault's fine you know like it's it's kind of weirdo conservatives exactly yes it
is it is that basic kind of feel to it so if that's your knee-jerk reaction i think we know
how you're going to react to just about everybody yeah yeah it doesn't it doesn't uh it was not an
enjoyable uh bit of time to listen to this show it's confusing yeah um so yeah i don't know we'll
check back in we'll see how things are going of course and uh but uh until then we have a website
we do have a website it's knowledgefight.com yep we're also on twitter we are on twitter
it's that knowledge that go to bed jordan we're on facebook we are facebook if you could please
find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out uh people doing god's work right now uh
we'll be back but until then i'm neo i'm leo i'm dzx clark i'm darryl rundis so what do you think
about them apples andy in chansas you're on the air thanks for holding hello alex i'm a first time
caller i'm a huge fan i love your work i love you