N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys.
I love you.
I'm going to get you.
Knowledgefight.
Dan and Jordan, Knowledgefight.
I need money.
Andy and Kansas.
Stop it.
It's time to pray.
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding us.
Hello Alex, I'm a fifth-time caller, I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
Knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding us.
Hello, Alex, I'm a big fan color, I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
Knowledge Fight, knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight, I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes, like to sit around,
drink novelty beverages and talk a little bit
about Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are, Dan.
Indeed.
Dan?
Yes, sir.
Quick question.
Jordan.
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, Jordan, I had a realization
that I've been listening to a fair amount
of some podcasts for entertainment.
Sure.
Decompressing that high stress week or so,
and I realized that one of the things
that I really gravitate towards,
there's a through line through a lot of them,
and that is Matt Gourley.
Matt Gourley's great.
I think he adds so much to a podcast.
He's great.
And his vibe is so gentle and friendly.
Underrated.
As a counterweight to my listening
to Alex Jones all the time,
it really feels like that's like a balm
that I can, Matt Gourley's a balm I can put on my hand.
Matt Gourley's a classic glue guy, you know?
He's like a Phil Hartman.
He's got that Dave Foley kind of like
straight man energy to him,
but he's also incredibly hilarious.
Very sharp.
Really, really funny.
And also I want to try and exploit my platform
to now be like, if we're big enough.
Hey, Matt Gourley, get over here.
Come on, Matt Gourley, come on now.
Hit a player up, Matt Gourley.
I like it, I like it.
Let's see if that works.
Let's abuse our privileges.
Yes, let's see.
Jordan, how about you?
Dan, I have the rare double Blight Spot.
Double Blight Spot.
No, the inverse of Double Blight Spot.
The Double Blight Spot.
That's a follow up to two Bright Spots.
Yeah.
This is unprecedented.
First, we're going to go in chronological order.
If you will recall, Dan, a while back,
I told you about a pear that I ate.
Sure.
It was a delicious pear.
Oh, I got some pears for you in the other room, by the way.
Of course, I'm going to enjoy those.
But my partner's moms both decided
that we got to do something for this.
So they ordered me a pear.
Wait, they realized they had to do something about you?
They had to do something about this pear thing.
They were inspired into action.
So they ordered me a pear from a place that has great pears.
Sure.
To the point where I can't eat it.
It looks too much like the pear.
It's like a platonic pear.
Yeah, it's like a platonic pear, where you're like,
I don't know what to do with this pear.
I'm going to eat it.
It's going to be amazing.
Yeah, of course you're going to eat it.
You got to.
And then you'll recall that I said something about how
my brain was functioning.
Yeah.
And Black Dragon Queen Christy sent me
an incredibly kind card.
Artistic pear?
Yeah, well, I wish it was a pear, always.
All things should be pears.
But she really touched me.
And it was very kind of her.
That is great.
Double bright spot.
Hey, things are looking real bright.
And I actually got to say, I may have another bright spot.
Oh, no.
And if you're going with two, I'm going to give another one.
We're going to do a quadruple bright spot?
I may.
And that is that I really got into today's episode.
You did.
You know, it's an Easter miracle.
I found something.
I was not expecting Alex to be at all kind of like, oh,
I can talk about this.
This is interesting.
So you would say that Alex has risen.
He's risen indeed.
And we will get down to business on all that.
But before we do, Jordan, let's take a little moment
to say thank you to some new wonks.
Oh, that's not a bad idea at all.
So first, Scroton the Strong, thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Scroton.
Thank you.
Next, Melissa Kay, thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Melissa.
Thank you.
Next, oh, man, I remember when I first
realized that Missy was short for Melissa.
It's a weird day.
Anyway, sorry, Melissa.
Next, Trek With Tyler, thank you so much.
You are now policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, TWT.
Next, Owen but not the Dumb One.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
There are a surprising number of competitions.
Troyer.
For Dumb Owen Tea, I was going to say.
Next, Kathleen Y. Thank you so much you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, Kathleen.
Thank you.
Next, pretty quick for a Canadian.
Thank you so much you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much! Pretty quick.
And we've got a couple of special things going on here over the weekend.
Alright.
We had a couple birthdays that I'd like to give a little shoutout to.
It's our April birthday shoutout that we're gonna do probably three or four more times this one.
First, Alexander reached out and wanted to wish Iris a happy birthday.
Oh, a happy birthday, Iris.
Happy birthday, Iris.
Yeah, of course.
Hope you have a good one, or had a good one, I guess,
because since this is coming out probably after your birthday.
Don't worry about it. Deal with it, Iris.
Now, this next one's very special. It goes out to a cat.
Okay.
It was a birthday cat.
Well, then we do birthday cats on command.
Yes.
On command!
Yeah.
No birthday months for cats.
That's the loophole.
Yeah, exactly.
And this is a cat named Pleiades.
Oh, well, shit!
How do you not wish Pleiades the cat a happy birthday?
I don't know, because the light from Pleiades takes several hundred thousand years to get to us.
Well, it just got here.
Oh, okay.
Happy birthday.
Nicely done.
So, Jordan, today we're going to be going over April 1st through 3rd 2021 Blackjack.
Ah! I never had a chance on that one.
No, I really sped up.
You were too good for that one.
Through the home stretch.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um, so this is Thursday and Friday of last week,
and then Saturday Alex fucked around and went into studio and recorded a special thing.
Oh, sure, why not?
And once we get going, you'll understand why I had to cover that Saturday thing.
No, no, of course, of course.
But first, here's an out of context drop from today's show.
The devil ain't cool, man.
He's not what gives you the hot cheerleaders and the partying and the fun.
Oh. Hmm.
Actually, I thought that was the...
I thought that's what he specifically tried to tempt you with.
Every depiction in media.
I was gonna say, he's the one who gets you that stuff.
God is the one who gets you eternal happiness by forgoing those specific things.
Yep, that's always been my understanding.
Every chick tract that I've ever seen.
Almost entirely like, hey, that hot girl, you gotta avoid her.
And the fun and the partying.
It's terrifying.
Don't do the fun and the partying.
Jesus hates it.
Yeah.
So, my man.
I want to preface this really quick.
Sure.
I want to set this up.
All right.
This April 1st episode, if it was an April Fool's episode, I would admire the hell out of it.
Because there's a number of things that go on that you could interpret as being like,
yeah, he's fucking around.
Sure, but it's not.
Like this, this could be an April Fool's gag.
And I've been doing a lot of studying the last few weeks on a particular subject that
Rob Doob brought to my attention and that the rest of the crew kept basically pestering
me about.
And I finally, last night and today, read it.
And it is the smoking gun of smoking guns of smoking guns.
This is green eggs and ham.
And I'm the type of guy that always gets on air.
And I tell you, next hour, I'm going to cover this big story.
And then I'll start telling you what the big story is right away.
Right.
The tactic and media, as I say, coming up.
So you keep listening.
I don't do that.
I'm bad at my job.
If you just put out the big news and don't have some fanfare, like a 20th Century Fox
intro, which is not how it goes.
A rip off of old British newsreels.
People don't care.
And it just becomes part of the background ambient noise.
And they actually get conditioned to the tyranny.
You actually become a tool of evil.
You know, I almost just go off air for a month and just shut info wars down.
And then if I came back and covered this, we might be able to save the planet.
I hate you so much.
You see what I mean?
April Fools.
I hate you so much.
That should have ended with, should I be saying any of this?
Perhaps not.
I have the gun, the smoking gun to end all smoking guns and...
See you in a month, assholes!
Yeah, I'm gonna disappear for a while.
This is your fault.
You don't get this smoking gun.
So that's an interesting idea for Alex.
The idea of disappearing like he's Sting going to the rafters.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
Not fighting for WCW or NWO.
If you love something, let it go.
I do like the idea of Alex coming back with just face paint.
Crow face paint.
A brooding Alex Jones.
I'm Bruce Lee's grandson.
So he doesn't disappear for a month, but he does do what I would say is the next best thing.
What have I told you?
I have the document from John Hopkins where they plan the whole attack,
plan the SARS attack, planned the Ebola attack, planned the COVID-19 attack,
and then have a plan through vaccines to brain damage you and give you Alzheimer's
and sterilize you.
And then how they're even going to blame the politicians
and how they even set up President Trump to do it.
I would be interested in that.
Imagine having that smoking gun.
I'm imagining it.
In your hand.
Mail it to me.
Word for word, admitting the whole thing.
And then you'd ask, why would they write such a thing?
Well, I know why.
I can explain it.
But you know what?
I'm not going to cover it.
I'm going to put together graphics and I'm going to put all the different pieces together.
And I'm going to come in here Saturday and I'm going to tape for one hour at noon.
Make sure it's all perfect.
Yeah.
And then at 2 p.m. central, we should have it ready.
We will stream it back to back hour after hour until I go live Sunday on Easter at 4 p.m.
Central Standard Time, as I always do on Sundays.
What a dick.
That's amazing.
I've got smoking gun proof, but I'm not going to talk about it.
Not until Sunday.
That's some Dom sub shit.
I can't handle that.
I'm not into this type of relationship, dude.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I mean, unfortunately for me, I was like, wow, that is ridiculous.
You can come on Saturday.
No!
That kind of...
Disagree.
That kind of presentation is ridiculous.
If you're listening in the audience, you have to ask yourself, why?
What kind of real person would do this?
What possible news organization would be like, we have proof of everything that is going
on and they're trying to kill everybody.
We're going to wait two days to reveal it to you.
You know what?
And news organizations do wait with information that they're not 100...
They don't tease it like this, though.
But they don't go... the New York Times doesn't have like a, hey man, we got some bombshell
shit.
We're going to see it in a couple weeks.
We're working on something that will...
This will change the game.
No.
No, no, no, no.
Dumb.
Absolutely not.
So the document that Alex is talking about is a 2017 scenario exercise called the SPARS
pandemic 2025 to 2028, a futuristic scenario for public health risk communicators.
Oh, that sounds like the smoking gun.
This document is essentially very similar in structure to the Rockefeller one Alex erroneously
calls Operation Lockstep in that the Johns Hopkins exercise began with the selection
of two important variables that could dictate what challenges could arise in a possible
future.
Is Alex real or is Alex not real?
In this exercise, the two variables were quote, varying degrees of access to information technology
and quote, varying levels of fragmentation among social, political, religious, ideological
and cultural lines.
Whereas the Rockefeller document explored all four of the possible futures that were
based on the variables they chose, this document focuses instead on just the one that the preparers
thought would present the most challenge in terms of medical communication.
Okay, so there are more positive simulations that could happen.
With those two variables creating a matrix of four scenarios.
But this paper is entirely about the worst possible scenario.
Maybe not the worst possible scenario because they don't lay out what the other ones are,
so I don't really know what they are.
It's a real bummer of a scenario.
Well, it's a scenario that is for an exercise for medical communicators.
Okay.
And so the one that would raise the most challenges, or they decided would raise the most interesting
challenges.
Perfect.
Is the one that they used.
Excellent.
Sorry, I just wanted a clarification.
That's an important clarification.
This was the possible future that they called the echo chamber, which represented a scenario
where there was widespread access to information technology and quote, isolated and highly
fragmented communities.
Reading over this document, it's really fascinating how there are a number of similarities between
the real world and the scenario that was laid out in this exercise.
The real world novel coronavirus was called SARS-CoV-2, whereas the scenario illness is
called SPARS-CoV.
Ultimately, these similarities are all things that make sense, given that the possible future
was laid out by public health experts who would be trying to make as realistic a scenario
as possible so participants could best explore the communication challenges that could arise
in the event of a public health emergency in a world where everyone was online and large
segments of the population lived in a slightly different reality from each other.
Yeah.
One of the problems that we keep running into with these scenarios, like this document and
the Rockefeller one, are that they're well written and engaging.
They contain a ton of details that flesh out the world they're trying to depict and as
such seem like more of a prediction than they intend to be.
This Johns Hopkins scenario relies on a template laid out by J. Ogilvy and Peter Schwartz in
their 2004 paper titled Plotting Your Scenarios, published by the Global Business Network.
In this paper, Ogilvy and Schwartz try to help businesses and organizations understand
how to best structure a scenario-based exercise in order to maximize its impact in terms of
the participants being able to learn about how to deal with new circumstances and manage
change.
Okay, so these guys are dungeon masters.
Yes.
Yeah, that's a good way to put it.
Yeah, that's what these guys do.
The strategy of using a scenario matrix is explained in this paper.
This is what both the Johns Hopkins and Rockefeller exercises used, where the planners come up
with a big list of key factors they think could affect the possible futures they want
to explore, then that list is whittled down to two central factors.
These factors are plotted on a matrix, which could go in one of two directions, and that
creates four distinct combinations of factors, each representing a scenario that can be explored.
Right.
An example that's given in this paper is about looking at possible futures for education,
where they choose to use hierarchy versus participation and inclusion versus exclusion
as the two main axes that were the most relevant to their exploration.
This created four scenarios, hierarchical and inclusive,
hierarchical and exclusive, participatory and inclusive, and participatory and exclusive.
Each of these possible realities looks vastly different from the others, so it's not too
hard to jump from there to scenario building and creating evocative narratives that characterize
each of these so participants can more easily relate to the challenges that each possible
future would present.
Totally, of course.
That's exactly what Ogilvy and Schwartz discuss in their introduction to this paper.
To be an effective planning tool, scenarios should be written in the form of absorbing,
convincing stories that describe a broad range of alternative futures relevant to an organization's
success.
Thoughtfully constructed, believable plots help managers to become deeply involved in
the scenarios and perhaps gain new understanding of how their organization can manage change
as a result of this experience.
The more involved managers get with scenarios, the more likely it becomes that they will
recognize their important but less obvious implications.
Moreover, scenarios with engrossing plots can be swiftly communicated throughout the
organization and will be more easily remembered by decision makers at all levels of management.
And if the CDC rolls an 18 or higher, then we defeat the pandemic.
Saving throw.
That makes perfect sense to me.
Ogilvy and Schwartz are business consultants, and this technique, using scenario-based exercises,
is a very common one among organizations that want to explore how prepared they are to face
potential challenges that could come up expectedly or unexpectedly.
Yeah, war games.
Yeah, these scenarios work better if they're written as compelling and engrossing stories,
and as we've learned, Alex has an incredibly hard time differentiating between reality
and fiction.
Yeah.
To compound the problem, these guys, they recommend that people, quote, invent catchy
names for the scenarios, saying, quote, when your managers feel the hot breath of crisis,
they should be able to recall the appropriate scenario by name.
Dan, if you recall, I have suggested to scientists that they need to rename things better.
Now, here's the problem, though.
I have also suggested they go outside of scientists for naming.
Yeah, but then Alex also talks about how, like, THX 1138 or whatever is-
Sure.
That's not a catchy name.
But I mean, we could come up with some catchier names.
What's this one called?
Well, this one is called the echo chamber.
The echo chamber.
Yeah.
Okay, I'll call it the shitty room.
Okay, all right.
You won't forget the shitty room.
No, that's true.
That might work.
So this technique, though, creating these names that you remember, it's a good strategy
for scenario-based planning, but the flip side, like you have pointed out, is that these
names could be exploited very easily.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Lockstep is a perfect example of that.
It's just a catchy scenario name, which is apparently so catchy that Alex has built a
gigantic conspiracy around it.
See?
Now I rename it Bummertown.
One, you remember it.
Two, nobody's like, oh, they're using Bummertown to defeat the globalists.
It's a classic Bummertown.
Yeah, this is the Bummertown scenario all over again.
Anyway, the bottom line here is that this document is none of the things Alex claims
that it is, and it doesn't prove any of the shit he's pretending it does.
Also, it's 89 pages long, so there's no way, I believe, for a second that Alex has read
it.
Absolutely not.
He talks a little bit more about it here, although he said he was going to wait until
Saturday.
Of course he did.
He actually doesn't talk much about it, because I think he actually hasn't read it at all.
Right, right, right, right.
He's just got no clue.
No.
No, okay.
Basically, anyone taking these vaccines, they're all designed to the same thing, is going to
have neurological disorders within one year, most of the people taking the vaccine will
be dead within 10, and this John Hopkins says it all right here.
That is not in the Hopkins report.
That would be a very strange thing for Johns Hopkins to release.
Yeah, the scenario is written from the standpoint of someone who lives in 2030, so there's not
even 10 years depicted in the exercise since the outbreak begins in 2025.
Sure, sure.
Alex is just making shit up because he knows no one's going to read it, and he's got all
the elements there that he needs to lie about.
It's 89 pages, it's got the name.
Yeah, you're golden.
Yep.
Just riff.
So every now and again I like to point out when Alex makes it abundantly clear that he
thinks that he's fighting literal demons, because everyone needs to keep that in the
front of their mind.
It's really nice to recall that this man thinks he's fighting the devil.
Right.
You know who authored this report?
It wasn't the Center for Public Health at Johns Hopkins.
It was Lucifer the Morningstar.
You bet.
Yeah, okay.
He's a master of public health, actually.
Got a degree.
Honorary.
Well.
Obviously this is not a human intelligence running this, and I just go back to that over
and over again.
I tell top generals that, top former head of intelligence agencies, senators, you name
it, at secret meetings, and they nod their head and agree with me, because everybody
knows.
Everybody knows.
I'm talking about fake low res of flying saucers here.
I'm talking about interdimensional entities.
Sure.
Hell-bent to destroy us.
Naturally.
And they are influencing humans on Earth to do this, and this is not a human plan.
It is a satanic fallen angel operation.
Sounds right.
I honestly might have more respect for low res pictures of UFOs.
I'd definitely rather talk to that guy than Alex.
Yeah, I would say that I am more convinced by the Loch Ness Monster photo than I am by
why interdimensional beings are controlling the plan that's not even happening.
Yeah, yep.
Yeah.
So Alex lies a little bit more about this Hopkins report, which again, he's not going
to talk about until Saturday.
No, of course not.
Hell on Earth is going to be released.
The total collapse is being engineered.
I mean, giant John Hopkins plans that are operational.
John Hopkins runs the whole thing.
Hee hee hee, I'm John Hopkins.
All spelled out says here, just like I surmise by 2030, you did not surmise the population
is dead or living dead.
Totally brain damage, totally gone.
And then we're going to have to, we won't be able to take care of people.
Then the good people to survive will have to join the globalist in exterminating who's
left because things will be so out of control.
Whoa.
Alex is making that up.
Yeah, no.
Big no.
Big pass on that one.
Yeah, so here's kind of the passage that I guess most closely resembles what he's talking
about.
Okay.
Quote, while the federal government appeared to have appropriately addressed concerns about
the acute side effects of Corovax.
That's the vaccine that comes up.
The vaccine for scars.
SPARS.
Scars Guard Cove 9.
The long-term chronic effects of the vaccine were still largely unknown.
Nearing the end of 2027, reports of new neurological symptoms began to emerge.
After showing no adverse side effects for nearly a year, several vaccine recipients
slowly began to experience symptoms such as blurry vision, headaches, and numbness in
their extremities.
Due to the small number of these cases, the significance of their association with Corovax
was never determined.
As of this writing in 2030, longitudinal studies initiated by the NIH at the beginning of the
vaccination program have not reached the next round of data collection.
So formal analysis of these symptoms has not yet been conducted.
Furthermore, these cases arose from the initial cohort of vaccine recipients.
Those in high-risk populations, including those with underlying health conditions, making
it increasingly difficult to determine the extent to which these symptoms are associated
with vaccination.
Yeah.
See, that's good dungeon mastering, but I would expect Alex would have added a little
more fire.
They're all dead.
We're all dead.
Yeah.
Just like, they're coming.
Those of us who haven't been vaccinated will be forced to kill the rest of everybody.
Totally.
You need a little bit of flair there.
That's all I'm saying.
The imagined scenario involves a small number of possible unforeseen side effects from a
vaccine that's just deployed to fight the pandemic.
And Alex has turned that into the clip that we just heard.
Sure.
He's claiming that John Hopkins is saying that by 2030, everyone will be dead or walking
dead.
That's a leap.
It's a complete fiction that he's just created out of thin air from his imagination.
The story that he's telling literally has no connection to the primary source that he's
pretending to cover.
That sounds correct.
But I can't wait until we get to Saturday.
They had days, and it's one of the most incompetent displays that I've ever seen.
There's no way that you heard, I'm going to get to this Saturday, and weren't like,
well, we're going to handle this Saturday.
That's when I'm like, all right.
All right, we'll see you then.
All right, I'm going to stretch.
Yeah, exactly.
You crack your knuckles a little bit, you do a little, all right, here we go.
And I got to say, I don't know who he's got for this Saturday show.
It's him, Rob Dew, and some dude named Mike.
I don't know who this Mike dude is, but he is a weirdo.
Okay, all right.
He is a sleepy weirdo.
All right, we're going to bring Mike into this.
Holy shit.
Okay.
Not to be believed, this guy.
Okay, all right.
So anyway, Alex is fighting Satan.
Sure.
And maybe he just wants to quit.
That's fair.
Satan's got infinite resources and is it a million years old or whatever?
I don't think Satan's interested in an information war.
That's probably true.
Yeah, it's time for the information war against heaven.
Did you know what you missed?
In the 40 days and 40 nights that Satan tempted Jesus in the desert, most of what they talked
about was Alex.
Well, when...
Dude, do you know what we're going to eventually have to deal with?
You have no fucking clue.
When Satan got all the angels turned against God or whatever, it really was information
warfare.
Yeah, it was. I mean, it's like you had to first convince them that their freedom was
stolen by an infinite creator.
It was mostly about vaccines.
Yeah, pretty much.
Anyway, Alex is fighting against Satan.
And we have now entered the operational shutdown of the planet as we know it.
And the decision has been made to overwrite every genetic system on the earth.
And the earth is to be completely sacrificed in the attempt to become God.
Sure.
In fact, their main mission, they say, is to destroy the earth.
And then only out of that metamorphosis can this new creature emerge.
That's what they've been told.
It is their universal code.
It is their ethos.
It is their religion.
And they've signed on to it.
And they've rebelled against God that made us.
And so I really don't even know if I can keep doing the show.
And I'm not kidding.
I think I'm going to have to just hand this over to somebody else.
This stuff's too big to even talk about on there.
If people don't know about this now, they're not going to figure it out.
I just need to get ready with my family.
I can't believe this, man.
Almighty, it's so horrible.
That didn't seem sincere.
Oh, I had a dream about the space baby from 2001 Space Odyssey.
And I just don't know if I can do this anymore.
It's just too big for me.
Oh, no.
So terrible.
The time baby is out there.
It's going to grow into a thing.
This is just big stuff, though, man.
Sure.
The globalists are trying to give birth to Satan to walk on the Earth.
Right.
This is too big.
No, I mean, that's a real bummer.
I kind of understand wanting to go to the woods.
But then again, in the best of times, I want to go to the woods.
That's true.
Maybe I'm not the person to talk about this.
I don't know.
Wouldn't the woods be a bad place?
Because Satan's all about the fire.
He does love fire.
Yeah.
You want more like a blacktop.
Sure.
Go move into a parking lot.
Desert.
Yeah.
A desert would be great.
And then whenever he burns it all, you've got glass to make really great windows.
This could be a good plan.
This is a plan.
Yeah.
We're going to make it through this apocalypse, Dan.
So anyway, back to lying about this document that he's not going to cover until Saturday.
Okay.
And they all know it's bull.
It's just every part of it is a lie.
And you're wearing a death shroud.
You're wearing this diaper.
And they even admit in the John Hopkins report that it gets an added bonus.
The bacterial pneumonia of the mask wearers is going to really increase their death toll.
The word mask does not appear once in the John Hopkins document.
That sounds right.
Yeah.
In the scenario, bacterial pneumonia is a condition that appears to be connected to the
invented virus spars.
But Alex is completely making up everything he's saying here about this document.
Wow.
Pretty great.
That's lovely.
I do like whenever you can toss in something that isn't even mentioned obliquely.
That's always good stuff.
Pretty solid.
Yeah.
So as someone who's fighting the devil, Alex has covered himself in the armor of God.
Sure.
And that means talking about the Bible.
Naturally.
And...
Gotta get into it.
And it's also Good Friday, right?
No, this is Thursday.
Oh, okay.
It's Maundy Thursday.
Apologies.
Right?
Isn't that what it is?
No idea.
I can't remember what the...
There's Good Friday.
Right.
Palm Thursday.
Palm Saturday.
Palm Wednesday.
Ash Wednesday.
But that's way different.
Don't worry about it.
We're doing great.
I don't know the week.
I'd forgotten.
Yeah.
Anyway, Alex also has forgotten some things about revelation.
If you believe the Bible, no flesh would be spared unless God intervened.
No flesh would have been spared.
None.
Sure.
And it says the rich men will sit under the mountains in their
fortresses under the mountains, beating themselves in the head.
So angry that they serve Satan and begging God to forgive them.
So like Trump, right?
And at that point they've come into the ultimate sin.
There will be no Holy Ghost.
There will be no forgiveness.
You have now chosen your side.
Yeah, like Trump, right?
Wow.
Wow. That's just a chance.
Weird.
Wow.
That's an intense thought, but it's also a delicious thought.
So weird.
So if the Bible did, in fact, say that rich people would live
under mountains, that kind of does sound like Alex's whole
thing about the elite globalists having underground bases.
Isn't he rich?
Yeah.
Unfortunately, Alex is leaving out a very critical part of
the verse that he's poorly referencing.
This is from Revelation 6, verse 15.
Quote, then the kings of the earth, the princes, the generals,
the rich, the mighty, and everyone else, both slave and free,
hidden caves and among the rocks of the mountains.
Oh, so everybody hidden caves.
It wasn't just the rich people.
No, it was a whole plethora of folk.
Yep.
Gotcha.
It's pretty much everyone trying to hide from the opening
of the sixth seal.
So it's pretty much everyone.
Yep.
Gotcha.
Anyway, much like Alex just writes fan fiction about the
nefarious documents he covers as news, he does the same thing
with the Bible, even like religious texts.
Everything is just a prop for him to use.
It really seems like that should be way more important.
You know, you want to know it word by word, really.
Yeah.
If you were fighting the devil, that is.
It's even like that would be your best weapon against the
devil is knowledge of the Bible.
Sure.
I've seen that in various Chuck Norris movies.
Yes, indeed we have.
So Roger is coming in again.
Great, great.
Which we saw on our last episode.
Yeah, it's time to pray.
It's interesting, though.
I got really weirded out by this.
Roger Stone has talked a lot about trying to draft Flynn to
get him ready to lead a national movement to run for
president or to support Trump for running for president.
But regardless, instead of overthinking it, I agree with
him, Flynn's got to launch it now.
And I'm going to leave it at that.
And obviously I've been talking to Flynn, and I just need
to we need to draft him here on this show.
We can't wait for Trump.
We can't wait for DeSantis.
We need General Flynn, who is a good man and a patriot
understand what's going on.
We need him to do this.
So Roger is at a dental appointment.
He's a little bit late.
He'll be popping in sometime next hour.
So on our last episode, the conversation was about trying
to draft Flynn or Gates.
Sure, sure, Gates might not be around for much longer.
We've gone a day, and Alex is just pretending that that
wasn't the whole conversation that they had.
Never happened.
No, we never defended that guy.
He's a real criminal.
Now, I mean, not to his credit, but Roger is still like,
he's innocent.
He's being set up.
Yeah, that sounds like a good Roger move.
Boy, has it deflated.
It is not like they spent over an hour on the last episode
incriminating themselves in order to defend the Gates.
Look, he just likes to party.
Hey, guys, we had a post debriefing on this one,
and we decided you guys should not commit any crimes
in the defense of someone.
Hey, everybody out there in the Infowars land, shit got bad.
Shit kept going the way it looked like it was going to go.
And we should have seen it coming.
Yep, yep.
I can walk away from this at this point.
Not hard.
Gunna.
Gunna bye.
Yeah, so I listened to this next clip,
and I kind of got the sense that, like, Roger is fucking
with Alex a little bit, which I can kind of enjoy.
Well, he just got back.
Roger Stone has been trying for a week to send me a report,
a secret report.
It's not a classified report.
It's a secret report.
My email doesn't work.
He can't send it to any of our emails.
They're in his email blocking it.
They're in our email.
Oh, no, it really is.
It's a total take over, folks.
The full weight of the government works against the country
to implode it and destroy it.
All right.
They're in his email.
My email doesn't work.
Roger can't send me emails, but he can't send me this secret
document.
I don't know why Outlook isn't working right now.
Yeah, I think Occam's Razor tells me Roger is fucking
with Alex.
Yeah, that would make sense.
So we get another headline here, and this is important.
This is really important stuff.
Breaking.
That's right.
The Alex Jones show there's a war on for your mind.
High school to re-educate students.
That's a quote who refused to wear COVID mask in Clearwater,
Florida.
Even a conservative city, conservative state.
They're the leftist are teaching their critical radical
race theory.
Teaching America sucks.
The high school in Clearwater, Florida, says it will re-educate
students who do not wear a mask when required.
Naturally.
This is a story about Clearwater High School.
And honestly, if I were involved, I would have just told
them to use a different word than re-educate.
That seems very easy.
Yeah, it says, quote, students who do not wear a mask when
it is required or refuse to do so should first be re-educated
on the importance of wearing a mask.
If after the re-education occurs, they do not comply, the
student administrator should be contacted.
The importance of wearing a mask should be reinforced.
Yes.
If not done so, if behavior has not changed, and then this
whole thing goes away.
The word re-education is something that means a lot of
different things in different contexts.
For Alex, the word means commies taking kids to camps and
doing that thing from Clockwork Orange.
Naturally.
In this context, it's really clear that what they mean is
that if a student is refusing to wear a mask, they should be
given a chance to better understand why a mask is important
in a schoolroom setting before any kind of disciplinary
action is even considered.
Right.
This is essentially what it's basically saying like the
kids get a warning.
The right wing blogs that are covering the story use this
quote, but seem to leave off what comes immediately after
it in the school's plan for the new academic year.
Oh, that's harder.
Quote, not wearing a mask when it's required is not a
disciplinary matter, but rather a health and safety concern.
Administrators will contact the parent or guardian for
support.
If the refusal continues, the principal must contact the
area superintendent to discuss options, which include
administrative placement into one of the other learning
options.
This placement is a non-disciplinary placement and
is based on the health and safety needs of all students
and staff.
So this same document literally says that students who refuse
to wear masks won't get in trouble, and if it's something
that can't be resolved, then accommodation will be made to
allow them to continue to go to class remotely.
That seems like going above and beyond to cater to people
who refuse to wear masks in public gathering settings.
Yeah.
But of course they use the word reeducation, so this is
somehow about critical race theory or something.
Yeah, that sounds right.
It's ridiculous.
Their plan is really well thought out and kind of
considerate and perhaps overly sensitive, you know, but it
is better than my plan of if a kid decides not to wear a
mask, you go to his house and scream in his parents face
until they leave you alone forever.
It's tougher to codify into a rule.
It's better that I wouldn't use the word reeducation.
Give less meat for Alex.
There you go.
Yeah.
So Roger comes on after the dentist and, you know, like I
said, they do not talk about Matt Gaetz much.
Sure.
It's much different than the day before.
Unsurprising.
The entire interview is about how Alex wants General Flynn
to announce that he's running for president and Roger trying
to explain to Alex that there's a game they need to play.
Roger is saying that if they're going to do this, the first
thing they need to do is gather massive amounts of data about
the people who would support Flynn, and then they need to
somehow get around all the social media bans that all these
shitheads like Alex have that limit their reach.
Right.
It's a farce of an interview, and it seems pretty clear to
me that there's going to be some attempt coming down the
line to try to replace Trump with Flynn as the figurehead
of the Infowars idol cult.
Roger is trying to subtly implant the idea that Flynn is
like Eisenhower.
He's a military hero who the people need to coerce into
running for office because it's his duty to the country.
See, Roger seems to realize that the only thing that's going
to work for someone like Flynn is a fully realized storyline
to push as a campaign, and his character works with that
kind of archetype, regardless of how disconnected from
reality it is.
It's the same thing they did with Trump, pretending that he
was a successful businessman who had never had any interest
in politics who won the presidency on his first try.
When compared to reality, that's bullshit, but it's a
compelling storyline for the base to enjoy.
Flynn being a reluctant candidate would have a similar,
you know, complete bullshit narrative thing if it were to
get off the ground, but could be effective.
I am wilded out by the idea that anyone would want anyone
who had any command during the Iraq war.
Oh, yeah, that's weird.
Also somebody who pledged allegiance to QAnon.
Yeah, shouldn't that be immediately disqualifying?
Like, I don't even care what your politics are.
You were involved with commanding in the Iraq war.
You are already a failure before you even began.
Yeah, you should maybe take a seat.
You should go away.
So Roger wants to build up to this subtly and softly,
whereas Alex is a little bit less patient.
They're just going back and forth about how Flynn needs to
go on the attack immediately.
That's what Alex is saying.
And then Roger comes back with, who knows what will happen?
And then finally, Alex has just had enough.
Here's the deal.
He's got to do it.
He knows it.
And the amount of money he can raise is staggering.
And so he's going to run for president.
I'm drafting him right now.
And so are the American people.
And as he does these quiet events to 10,000 people here,
10,000 people there, 1,000 there, everybody that goes to
these things he quietly has that are packed out need to
tell him you're doing it.
And I'm not being presumptive here.
Listen, they want you and I in jail because they know we
helped light the fire with Trump.
They know that we're not afraid and they know we've got
lightning in a bottle and they know that lightning does
strike the same place repeatedly.
That's how Will and Zeitgeist and.
Wait, what?
Yes.
So obviously I could sell off of the sunset right now.
The globalists are ready to buy me off like that.
I could snap my fingers, $100 million, private jets,
everything, but I'm not selling humanity out.
So and he's not either.
He just keeps overthinking it.
He needs to listen to you.
He needs to announce soon.
Alex is sick of the bullshit and he wants a hero figure to
get behind and it's the best thing out right now out of
options for God King.
It turns out without his inimitable platform, Trump's shit
talking doesn't work.
Yeah, I am not really all that good as the center focus.
Exactly.
Me, Alex Jones, not good as center focus.
Need to be someone else's hype man.
Totally.
That person I'm hyping is absent now.
Not gone.
This does not work.
I'm really flailing.
I need a dad.
You are 100% correct.
Yeah, that is exactly what's going on.
So this clip means nothing, but I just thought it was kind
of interesting to hear Alex describe the plot of Romeo and
Juliet.
I think he gets some of the beats right.
Okay.
I'm really, really interested in this.
I'm going to be honest.
This is the first time in a while I've been like, I'm going
to be on the edge of my seat.
Alex's literature recap.
Like reading a William Shakespeare play that you've already
read before.
You know, you turn the page and Romeo and Juliet meet, tell
me you love and their parents are mean to them.
They have their problems.
And by the end, they commit suicide.
You know, you know the play.
All right.
Well, I mean, he's not wrong.
He's not wrong.
It didn't exist as a venerated play for hundreds of years
because of that plot synopsis.
I mean, look, look, look, look, the skeleton is there.
There's a thing.
Their parents are mad at him.
They kill themselves.
And it's a great play.
The parents are mean.
You've read it before.
It does not sound like you've read it before, sir.
Oh, God.
It sounds like you saw half of the Leonardo DiCaprio version
and then woke up at the end.
You're one of these literature major types, though.
Like from where?
I'm from the streets, right?
Sure.
No, no, no.
I'm with you.
For someone like me, I hear that.
And I'm like, yeah, that is what Romeo and Juliet is about.
Because it is.
Yeah, but even if you're watching West Side Story,
there's more to it than that.
I disagree.
OK, well, that's fair.
That's fair.
You could cut out a lot of those songs.
A classic tale of people meeting,
their families being mean, and then they kill themselves.
I mean, you know, it does have an arc.
Yeah.
So Alex cares about the theater, cares
about classic literature.
But what he doesn't care about, money.
OK.
And you know why I feel so upset?
I've never cared about money.
And back when I could have made a ton of money
before we were censored, I would make enough money
to fund the operation.
And if I had extra money, I'd hire more people
and expand because my mission was to beat the New World Order.
I never cared about money.
But now I can tell you going into the future,
you'll be able to stave this off a little bit longer,
but not longer if you do have money.
I mean, this is a world civilization ending event
coming up, and it's all right there.
I mean, man, they are talking about everyone vaccinated
is going to have Alzheimer's, including children,
and society is going to collapse and they're
going to have to have robots clean us all up
off the streets.
And I mean, I knew this was all coming.
I already laid it out.
But my God, this is scarier than my film Endgame.
And they were going to be like, oh, well,
this is scarier than my film Endgame, and they wrote
the damn thing.
Oh, God.
Do they get royalties for that?
I don't even know what to do at this point.
Just please save us, God.
God's like, yeah, well, stop killing all those babies.
Weird God.
So just a quick fact check.
There's literally nothing in the Johns Hopkins report
about anything close to what Alex is making up here.
The robots cleaning up dead body stuff is just from Soylent
Green, and the word Alzheimer's doesn't even appear
in the document.
Now that makes perfect sense.
The Johns Hopkins document is about public health
communication challenges that could come up in the event
of a disease outbreak.
It's comically stupid for Alex to pretend there's
a chapter on how everyone's going to be dead and robots
will clean up our corpses.
It'd be a really weird flourish for them to just be like,
oh, and also the vaccine causes Alzheimer's even in children.
Like, that's a clause.
Also, Alex loves money.
Yeah, so much.
He should be swimming in a Scrooge McDuck style.
Yeah, yeah.
Also, at the end of the April 1st show, Alex interviews
James O'Keefe about some footage he apparently got of
immigrants living in poor conditions.
This falls under the heading of a subject I care about,
and it's a political issue that means quite a bit.
It's something that people should be paying attention to,
but I do not trust that the person delivering this message
is acting in good faith.
Oh, no.
And I don't care.
No.
I've reserved the right to ignore anything James O'Keefe
does, so fuck him.
Let's move on to April 2nd.
Yeah, 100% fuck James O'Keefe.
I could have seen that being an April Fools episode, though.
The way Alex is like, I'm not covering this document until
Saturday.
Then he lies a bit about it.
A little touch and go on it.
James O'Keefe's existence is a joke.
Has Roger on, and Alex sort of pretends that the conversation
didn't involve Matt Gaetz the day prior.
Sure, sure.
It's very weird.
Never thought of Matt Gaetz before, honestly.
So we get to the second, and the tone is completely changed.
Things are totally different.
Look at these headlines on Infowars.com.
Biden infrastructure bill includes $20 billion
to destroy highways for being racist.
Now, if you're not aware of this, I'm not joking.
Here's some of the headlines.
Here's out of the News Gazette.
Biden administration may target racist highways.
That was December.
A woman called for highway removal in a black neighborhood.
Oh, my God.
One person calls for a statue to come down.
One person calls for a cross to come down.
One person calls for a highway to come down.
The White House singled it out in its infrastructure plan
as racist, and they're announcing the big, giant highway
that brings all the jobs to the neighborhood,
and people can get around the town will be destroyed.
I mean, I shouldn't laugh at this.
This is so evil, ladies and gentlemen.
We covered this back in the endgame coverage,
so I don't want to dwell too much on the subject,
but in case Alex is listening,
the history of the placement of highways is incredibly racist.
The fact that he's laughing at the idea and mocking it
really only reveals that he has no idea
about the history of that subject.
Totally.
No one's calling for all highways to be gone,
so there can't be business or travel anywhere.
The conversation is about how the ways
that highways have been constructed in the past
often has been done with absolutely no regard
for minority communities and often to their detriment.
There's tons of primary sources Alex could read up on
if he's interested in the devastating impact
that practices like redlining had on communities of color
in this country in terms of social impacts
and the destruction of economic power over generations.
The history of redlining in Chicago is so fucked.
Yeah, Alex is a stupid, stupid bigot
who doesn't actually care about reporting accurate information
or depicting reality to his audience.
He's just interested in protecting the notions of whiteness.
And I am demanding that Joe Biden destroy
all of Illinois's portion of Route 66.
I want it all gone.
You don't want to get kicks anymore?
No more historic Route 66.
I want all the signs taken down.
I want the asphalt dug up.
I have no skin in this game, so I'll support you on this.
Historic mote 66 is what I want.
Fill it with water.
Fill it with water and crocodiles.
I don't want to see that part of the state anymore.
Does the Dan Ryan survive?
Well, why not?
Okay.
So, tyranny.
You heard of it.
I am familiar.
It's speeding up and has been speeding up over time.
That doesn't sound 100% wrong.
And we're there.
It's fucking tyranny, man.
This is what they like to do.
And they're doing it to us in an act of raw power and domination.
And we sit here with our open free society model
in a daze as it moves so quickly.
Ten years ago, we were going five miles an hour.
Five years ago, we were going 50 miles an hour.
Ooh, that's faster.
Three years ago, we were going 100 miles an hour.
Whoa.
Honestly, though, if you think about the time in between these speeds,
that is a very slow acceleration.
Yeah, it's not quite parabolic, is it?
Two years ago, we were going 200 miles an hour.
A year ago, we were going 500 miles an hour.
And now we're going 10,000 miles an hour down the rattle.
That's a big job.
That was parabolic.
And we're going to go a million miles an hour.
And two million miles an hour.
That's quick.
And a billion miles an hour.
Right into hell, ladies and gentlemen.
That's how tyranny works.
It builds up.
It gets its confidence going.
People submit.
And like dominoes, boom, kills everybody.
OK.
And John Hopkins, I'll cover it tomorrow, has got it all laid out,
how the collapse is going to work, how there are going to be so many brain
damaged people from these vaccines that society will shut down.
Naturally.
We're just going to have big mass reclamation centers
right out of Soylent Green where we're just killing people around the clock.
Young people, old people, you just sign the paperwork,
roll your son in, your daughter in, your mama, your daddy.
20 years old, 30 years old, 60 years old.
Because they could have just given them something that killed them right away.
That'd be too obvious you'd fight back or something kills you on the road.
But instantly when you finally die, they want it to be something that wipes you out.
They want it to be something that weighs on everyone.
They want the sorrow and the pain and the breakdown and have the big medical system
suck everything out of you, squeezing you dry before they blast you out of the dust.
None of that is in the document.
Yeah.
I like how he describes something from Soylent Green
and then says that it's in the document like in Soylent Green.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's real convenient.
It is really helpful for movies to tell you what is in the document you're talking about.
Yeah.
Yeah, I could describe any movie and then just claim that it's what a document says
and be like, it's like The Matrix.
Sure.
It doesn't matter.
Oh man.
You're not doing anything.
Dude, the Rockefeller report on 13 going on 30 and body swap issues.
Holy shit.
Insane.
Yeah, that's insane.
We're all going to swap with our parents.
I read that document out of the Aspen Institute about body swapping.
No, we're going to learn important lessons about walking in each other's shoes.
It's actually going to be great.
Right.
But the people who don't learn those lessons, it's going to create a community of-
Oh no, we're going to be robots in the streets cleaning them up.
Displaced within other people.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, it'd be terrible.
Terrifying.
Illegal immigration inside a body.
Ooh, that's a-
We're going to have to have a lot of new regulations.
Oh, it's going to be an issue.
And the Aspen Institute is working on that and I appreciate it.
I think it's good.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I've been saying that Alex isn't really supporting Gates as much.
Right.
And that is mostly because it was aggressive at the end of March.
Those last episodes in March, it was over the top.
I fucked underage women.
What?
I didn't mean to say that in defense of Matt Gaetz.
I meant to say it's okay if you fuck...
Nope, that's not good either.
Oh boy.
Wait, you're telling me he dated a 17-year-old three years ago?
What's the big deal?
Yeah, she's...
Yeah, it's fine.
So, but in total fairness, Roger was still defending him.
And Alex on the April 2nd episode does sort of support him.
But you can sense a lack of enthusiasm.
A little reticence.
A little bit just like...
But Matt Gaetz with no proof why he's got to be removed.
While they're saying he might have given a 22-year-old girl $1,000 one time.
And maybe she flew on a commercial flight with him.
So that's sex trafficking.
Of course, he's not on the Alita Express flying to a Caribbean island.
And now we're learning it's not a 17-year-old girl, but it's okay.
Because Tim Cook runs Death Tamps.
What?
They're the moral media.
They're gonna get that Matt Gaetz.
Matt Gaetz did something real.
I'd throw him under the bus just like that.
But that's not what happened here.
I've also gotten to experience them doing it to me.
But of course, I said, go ahead, publish all your lies.
And of course, they don't.
Still needing to bring himself into it.
I know.
Unnecessary.
Very strange.
I want...
If he says something like, oh, if it's real, I'll throw him under the bus.
I want a countdown clock to appear right over his head.
Sure.
You know?
Just like Ted.
But you can sense the different tone.
Like, that's very different than he was before.
This is the dismount.
So anyway, Alex goes to calls, and he gets this one caller.
And this is sort of...
The call wasn't interesting, but he said something that I wanted to play as like,
this is the type of person who believes in Alex's shit.
Sure.
When you think about the UN, the UN was created because of the Club of Rome, basically,
to give the Antichrist his power.
That's what the UN was created.
I'm sorry, what now?
So the Club of Rome was founded in 1968, and the UN began in 1945.
Yeah, because they knew the Club of Rome was coming.
Right.
Yeah.
I mean, do you understand, like, there's just this...
This is the sort of thinking.
No, no, no, no, Dan.
You're not understanding.
I believe the Club of Rome he's speaking about...
Oh, boy.
Is Romulus and Remus.
And the wolves.
Exactly.
I mean, like, okay, so the Antichrist needs to get its power.
Sure.
And that's why they made the UN.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
13 years later, the Club of Rome is founded.
It just doesn't make any sense.
Anyway, Alex in between calls rambles a little bit about how,
oh, God, wouldn't it be so great if the US and Russia became best friends?
Oh, that would be great.
And anybody that studies geopolitics knows that the US links up with Russia geopolitically.
It's over those two countries could dominate the world for good and a new golden age.
But alas, we know that's not how it works, right?
Anybody can read Revelation and the Dragon.
The whole war that happens, we all know it unfolds.
What?
So now the holy war that unfolds is between the United States and Russia.
I guess so.
But also, this is a real strong argument of pre-determinism.
Yeah.
There's no free will.
It does seem like that.
Yeah.
It does seem like we're dipping into Calvin territory.
This is a horrifying view.
Of course, we all know what happens in Revelation.
Yeah.
Geopolitically, if the US and Russia teamed up, they could dominate the world.
But we know from Revelation that's not going to happen.
But that's such a fucking cop out.
Fuck you.
Fair enough.
How dare you?
The Book of Revelation doesn't also include, like,
a hundred years of prep time for the Antichrist to rise.
There is that part in Revelation about how the devil's ten years behind.
Wow, that was an interesting thing for Jon to add.
Yeah.
So we get another caller, and this dude is on every fucking episode.
He calls in all the time.
There's a dude named Carlos.
Okay.
And he thinks that everything that's going on right now is an attack on Christianity.
Sure.
What do you...
Obviously, I'm going to cover this John Hopkins document tomorrow that admits we're in a simulation
takeover.
The vaccines are going to make a lot of people sick.
It's a society collapsing weapon.
It's so incredible.
What is their big end game?
Why are they so savage?
Why are they moving ahead with something so incredibly dangerous and committing these
giant mass crimes?
Because what people don't realize, and this is Good Friday to think about it, this is
an Antichristian worldwide movement.
Sure.
It is led by individuals who are not Christians.
Exactly.
The US is taking more vaccines than anybody else, and predominantly it's Christian countries
being hit by this.
You're exactly right.
I don't know how this dude gets on every day.
Almost every day.
It makes me think that either he has a priority number or they don't get that many calls.
I doubt they get that many calls.
Because that Carlos dude is on all the fucking time.
Okay.
And Alex has a bizarre level of deference for him.
He lets Carlos talk for quite a while.
Carlos seems like a guy that is in the circle.
He has some thoughts.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know, maybe he's just letting people talk too much now because he gets another
caller, and I will say that he let this guy talk too long.
Too long?
A little bit too long.
Oh, that's unsurprising.
Not the same kind of problems that Harrison Smith gets when people talk too long.
Sure.
This guy just sounds a little bit sovereign citizen-y.
Oh.
You know, we have some really big issues.
Trump owns the original post office, and it's been...
The original post office?
The wars are between post office.
And, you know, this whole thing is about the legal fictions that Congress created to our
birth certificates that were representing that all caps name.
So...
Is that MF2?
What you said over and over, we're operating under color of law.
Color of law.
And until and unless we refute their presumptions and stop representing that all caps name,
now you can find an explanation of that at Adebon Red, Article number 73.
She really, really gets into it and has sent notices.
Beautiful, brother.
I got to tell you, everybody, thank you, Steven.
Beautiful.
Wow.
So...
All caps when you spell the man named, and...
Do do do do do do do do do.
Right.
Beyond that, and that's just standard sovereign citizen stuff.
Yeah, naturally.
Hooray for that.
All caps, birth certificate, you're great.
Now, I was unaware that Trump owns the original post office.
I was surprised to discover that as well.
And that all wars are wars between post offices.
Did you not know that?
I didn't.
Did you not know that there has been a hundred year secret war between post offices?
Ever since one guy, his horse knocked over another guy's horse and started the great
post office war.
I feel like probably there were, in earlier times, some feuding...
Sure, of course.
Between, like...
Capitalism is capitalism.
If you're getting paid by the letter, yeah, people are going to fight.
Oh, these days.
A little different.
Not sure.
So this show sucks.
This episode is not good.
Sorry, I just got the image of, you know, just a regular post office driver just driving
on the with the door open on the wrong side.
And you're like, isn't that cute? You guys are driving.
They get out and then they're suddenly attacked by another post office guy.
Throws him into the open window of the car and lights it up on fire.
The FedEx boys jump UPS boys.
It's the IRA of post offices.
Yes, I gotcha.
So, like I said, this show sucks.
This episode's bad.
And in the third hour, Alex has Drew Hernandez on, who's another reporter baby.
I find this guy's voice incredibly annoying.
He's on to talk about the border and talk about, oh, everything is.
Oh, those people from not here.
They're coming to here and we don't want them here.
They're from not here.
But Mike down for this, because this is how the interview started and where I turned it off.
OK.
You were saying, yeah, well, let's get into the border, but also some of the culture war stuff
and some of the things that are going on as they put us onto this virtual economy.
Tell us about it.
Yeah, I mean, I'm pretty sure your viewers are familiar with Bad Baby.
You know, she's the catch me outside girl that was on Dr. Phil and extremely viral,
totally depraved.
She made an OnlyFans.
I got to go.
I don't know.
I don't know what good is going to come with this conversation about the cash me outside girl.
No, we get only fans.
No, I don't care.
Did you know that somebody in a viral video has an OnlyFans account now?
Did I know she's a rapper?
Do I care?
No.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, sir.
Yeah.
I don't I don't care to listen to you, I guess.
I mean, best case scenario, shame someone for being a sex worker.
Like, I don't give a I don't I know people with OnlyFans accounts.
Cool.
Have fun.
Yeah, great.
I hope you supplement your income, I guess.
I don't know.
Yeah, if he's on to talk about the border.
But first, we're going to get into culture wars.
Someone has an OnlyFans account.
I'm mad about it.
I have to leave.
I can't I'm not going to take you seriously.
No, that's that's a dynasty level offense.
If I had a glass of wine in my hand, I would throw it in that guy's face.
How dare you say that.
The temerity.
Yeah.
And plus, like, I mean, realistically, Saturday is just right around the corner.
Of course.
I'm not going to waste my time with Drew Hernandez.
Yeah.
I'm not going to waste my time.
You've got an hour of meat and gristle to really dig your teeth into.
Yep.
So here we go.
This is where things start off with Alex covering the Johns Hopkins document.
Sure.
Now, most people that are informed have heard about Event 201.
They've heard about Operation Lockstep.
They've heard about Crimson Contagion.
They've heard about Disease X and the UN Drills.
But have you heard about
2025, 2028, it is all of those plans together.
It's not.
But not set in the near future, like those previous drills were,
but set out a few more years in the future.
That's the time we're in now.
So just superimpose 2025 to 2028 with 2020 to 2023.
And it is exactly what's happening.
So I love the idea that Alex says the Johns Hopkins scenario depicts things
exactly as they're happening in real life, just superimposed on a different date.
Also, nothing funnier than it's not a little bit in the future.
It's a few years.
It's not in the near future, idiots.
It's in the near, near future.
Alex didn't know where that sentence was going to end when it started.
That's a bad dismount.
So when he's talking about things being exactly like real life, just a few years off.
Sure.
I have a few things to say.
Okay, toss it at me.
First of all, one of the main tensions of the Hopkins exercise is messaging issues around
a drug that was believed to be effective against spars called Calosevir.
Calosevir.
There wasn't a drug that the government was trying to push for the treatment of COVID
in the way that the medical community gets behind Calosevir in this exercise.
Maybe remdesivir, possibly, but...
Yeah.
I mean, your basic there is like Trump and his messaging campaign pushed
hydroxychloroquine so hard.
Yeah.
The mixed messaging though.
Yeah, yeah.
It doesn't fit for this.
And I don't think that remdesivir does either in terms of the way it's depicted in the exercise.
So to me, this seems like one really big problem with the scenario matching real world history.
Second, backlash to Calosevir begins in February 2026, four months into the outbreak,
when a video of a child projectile vomiting after taking a dose goes viral online.
This did not happen four months into COVID, even metaphorically.
That's fair.
Third, in May 2026, a made up rapper named BZ suffers a public embarrassment when trying
to promote sparse treatments to his audience when he compares people who volunteer for
vaccine trials to participants in the Tuskegee experiments.
This did not happen in the real world.
Exhibit A in why scientists don't become rappers.
Our fictitious rapper is named BZ.
Sure.
There are plenty of examples of things like this that did not happen in the real world,
but do in the scenario exercise, because the point of the events that happened in the scenario
is to create situations where messaging challenges would arise that the exercise participants
could reflect on how best to respond.
The inclusion of a situation like this rapper making a public gaffe in this scenario doesn't
make sense out of context.
When you don't see this exercise within the context of why it exists, it seems really weird.
But when you understand that it's designed to assist medical communications professionals
brainstorm the ways that they might need to respond to various events in a crisis, the
picture makes far more sense.
At the same time that BZ makes his comments, the fictional former president, Jacqueline
Bennett, gives a noncommittal answer about whether or not she would give her grandson
callous of ear, which creates a similar but slightly different messaging problem for the
exercise participants to reflect on.
Sure, sure, sure.
Anyway, the point is a bunch of things that happen in very differently in this imagined
scenario than have happened in our real world outbreak.
Alex is just trying to pretend everything is the same because it's more fun and profitable
for him, but it's all made up.
So is this SBZ supposed to be a play on Yeezy?
I thought Jay-Z.
Well, I mean, but the very public gaffe would suggest more of a Kanye circumstance.
Yeah, you're not wrong, but I think that...
Are they saying that Kanye is going to Taylor Swift COVID-19?
No, because in the context of the scenario exercise, BZ is one of the people who was
enlisted to help get messaging out about the safety of the treatment.
And then he said George Bush doesn't care about black people.
I don't think that Kanye would be enlisted by the medical community.
Not anymore, not anymore.
So this document, my friend, is a timeline.
This is what you need to understand.
Naturally.
Timeline.
But a few years off into the near near future.
Basically, you just transpose the beginning of the outbreak to the outbreak in the document.
Sure.
You could tell what's going to happen in the future.
That sounds right.
And unfortunately, we are six months away from something bad.
Oh, that's bad.
Now, here's what's devastating.
We're about 13 months into the simulation that, again, is not really a simulation.
They're using that to cover their operations.
In case they get caught with the documents, they just say it's part of the drill.
That's a classic operation by intelligence agencies, governments, but also health agencies.
Classic by health agencies.
Next, they say that within six months to a year of people being inoculated with these
experimental GMO gene therapies, that you will have massive brain damage and spongiform
encephalopathy, basically, or prion disease, mad cow disease.
So that's good, good times.
That's a real bummer.
That's going to be a really rough six months to a year from now.
Don't worry, it's bullshit.
Oh, okay.
So in the exercise, there's this potential basis for a vaccine discovered in the form
of an animal vaccine for hoofed mammal respiratory virus developed by a company called GMI.
This condition was similar in many ways to SPARS, so researchers began looking at whether
or not it could be effective for humans.
One of the initial downsides was that, quote, data provided by GMI suggested that the vaccine
was effective at preventing SPARS-like illness in cows, pigs, and other hoofed mammals, but
internal trials revealed several worrisome side effects, including swollen legs, severe
joint pain, and encephalitis leading to seizures or death.
Right, and cows learning how to talk.
Sure.
In this scenario, in May 2027, a group of parents, the size of the group is unspecified,
they sue the government because they believe that their children got encephalitis from
the vaccine.
The claims are not presented as necessarily accurate.
It's just more detail added to make this a more real scenario, since this mirrors real
world anti-vax folks, and it's something that presents a challenge to the messaging that's
required for medical communicators.
Naturally.
The scenario does say that, quote, after showing no adverse side effects for nearly a year,
several vaccine recipients slowly began to experience symptoms such as blurry vision,
headaches, and numbness in their extremities.
Due to the small number of cases, the significance of the association with Corvax was never determined.
As of this writing in 2030, longitudinal studies initiated by the NIH at the beginning of
the vaccination program have not reached the next round of data collection, so formal
analysis of these symptoms has not yet been conducted.
Furthermore, these cases arose from the initial cohort of vaccine recipients, those in high
risk populations, including those with other underlying conditions, making it increasingly
difficult to determine the extent to which these symptoms are associated with vaccination.
I read this earlier, but I wanted to read it again because this brings up an important
point, and that is that these elements of the scenario, it's left intentionally open
ended because it exists to pose a question to the participants, not to depict a reality
that actually exists.
In that scenario, how does a person in a position of medical messaging respond?
How do you convey confidence on the medical side of things, while still acknowledging
certain uncertainties?
These are the sorts of questions this story arc is meant to bring up.
Because Alex knows better and he's a psychic, he's realized that this is actually the globalists
admitting that they're going to give everyone mad cow disease, when the encephalitis is
really just the animal vaccine that GMI created, and it's just encephalitis in animals, and
then there's some parents who allege encephalitis, but it's not actually proven in the case of
the scenario.
No, and that's maybe the most important question for the study to ask, which is how is it that
we can tell people, honestly, we don't know, and at the same time reassure them that they
can trust us?
Yeah, and one of the other things that they take great care to point out is exploring
ideas of how to be compassionate about the uncertainty, because it's an understandable
feeling for people to have, and how do you mix that compassion about the uncertainty
with the confidence in medical science?
It's a challenging thing, but that's why you do exercises like this.
Yeah, my message would probably not be good, it would be more something like, listen, we
know public education has failed you between first and eighth grade, at least.
You wouldn't make it through the exercise.
So the thing is that Alex is connecting this with the study that he's found, right?
So they say encephalitis in the scenario, right?
And that's like the Zika virus, right?
I just mentioned to you spongiform encephalopathy, or prion disease, microbiology infectious
diseases journal, COVID-19 RNA-based vaccines, and the risk of prion disease.
That was put out in 2021 by prestigious scientists.
Whenever you hear Alex say that a claim is being made by a prestigious scientist, that
means he has no idea who the person is.
Yeah, I was going to say that's a huge red flag immediately.
It's an unknown quantity, but he wants to elevate this claim that they're making because
it works well for him.
This claim that the COVID vaccine causes prion disease was based entirely on a non-peer reviewed
paper by a guy named J. Bart Klassen.
No one agrees with his conclusion, and he is not a prestigious scientist.
According to USA Today, quote, in 1999 he claimed the influenza vaccine caused type
one diabetes, a claim disproven by Johns Hopkins University Institute for Vaccine Safety.
He's just an anti-vax weirdo who makes these claims pretty regularly whenever there's a
vaccine that needs to be smeared.
Vaccines cause IBS!
Alright, man, okay.
So now Alex is there.
He's rolling deep, though, with the crew.
Sure.
To quote B.Z.
Nicely done.
He's got Rob Dues.
It is Easter, so Jesus walks.
Oh.
So Rob Dues is in studio, the corporate representative Rob Dues, and he's just blown away by this
document.
Rob Dues.
Yeah, so the parallels on this are just from a, when you looked at 9-11 and you saw the
parallels that happened, this has got the same thing in it with like massive power outages.
You've got a male and female president, the president who's a male stops after a few years,
the female who's, she's only in for one term and then she leaves and then the male president
takes over.
We kind of have that going on.
So first of all, Biden hasn't stepped down, so this isn't actually a similarity at all.
No, it's exactly like that.
It's happening, though.
You can see it.
I don't know if the Infowars universe is just so convinced that it's going to happen any
day now that they've just decided it's already happened, but this is just a similarity in
Rob's head.
So in this scenario, the president is named Randall Archer.
He'd previously been the vice president under Jacqueline Bennett.
She didn't step down, she just decided not to run for a second term after being president
from 2020 to 2024, at which point Archer ran and won.
Shouting, fuck you guys, you were shit.
Bennett is still actively involved in being an advisor, but was not up to seeking re-election
quote due to health concerns.
This is the case in the scenario because it creates an interesting dynamic where there's
a new president, but also a fully functioning and intact staff at the Department of Health
and Human Services.
In terms of what the exercise is designed to explore, this makes total sense.
Essentially, former President Bennett exists as a prop, so she can be a character that
makes a media gaffe where she gives that non-committal answer about Calus Avere.
Sure, sure.
The character that does that should be a beloved public figure, you know, because then it works,
there's a weird dynamic there, but it also shouldn't be the current president because
that's too weird.
So a former president works great.
In order to make that scenario work, she would have to have just had one term, and ideally
she shouldn't have just lost an election.
Seems like the best way to get to that story beat would be if you just didn't want to seek
re-election.
Everybody still trusts her, so the gaffe would carry so much weight that they would be influenced
by it, while at the same time, you couldn't lose an election and have everybody be influenced
in the same way.
It would be weird.
And you don't want it to be the current president because it adds a whole layer to it.
The other specific that Rob uses is this power outage, which I will admit is in the scenario.
There's a massive power outage in the Pacific Northwest just one week prior to the rollout
of the vaccine, which doesn't match up with what Rob wants it to in the real world, sure.
He's trying to compare that to the Texas outages, which happened well after vaccination programs
began and are reality.
Again, it's important to understand why this specific detail is included in the exercise.
This is all about medical messaging in a public health emergency, so this power outage was
added to the scenario so participants could consider what methods they might employ if
they didn't have access to things like social media.
With a massive power outage, one of the main methods of communications is less effective.
But you need to continue helping the public through, so what do you do?
This is super clear from the exercise if you read it, but if you just want to make random
connections, I guess you could do what Rob Doo is doing, and it's really embarrassing.
I mean, look, this is what it says in the text, quote, all communication about the vaccine
rollout was published in electronic form, and consequently many individuals in the affected
areas were initially unable to access information provided by state, local, and federal health
authorities regarding CoraVax dispensing.
Reasonable.
Immediately after this, there are study questions for the participants in the document, like,
quote, while greater use of electronic media opens new opportunities for broad outreach,
what communications vulnerabilities exist that could impede communication efforts via
electronic media?
Or the other question, quote, how can public health communicators remain flexible when
multiple disasters occur at once?
Right.
In their paper about designing scenario-based exercises, Ogilvy and Schwartz discuss the
need for stories that follow various plots, and one of the most common archetypes is crisis
and response.
This plot element is about introducing a big problem, and then the participants get to
respond.
The paper discusses an exercise they ran with Shell that followed basically this exact same
path.
Quote, first comes the scenario's crisis.
Initial signs of environmental degradation lead reputable scientists to conclude that
an environmental disaster is fast approaching.
A few leading governments and companies change the way they do business.
Disasters begin to occur in countries that could not or chose not to adapt, and there's
public outcry.
The playing field, the organizational operating environment, is suddenly dramatically altered.
The innovative firms that learn to make difficult changes in their business practices to avoid
environmental degradation are now positioned to become market leaders.
In the Johns Hopkins exercise, the outbreak itself is the initial crisis.
Then things like the power outage in the Pacific Northwest or the video of the kid vomiting
represent new crises that the participants have to deal with.
This is the context of what Alex and Rob are lying about, and it makes total sense there's
no way to read that document and not understand that that's what it is.
That's so funny to me that they missed the most important question of having that kind
of power outage a week before the vaccine rollout, which would just simply be like,
okay, an astonishing number of people are going to think that God is punishing us for
this vaccine.
How do we deal with that?
Or are all the Proud Boys accounted for?
Yeah, is this witches?
People are going to ask us why God punished us with this power outage before the vaccine.
You know what?
That isn't in the exercise, but I think...
It's a subtext.
Jordan, to be fair, it was made in 2017.
That's true.
If it was made today, that might've been a relevant messaging question, but yeah.
Okay.
People are going to assume meteorologists are witches.
What do we do about that from a health standpoint?
It's interesting to me that this is how Rob Dues starting it out.
He's talking about these similarities.
One is not a similarity at all in that Biden hasn't stepped down, and even if he did, it
doesn't match the scenario that's depicted in the exercise.
And then the other one is that there's a power outage, but they're completely different situations.
And if you understand what the document is for, it makes total sense that a power outage
would be in there.
It creates an important teaching moment about using non-electronic methods.
Every time Dues goes to a diner, he has failed the, what are the three differences picture.
Oh dude.
He's never gotten one of those cereal boxes, placemats, it doesn't matter.
Shut up.
I just had a great idea.
Okay.
Have you ever played Overcooked?
Uh, yes.
We tried one time.
Yeah, it's that game where you have to cook meals, you know, like you're running around
chopping up an onion.
You gotta do the thing.
It's like Burger Boss or whatever it is.
I have a new idea.
Okay.
Dues Diner.
Try and figure out puzzles that are way too easy.
No, no, no.
It's Overcooked, but the goal is to fail.
You just have to fail interestingly.
Yeah, yeah.
I like that game.
That's a good open-ended game.
Anybody who can program an app, don't waste your time on that.
Please don't.
Uh, so Alex gets to starting up reading the, uh, the document and this is fun.
I love this.
Let's go ahead and begin here.
Here is the project team who is on it.
All these different top eugenicists, top globalist, uh, from around the country.
John Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health.
The team, uh, it's top eugenicists, right?
It's five senior associates with the Johns Hopkins Center for Health Security, a professor
from Texas State, and a Masters of Public Health candidate from Columbia University.
Well yeah.
Top eugenicists.
How do you get any of those things without a proven track record of top eugenicism?
Alex has no idea who any of these people are.
Why would you?
Just making this up.
Why would you know who they are?
Oh yeah, this Masters student is a fucking top eugenicist.
A sane person who doesn't directly, uh, affect, uh, interact with these people know who they
are.
This Columbia University grad student is a sixth generation eugenicist.
Sure.
Ah.
So anyway, I warned you earlier that there was a squirrely weirdo coming up named Mike.
Mike.
Mike the squirrely weirdo.
I honestly don't know who this dude is.
I think he might be an Infowars employee.
He might be Harrison Smith's roommate.
Sure.
I don't fucking know.
Could be anybody.
But he is weird.
Wife's tennis instructor.
He is weird.
He's a liar.
Okay.
And, uh, this can be found inside of the sparse document word for word after showing no adverse
side effects for nearly a year, vaccine recipients slowly began to experience symptoms as time
passed and more people across the United States were vaccinated claims of adverse side effects
began to emerge.
As the investigations grew in intensity, several high ranking officials at the CDC and FDA
were forced to step down and withdraw from government.
They're setting up the health officials and the politicians to take the fall for this.
What Mike is reading here, that's definitely from the document, but he's made a classic
Infowars move here and that he's taken two unrelated passages from the text and combine
them, pretending they're about the same thing in order to lie about this document.
Yeah.
The part about people experiencing side effects after a year is from chapter 17.
It's on page 60.
The second part about government officials stepping down is chapter 19.
It's on page 67.
It's completely unrelated to the previous chapter's conversation about possible side
effects.
Here is the paragraph about the government officials in full quote after action reports,
government hearings and agency reviews following the pandemic were too numerous to count.
Emergency funding appropriated by Congress to fight the disease became available partway
through the course of the pandemic, but federal state and local public health agencies struggled
to manage the procedural requirements to spend it.
That does sound familiar.
As a result, significant amounts of emergency funds remained unused as the pandemic wound
down.
As the investigations grew in intensity, several high ranking officials at the CDC and FDA
were forced to step down and withdraw from government in order to quote spend more time
with their families.
The investigations that are causing these imaginary officials to step down are not related
to possible drug side effects.
It's clearly about mismanagement of funds.
If this guy's read the document as he's presenting himself as having done, then he knows fully
well that the two passages he just read as if they were one paragraph are actually two
completely different sections of the document.
If this document actually said what he wanted it to, he wouldn't have to lie like this in
order to make it look like it met his needs.
This is bullshit, weirdo Mike.
That is funny that even in the Johns Hopkins report, it's like, listen, we all know at
least 15 to 20 senators are corrupt as shit.
We're just going to put in that some of them had to quit.
I mean, I think that the scenario paints a very realistic portrait of some of the things
that you could expect might happen.
Absolutely.
We'll deal with another one of them that Rob Dew thinks is maybe wizardry a little bit
later, but I don't know.
From reading the document, I think there's some pretty fair assumptions that are made
and then also some ones that are like, that's a little silly, but they're all in service
of what the document is for.
Right.
They're teaching documents.
They're still focused around this exercise that is how do medical communicators rise
to various challenges.
Now I think that clip right there where Mike is reading two different sections as if they
were the same, because when he's talking about these side effects, he then says, as investigations
grow in intensity, and that's meant to lead the audience to think that these investigations...
Very clearly split those quotes, but then combine them together to form a single quote.
Which leads you to believe that the investigations are about drug side effects, and that's how
they're going to set up the politicians to take the fall for this, has nothing to do
with that.
He has to know that.
And this is the point at which any reasonable person would just be like, fuck this.
You're absolutely misrepresenting the primary document you're talking about, and there's
no way that that is an accident.
There's no way you did this accidentally.
Well, I mean, it's somewhat similar to Alex's synopsis of Romeo and Juliet in so far as
he leaves out a bunch of the middle between those two things.
No it's not.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, I know.
It would be like if he threw in a little bit of Hamlet.
Yeah, that sounds fun.
So anyway, Mike gets to being weird some more about a passage about vaccine distribution.
To determine how to best distribute limited doses of Corovax to members of priority groups
across the country, the US government resorted to new controversial tactics, notably having
health care providers access patients' electronic health records to determine the number of
individuals in high-risk populations receiving care in particular areas.
This passage really undercuts the argument that this document represents the globalist
plan because they didn't do that.
Also, while we're on the subject of things that didn't happen in real life that do happen
in the scenario, we should look at chapter 10 and see one of the big, uh, giant, gigantic,
I'm going to come up with more words, one of the big public messaging crises that come
up over the course of the exercise.
Gojira emerged from the ocean.
No, that's chapter 12.
Oh, okay, okay.
In chapter 10 of the scenario, there's a huge public backlash because doctors and nurses
aren't included in the highest priority group for the distribution of the vaccine.
Yeah, that would cause a huge public backlash.
Yeah, they even designed two fake tweets that illustrate the outrage that was happening
in the medical worker communities.
There's a strike in Milwaukee among health care providers when they won't go to work
unless they're made of vaccine priority.
Yeah.
And none of that happened in life.
Yeah, no, that's a totally reasonable thing for them to do were that unreasonable thing
to occur.
Sure.
Yeah.
Also in the scenario, there's a groundswell of college activism taking place in the social
media app that's created for this exercise called Unequal.
On the exercise, quote, another group that was not generally affected by the government's
Corovax promotion efforts were college students, especially those attending school on the east
and west coasts.
Public health officials had no explanation for the lack of vaccine uptake among this
population until protests began at several college campuses, including UC Berkeley, the
University of Washington, Reed College, Harvard, and the University of Chicago.
The focus of these protests was the lack of access to Corovax, particularly for populations
in less developed countries like Haiti, Guatemala, and Cameroon.
The college students involved declared that they would not accept Corovax until it was
made available in terms of both access and expense to everyone in the world who wanted
it.
Right.
This, too, did not happen in the real world.
Right, right, right.
Yeah.
The reason these events are included in the scenario is the same as anything that is in
there.
They present an opportunity for the participants to wrestle with challenges in the field of
medical messaging.
None of it's real, but it portrays situations that are close enough to seeming real for
them to be effective in role-playing situations.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And that's enough for Alex to think that it's all secretly real.
Yeah, I mean, it seems fun whenever these studies predict events that do wind up occurring,
because you're like, ooh, look at how good those predictions are.
But it's really just based on the shit we've already seen that's going to almost certainly
happen again, because people don't learn lessons from things exactly like the thing that we're
writing now.
So Mike is a weirdo, I've decided.
And he reads this passage, and again, normal people would have checked out already, but
I'm not normal.
I still want to hear more.
I mean, this gets worse, Alex.
Severe side effects, including swollen legs, severe joint pain, and encephalitis potentially
resulting in seizures, seizure disorders, or death occasionally occurred word for word
from the document.
Something now happening in Max.
We've got to add all the B-roll to that.
So what Mike is failing to mention here is the passage he's reading is about the side
effects.
It's not for the Corvex human vaccine.
It's from the section about the vaccine for animals.
There's an added bit of comedy in that he's reading a quote from a fake email that the
scenario created in order to depict an exchange of information about an animal vaccine, and
then Mike's dumb ass is pretending it's a document talking about human side effects.
Just amazing.
That is real, real bummer town level shit.
Here's what he read in context, what the actual thing says, quote, in 2021 a coronavirus caused
an outbreak in region seven, parenthetically Southeast Asia, in the hoofed mammal populations.
Our researchers developed and produced in-house an effective vaccine against the infection.
Its subsequent approval and use successfully ended the outbreak in the region.
While largely effective in preventing infection, severe side effects, including swollen legs,
severe joint pain and encephalitis, potentially resulting in seizures, seizure disorder or
death occasionally occurred.
Given the millions of vaccinations required for region seven, this resulted in measurable
losses in the animal population.
This is critical to understand.
If this document actually said what these dumdums were claiming it was, they wouldn't
resort to tactics like this.
This is so manipulative, it's nonsense.
This is bullshit.
If it were truly a smoking gun, they'd just be able to read it.
They wouldn't have to pretend that they were reading this fake email from the document
as if it's a real thing about a human vaccine.
What's the point of having these things if you're just going to highlight like one paragraph
from every other chapter and then just combine them into a single double-spaced page?
You know?
Why?
Yeah.
Fuck off.
So Mike reads a passage about conspiracy theories that go around.
And Alex gets so excited that he has to read it himself.
Oh boy.
I think it's because he's like, I want to maybe use a cut of me saying this later, like
in a John Bowne report, and I don't want to have this weirdo reading it.
I want it to be in my voice.
Conspiracy theories also profited across social media suggesting that the virus had been purposely
created and introduced to the population by drug companies or that it had escaped from
a government lab secretly testing bio-weapons.
This is in 2017 right after Fauci says a virus will be released.
It's going to happen.
It's going to challenge Trump.
It's going to be a surprise operation.
Fauci didn't say that.
In the speech that he was given, we've talked about this, he was talking about how every
administration deals with an unforeseen health crisis.
And he said that conspiracy theories would abound that it would escape from a government
lab just 20 years after Alex started saying that every four months.
Yeah.
That's interesting too.
It's like, we listened to that 2003 episode and now it's just saying foot and mouth came
out of port and down.
Yeah.
The same thing.
It's like, yeah, of course they would add that scenario in there.
That's what you do.
That's one of the things that's like, oh, this is giving texture to the world.
Exactly.
And it's not even a major point.
That's not even like...
It's just mentioned.
Yeah.
And it's after the fact.
It's after the entire course of the outbreak happens in terms of the document.
Call me when conspiracy theorists in this paper decide to inspire people to overthrow
the country.
So Mike, I mean, look, some of this stuff, I don't know.
Like someone who's really generous might be able to say he's just sloppy.
Sure.
But there's intention behind the misrepresentations he's presenting.
I don't believe that he did this by accident.
Someone incredibly generous, neither of which are we.
No.
Also, I think...
I heard this and I got really worried.
This took me two weeks to read, by the way.
The wording, it weaves everything together so you're like, what is going on?
Is this an exercise?
Is this real?
I was just trying to do the best job I can to extract everything.
So if you had five minutes, you could just understand what's happening.
Oh my God.
Bad.
Super bad.
Oh my God.
Some things require more than five minutes.
That's a good thing.
Sure.
I can't imagine taking two weeks and then coming away with that sort of sewn together
quotation that misrepresents the point.
I don't understand, too, being able to look at this and not be able to understand fairly
quickly what it is.
I understand if you see it out of context, completely out of context, it could be confusing
for a bit.
Sure.
But if you sat down...
Perhaps you only had five minutes to hear about it.
Sure.
If you sat down and actually read a couple pages, it explains the exercise at the beginning.
Yeah, of course.
It explains...
I don't know.
It starts with, Dear Alex Jones, please, we're explaining the exercise.
You literally can't use this for your propaganda.
I really, really don't understand the idea of anyone sitting with this for an hour, let
alone two weeks, and coming away with any confusion about, oh, also there is a disclaimer
that Alex shouldn't use this.
Let me read this, quote, this is a hypothetical scenario designed to illustrate the public
health risk communication challenges that could potentially emerge during a naturally
occurring infectious disease outbreak requiring development and distribution of a novel and
or investigational drugs, vaccines, therapeutics, or other medical countermeasures.
The infectious pathogen...
Oh, I just did an Alex.
The infectious pathogen, medical countermeasures, characters, news media, excerpts, social media
posts, and government agency responses described herein are entirely fictional.
So there is a disclaimer.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But that does not stop these dorks.
Doesn't sound like it.
Dan, it's about what they're not saying.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
It's like jazz.
Yeah, exactly.
So here's Mike.
Two weeks of study.
Two weeks of intense study.
And now he's going to bring back up this power outage.
Okay.
A week before Corovax was released for distribution in the United States, the power grid at the
Grand Coulee Dam in eastern Washington state experienced a catastrophic failure.
While the event did not destroy any infrastructure or result in any deaths, it did cause widespread
power outages in Washington, Oregon, Idaho, Montana, and British Columbia.
Though power was restored within a day of the initial outage, blackouts continued plaguing
these areas over the next three weeks.
And the resurgence of the banned widespread panic.
Why would they put that in a vaccine exercise?
Because they're all behind all this.
They're showing off to their people.
Keep going.
Yeah.
So Mike seems so confused by why they would include something about a power outage in
this document about a medical situation.
But if he'd actually read it, he shouldn't be confused.
It's literally spelled out in the exercise.
This is very clearly to get participants to consider how to be effective in getting messaging
out in a real non-digital world.
From the scenario, quote, state and local public health officials scrambled to hand
deliver flyers printed and copied at local emergency operation centers using backup generators
to explain vaccine prioritization and POD information.
This extremely time-consuming effort exhausted the public health workforce already stretched
thin by the epidemic response and several years of budget cuts.
But it was ultimately successful.
Early vaccination rates in Washington, Oregon, and Idaho were very similar to other states
and in some cases above average.
In spite of this success, the incident underscored the shortcomings associated with relying solely
on electronic communication strategies.
That what I just read to you is immediately after the part he was reading.
Yeah, it makes it very clear.
Almost impossible to misunderstand.
Yes.
There's no way to believe that he took two weeks to read this and couldn't understand
what the point was.
This is either someone who's deeply disturbed and needs help, needs like mental help, or
he's a willful liar.
And I'm more inclined to believe it's the latter.
Yeah, I mean, this is not a generous interpretation, but the idea of these people reading a document
that tells them what it says absolutely does confuse them.
Like on a deep level.
Yeah, yeah.
Because they can't just be like, oh, like that's not a thing they can do.
They can't read an explanation of what's happening and go, oh, well they're being honest with
me.
I understand that.
You know?
I understand that dynamic.
Now, if they weren't copy and pasting various parts of the document in order to create a
misrepresentation of what it says, if they weren't pretending that side effects and animals
were actually humans, like if they weren't doing stuff like that, then maybe I would
be like, oh, this is just suspiciousness run amuck.
But there is work that's been done in order to misrepresent this document.
Not two weeks' worth, but there has been work done.
No.
Now, Jordan, Rob, do he's about to have his mind blown, man.
This doc.
Okay.
It's crazy.
Let's go to the next one.
You look at the similarity to the names, spars, COVID, and then we have SARS COVID two.
Okay.
Same.
Almost same exact name.
And they wrote this three or four years before they added a number and they, and they, and
they just added a P, they added a P and a V.
Exactly.
It's really crazy.
Where's the V?
It's almost like scientists aren't interested too much in different naming conventions when
it comes to viruses.
And instead it's almost a classification.
Yeah.
Spars, it means St. Paul acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus, which is similar to
SARS COV-2.
Yeah, sure.
The reason that this is probably, it's named after the city that it popped up in.
And the reason that it is that, and we've had this whole thing about not naming things
after places is because that whole thing is a world health organization convention that
you don't name something after the city or the location where it came up and the world
health organization isn't involved in this exercise.
Because that would give a massive incentive for people to be like, never fuck with those
people ever again.
Don't go to St. Paul.
Exactly.
Plus this was in 2017, which is fairly shortly after the world health organization changed
its best practices about that whole thing.
So there may have been some lingering confusion about naming conventions.
Sure.
I almost guarantee that if the world health organization had made this scenario, it probably
would have named the condition SARS COV-2 and like Rob Dew would have a heart attack.
Yeah, no, he would shit.
Yeah.
He would just shit.
Fuck it.
I might shit.
Yeah.
It is not weird.
No.
At all.
It's a convention.
It's a naming convention.
It's a fucking taxonomy, you know?
It's like kingdom phylum, you know, it's yeah.
In terms of like a conspiracy theory, this is the one that rises to the level of, eh,
eh, eh.
How about that?
Their names are, yeah.
That's how they name stuff.
Yep.
There's another connection with the real world though.
Do they want them to name viruses like they do hurricanes?
Like this is virus Maria.
Is that what they would feel better about?
Maybe.
Well.
Let's flip another thing in this, uh, this next clip that, uh, that it is kind of similar
to real world.
Then we have the inflated fatality estimates.
Initially they write in the scenario, CDC fatality rate, almost 5%, who fatality rate
14 and a half percent.
And then the fatality rate of over 64 is 50%.
This is fair.
The inflated death estimates are in the scenario, but they're there for a few reasons.
The first is that the scenario is supposed to depict reality and the reality of dealing
with a completely new disease is that sometimes you get some things off.
One of the main reasons is actually spelled out in the document.
If you read it quote at the outset of the sparse outbreak, physician's understanding
of the disease stem primarily from extremely severe cases resulting in pneumonia or hypoxia.
There required hospitalization and extensive medical treatment, mild cases of the disease,
which produced symptoms, including cough, fever, headaches, and malaise were often perceived
as the flu by people who had them and consequently often went untreated and undiagnosed by medical
personnel.
As a result, early case fatality estimates were inflated.
This is a real dynamic that we've seen play out in the COVID-19 outbreak, but it's been
true in other past outbreaks as well.
The issue is that you can't always assume that it's going to be the case or else you're
putting yourself in a position to get blindsided by a super deadly condition that you happen
to underestimate.
It's far better to be over cautious with new diseases than to just let them go and see
what happens.
Again, this is what we talked about, diseases have killed almost all of us.
Yeah, be careful.
We should be crazy.
Be careful with that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So the other reason that this is in the document is because it's made as an exercise for medical
communicators.
And what could be a greater communication challenge than having been wrong initially?
The study question for this section is quote, how can health authorities best meet public
demands for critical information such as what is the health threat and what do I know about
it when the crisis is still unfolding and not all the facts are known?
If you understand this in the context it was written and used, all of the things that they're
trying to create paranoia about just sound fucking stupid.
Yeah.
It's awesome.
It is awesome.
Dude, this next thing that they try and make like a conspiracy out of, holy shit, these
guys are dumb.
All right, sell me on it.
Let's go to the antivirals is the next slide.
In this scenario, they have one called Calosovir, all right?
Teens in an IR, side effects, nausea, headaches, vomiting, and body aches.
There's actually a viral video of a boy in this scenario taking the Colosovir and then
immediately projectile vomiting everywhere.
Yeah.
They even have videos of their scenario.
It's crazy.
And then, and they go back to it, then three years later, it's Remdesivir.
And this is not the real name.
This is the name they gave it later.
It's actually got a different name that they, that it's, that it's made from.
And remember they said Remdesivir was this new experimental thing they just developed.
Exactly.
But they had the damn name three years before.
Same side effects.
Nausea, constipation, vomiting.
They only changed a few letters.
It's all about rubbing in their faces.
It is.
They really do.
This is smoking gun.
If these dudes cared at all, they could learn why these drugs have similar names.
They could learn so much.
Yeah.
These are generic names for the drug, which is to say they're not brand names.
Right.
The convention for naming generic drugs is to have the suffix of the word indicate what
the drug is.
For instance, antiviral drugs generally end in the suffix V-I-R for viral.
This isn't universal, but most of them end up with this, uh, this, and that's why these
two do.
Sure.
You know, you can go down the list of antiviral, and then also like penicillin derived drugs
have cillin, like a box of cillin.
Right, right, right, right.
It's how drugs are named.
It's very simple.
It's, and it's done that way on purpose to be simple so people don't have to, yeah, no.
The people making the scenario were striving to fill it with realistic details, so they
followed accepted conventions for naming the drug they made up in it.
Alex and Rob Dew are so stupid and so addicted to thinking coincidences mean something, that
they take that as a sign that the document is mocking them.
This is nuts.
Yeah.
It's, it's like just such a, just don't talk and just scream repeatedly, I refuse to learn
anything!
Yeah, it's outrageous.
Oh, they both end in I-O.
I refuse!
I refuse to read the first page of Google!
No!
They just changed a few letters.
You could type any of these questions into Google and the first result would tell you
what.
Yeah, it's really easy to understand these things.
It's so easy.
So this, this clip is just where everything turns to parody.
Rob is in the middle of complaining about like medical ads and stuff.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
Yeah, and then, and then you have the native ads, which are put out by the vaccine companies
saying the vaccine is safe and effective.
And that's all they do.
Vitamin Mineral Fusion is a remarkable product and it's back in stock 40% off at infowarsstor.com
right now.
Don't.
Don't do that to me.
It's almost like whoever edited this did that as a joke.
Did it on purpose, yeah.
That's, that's just too much.
He's complaining about like medical ads.
That is too much.
And then in the middle of it.
It's safe, they, these people, all they do is put out these ads that say things are safe
and effective.
Anyways, let's go to a commercial of Alex saying that his stuff is safe and effective.
Oh wow.
So yeah, they, they've, they've gone, gone a while now and Alex realizes.
We did it.
We, we, we have not done it.
Oh no.
We're all humans.
We're all people that care about freedom.
I get upset.
Rob gets upset.
As we spend weeks studying this, we finally get on air and it's just, it's so upsetting.
We've covered 10% of what's in front of us.
Every bit of this is just as insane or more insane.
I haven't even gotten to the part where they admit they're doing this to kill you and get,
and save the earth.
I mean, they admit they're doing this.
That part is not, not in the document.
They specifically say they're not doing this.
Although that would introduce a very interesting medical messaging challenge.
That would be an interesting medical, okay, let's say in this scenario, our secret plan
has gotten out and gotten into the hands of the least reliable and credulous person.
Now what do we do?
You can have, what do we do?
Let it go?
I guess.
Yeah.
Hit the panic button.
So yeah, I, I, this is, this is where I checked out.
Yeah, that's a good place to check out.
Well, no, this next clip.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
I should have checked out whenever Weird Mike was doing that stuff about the cut and
paste job that he did.
Naturally.
That's when you have like, all right, your credibility's out the window, I got to get
out of here.
Gone.
That's what I'm talking about.
This show is about giving too many chances.
Okay.
Um, and here's where I was like, Alex, go fuck yourself.
Spend a few minutes just in summation of, of the bombshells that have been released
here.
I mean, to me, the strongest thing is the drug name's the same before a drug even exists.
The virus name the same before they release it.
Them running the lab.
I mean, this is smoking gun one in 85 trillion quadrillion.
Wow.
So the, the, the thing that, that is so convincing for Alex is that there's similarities in the
name of Spars Cove and SARS-CoV-2 and the, uh, the name of two antiviral drugs end in
the same suffix.
This is nothing.
Yep.
This is outrageous.
Alex started promoting this on Thursday and this is the best he can do on Sunday or on
Saturday.
Wow.
It's, it's offensive to my professionalism.
What blew me away was that naming conventions can be used in a fictitious scenario also.
Yeah.
I never would have imagined that these people would have done something so insane as to
stick to basic borderline universally standardized naming conventions.
I'd listened to over an hour of this Saturday thing that they were doing and then Alex said
that.
And then Abdu brought up, oh, also, uh, they use some of the same hashtags and fake tweets
that they have on there that people used in real life.
I said, I gotta go.
Nope.
Don't care.
Throwing things.
No.
Immediate throwing of things.
That means nothing.
Yeah.
So anyway, I got really excited because, um, you know, I think after our last present day
episode I was, I was in the doldrums.
I felt bad.
Sure.
It was a very weird, uh, defense of Matt Gaetz.
And this was a promise of a primary source.
And, and no, no, I mean, that's what we found eventually.
Yeah, of course.
But, but Jordan, I mean like we were, you know, we talked over the weekend and I was
telling you, like, I really think that, you know, I, we've got to stay in the present
for Sunday.
I think Alex is probably going to have some, uh, some, something.
Yeah.
He's going to have something.
I thought for sure this Matt Gaetz thing would continue.
Because Matt Gaetz has had more information come out, it looks worse and worse.
I thought that Alex would either have to double down and triple down or he'd have to cut bait.
I didn't know what he was going to do.
And so I was like, well, I think in the interest of keeping people up to date on the, the goings
on of this, this, and then I dig in and here we are, we got, we got a new lockstep document.
And it's nice because, you know, I think, I think sometimes one of the things I enjoy the most
about doing this show is the opportunity to understand something like this document that's
called, it causes such fear for people.
Yeah.
Like to be able to, to see this, uh, Freddy Krueger on paper and understand it for what
it is and understand like some of the very interesting lessons that actually could have
been learned and, and, and, you know, that, that people are doing these, these kinds of
exercises that they probably did pay dividends.
Like we probably didn't see enough of the lessons learned, but on a, on a granular level
in terms of some people being able to better deal with the challenges that came up over
the course of this, this pandemic, this probably helped a lot.
Right.
Yeah.
And I appreciate that.
I like getting that glimpse.
Yeah.
It was a little bit like if, uh, Jamie Lee Curtis was running away from Michael Myers
the whole time.
And then at the end it was like, lady, I've been trying to deliver you this letter from
15 years ago.
You've been served.
I've been hanging onto it.
Yeah.
That whole thing of just like, this was a complete waste of time for everyone involved.
Why are we here?
I honestly enjoy having my time wasted like this far more than I enjoy most of present
day Alex Jones though.
At least you're having fun running away from Michael Myers, you know, you're not just sitting
at your home being like, this is a waste of time.
I'm getting a jog in.
Yeah, exactly.
I'm getting some calories burning.
Yeah.
I'm getting that cardio.
It's good stuff.
So thank you, Alex.
I don't look forward to him constantly bringing up this document.
Nope.
Uh, cause it's a big old zero.
Yeah.
Uh, but you know, Hey, whenever these things happen, it's often good for us to spend time
looking at it before it gets too out of control.
Too boring.
Yeah.
Cause I think, I think that this is something that definitely could have, could stand to
have traction in other communities or conspiracy spaces.
Possible.
Yeah.
Hopefully Tucker covers it.
That'd be funny.
That would be funny.
Oh boy.
Anyway, we'll be back Jordan.
Will we?
Yeah, we will.
But then we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
You bet.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledgefight.com.
Go to bed Jordan.
We're also on the fake social media app from the scenario unequal.
We are on unequal.
And if you'd like to tell us an equal, and if you could please find a local charity or
bail fund in your area to help out people doing God's work right now, we'll be back.
But until then I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
So what do you think about them apples?
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.