N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Damn and Jordan, I am sweating
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for Knowledgefight
Knowledgefight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Shang, we are the bad guys, Knowledgefight
Damn and Jordan, Knowledgefight
Rattle her, rattle her, rattle her
Need, I need money
Andy and Kansas, Andy and, Andy and
Stop it, Andy and Kan, Andy and Kansas
It's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding us
Hello Alex, I'm a victim caller, I'm a huge fan
I love your work
Knowledgefight
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledgefight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're Gible Dudes, like to sit around, drink novelty beverages
and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are, Dan
Jordan
Dan
Quick question
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, Jordan, is, uh, hey
I finally got an appointment to get a vaccine
Yay!
Oh yeah, thank you
Very exciting
Um, it's been, I've been, uh, I'm past due in terms of, like, the groupings and what have you
and I've been trying to, uh, find a place where I can go get a shot
and I'm finally, as people are listening to this, it comes out on Friday
Oh that's true
I'm going tomorrow
Yeah, yeah, yeah
to get my shot, so, uh, I'm excited about that
I'm very excited about that
I'm excited about embarking on this next chapter of, uh, life
We're free!
Or something approximating it
Something like that
Yeah, and, uh, also as a sort of byproduct of this, this bright spot
Um, I don't know if there's going to be, you know, any kind of side effects
like a fever or, you know, tiredness or anything
and so, in the interest of that, I'm going to give myself the weekend for just self and rest
Recuperation
Um, and so our Monday episode, uh, will actually come out on Wednesday
Yes
We're gonna push that back just, uh, for the sake of
Safety, better safe than sorry
I'd like to sit around and drink some tea, maybe, or something, you know, like
If there's anything that the pandemic has taught us, it's maybe be overly cautious from time to time
Yeah, you know, it's sort of, uh, I wanna, I wanna be like that image of what my parents thought I was doing
when I stayed home from school sick
When I was in school
Oh, he's just watching the Price is Right like everybody else does
Just sipping soup
Just sitting there with a little blanket on
Just broth
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah
Letting those, those fumes open up my pores and my, uh
Absolutely
My sinuses
Yeah, you got it
Um, yeah, so that's, that's exciting
That's wonderful
Yeah, how about you?
We're all very excited
Uh, my bright spot, Dan, is, uh, Godspeed You Black Emperor
Yeah, you were telling me it's a new album
Has put out a new album
And it is spectacular
Yeah
It is so good
Mhm
They're on, like, almost 25 years as a band or something
They're incredible
It's fantastic
They still got it, Dan
I feel like you and I were supposed to do something and you couldn't because you had to listen to the album on repeat
I was too busy listening to Godspeed
Uh, hey, work can't get done
Sorry, I would, look, I would love to help
But, uh, Godspeed released a new album
So I'm gonna have to listen to this 40-minute opus
I understand
Yeah
Um, so, Jordan, today we have an interesting, uh, little bit to go over
I don't know if you've been able to keep unaware of some of the news
Some of it I have been unable to stay unaware of
Right, so we'll get into some of that
Alright
Oh, boy
Um, but before we do, let's take a little moment to say hello and thank you to some new wonks
Oh, that's a great idea
First, uh, this person, J-D-O, J-D-O, I don't know how to pronounce that
Sure
J-D-O
Um, they, uh, also, uh, were kind enough to mention, uh, keep, uh, tell me about an event that's coming up in Oklahoma
Uh-huh
Where, uh, all kinds of weirdos are speaking and, man, I wanna go
I believe Mike Adams is giving a speech
Oh, no
Uh, I really would like to go, but I don't think I'm gonna be able to make it
But anyway, thank you, J-D-O
I'm a policy wonk
You're now a policy wonk
Thank you
Next
Oi, hawkin
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Oi, hawkin
Uh, this person also wanted me to give a shout-out to the Knowledge Fighters
Apparently there's a Discord, uh, uh, server?
Is that what it's called?
I have no idea
Discord is beyond me
Yeah, me too
Um, but, uh, there's apparently a place where, uh, listeners of the show congregate and, uh,
chat, uh, up
And I've heard it's a lot of fun
Oh, that's great!
Yeah, so
That's really great that I'm just now finding out about it
Uh, next
Justice for wonk
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Thank you, next
And that is our rallying cry, Dan
Next
Pee Biggs
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Pee Biggs
Thank you
Next
Durk
Queer
Queerdinker
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Durk
Queerdinker
Oh, boy
I think they said that they wanted me to mispronounce
Mispronounce it?
Yeah, okay
Next
Zap
Rodoser
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, Zap Rodoser
Rose Dozer
Zap Rose Dozer
Apologies
I, I only hear Zap Brannigan in my head, so that's what I got
Next
Jucks
Jucks definitely killed his daughter
Chuck Norris wasn't wearing a wig
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much
Thank you very much
And finally, I'd like to say thank you and give a shout out to a new technocrat, this
is, uh, thank you so much, Treadmark, you are now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
Crikey, mate, that's fantastic, have yourself a brew
How's your 401k doing, bro?
Alright, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, alright?
Let's just get down to business
We ain't making that money off that heroin
Why you pimps so good?
My, my neck is freakishly large
I declare info war on you
Thank you so much, Treadmark
Yes, thank you very much, Treadmark
Treadmark also wanted me to give a shout out to, uh, Reddit board, ah shit, I forgot the
name of it
Um, R The Donald, I believe was the one that he really wanted to get out there
So Jordan, there's been some news
Yes, Dan
So I'd been all ready to go back to 2003 for today's episode, have some fun, learning about
the past and what have you
Of course
But then at the last minute all my plans got thrown into whack
As is always the case
Alex went down to the border, he was looking for a soul to steal
And on Wednesday he released a video of himself accosting somebody who was transporting some
children, possibly recklessly in the back of a station wagon
Sure
Alex, or maybe it was more of a van, I don't know, I don't know car types
Anyway, Alex and his associates yell at the guy driving the car about how he's been caught
smuggling people
Sure
And it is a huge mess
Uh huh
I don't know what all the details of this situation are at this point, but I do know
that I don't believe for a second that Alex and his dumb posse found someone just smuggling
children casually
I'm gonna wait to dig into this until there's a little bit more public information because
I could see this going a couple different directions
And honestly, Alex better keep his fingers crossed because it looks like a couple things
in that video that he released could be crimes
Oh, that's not good
He's sitting there banging like on the roof of a car trying to physically stop it from
leaving
Yeah
Which could be a problem
He's acting in ways that some might interpret as defamatory
I mean, it does a little bit sound like Alex Jones just started attacking Clark Griswold
on the way to the fucking theme park
I'm not a legal expert, but it really looks like this video is an open and shut case of
defamation against a charity that is alleged to be involved in this smuggling
This is Catholic Charities RGV
Their address and signs are clearly shown in the video
That's not good
And the accusation is very clear from Alex's actions that this charity is essentially a
front for smuggling
That's probably defamatory
This organization is the Catholic Charities of the Rio Grande Valley
And the specific building that Alex was staking out was the Humanitarian Crisis Relief Center
that they began operating last summer
Right
According to their website, this is at the Sacred Heart Catholic Church in McAllen, Texas
And quote, the center provides a place for the countless men, women, and children and
infant refugees to rest, have a warm meal, a shower, and change into clean clothing
as well as receive medicine and other supplies before continuing on their journey
So Alex was like, quick, someone's acting Christ-like, destroy them!
Yep
Okay
If you look into this specific charity, it becomes a little interesting that Alex would
choose this one to focus on
The organization was started by a nun named Sister Norma Pimentel
who was a very fierce and public critic of Trump's border policies
To her credit, she was also a vocal opponent of Obama's policies, but that probably doesn't matter to Alex
She wrote an op-ed in the Washington Post in February 2020 titled
quote, President Trump don't ignore the suffering at the border caused by your policies
In 2019, she was invited to participate in what was called a roundtable conversation
about issues at the border with Trump himself
That one was called Back in the Habit, I believe
Sister Pimentel was disappointed by what she experienced
as she discussed in an interview with Texas Monthly
Quote, Trump asked every single person at the table to say something
and I realized that when they were speaking, they were just reaffirming what it was
that he had talked about and congratulating him
I realized that the roundtable was about listening to and reaffirming his plans
He didn't really give local people an opportunity to say anything
That is unsurprising
Very recently, in March 2021, she was featured in an article in the Rio Grande Guardian
that begins like this
Quote, the executive director of Catholic Charities of the Rio Grande Valley
thanks God for President Biden's decision to reverse the Trump administration's
Migrant Protection Protocols policy
Sister Norma Pimentel says it's God's plan to have asylum requests
of unaccompanied minors from Central America fully processed in the United States
Sure, mere days ago, on April 4th
Sister Pimentel was interviewed on Face the Nation
where she discussed how Biden's changes to Trump's policies have changed her work
Okay, so you're saying that a few days ago
Just a few days, perhaps even, what?
One or two days before this incident occurred
Eh, right around
The person who began or started the very charity that Alex will accosted
and defamed
Who has also been a long time public critic of Trump's policies
and again, for the sake of giving it up for moral clarity and consistency
was also a critic of Obama's policies
and is a critic of these new policies not going far enough
but inasmuch as they are representative of progress in the areas that she works in
she is congratulatory of them
So what you have just told me is that this was a completely extemporaneous event
Alex was wandering around and heard the call to action
No, but here's the thing
Instinctively ran to stop this human trafficking from occurring
I can totally believe he doesn't know any of this
I actually can totally believe that too
It could totally be a coincidence
Yeah
I was looking into this charity and trying to understand a little bit more about it
and all these things like, oh, this is a person who is someone who Alex absolutely would target
Oh, despise, yeah
But at the same time, I can totally see this just being a situation where
he went to McAllen, Texas
was hanging out outside waiting for the optics to be right
Sure
Then he created a scene
did a publicity stunt
and blah, blah, blah, here we go
Yeah, that sounds about right
But, better hope this doesn't go to court
because I think you could make a pretty compelling case
that Alex has a reason to have animus towards this organization
based on their political differences
I'm struggling to live in a world where a judge might disagree with me
on what is very clearly an open and shut case
I don't like living in a world where a judge is like, well, if you interpret that
Nah, nah, nah, this is too obvious
Yeah
So, I don't really care to deconstruct this video in and of itself
because it's just Alex yelling at a guy in a car
It's great
On April 8th, the Catholic Charities released a statement hoping to clarify
the various defamatory claims made by Alex
The response makes total sense
Fuck that guy
The only thing that I think is missing is a threat of legal action
Yeah
But again, this is up to everybody themselves
Of course
to deal with on their own terms and decide whether they want to go through that
rigmarole and that public embarrassment and difficulty
Oh yeah, I wouldn't wish that on my worst enemy
Nah
I would wish it on Alex though, so never mind
I would wish that on my worst enemy, yeah
I wouldn't wish whatever the person suing him would have to go through
all the difficulty
Yeah
I understand why some people are reluctant to
Totally
But boy, this seems like a pretty easy case
It shouldn't take too long to work its way through the courts
Yeah
I can imagine Alex giving a blustery speech about how he'll fight this or die
Sure
And then a week later issuing a public apology
Listen, I don't want to get in the way of nuns doing all their business
Love nuns
Nuns are good people, yeah
Did you see Sister Act 2 back in the habit?
This is how I'm going to poach Jordan's joke
It was pretty great
So yeah, I don't want to talk about that video in and of itself
but what I thought might be interesting is seeing what happens on the 8th
because this is Thursday, this is after he's had the social media flare up
over this video
Sure, he's had his moment
It's been posted, we went all kinds of viral and stuff
Yeah, of course
And yeah, I wanted to see where he was at on the 8th
Yeah, sure, let's see what happens
So here's another context drop from this show
I'm not okay
And is anybody the good guy in Ukraine?
They've been killing each other for so long, eastern and western Ukraine
It's like the half-cocks and McCoys
What?
Is anybody the bad guy in Ukraine is a dark question to ask
Well, you're focusing on a different part than I'm focusing on
I understand that
The half-cocks and the McCoys?
I don't know what to do with the half-cocks and the McCoys
I just heard that and stroked out
Yeah, I know that the people misspeak and whatever
And I'm not a nitpicker
But this is an out-of-context drop, first of all
And second of all, if there's anything that Alex's persona should know a lot about
Oh, the Hatfields and the McCoys?
Yeah, you think so?
Yes
Not the half-asses and the McCoys?
The half-cocks
Yikes
Oh man, now I want to start a gang called the half-cocks
And just never explain the name
Sure
People are just like, why do they call them the half-cocks?
They say, we should get windbreakers
Unrelated to this conversation entirely
That was just a random thought
We should just get windbreakers
So we're going to start here on April 8th
And I will say, it seems like Alex isn't even thinking about the border, this video, anything
Of course
The alarm bells are hitting
China has now, with aircraft carriers and over a hundred ships
Thousands totaled
Encircled Taiwan and has heavy bombers flying over it
The Taiwanese say they may start firing missiles any minute
That was this morning, last night there
All hell is breaking loose
The Russians are massing troops on the edge of Ukraine because Biden's sending in heavy weapons
And there are major artillery battles going on
Between proxy U.S. and Russian forces and we are not the good guys in this
So we got a world war coming together here
Yeah, that does sound pretty much the canary in the coal mine
This seems to be the line that Alex is taking now
Which I find interesting because a couple days prior
He was really going hard on this SPARS document
Sure
And then he went to the border and did a giant publicity stunt
Right, right, right
And now it's world war
Now we're moving on
This is confusing
I hear, I hear
This is chaotic
What I am hearing while he speaks is the advice of a lawyer in his ear going
Don't explain anything about that
Talk about
The more you talk about it
Something else
Do you remember what happened with the million dollar bounty? Do you remember?
Oh no, I mean you're wrong about that
But it's weird that he starts the show like this
He does get into the video eventually
Oh okay, well of course
So if there's a lawyer in his ear he forgets about it very quickly
You gotta keep the lawyer in there at all times
I think that one of the reasons that Alex is going on and starting his show
Sort of leading with this idea about world war and all this
Is because that day Biden was giving a speech
About gun control, regulation ideas
Sure
And that fits more in those sets of narratives
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I'll make more clear what I mean a little bit later as we go through
But the beginning of this show and a large portion of the top of it
Is Alex playing Biden's speech and then just sort of rambling over it
Sure
Thank you for having the courage
He cares so much about violence
That's why Obama fought in the Arab Spring
Fast and furious, killed millions
Senator Blumenthal understands it
With the guns of what the Middle East and Mexico
A lot of the folks out here understand it
He transitioned weapons to terrorists in Mexico
Thank you
With Obama
To turn pain into purpose and demand that we take the action
He's a gun running communist Chinese criminal
Enough
Yeah, enough of you funded terrorists
You drug dealing pedophile
Oh boy, so it's that, it's that for a while
He's interrupting like Joe Biden is the highwayman
It's a little annoying
Yeah, that's frustrating
Yeah, so he keeps insisting that fast and furious
Is the silver bullet that will take down the O'Biden administration
Ooh, how long did it take to get there?
It seems like that should have happened way earlier
He kept calling Biden Obama and then
And then he just put it together
Yeah, for a while he's been calling
That's so frustrating
Oh, the reason I keep calling him Obama is because it's O'Biden
O'Biden was right there, guys
It was right there
It's not hard to get there
Nope
This is Alex doing his level best at being Rush
This is why the right is terrible at comedy
They can't even pick up found jokes
Yeah, terrible
I would say that if Alex were to get sued
Over this video where he is, you know, in my opinion
Probably defaming this charity
Yeah, almost certainly
One of his best defenses might be that like
Not many people saw it, you know, it's no big deal
Unfortunately, here he is bragging
See, now there's where we get into trouble
And then what happened yesterday, two days ago
We put out the video that has probably 50 million views
I mean, it's just everywhere
And the smuggling going on, it's all illegal
He didn't sign an executive order
He didn't pass a law
He didn't repeal a law
He just said, surge us before he even stole the election
And then now he congratulates them on the great job they've done
And then there's the quote Catholic charity that's run by the Democratic Party
Just one of the facilities there in McAllen, Texas
And there they are loading little kids in to a trunk like luggage
And we stop them, the police say, yeah, what you're doing is illegal, take them out
They go inside, we catch more cars doing it
We haven't even put that footage out
I don't think you will
No, no
I suspect that that footage is not forthcoming
Yeah
We'll see though
Yeah, I mean, he's just bragging about how many people saw this
Which I think works against his eventual probable argument that he's gonna need to make
Yeah, he's not good at this
To downplay this
He's not good at this
Yeah
This is not good
But then again, if he doesn't get sued and there's no legal trouble
Then I guess he
Wee
Yeah
Yep
Anyway, Alex has this bee in his bonnet about the idea that people are saying that he staged this whole thing
He went down to the border and he staged it
Well, it seems like he didn't like capture a coyote
No
So much as found people who were doing exactly what they said they were going to be doing
And accosted them
Yeah
And then how does literally dozens of national newspapers said, Jones probably staged this
There are no crisis
Yeah, I staged the McAllen police
I staged the kids being put in the trunk
I mean, if I could stage something like that with a hundred million dollar budget
I would be better than
Is Joe Rogan gonna pay for it?
The top directors out there
Alex couldn't think of one director
Spielberg, no, he's a globalist
Scorsese, no, he's a globalist
Clinton Tarantino, I hate him
I hate that guy
Ryan Johnson, no, I wasn't a fan of The Last Jedi
What else do we got?
I'm still bitter that I wasn't in Guardians of the Galaxy
James Scott, yeah
Add that one into the list
All he's got is Clint Eastwood
Probably
So the media didn't say this about Alex
On April 7th, I couldn't find like any media outlets even really covering this publicity stunt
Any actual media outlets, I mean there was like a gateway pundit
Sure, sure, sure, sure
But there were a bunch of random people tweeting about it
And I think that Alex is just pretending that random tweets saying that he probably staged the videos
The same thing as dozens of media outlets and national newspapers covering it
What is new media other than tweets going national, man?
That's new media
I think I've come up with this equation
And that is random tweets plus narcissism equals literally dozens of national newspapers
That's a good, that's a good equation
Yeah, I think that's what's going on
So Alex is saying that everybody's saying that he just made this up and he staged it
And it's like back in 2009 when he covered Bilderberg Man
And everybody said that he was making it up
And the New York Times said
It did not exist and that I was having a full schizophrenic breakdown in the parking lot
That's because back then folks Bilderberg didn't exist
Within two years it was all over the news
Because back then the Drudge Report was not I guess run by CNN
I was told that CNN bought it two years ago
I didn't believe it, it looks like it's true
But Drudge, the real Drudge back when Drudge actually owned it
Exposed all that
This is so fucking stupid
A quick search will disprove the idea that the media claimed that Bilderberg didn't exist until 2008
I'm sorry I said 2009 earlier
When Alex and Drudge exposed it
For instance there's a September 2005 article in the BBC titled
Quote inside the secretive Bilderberg group
Or you could look at Jon Ronson's 2001 book
Them Adventures with Extremists
Excerpts of which were published in the Guardian
And it was accompanied by the release of his TV show Secret Rulers of the World
Which featured an episode where he and Alex Jones go to Bohemian Grove
And the other episode of it was about the Bilderberg group
No tweets at the time
Oh there's also a reference to the Bilderberg meetings in a 1999 Wired article you can easily find
Alright, alright
When Alex said that the media said that he was imagining the whole thing
What he means is that no one accepted his imaginary framing of real life events
People didn't say that the meeting or the group itself didn't exist
Just that the stories that Alex was selling his audience about them didn't stand up to scrutiny
That's the accusation
Not that he made up the Bilderberg group
Excuse me Alex, you're full of shit can mean many different things
Also I'd like to learn more about how the Drudge report was secretly sold to CNN two years ago
Sounds like another thing that Alex is pulling out of thin fucking air
I would be interested to hear about that
Did you look deep into that?
I didn't
Did you reach out to Drudge for comment?
I looked for tax filings
I don't know
It's nonsense
Yeah, whatever
So I think that there's overlap between this idea of like
When people are accusing Alex of making stuff up
They're not talking about like the actual event
Right, right, right
And so like with the video that he shot down near the border
It's the same thing
It's like you didn't make up that someone got in a car
You're just lying about the surrounding context
9-11 was an inside job, you're full of shit
You don't think 9-11 happened?
No, obviously it happened
Yeah, you may have actually said it didn't happen at some point
Yeah, exactly, that's fair
I gotta review all the tapes
So when Alex is making these accusations, obviously
That's bad
But there are certainly ways that he could make the situation worse
Which he decides to do in this next clip
Putting out a million dollar bounty
I'm not gonna say what we're gonna do
But I'm obviously gonna be going back to the border very soon
I'm not gonna say it's gonna be tomorrow, even this weekend
It might be today
I'm just gonna tell you that
I've already decided when I'm going, I'm going
I'm going
I'm not gonna tell this system how or when
And quite frankly
If I had the money, because we're maxed out right now
I would have a full-time team just in McAllen
And in Brownsville, rubbing the Texas border
It is wild, wild west
Insane, illegals everywhere you go
Buses everywhere you go
Total children sleeping in dirt under bridges
We sent a drone in there, they had a geo fenced up
So we couldn't show them in the dirt
But Project Veritas got folks in there
We have all these whistle blowers
All this whistle blower video
People that saw children being raped inside the facilities
We broke that on Monday
Now you see Governor Abbott talking about it
I mean, I flew over with a helicopter
We have hours and hours and hours of this footage
And that's why you need to go to Infowarsstore.com
So we can stay on air
Wow
Now do you see what's happening
As everything we talked about went on
Despite the fact you're trying to censor us and block us
Infowars, I want to report to you our success
So that you understand why you supported us
As the core audience of the core radio stations
That are like, you know, funding us to go out and be the missionaries
To tell the truth against the globalists
That's what you're doing here
So there's something a little bit disgraceful about using this as a
Like directly as a fundraising
Yeah, it's a little bit like holding your audience hostage
Yeah, it also will be difficult for Alex
Were somebody to sue him for this
It would be hard for him to argue that he's not using it
In order to make money
Yeah
Because that's literally what he's doing here
And as far as the criminal malicious intent towards the border
Saying, I'm not going to tell the system how or when I'm going to get there
Seems like admitting to a certain amount of suspicious activity at least
I'm going to be sneaky
Yeah, exactly
Now, if you want to escalate this even further
Alex has a great idea for you
And that is one of his old tricks
I mean, I have to tell you, ladies and gentlemen
That anybody
Because I don't care about getting the scoop
If Ben Shapiro wanted to go down to McCallum
Or if Tucker Carlson wanted to go down to McCallum
He probably will
Or anywhere
Ted Nugent says he wants to go with me down there
I'm going to take him down there, he's a fellow Texan
You'll sit there for 30 minutes and you'll see kids getting crammed in trunks, okay
I mean, you can't swing a stick in the dark and not hit smugglers down there
There is a sense that Alex is giving off that is like, you should go
Yeah, of course
Everybody should go
We're all going, it's going to be a great big party
Anybody who goes down there will immediately find proof of this illegal human trafficking ring
And you need to, you know, hey, all these people
If they went, if Ben Shapiro had the nerve to do it
He could get the scoop
I don't care about getting the scoop
Everyone should go, you should go
That's a bad thing to do
When you're escalating people's suspicion
And belief that they're fighting the literal devil and all this
To such a heightened point
And be like, oh hey, you all should go down there
You'll find direct evidence of all this stuff
I mean, you're asking for trouble
Like he has every single time in the past
I don't want to, like, here's the thing about
You know, you don't want to get into slippery slope arguments with restricting speech, of course
So what I think we should do
Is write a very, very narrow law that puts out step by step what Alex did for Pizzagate
And then is like, you just can't do that
All of that stuff, you can't do it
And then Alex wouldn't be able to do this shit
And you know, the part about it that always gets a little bit muddy
Is that like, yeah, not every time that you behave like this
It causes a horrible outcome like a shooting
Of course
But
We have proof that it can and does from time to time
So stop doing the things that lead there
Here's why it's not a free speech argument
Are you going to or have been
Inspiring people to go commit terrifying acts
And have you really faced any consequences
Yeah, exactly
I would say you've been rewarded
Yes, exactly
Anyway, so Alex spends a lot of time on this episode
Talking about Biden trying to take the guns
Because Biden has some ideas about, you know, hey, it is a little bit terrifying
The prospect of, you know, being able to get kits where you can make a gun
And none of the parts have any kind of serial number
Totally
Completely untraceable guns
It's certainly something that in the wrong hands could lead to a lot of trouble
Also the ability to just, you know, buy guns on the internet
I mean, they trace fucking cold medicine
Yeah, and so he has, you know, he has some ideas
I'm not the biggest expert in the world
But when I was listening to the ideas it didn't sound like anything that was too terrifying
No, I think I will be fine
But anyway, Alex thinks that Chidna is trying to use Biden to get the guns
For a specific reason
Really, the big news is the Chicons are trying to cause a civil war
Knowing that this will trigger a civil war
And a bloodbath for everybody, which I'm not looking forward to, which I do not want
But nevertheless, is a fact
So there you go, that's what's going on there
Everybody else in the bay, oh, he wants to save children
This doesn't make any sense
No
Now the globalist plan is to start a civil war
Like at the behest of China for some reason
And that's gonna, I guess, kill a lot of people
Yep
I thought their plan was soft killing everyone with vaccines
And then having an orderly extermination
And if that didn't work, then their plan B was to release super bio-weapons just to kill everyone off
Yeah, but that was last week
How does a civil war or world war fit into that plan exactly?
Like, how is gun regulation a part of the bio-weapon plan?
Yeah, it would be a really dumb civil war to have if, like, while you're fighting it
Half of your army is just gonna drop dead from the vaccine at any moment
It seems like if the plan was these bio-weapons, the globalist shouldn't care if you have guns
Like, you can't shoot a virus
I kept this clip in to illustrate how none of Alex's narratives mean anything
Everything is self-serving and meant to escalate whatever he's decided to make his audience afraid of that day
In this case, Biden's giving this speech on gun reform ideas
And thus, the thing to profit off making the listeners scared of is gun confiscation
That narrative doesn't really match up with the whole thing Alex has been doing with vaccine fear-mongering
So he can't really say that the gun regulation is part of the whole bio-weapon thing
Thus, he pretends that, you know, this isn't the entire thing he's been ranting about forever
And now it's time to be scared about war
It's war that we need to be scared about, it's the summer of rage, Dan!
Also, if all Alex's enemies were working for the literal devil, it seems like they wouldn't be all on such different pages
Like, if the devil had this plan that they were supposed to be trying to carry out, why would China mess around with Taiwan
When that could only really get in the way of following through on the larger plan?
That seems really weird, and I would love Alex to explain that
Well, what it is, so it's, what it is, it's a Japanese management strategy that the, that the devil is using here, alright?
You have many different divisions, and you don't share all the information because they're all working for the same end goal
But, they've got their own strategies, that's how you create new solutions to problems, Dan
I feel like the devil, were this devil to be singularly focused on one objective
Sure
I don't know if there would be a need for teams to be working across purposes
But you haven't been reading Japanese management models
You do make a fair point
Yeah
So anyway, Biden wants the guns
Sure
And Trump, you know, he said that he wanted red flag laws
Right, right, right, but that didn't happen, so we're good
But also that was, he was being sneaky and it was different
Of course, completely different, completely different
And of course, the red flag laws, you know, Trump was like, oh red flag means if you've been adjudicated mentally ill and you're schizophrenic
And you were, you know, kicked out of the Air Force was the case they brought to him
But he, they never put the Air Force records in that he was dishonorably discharged in an Air Force mental institution for two years
Trump's like, yeah, that guy shouldn't have a gun. Oh, the conservatives, Trump wants to, no, no, no, okay, well Trump's gone
Let's not, bad guy's gone, don't have him to kick anymore
We got Biden saying, if anybody has a concern about you, your guns are gone, you don't get them back most of the time
And you get the SWAT team raid that ensues
So civil war, civil war, civil war
Whoa, so this is how Alex wants to remember Trump's comments on red flag laws, but that's not what Trump said
This was in 2019 after the mass shootings in Dayton and El Paso
Trump said, quote, first we must do a better job of identifying and acting on early warning signs
I'm directing the Department of Justice to work in partnership with local, state, and federal agencies as well as social media companies
To develop tools that can detect mass shooters before they strike
That doesn't sound like adjudicating someone as mentally ill
That seems like talking to social media, taking the posts from social media to identify people who may be unwell and then getting their guns taken away
It's almost like Alex thinks reality is whatever fits his narrative at any given point in time, it's really weird
Honestly, what Trump was talking about seems way more invasive and draconian than anything that Biden's proposing
Trump went on, quote, we must reform our mental health laws to better identify mentally disturbed individuals who may commit acts of violence
And make sure those people not only get treatment, but when necessary, involuntary confinement
Seems like Alex should be against that pretty strongly
These people have not committed any crimes, but because some globalist doctor is saying that they might commit one, we should have laws that they get locked up
This is pre-crime, Trump wants to bring in the guys in the tanks from the Tom Cruise movie
Yeah, it's precogs, it's Mission what, not Mission Impossible, Minority Report
Yeah, oh, this is Philip K. Dick shit
They're coming for us
Trump continued, quote, we must make sure that those judged to pose a grave risk to public safety do not have access to firearms
And if they do, those firearms can be taken through rapid due process
That is why I've called for red flag laws, also known as extreme risk protection orders
Today, I'm also directing the Department of Justice to propose legislation ensuring that those who commit hate crimes and mass murders face the death penalty
And that this capital punishment be delivered quickly, decisively, and without years of needless delay
As a libertarian type and someone who's insanely anti-government, Alex should be really afraid of a president calling for expedited death sentences
Especially since Alex thinks that most people who commit mass shootings are secretly patsies
Also, that was the speech where Trump said, quote, may God bless the memory of those who perished in Toledo
And may God protect them, because he misread a teleprompter, the shooting was in Dayton
Yep. Anyway, the point of this is that Alex has created an ahistorical version of Trump's response to mass shootings and his public support for red flag laws
Because what Trump advocated is directly counter to a lot of what should make sense as Alex's position, so that's kind of messy
I think it's easier to hand wave it away and say the past is the past, let's move on and think about the future
Trump isn't president anymore, we don't need to think about all the stuff he said
We even sputtered through that in that clip
We don't learn from history here, how dare any of you
Let's not deal with what was said realistically, let's just have fun
So, who do you think the world's most powerful doctor is?
The world's most powerful doctor? Doom?
Sure, he has his own country
Exactly, he's pretty powerful
What about Oz?
Dr. Oz? No, I don't think he's very powerful
Dr. Phil is rich as hell
Dr. Phil is pretty powerful
But you couldn't stand up to Dr. Doom, I think you really cheated the game there
Dr. Doom is a little bit of a winner there
He has lightning powers, right? What powers does Dr. Doom have?
No, the super stretch man is a doctor too, he's more powerful than Dr. Doom
Mr. Fantastic?
Yeah, Mr. Fantastic, why do I call him super stretch man? I don't know
Super stretch man
See, this is why people think that I'm not amused by things you said
I was just laughing really hard but silently
Yes, yeah, yeah, naturally
Sometimes it just doesn't play on the mic
It doesn't happen
Yeah, Invisible Woman was a doctor too, right?
Yeah, I am
All of them, all the Fantastic Four
No, no, no, Invisible Woman, the flame guy, Jesus, I'm not doing well today
Human Torch?
Yes, I understand
I'm not even a dork and I know these names
Honestly, I was going to call her Mrs. Invisible, which I recognize is not okay
Who else did she marry to him?
I think so, I can't remember exactly
And then The Thing wasn't a doctor, he was just an astronaut or something
Yeah, he was a military guy
What are we doing?
I think The Thing and Human Torch were like
This is why Discord is beyond us, we're not even, yeah
I think they were cool military guys and then Invisible Woman and Reed Richards were doctors
Yes
I think
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Still Dr. Doom more powerful
He does have his own country and they never really put him away, you know
Anyway
My point is that if you Google it you'll get a different answer
Okay
Well, who runs the UN?
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun
I tried this this morning and it works, we'll see if they've changed it
Guys, please go to Google for TV viewers
Any radio listener can do this
Type in who is the most powerful doctor in the world
And before you even say powerful, who is the most powerful?
It says Bill Gates
And they say he is the most powerful doctor
He is in charge and he will do what he will to you
So this is actually true
If you Google the words who is the world's most powerful doctor
The results do say Bill Gates
This is because the search terms identically reflect the title of a 2017 Politico article titled
quote, meet the world's most powerful doctor, Bill Gates
Okay
The article itself is highly critical of Gates' outsized influence on the World Health Organization
Given his status as a major donor
But it's not critical in the same way that Alex might be
For instance, the article points out that quote
Rather than focusing on strengthening healthcare in poor countries
That would help, in their view, to contain future outbreaks like the Ebola epidemic
The agency spends a disproportionate amount of its resources on projects with a measurable outcome
That Gates prefers, such as the effort to eradicate polio
Anyway, the fact that this Google search result comes up
You know, it went slightly viral recently
As it has in the past a couple times
Alex probably just saw it on social media
Now he's complaining about it on his show, which is really sad
Yeah
He hasn't even read the Politico article
Because if he has, he would recognize that it actually
He'd be like, oh, that's why it's
But it actually would be like, oh, this is kind of critical of Gates
Yeah
That kind of doesn't work for him
It really seems far too obvious to say that a billionaire shouldn't have anything to do with
Just about any decisions regarding, well, anything
But especially health in the modern world
Yeah, I think it's a complicated question
And I think that, you know, based on the fact that there are Politico articles like this
There are people who are in the appropriate places asking those sorts of questions
And wrestling with it
Anyway, because Alex has found this Google search result that he thinks is real cool
Yeah
He lets himself off the chain a little bit
Okay
There it is
Who's the most powerful doctor in the world, ladies and gentlemen?
Bill!
I'm gonna kill your ass, Bill Gates
Woo!
Meet the world's most powerful doctor
And for four pages it says the same thing
Because he paid in the search results to tell you
I am the big swinging Johnson
I'm gonna put it in ya
Whoa, family show, man, family show
The big swinging Johnson
It's not something that I want repeated anywhere
Nah, it's not fun
So, uh
Also, isn't the title is ironic, or sarcastic at least
Meet the world's most powerful doctor, Bill Gates
Yes
He's not a doctor, that's the point of the title
Is that this is not how it's supposed to be
There's an irony, yes
Yeah, exactly
Yeah, yeah
So he's taking a sarcastic headline literally
Yep
Yeah, gotcha
Just wanted to be sure about that
Yep
He's good at this, man
He's great at, reading comprehension is his jam
So now, someone else is good at things
Like guitar
Sure
And being a real creep
I don't know if he's good at those things
Look, I'm not a music scholar, I don't know anything about this
But Ted Nugent is on the show
Of course
I gotta say, Uncle Ted sounds like a bit more of a lunatic than usual
Okay
This is an incredible time to be alive, but I'm glad Ted Nugent is there
Imagine saying that
Imagine saying that seriously
Thank you for joining us, sir
My pleasure, Alex, I'm celebrating life, liberty, and the pursuit of happiness
I got my priorities
I think we should quote the greatest philosopher of all times
I think we agree, that was Dirty Harry
When he said, a good man knows his limitations
So as I fight against the curse of self-inflicted apathy and Marxism running amok
And whatever creature that is
That pretends to be the commander in chief and all his crazy supporters
The Nugent family is living the American dream
He always sounds like he's on coke
But he claims he's 70 years sober
Yeah, my immediate thought was
He got about halfway through his sentence
And I was like, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
You just slow it down, buddy
Slow down
You're already going a little too fast to be taken seriously
Yeah
So Ted Nugent seems, I mean like the Motor City madman
Might be a little bit more literal
Sure
He sounds nuts
I mean, he doesn't live in the Motor City anymore, so
Well, he does, part time
Oh, fair enough
Well, somewhere in Michigan it is
He's making this metaphor
It's pained
I think in this metaphor, Old Yeller is the government
Okay
Or something
So you're setting this up as we're going to take a long trip to get to the end of this metaphor
You bet
Okay
Same group suing, NRA are suing me
I mean, this is a war and lesser do you know it's a war
Well, you know, not just spotlighting the cockroaches
I think the most important lesson has been hidden from generations
And that's the lesson of Old Yeller
We love dogs
When Old Yeller protects us from the snake and the cougar
When Old Yeller brings us the newspaper and our slippers
We give Old Yeller a kiss and a hug and a biscuit
When Old Yeller, the same dog we love dearly
Begins foaming at the mouth
We know what we have to do to Old Yeller
But we don't embrace difficult and discomforting decisions in life
I use the reference of the Germans who pretended they weren't complicit
By their cult of denial of what happened during the genocide
There are Americans today that are hiding from the indicators
Hiding from the evidence
So here's the answer
Number one, Alex
Everybody who believes in freedom right now more than ever
You have to be a member of the National Rifle Association
Gun Owners of America
The Texas State Rifle Association
All your state second amendment organizations
You have to communicate with your mayor
Your senator, your congressman, your governor
On a weekly basis
I'm just a guitar player
Slow down
Yeah, you are just a guitar player, sir
Wait, this is about guns?
I guess
I think he's saying we need to overthrow the United States government, right?
We need to put it down like Old Yeller
Yeah, that's kind of his point
Because they want gun regulation now
Was that the lesson of Old Yeller?
Now, when the government just lets you have all the guns you want
You give it a pat on the head and give it a biscuit
I would like to know Ted Nugent's interpretation of Romeo and Juliet
I would like his explanation of that
He's too people mean
Great piece of literature
Too people mean to fall in love, parents are mean
Kill themselves, it's all good
Yeah, that was weird
That was weird
I guess he's saying that we're not happy about it
But we gotta kill the government
Yeah, I guess we just have to kill the government
Huh
Strange metaphor
Interesting
So, Alex has gone and done this possibly defamatory video about this Catholic charity
And if I were Ted Nugent, I might not want to sign off on that video
Just in case
I don't want to get ensnared
I don't want to actually be on public record being like
Hey, that was an awesome thing you did
That was super cool
And I'm glad I helped playing it with you
We have to fight back on the activist level peacefully
But communicate on a regular basis
And yes, Alex, Shamane and I with our Ted Nugent Spirit of the Wild show
And our Spirit Campfire
And all the different incredible communication that my wife Shamane accomplishes
We're coming down to the border because everybody has to know
That these children are being trafficked
And when you catch a guy doing it, he plays dumb
Well, that's not dumb, that's demonic
We have to spotlight these devil cockroaches
These devil cockroaches
This is not good
This is very not good
That's not good
Yeah, Ted Nugent is clearly talking about Alex's video
Yeah, absolutely
There are a couple of huge problems I have with it
Number one, obviously, is Ted Nugent is not allowed to say traffic head
Traffic head, he says it twice
No, unacceptable behavior
Unacceptable behavior
It's very weird
And I want to know the spelling of demonic
Because immediately following dumb, it should be D-U-M-B-O-N-I-C, right?
Dumbonic
Yeah, I mean, if it's on paper, probably
Yeah, it has to be
So, jumping from there, I mean, he sort of is endorsing Alex's video
And we have to flush out these folks, these demons
Obviously
Now he's sort of saying that they need to kill people
Who are like the people in Alex's video
You know, we've been to Africa many times
And Shamane has done a lot of interviews with some real heroes of law enforcement and the military
Who have dedicated their lives to saving these women and children that are enslaved and trafficked
And it's happening on a daily basis
And thank God, a big salute to you
Not just from the Nugent family, Alex
But a lot of people are watching you spotlight these devils
And we thank you for that
But more and more people have to do it
And then they have to act upon it
You can't identify a foaming-at-the-mouth dog
And then go back to your gardening
You have to deal with the rabid dog
You have to eliminate the rabid dog
And if you're not able to do it, call your wildlife control office
But call somebody
That metaphor fell apart
I think that what we're listening to is
Ted Nugent taking these sort of ideas that Alex has had about
Everybody's got to go down to the border and, you know, find all this
And he's going one step further and saying you have to take action
Against the people who are trafficking
And boy, you know, that could get really out of hand
If your standard of who's trafficking people is as low as Alex is
This is directly inciting
See, this is why we have my new Pizzagate law
If you do a Pizzagate, it's against the law
He was just talking about literal dogs, though
He was saying that if a dog has
What if you just have, like, some stuff on your glasses
And then you just murder a dog
Maybe you should think a little bit more
I can't stress enough how, like, I saw that video
When it was making the rounds
I'm like, this sucks
But, you know, this is Alex doing what he does
I hope he gets sued for it
Then I listen to his show and I'm like
It sounds like he's kind of encouraging people to go and do what he's doing
And I think that's probably bad
That seems like the kind of behavior he's done in the past
Nothing could have prepared me for Ted Nugent coming on
And making this pained metaphor that is so much worse
That seems to imply that what people need to do
Is come down there and kill people who are trying to help
Asylum seekers and refugees
Yeah
It's so fucked up
Yeah, I don't know if there's anything that could prepare you for
A sudden appearance of Ted Nugent telling you to murder
In a bad metaphor
Yeah, that's something that I
That's Kool-Aid Man levels of surprise
Oh no
Yeah
Now, much like the Kool-Aid Man, he barges through walls
You know that
We're about to get someone else barging through walls
And that is Ted Nugent's son
Sure, sure
I want to hear what Ted Nugent's son has to say
You actually do
Okay
Ted Nugent's son is there with him
And Alex wants to talk to him a little bit
Sure
And, oooh, Nelly
Here we go
And Rocco, I know you're an articulate person in your own right
The great son of Ted Nugent
Well, what is your view on all this?
Man, I'm a little bit more oriented to the metaphysical aspects of it
I feel like I got this guy on the front lines of the
The terrestrial aspect
And me and some of my friends have been tuned into what you've been doing
And others, like David Icke
And I got more interested in like, you know
Who's really behind the cabal
Extraterrestrial beings that are hijacking energy fields of the planet
That are installing slaughterhouses
That are, you know, the motives
By the way, I totally agree
When you hit the bottom of the rabbit hole, whatever it is
It's anti-human, it's anti-success
Yeah
Yeah, so Rocco, Ted Nugent's son, is into the spiritual side of this
Another new law
It should be against the law to grow up rich
That's what I heard right there
No!
So I wanted to understand this a little bit more
I had no idea, I'd never heard Ted Nugent's son
And I was like, oh this is interesting
No, it was about, there was a cartoon
It was Modern Life, something?
Oh yeah, it's fun
Thank you
So, this guy's modern life
Apparently consists of putting out YouTube videos
Where he's driving, you know, you got the camera on you while you're driving
Oh no, he's doing those?
Mic down for this
Oh boy
This was terrifying
Hello Earth
And anyone else who may be tuning in
The download to be shared today in this moment
While the highway is being driven on
Is a message that just came through
The reference point many know as Archangel Michael
And my relationship with Archangel Michael has been one of
He's almost been like the older brother that you didn't really know
Because you were really young when he was at home
And then he left for the military or something
And then you like grew up
And then he came back and he's all like stern and transformed
And then he leaves and never comes again
And so he's like this image in your mind of like discipline
And yeah, like the little brother, like the big brother
He's the bigger brother that holds you accountable to your highest potential
And he has this sword, at least in my interfacing with him
He has a sword that he carries around with him
And it's like a sword of light
And it seems to also be a sword of the divine masculine personified in a device
In a moment as a sword
So it's a dick? Is he saying the sword's a dick?
Yeah, I believe he's saying that the Archangel Michael has a lightsaber shaped like a penis
Is essentially what I'm hearing
Yeah, so Ted Nugent's son puts out videos where he rambles about how he talks to angels
Yeah, somebody should take away his license
Cool
Now, I was watching a few of these and there's just a bit of
Of course you are
There's just a bit of like, you know, sort of that spirituality that is kind of untethered
And a little bit Project Camelot-y in many ways
Well, he's talking about the Archangel Michael as that older brother who went away
In the military and then came back to you and also has a giant lightsaber sword that looks like a dick
And he gave him a download
And the download, spoiler alert, is the greatest FOMO
You know, the fear of missing out?
No
You do not
No, you do not continue, sir
Sir?
The greatest FOMO is missing out on what you could have been if you didn't get your shit together earlier
I really, really, really need to throw a thing
Yeah
Archangel Michael coming down with his sword to blow mines
So now, I was thinking like, okay, I could play some more things from these videos that are just kind of silly
But honestly, like, I don't know, that just kind of, that kind of content is the kind of stuff that I'm like, I gotta go
Yeah
I gotta get away from this
And I figured there's something better I could tell you
And that is
Sure
The Ted Nugent's son is also a rapper
Oh no!
Oh god
Don't do this to me
No
No!
Mmm
Had to tell you no Had to tell you no Had to tell you no Had to say no
I had to walk away I had to talk to me I had lost my faith I had lost myself I had lost my health
Tearin' in the windows Pay a chance to get help
Yeah, it's basically that
I, um, yeah, I found that it was a little bit, I mean, it makes a compelling argument for there being, such a thing as too much autotune
Yeah, yeah, that's, that's definitely the case, man, how much would it suck to not even suck as much as Chet Hanks?
You know, or just suck more than Chet Hanks, like, that's bad
I feel really bad because I don't want to, like, mock someone's creative outlet
Sure
I think that's bad, but also
I want to mock rich kids' creative output, I'm fine with that
Yeah
I mean, I think that this is not quality music
I think it's funny that it's Ted Nugent's son
Trying to make this nonsense music
You're not even the best, worst son
That's the worst part about it
Oh, man
Jesus
Anyway, this has been Get to Know Rocco in his modern life
Yes, yep
And now we move on
Now we would like to un-know
Yeah
So they leave, the Nugent family leaves
Oh, also just remember that Ted Nugent's wife is a really huge QAnon supporter
Yeah, yeah, yeah
We went into an argument about it with Alex
Of course, of course
A couple months back
Naturally
Good family
Yeah
So they leave, and Alex lights a literal candle, but maybe it's also a metaphor
I'm being honest with listeners, I know the metaphysical's real, I know God's real
I know the spirit's like a fire, and you can't just keep that fire under yourself
You gotta share it with other people, like this candle
I'm lighting here in studio with Ted Nugent right now on TV and radio with his simulcasting
They want to put America's flame out, they want to put our republic's flame out
But they can't do it if we continue to share it
But if they're able to demoralize us and make us be cowards and make us be fearful
They can put that flame out, but you're aware of them trying it
They don't have the power to do that anymore
Alex is becoming more and more of a prop comic
Yeah
Yeah, so he's doing like one of those Christmas candles where you only burn it for the, you know
It's like red, green, red, green, red, green, and every day before Christmas you burn the red one off
And then you turn it out, and then you burn the green one off
But it's for the end of the republic?
Something like that
Okay
Yeah, just like, you know, when he had that skull and the goblet or whatever
A lot of people will think, what does this mean?
And I'm asking you, what does this mean?
I am gonna light this candle because I want to talk about the metaphor of a candle
But I also want you to be able to see it
I just, because there's a moment before this where he screamed at some 18 year old
Get me a candle
That's the problem here
I would say there's a pretty good chance
So Alex has not really covered a lot of news
But he has a lot of articles in a stack, but who cares
Well, they're tweets
I could spend an hour on each one of these articles and discover every little piece of it
And talk about how it works and talk about how it's a deployment
But at the end of the day, you get caught up in making it your god by giving it all your attention
Just know this, whatever comes out of these people's mouths is meant to kill your ass
Oh, okay
Wow
Okay, we can just make that decision
What you need to know is that I need you emotionally aroused at all times
But if you learn anything, that will stop
I don't think that there's any better encapsulation of Alex Jones' sort of style than that
That I could spend an hour on this and all the information, all the minutia
Get really into the weeds on this
Yeah, well he's a policy wonk as we know
We could really get into this, but just know that whatever they're saying, they're trying to kill you
So really, there's no point for me to have any of this in front of me
So instead of getting into the nitty gritty, being a policy wonk
Which he could do
Oh, no, of course
You just assume that they're just trying to kill you
Instead of getting into the weeds and really figuring this out, he decides to spend his time doing the big work
And that, of course, means complaining about Saturday Night Live
We never aired it, I don't know if they could find it
But it's the Saturday Night Live
And they're like, coming up on Saturday Night Live, black people won't take the vaccine
So they have a black guy with a British accent, like he's smart, but other black people aren't
They love British accents
Don't pull up
It's the black, a British guy
You got an engine on fire
Literally going, I'll give you black people barbecue and watermelon or whatever
If you take the shot, and the black guy has a classic southern voice like that's dumb
You are no Sully Tullenberger
And it's literally them, caricatures, making fun of black people
With a black guy with a British accent, being racist to them
Because of their accent from where they are, saying they're fighting racism
And then it's on CNN
I mean, I can't, these people piss me off, man
And it's constant
What?
Okay, so, one
Did you see that SNL sketch?
I saw the first little bit of it
I got it
Yeah, yeah
You get it
It's not hard to get
I think that there are some people who took umbrage with it
And I say huzzah, rightfully so
That was probably a poorly conceived sketch
I think that people did not enjoy it
And you can find articles in all sorts of media expressing that sentiment
That it was maybe poorly constructed and conceived
Yeah, yeah, yeah
That said, Alex's point about it is outrageous
I mean, I think he was trying to say that it was a racist sketch
But he did so by being more racist towards
Yeah
The person who's hosting
Daniel Kaluuya?
Kaluuya, I believe, yeah
He is British
Yes
But he's not doing a British accent in that sketch
No, he's not
No
And specifically, he's not doing a British accent
Yes
Despite having one
And I think that what happened is that Alex just saw like an outrage compilation
Right
Of like some of his jokes from the monologue
Right, right, right
Where he's speaking in his British accent
So he knows that the guy is British
And assumes
Well, he doesn't know that the guy is British
And he assumes that that carries over to the sketch as well
Right, right, right
Or he doesn't understand how the structure of Saturday Night Live works
No, absolutely not
But yeah, so if you haven't seen the sketch, the idea was that there's this guy who is
a doctor and his family won't take the vaccine
Right
And so he's having a game show to get them to take the vaccine
Yeah
And he keeps offering money
Yeah, yeah, yeah
For the correct answer, which is yes
Yes
I will take the vaccine
I will get the vaccine, yes
And so one of his family members played by Keenan
He asked what he would do with the money if he won
Sure
And he says, I'll roll up some joints, smoke some weed
Sure, sure, sure
Get a big barbecue block party, go and get a new grill
Yes
Or whatever
And that, Alex has extrapolated out into being like trying to entice black people with barbecue
and watermelon
Right, right, right
He has added an even more racist layers
That's what I was saying
Yes
He didn't need to add the more racist part
No
And SNL was, you know, like you get it because they were creating that caricature that they
love to do on Celebrity Jeopardy, but what actually happened is they relied on stereotypes
to make fun of, yeah
Um, so I think that Alex thinks that because this sketch is clunky and possibly somewhat
offensive
Yeah
It gives him carte blanche to be even more racist
I give you the barbecue you take
No
Can you imagine if I had a show
And I got up there and I went I give you black people some barbecue, in fact, chew that up
if you can
This is what I'm talking about, it is the, everything they say we are is them
What about Fentanyl the dragon?
I was gonna say also it kind of sounded like he slipped into Fentanyl the dragon there
He doesn't have a lot of rage
He's trying to do a racist black person accent and then he slipped into a racist Chinese
accent
So that's great
He's a Caliendo
No, no, no, no, he is not Rich Little
No
So Alex tries to play the clip of it and he fails
Yeah here it is, let's cue it up, let's cue it up, in fact if you have the audio ready
you got the audio ready?
You guys can pull it up really quick and great, they have it, okay here it is, well watch
this for yourself
It's okay, our computers, hey I only have like a hundred thousand dollar computer in
there it's not the crew's fault, the hundred thousand dollar computer messes up about one
percent of the time, the million dollar computer hardly ever messes up so I can't afford the
million dollar switcher so it just locked up on them but whenever it boots back up we'll
play it for you
What?
You gotta boot back up?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you know
What?
You gotta restart it, I mean look it's a million dollar machine but it still runs on Windows
This is the hundred thousand dollar one, you can't afford the million
That one doesn't even run on Windows 95, that guy's running DOS prompts
I wonder if like what actually happened was that there was like a producer in his ear
during that long silence that was like hey those voices that you're doing and the way
you're characterizing the sketch, if you play the sketch
This is not gonna go well
You're gonna be shown to be wrong
You're a racist
Yes, this is gonna look bad
I wonder if that's what happened, it would make sense based on the incredibly long pause
and then eventually they do play what I think is the outrage compilation, the only thing
that he's aware of, which is the clips of the monologue and then a short clip of that
sketch and then he's just written a story about it in his head that is more racist than
the original version
Wild, wildly racist
Yep
So at this point Alex has a reporter named Sheila Gunn-Reed on his show, she is a reporter
with Rebel Media
Sure, sure, trustworthy
Great
Yeah, yeah
And she's on to talk about a certain church in Canada that is under attack
Uh oh
Well thanks for having me Alex and thanks so much for your ongoing interest in this
story
It's truly an international story despite what the mainstream media in my home province
would have you believe
This church has been the flashpoint for the fight for religious freedom in Canada during
the pandemic
I doubt it
The pastor there, Pastor James Coates, was arrested and incarcerated for 35 days in
a maximum security provincial facility for refusing to limit his congregation to 15%
of fire code capacity as per the public health orders here in Alberta.
He refused to comply, he said it violated his religious freedom, so he was taken into
custody.
He's been released now, but the crackdown on his church has not stopped
So this is the Grace Life Church in Alberta and like Sheila was saying, the pastor of
this church James Coates was arrested in February after repeated breaches of COVID safety measures
He was given multiple opportunities and warnings to follow the rules and he refused to do so
So he got arrested and then released on the condition that he stop breaking the rules
which he immediately proceeded to break again
Literally everybody involved was like dude we don't want to do this, you don't want to
do this, well obviously you want to turn yourself into a fucking martyr
So in response to his trouble, a group of 28 community leaders from various religious
backgrounds released a statement that quote stress the need to prioritize the well-being
of all members of society over individual needs during the pandemic and to follow the
directives of public health officers and the government
Someone acting Christ-like, kill them!
Just this week, the Alberta Health Service shut down the church by putting fences up
around it, quote until the church can demonstrate the ability to comply with Alberta's Chief
Medical Officer of Health's restrictions
Do you hear what they said?
You are teens, they put you in time out until you can eat your goddamn vegetables, you don't
get to go to church
Yeah you can't use the phone until you can learn to not prank call people
Yeah I mean it's insane
Yep
I think closing the church is kind of murky territory honestly and I'm not sure how I
would proceed if I were in charge there but this is Canada
If the local folk there in Alberta are terribly opposed to this closure then they can work
on that with the local government but from everything I've seen pretty much everybody
outside the church itself seems fine with the fact that they, you know, if you're not
going to follow the restrictions they're not even, the restrictions are 15% capacity
Yeah
It's not even closing the church
You don't even have to close the church
No
Just fucking live stream it, dude we don't want to put you in jail, it would be stupid
this is stupid, you're a child
Let's find ways to work this out in ways that work for everybody
Please just go away
Anyway there's a 15% capacity that he's supposed to follow but not everybody has to follow
that
Because it's 15, one five percent of fire code capacity but the Walmart up the road
but the Costco up the road they can operate at 30% of fire code capacity so this is why
this is truly amazing
Your church doesn't sell food
It knows if you're going to Walmart or if you're going to praise God
This is embarrassing pretending to not understand the different capacities for different things
No get the fuck out of here
Like I would totally bet that Walmart would have a 15% capacity order if it were a place
where people congregated for long periods of time, sat in place and sang
So stupid
The things you do at Walmart while you're wearing a mask which they didn't do at this
church
Oh that was really surprising to me, I assume that they all still wore masks
No
No that's surprising
You know you're required to wear a mask to enter the Walmart and you walk around and
leave
Yeah
That's why maybe you could have 30% capacity there safely as opposed to a building where
everyone sits and sings
Yeah that is like, listen I know the word is supposed to be mainly geometry based but
you are being obtuse
That is ridiculous
Yeah
So Alex gets to talking about his Spars conspiracy a little bit
Sure
And I thought he was kind of done with Sheila and the church
Yeah
He is not
He does say this and I think it's silly
Emergency Saturday broadcast world shocked by Spars 2025-2028 document 2,000,073,000 views
Well that sounds great at Bandai Video
It needs 100 billion views and we beat these people, it's all right there
But 2 million is a good start
But I'm not doing this and putting my life on the line and flying a helicopter right
on the Mexican border where they shoot at helicopters and doing all this to like lose
Yeah I think that that's really illustrative too, it's like Alex's gauge of being able
to beat the globalists has to do with his metrics, they are traffic related, we will
win if we get a hundred million
No you won't
The globalists just watching the view, oh shit he's at 99,999,998, if he gets two more
we lose
Sir, shut down the internet
Shut the internet down
Ridiculous
Yeah
So I thought it was a little bit irresponsible that Alex is you know largely, at least subtly,
maybe not so subtly encouraging people to go down to the border and behave as he did
Yeah
Yeah just to cost people trying to help, I think that's a, humanity is generally widely
recognized to have evolved society by killing people trying to help
And I think that the only effect that that could possibly have is escalating a situation,
raising the temperature beyond the point where it's easily handled by responsible people
Yeah
This is not the only instance of him doing this on this show
This should be the Christian Woodstock, everyone in Canada can get there, I'd say the US but
your borders are so controlled, unless you're a legal alien, everyone should go there, bring
pizzas, bring barbecues, bring, I think if 20,000 people show up it will turn the tide
against this tyranny
Don't you agree everyone should come there, tell us where it is
So that church is just west of the capital city of Edmonton, Alberta, it's really just
a couple of miles outside of the city limits, it's very easy to get to, and you know there's
a public road right there, you can get there and
And for those listening, they must go now, what is the name, what is the address, everyone
must go now
It's Grace Life Church
So yeah everyone's got to go, everyone's got to go to this church, it should be the Christian
Woodstock
Uh huh
So that means Jars of Clay will be performing
Sure
DC Talk is going to reunite
Oh it's about time, it's about time, Red Hot Chili Peppers is going to play with just the
socks on
Ted Nugent's son is going to sit
Yeah this seems irresponsible
Yeah
And it gets kind of worse
Oh of course
It's 51520 or 51529 A Range Road 262 Spruce Grove AB, is that right?
Yes
Alright so here's the deal, instead of being like, I'm not putting you down because you're
just like me, you're like oh thanks for carrying, they've put a fence up and arrested the preacher,
thanks for carrying
Sounds insulting
We're under attack okay, you're under attack so are we, all of us need to go there, if
you're in Canada or if you're near the border, you get in legally, go there peacefully, give
aid and comfort to Christians under CHICOM, Governor, attack the CHICOM agent, I just
showed you him pledging allegiance to Xi Jinping, Trudeau, everyone should go, they're scared
aren't they?
Trudeau did no such thing
No he did not
Um yeah so this is irresponsible and certainly hope that nothing ends up happening there
that Alex might look bad in hindsight, giving the address out and soliciting and inciting
people to go because the church is under attack by the communist Chinese and Justin Trudeau
fucked up
Yeah there's no other way for that to, like it goes two ways, it goes with a bunch of
people showing up and being like oh shit this was dumb, or a bunch of people showing up
and getting whipped into a mob and like let's go down two miles and start wars, you know
like that kind of thing
And when you think you're fighting the fucking literal devil, it seems like the latter is
more likely
Yeah
Yeah so I don't know, I don't think this is good, and I mean it's obviously that they
are fighting the devil
Alex, I've never ever seen overt Satanism in real life before
Oh yeah you told me one of them said Satan is good, tell people about that
I've never seen overt Satanism like that, as you and I both know the enemy works through
all kinds of people but this person drove by in a pickup truck, screamed at women and
children whose church they're looking at being locked up, so they're distraught and this
guy screams at them that he's happy that their church is being closed and then he yells at
other people and he says to them even the church of Satan follows masking laws and that's
why you should too
As a Christian, if you're telling me that Satan likes it, I'm more inclined to not do
it but that's the level of public discourse here
Yeah some guy in a truck said that we're Satanists and even we wear masks
That's the level of overt Satanism
Man, this is the weakest of teas, this is weak tea because I wouldn't even have bought
it if she was just like he screamed out the window I love Satan because then it's like
yeah of course you say that shit, they're a bunch of assholes
She doesn't seem to be as willing to let it fly as Alex
No clue, he's just like hey guys, ostensibly your most evil worshippers in the world are
still not dumb
We're more concerned with public health and our fellow man than you
Satanists don't want people to die of disease, do you not understand where you are in this
situation
Yeah that seems to be with this Satanist alleged Satanist because you might have been
just fucking around
Yeah that sounds more like that
Anyway some guy yelled for him in the truck and all this is going on and so Alex encourages
something man he should be careful with his language
Well I'm telling my listeners, I'm telling them if you live in Canada whether you're
500 miles away or 20 you must go there, bring some muffins, bring some food, support these
great people because the system has drawn the line here, the enemy has drawn a line
at your church, the enemy's drawn a line and said and so they've chosen this as their Stalingrad
and I think we should make this their Stalingrad
Oh boy
Who's chosen this as their Stalingrad?
Nobody's chosen this as a Stalingrad, this is way below the level of Stalingrad
You bet
Also not for nothing the Soviet Union won that battle
Well
The communists might want a better metaphor, also Stalingrad was incredibly violent
Yeah
I don't know if Alex wants to evoke that kind, I mean obviously he does but it doesn't seem
responsible to evoke that kind of imagery surrounding what he's trying to incite people
to go be a part of
Yeah I'm gonna be honest here, okay, here's what I'm putting together, on this very episode
he said literally like everything they're doing, everything they say we're doing is
what they're doing
Right
Right, now I would say that that is revelatory about what he's doing and I'm gonna say that
he worships Satan because this is the behavior of someone who worships Satan
That was just when he was younger
I don't think he stopped, why isn't that a possibility?
That's a long term theory of yours, I understand that
So look dude, I think that this episode is really fucked up, there's multiple incitements
towards listeners going to places that Alex seems to want to get out of hand
Yeah
A little bit
Yeah, even if I was the shithead pastor of that church I would be like Alex no, no, no,
no, no, we don't, no, no, no, no, we don't want that
We want support but you're, this is bad
You're bad support
And really honestly, Sheila wants to bring up that this could all be solved if all the
pastors in the area weren't against this guy
It's very disappointing to see some of the other pastors in the area say well why isn't
this church making the same sacrifices that I am
Oh they make it a sacrifice not to be shut down, they make it a sacrifice to traffic
kids, they make it a sacrifice to submit, those aren't real churches and God knows it
Oh boy
These other pastors, I mean if they can reconcile
These aren't pastors, these are world council of churches, Rockefeller pimps
So this is a point of the episode where I was sort of lost in thought and I started
to think, I have an interesting thought experiment, maybe it's not a thought experiment, rhetorical
question
Sure, sure
Do you think that Alex Jones could name a living member of the Rockefeller family?
Absolutely not, absolutely not, zero percent chance
I don't think he could
No, I do like that this also plays into what should be very obvious to anybody is if it
weren't for immigration and racism, Christians would be murdering each other left and right
They hate each other, they don't believe the same shit, they're all nonsense
Well I mean with this letter of the 28 religious leaders in Alberta, they were all like hey
come on, let's take this seriously
Do you know what was in that letter?
Even the Church of Satan is willing to
That letter was delivered from a truck
From a truck, yes
It's rare that you get the Christian, Muslim, Jewish, Buddhist communities walking arm-in-arm
with the Satanists
Yes, exactly
But this church is enough of a pain in the ass
Oh my god guys, anyway they're giving us a bad name
Alex is trying to get people to go to this church and have it be their Stalingrad, someone's
Stalingrad
Anybody's Stalingrad
In order for this to sound better, he wants Sheila to do it
He wants her
He wants her to tell everybody to go there
Yeah, because
Naturally
Then he could be like ah, she did it, I didn't do that
Yeah, absolutely, implicate somebody else in your crime
She's not as into it as Alex hopes
I feel it, I see it, I think it'll be 5,000 people tomorrow, 10,000 this weekend, I think
they've jumped the shark
Call, you need to do it, beautiful, beautiful soul, tell people, Sheila Gunn-Reed, come
peacefully now, call them, tell them
If people are going to come to support Grace Life, they welcome the support, but if you're
coming, come peacefully and come respectfully, but they would appreciate your support, they
need it now more than ever, their church has been seized by the state, they need all the
support that they can get
I don't want to be peaceful, but we need you to then call them, say, help us, call them
Well I don't want to speak for the church, Alex, I really don't want to speak for the
church
But just as a Canadian, as a human, I'm just saying that everyone needs to hear you call
for that, I'm calling for it, we call for people to stand up for religious freedom
Absolutely
Sheila, I'll go that far
Yeah
I'll support religious freedom, isn't this what like journalists do?
I guess
Is this what Alex thinks reporters do, they come on shows and try and
Demand murders!
I mean, if she's supposed to be covering this story, it doesn't make sense for the interview
to end with him begging her to call people to come to this church
Yeah
That's weird
Yeah, that's bad
Yeah, this isn't any kind of reporting
This is, at best, activism, and at worst, and in reality, incitement
Yeah
This episode is nuts
Sheila, you're a bad person
I mean, I think she's, I don't know enough about her to really have a full picture, but
based on her behavior, I think she's trying to stay a little more neutral than Alex wants
her to be
I do, I do agree with you there
She doesn't understand that Alex is like, she's talking to a guy who's a parody version
Yeah
Of a right-wing media outlet
Oh boy
She's used to, you know, uh
Pretend seriousness
Oh, and at least like, I don't necessarily want to get sued
Sure, sure, sure, sure
Alex doesn't seem to care
I'm behaving in ways where I clearly want people to fucking sue me
I fear consequences, and Alex apparently doesn't
Yeah
In Canada, we might get consequences
In America, Alex receives none
Alex has learned over the course of his career not to respect the idea of chickens coming
home to roost
Of the law, yeah, yeah, yeah
And that's why he behaves the way he does
Yeah, pretty much
I listened to this episode, and I was blown away by like, okay, I thought that video was
bad
Yeah
I thought it, I still think it's bad
I think it's terrible
I think it's legally actionable, and uh, you know, whatever
Yeah
I didn't expect for the episode afterwards to be worse
Yeah, I was, I was surprised, I thought we were gonna have a little fun clowning on that
dumb video, I hadn't seen it, so I was, you know, I was waiting for the show, obviously
And
There's not much to see
Instead, we got a concentrated bullion cube of racism and incitement to violence
Yeah, yeah, and I really, I mean, I mean this, I hope that nothing happens
Yeah, me too
His behavior in the past has led to people going and fucking with people and victimizing
people in ways that are irresponsible and terrible, and for him to have two targets
of like, everyone's gotta go to these places
Yeah
In one day is really, really scary, what it could portend
No, admittedly, it could lead to nothing
But the danger is there, and that is, I just don't think it's acceptable to act this way
Yeah, I mean, see, can't you see in a courtroom, like, your honor, in this trial we aim to
prove that Alex Jones did another Pizzagate, so if we prove that, then he goes away forever,
right?
That's good
I don't know
I'm a bad prosecutor
Yeah, certainly
I don't know how you do that in court, but like, just for the sake of like, a podcast
that explores these things
Sure
I think you can definitely say he's behaving in exactly the same ways as he has when things
have gone bad
Yeah
It's bad
Not good
We should learn from the things that have already happened
Yep
I think that would be wise
Yeah
So, fingers crossed, things work out okay, and I guess we will find out on our next episode
I hope calling on people to not go to the border, or that church
Yes
I strongly call on everyone to not do either of those things
Yeah, I'm in favor of people
Stay home!
Yeah
Have a nice little cocktail
Isn't that better than going to the border or a weird church in Canada?
Yep
I think so
And we will be back, but until then Jordan, we have a website
We do, it's knowledgefight.com
Oh wait, I forgot, also
What's that?
Like I said, we're gonna, our Monday episode will be on Wednesday
It'll be on Wednesday, yes
But if I'm feeling better, might put out a little funny fun thing on Monday
We'll see
Also, we're gonna be on Twitter
We are on Twitter, it's at knowledgefight.com, go to bed Jordan
We're also on Facebook
We are on Facebook
If you would like to download the show, and if you could, please find a local charity
or bail fund in your area to help out people doing God's work
Yep
We'll be back, but until then, I'm Neo, I'm Leo, I'm DZXClark, I'm Daryl Rundis
So what do you think about them apples?
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan, I love your work
I love you