N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am SWEATING
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledge fight
knowledge fight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
saying we are the bad guys
knowledge fight
Dan and Jordan, knowledge fight
RIDDLER, RIDDLER, RIDDLER
I need, I need money
Andy and Kansas, Andy and Kansas
Stop it, Andy and Kansas, Andy and Kansas
Andy and, Andy, it's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding
Hello Alex, I'm a victim caller, I'm a huge fan
I love your room
knowledgefight
n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're a couple dudes, like to sit around, drink novelty beverages and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are, Dan
Jordan
Dan
Quick question for ya
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today is that I have been vaccinated
Yay!
I got it all taken care of and I'm okay
Yes indeed
At this point, it was an interesting weekend
I actually, I got my date wrong and ended up getting the vaccine on Saturday
Yes, yep
And I had heard from some people, I had some friends who have gotten shot and they've told
me about like, oh, you know, hey, the next day it's pretty bad or like I had a little
bit of, you know, some, some effects
Sure, sure, sure
And so you were kind enough to drive me to get the vaccine and I went and immediately
I was very cocky
Oh!
I was so cocky
I was very much like, I'm not even having any side effects, I wanna, I wanna be part
of the team, everybody's suffering through this
I appreciated very much the hubris of saying, you know, I feel like I'm not even a part
of the communal experience of the side effects
Yeah
And so that evening, Saturday evening, Wrestlemania was on
Right
Saturday and Sunday and it was the return of the live audience at a Wrestlemania and
there was this weird resonance between, I got vaccinated on the same day as Wrestlemania
is having crowds return
Sure, sure
There was sort of a swell of emotion of like normal, pseudo normalcy
You can see the horizon
You can see the horizon over there
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah and so I was watching it and right at about 9.30 I got hit by a train of a fever
Just a, just a locomotive and so I had a little bit of a fever through the end of Saturday
night of Wrestlemania and went straight to bed and felt fine, Sunday really
Yes
But felt real stupid
Well, I mean, Dan, you got your wish, you joined the communal experience of side effects
Dan
Yeah
You and I are both fully vaccinated now
I felt really stupid cause I was like looking at my texts to you and I was like, there's
no side effects
I'm fine
It was very funny
I'm a superman
It was very funny, I didn't feel any like resentment towards you, I was just sitting
there going like, oh, I've heard some people don't have side effects, maybe Dan will be
one of the ones
In the back of my mind I was like, something's gonna happen
Yeah, it wasn't too bad too, like it wasn't even like a really bad fever, I'm just kind
of weak
Yeah
I'm very soft and a little bit of a fever and I was just like, I need to put on a little
hat, a little bedtime hat
A little bedclothes, nice little sleepy time tea
Yeah, and so also, I just feel like I should do this, a little review of Wrestlemania
Sure, sure, of course
Boo
That was a very little review
Yeah
Wow
Real bad?
Mm
How did, we had a conversation about Bray Wyatt and his nonsense, did they do what
we, I surmised that they would do a movie like that, where they go inside of a, nope
What happened?
So for the listeners who don't watch wrestling, Bray Wyatt was a guy who was a swamp hillbilly
cult leader
Sure
And was a lot of fun
Unofficial mascot of this podcast, I believe
Sure, yeah
Our first tweet was, yeah, yeah, yeah
No, I don't think that was our first tweet, but it was the first one I tagged Alex Jones
in
Yes, yeah, yeah
He was on Twitter
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
So he used to be a swamp hillbilly cult leader, and that was a lot of fun, he gave rambling
sermons, and then he went away and he came back as a children's TV show host
Sure
It was a little bit creepy
At the Firefly Funhouse, and then he also was possessed by a demon called the Fiend
Right
That made him nearly indestructible, and there's a bunch of convoluted nonsense storytelling
Of course
Then at last year's Wrestlemania, they did a cinematic movie type match, where it was
called a Firefly Funhouse match
Sure
Where the Fiend deconstructed John Cena's ego in his entire career
Right
Through a weird psychological deconstruct- it was amazing
No, no, we- I watched it, this is one of the few things about wrestling that I've ever
watched, we watched it together, and I told you this was actually very, very good
It was a lot of fun, so over the course of this year, the Fiend, the demon guy, he got
burned alive
Sure, sure
Randy
Professional wrestling, correct?
Okay
Randy Orton set him on fire, and burned him alive, and he disappeared for a bit, but by
that point, he had indoctrinated Alexa Bliss, who was another character on the show
Sure
Into the dark arts, or the evil
Naturally
Or whatever
Yeah, whatever it is they do
And so she was sort of pestering Randy Orton, and throwing fireballs at him, because she
can throw fireballs now
Well yeah, but why not?
Sure
You burned a man alive, you might as well give his buddy the ability to throw fireballs
So at the last pay-per-view, Alexa Bliss had talked Randy Orton into a match with her
Sure
And of course, this was all a trap
Well yeah, she shoots fire
And the Fiend came back, and he was all burned and everything
Okay, alright
Charred up, and like, oh my god, he's a zombie, he's back
Sure, sure, sure
You will be visited by three other ghosts immediately following this one
Yes
Yeah, yeah
So at this WrestleMania, on night two, they had the match between the Fiend and Randy
Orton, and it was like, what the fuck is this gonna be?
They've already burned him to death
Yeah, yeah, so I would say, you know
A wrestling match
A chalk and ash bone match
I was like, this is so stupid
And so actually, during the pre-show of night one, I was yelling at the screen, open with
the Fiend match you cowards!
Yeah
Because it's the worst idea, why would you ever open the show with that match?
Oh, it's a terrible idea
And they opened the show with that match
They did not
And it was so dumb
They opened the show with that match, that's a terrible idea
Yeah
Oh my god
It was really bad
Oh boy
Yep, and it started with Bray Wyatt as the Fiend, charred, walking down the hallway
And as he walked down the hallway, all the char dropped off him and he was magically
healed
And he regenerated?
Yeah
He regenerated?
Oh man
Yep
Oh shit, that should have been on Easter
Should have been on Easter
The Fiend comes back on Easter Sunday?
That's the way you do it
I would explain what happened in the match, but I don't really understand it and it was
dumb
I will say my high point, and this is damning the Wrestlemania with faint praise, my high
point was the rapper Bad Bunny
I have been hearing a lot of people say positive things about a rapper who did some flips
Yes, that was on night one, it might have been when my fever was setting in, but he
killed it
It was a lot of fun to watch him have just the best time
Clearly he was having a lot of fun
That didn't happen, I checked with some people before the show and they were like no, Bad
Bunny's never been on Wrestlemania, Dan just had a terrible fever
Oh shit
Dan, your fever was so bad, your brain was torturing itself
On night two they had a great video, like a little piece where Bad Bunny comes walking
up onto a street and Triple H is standing there with a briefcase and he's like you did
great at Wrestlemania, now you go do what you do
Oh god no
So he hands him the briefcase and he's got a microphone
No no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
I don't even know anything about Bad Bunny's music and I have been won over, he seems charming
Anyway, this has been my protracted bright spot, how about you Jordan
Dan, my bright spot of all things, there's a new TV show called Made for Love
Features someone who's burned to death, comes back
Close, surprisingly close, it's like a, you know, tech billionaire, he does some stuff,
it's quite funny, but the main thing is Ray Romano is incredible in it
Oh yeah
He has turned himself into an actor with a, with a capital Taur
I think he's always been pretty good
He's always been pretty good, but you wouldn't expect everybody loves Raymond to be this
guy and to pull it off as well as he does
I don't know, have you seen Men of a Certain Age?
That was pretty good
Was it?
Was it Andre Brauer?
Wait, Men of a Certain Age, which age?
Yeah, Ray Romano, Quantum Leap Guy, Scott Bakula
Scott Bakula is still alive?
It was a while back, there was a show, I remember
Scott Bakula was alive a while back?
He was of a certain age
I remember that show being alright, I might be wrong about that
Wait, it was a show?
Yeah
I thought it was like a
It was on like USA
I thought it was like the Deep Impact to Wild Hogs's Armageddon if you will
You know, Men of a Certain Age and Wild Hogs both came out the same year kind of thing
There's thematic overlap
Sure
Aging
Anyway
Okay
Jordan
Yes?
Today we have an episode to go over
Oh we do
Yup
Was that what we were doing?
So I had this weekend of, you know, sort of recovery and what have you and convalescence
Even though I probably wasn't nearly as, you know, in need of that as I might have thought
I might need to be
I appreciate everybody allowing us, you know, being cool about Monday on Wednesday this
week
But as I was getting back to work I was like, I don't want to do this stuff
Like I didn't want to look at the present day
There have been some shootings and, you know, police involved shooting in Minneapolis
And I just, I just didn't have the stomach to jump right back into that with Alex
And so I decided we're going back to 2003
Okay
We're going to dip our toes back in
We'll deal with the present day on Friday
Sure
But I needed to have something that had a little bit less stakes in order to dive back
in on
And we'll talk about that here in just a moment
But before we do we've got to take a moment to say thank you to some folks who have signed
up and are supporting the show
That's a great idea
So first, Scatman AKA Dan, thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks Scatman AKA Dan
This is a good point for me to also apologize
It has been brought up to me that I did say on an early episode that if we ever made it
to a point where we were comfortable doing this podcast
Oh no, we don't bring that up anymore
That I would change my name legally to Scatman
We don't bring that up anymore
I'm not going to be able to do that
Well, we were not expecting it
Yes
We were putting, we were putting a lot of money on not making any money
I do keep open the possibility of a Scatman John tattoo or just his mustache
Oh yeah
Next, Willard Wonka in the policy factory
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks Willard Wonka
Next, Courtney B, not a walk-in but I was in a Nelly song
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks Courtney
Good to know that is not a walk-in
That's not a walk-in
No
You know Courtney B telling me about a party up in NYC
I don't
Gotta make it damn right
First flight, first flight, first flight
Ah, come on
Mix the Vanna White
I don't know
I'm never going to understand it
The world still thought Nelly was a good idea
Must be the money
They really did
That's a great song
Okay
Anyway, uh, Toko, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks Toko
Thank you
Next, Davey Pancakes, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Davey Pancakes
Thank you
Next, evil commie feminist witch definitely coming for your guns, thank you so much,
you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Hey, and finally, uh, I got a little technocrat shout out going out to Conal
Thank you so much, Conal, you are now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
Crikey, mate, that's fantastic, have yourself a brew
How's your 401k doing, bro?
Alright, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this Watson, alright?
Let's just get down to business
We ain't making that money off that heroin
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large
I declare info war on you
Thanks so much, Conal
Yes, thank you very much, Conal
Also, Jordan, I know you know this
What's up, Dan?
Now, the world needs to know this
Okay
There are two April birthdays, uh, myself
Indeed they are
Myself
There's one, you have two in April as well this year, I believe
And Dr. Gums, my buddy Dr. Gums also has a, uh, has a April birthday
Alright
You know who else does?
Brad.
How's it going, Brad?
Happy birthday, Brad
Uh, Tyler got in touch with us and wanted us to wish Brad a happy birthday
So, Brad, happy birthday
Happy birthday, Brad
We didn't say when your birthday was, though
It's just in April at some point
Not important
It doesn't have to be in April
My birthday's in April and so is Dr. Gums, which means that it's the best month
Also, Mandy Moore, Cedric the Entertainer, Kelly Clarkson
Okay
Anyway, Jordan, today we are going over May 5th, 2003
Alright
You may recall that our last episode was about May 2nd, 2003
And you're like, what the hell, why are we jumping?
We aren't jumping
Okay
May 2nd was a Thursday
Uh-huh
It was a Friday
Now we're back on Monday
It was a busy Friday
Yeah
He doesn't have a Sunday show at this point
Gotcha
So we're just back on Monday here
And here is an out of context drop from today's show
Kids are now being arrested for stepping in water puddles
That's an aggressive move
That is an aggressive move
Yep, kids are being arrested for stepping in water puddles
Stepping in water puddles?
Yeah
How deep are we talking?
So deep
I want to know, I want to know the regulations on what pools
What is the pool of water in this circumstance?
I regret to inform you that Alex does not get into that
Oh, that's a real bummer
Any of the specific details on that front
Alright
So Alex begins the show complaining about how the bath party is being put in all the
positions of power in Iraq
Which in retrospect sounds really right on
He's right about everything
He will shortly be very, very, very wrong
And then we get an edition of the game that I like to play
That is Where in the World is Saddam Hussein?
And they are setting up a dictatorship
They are putting a regional governors in
All former bath party officials in the 23 ministries
That is official, White House last week
Most of Saddam's former people, most of them trained in the US by the CIA
That was the CIA government under Saddam until they broke
When he followed orders to invade Kuwait
And got a lot of trouble, they set him up
As Saddam said on ITN, now comfortable living in Russia
So apparently Saddam is now comfortable living in Russia
Okay
On our last episode he was in Haiti or was it Cuba?
I believe he was in Cuba
Yeah
He was in Cuba
So now he's, in the last couple days he's gone from Cuba to Russia
I think there was an Indiana Jones style interstitial
Where there's the plane and the red line going from spot to spot
I believe
Yeah
Boy, he gets around
Nobody, nobody has seen him get on any of these flights
No
Cuba, Russia
Right
That hole
That, yeah
Where he was found
Yes, exactly
Yeah
Quite a travel itinerary
Yeah, so this is interesting the way that this is playing out
That Alex is very much on the page of the bath party is going to be in charge of everything
Naturally
It's just going to be very, very wrong in a very short period of time
Yeah
So at this point in Alex's career, he's a different Alex Jones than he is in the present
day
In some ways and he's the same in some ways
Right now in 2021 even as he's being a real dum-dum on air and being very sad and not
great at his job
Just a real shit pile
He's still in a million dollar studio
Yes
He's still got the LED screens behind him
True
He's the kind of guy who shows up with bullhorns at events that he didn't organize in DC and
people chant his name
He can afford to hire at least 15, 18 year olds at a time
And you know, he can draw a crowd
He can lead some people from Trump's rally to the Capitol in a way that might look bad
in hindsight
We don't need to worry about that
In 2003 he was a little bit different
The kind of bookings Alex was taking back then
Oh no
But before I go any further, a couple quick announcements
I rarely traveled, but I will be up at KCXL 1140 that carries the daytime show
KCXL 1140 for the Liberty Factor, May 17th, that's a couple weeks from now on a Saturday
May 17th and that's going to be from 10 a.m. to 9 p.m.
Colonel Craig Roberts and others will be there speaking
And I'll be speaking for several hours and doing a presentation and it's going to be
a great event and it's a benefit for KCXL
And I hope to see everybody there
So Alex is basically, he's doing a local radio gig
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I like that
I appreciate that a lot
There's maybe a minor league baseball game somewhere nearby
There's a car dealership opening that he's going to be appearing at
So I was wondering about this station because it's like Alex is going out of his way to
go to this station
Yeah
It seems weird
Like what can we find out about this place?
And, well, there's a 2020 article about the station that I thought was a little bit interesting
seeing how things turned out for them
So wait, this was just last year?
Yeah
Okay, alright
So this station is owned by a guy named Pete Chartel and he signed a deal not too long
ago with Radio Sputnik to air their broadcasting for six hours a day on this station AM 1140
as well as two other stations he runs for approximately $60,000 a year
Ooh, you know, it's tough keeping a Ma and Pa radio station alive though
Right
So like, you gotta find revenue where you can
Yeah, sure
Yeah, you gotta do what you gotta do
It's interesting, I find that interesting, not necessarily all that damning or anything
No, no, no
Weird
Yeah
Also, prior to this, this station was airing people like Alex Jones and of course Rick
Wiles who you may remember is that fundamentalist asshole who called the Trump impeachment a
quote Jew coup
Yes
This line in a KCUR profile about him and this station is actually kind of stunning
Quote, Chartel acknowledges that KCXL has at times given platforms to people who quote
seem antisemitic
But Chartel said that he thinks his listeners are well informed and should be able to quote
decide for themselves whether they think something is anti this or anti that whether it's based
on prejudice or upon someone's wrong interpretation of the facts
Now, now I feel like we're misunderstanding a real issue there
I understand it's up to the listener to decide whether or not they believe it is antisemitism
however it is and you put it on the radio, sir
Well, he certainly says it seems like it is
It doesn't get, we don't get to go back from seems, we don't get to go back from seems
you put it on the radio
Yeah
And plenty of your listeners were well aware of that it was antisemitism and it was a selling
point for them
I'm taking up time on my broadcast to air Nazi stuff and I'm gonna, you know, run commercials
during it
Sure
But I trust that the audience gets that I don't like this
I'm not gonna, I'm not gonna stump for them
I'm just gonna give them a place to spread their views without any pushback
Yeah, so that's the station that Alex is going to do
Good stuff
Great
So Alex has some gripes in 2003
He's got some issues but there's one issue that is rises above all of them
Okay
The biggest thing we face is the overnight talk sensation types that talk about deliberate
disinformation on purpose
They'll have five stupid guests for one good guest that talks about real information
What that then does is when the average American hears somebody talk about famous corrupt world
government they've heard that mixed in with the Green Martians from the South Pole or
you know Planet X or whatever and then it neutralizes all of it, it's the poison pill
Whereas everything we talk about here is proven and is documented and is in your face
So the biggest issue that the truth movement or whatever Alex is engaged in at this point
The biggest issue that they face is these opportunistic radio people who talk about
some of the real issues but then mix in stuff like aliens or let's say extra dimensional
demons and fighting the literal devil
Right, right
One could say that he has become everything that he hates most in this exact moment
Alex's biggest problem in 2003 is his future self
Is Alex in 2021
Yeah
Oh boy
Gotta love it
So I heard that and I thought like well that's just good fun
That is
But this actually leads to what I think is a really interesting moment later in the episode
Okay
There's something that rises this up to a level of relevance that it wouldn't have otherwise
But before we get to that Alex has got to complain a lot about how they're going to
outlaw homeschooling
Okay
I've got the headline right here homeschooling under new law to be abused in California just
says period you homeschool it's abusive
Yes it's the new America folks this is who they're coming after hope you know the terrorism
manual say Christians gun owners homeschoolers word for word and you thought it was the Muslims
oh no they work for the CIA any real Muslim terrorists is flying around in a plane with
bars of gold from your tax money
What?
Any real
By the way Senate reports before I end this segment you want to find out about those Muslim
terrorists that work for the CIA get 911 the road to tyranny and part two of that the masters
of terror
Interesting add pivots
Wow
That's the way it worked back then
If you want to find out about the Muslims terrorists
Flying around with bars of gold
With bars of gold from your tax money
Okay
Yeah
So all the terrorists without bars of gold are fake Muslim terrorists?
I think that Alex is saying that there aren't really any except for CIA run Muslim terrorists
yeah it's interesting
That is interesting
Yeah
Okay
So they're gonna they're gonna get rid of homeschooling they're calling it abuse
I mean I have a problem with homeschooling as a way to avoid learning that's a big issue
where they're like I don't want my kid learning any of that devil math that's an issue
Right
So they should learn the math of the spheres
Yeah homeschooling in and of itself isn't necessarily abusive but it can be an element
of abuse if you're keeping your child in a you know raising them in some kind of absurd
way
Perhaps
Let's say homeschooling could be an element of that but just because someone decides to
homeschool does not necessarily equate to that
Yeah
And I think that Alex likes to play the margins there likes to pretend that everybody is saying
that homeschool is intrinsically
Sure
Inactive abuse
I mean yeah
I don't think that those are the arguments that people are making
You know I mean in my small community growing up we had a couple I had I had that but I
think we had both ends of the spectrum of homeschool kids the kids who are homeschooled
who were clearly way overachievers and you meet them and they're six years old and you're
like yeah you shouldn't be in with the rest of the chattel you need to be raised by your
weirdo parents to become a math genius that's fine
And then the other end of that was the like well okay so they know everything about the
Bible and then beyond that we're in real dicey territory
Sure
Yeah
And I think one of the difficulties and challenges of homeschooling is obviously like socialization
and I think people have figured out ways around that with like you know groups and
strategies and stuff like that
Yeah yeah yeah yeah the whole thing
Yeah but I don't know the way that I look at it is like yeah there's some homeschool
stuff that's bad and there's some stuff that's fine
Yeah
Alex on the other hand when he looks at school
Sure
It's all bad
Oh well and all over the country cesspools like California run by socialists and gun
grabbing creatures like Davis are first saying oh we're gonna rescue you homeschool we don't
have a teaching certificate not a law they just say it same thing in Illinois they're
trying it all over now even some southern states it's all about intimidation it's less
than 1% it's to scare you than to be highly publicized we've talked to Christopher before
he's given us this great analysis and I agree with him it's what they're doing now though
they're trying to put it into law and call it child abuse where they just refuse the
school refused to give you quote your form then you don't put your child in their abusive
system where your child learns how to be a crack whore or learns how to worship world
government or learns how to report mommy and daddy thrown in guns
Are they the only three?
Christianity is seen as a cult religion but they teach you how to be a Muslim I mean it
goes on and on
What?
The nightmares in these schools when your kid gets arrested if they're caught playing
tag or dodge ball
These are weird examples
Yeah this is a very strange dystopia that he's painting a picture that if that were
real you would that's some very weird adults doing some weird stuff like as a whole
Yeah I don't know how public education teaches you to be and I don't like this term but as
Alex is calling it a crack whore
A crack sex worker
I don't know what that educational curriculum is like I also think yeah I mean like obviously
tag and dodge ball that's just those right wing talking points around this time and periodically
whenever they want to deploy those yeah it's weird
Yeah I don't think I remember any classes growing up that was just like okay we're gonna
watch the wire and then you figure out what character you want to be and we'll build a
curricula based on that
Yeah I also don't know I don't know what classes ever have been like Christianity is a cult
and oh here's how you become a Muslim
I don't know if I've ever read it yet
It's a little
That's not very
It seems a little bit like a caricature
I feel like he might be describing a women's studies course in a very wrong way
I don't know so Alex has an example though of like the way that this is out of control
in the schools the schools are out of control they're trying to get everyone jammed up
Okay
Like here in Austin Texas if you're late to class three times that's considered truancy
they criminally charge you in one school over half the kids have been charged though the
state law says 12 to 14 truancies in a semester they're not even following the law anymore
I met a lady she showed me the documents and she actually works for someone in my family
and she brought she showed me the documentation her child was in kindergarten six years ago
and was out for a week with pneumonia they have now criminally charged her for truancy
in kindergarten and we went look at the statute of limitations it's like six months because
there's not even a criminal charge and they're now criminally charging her they're not even
following laws now sir
What?
That seems uh if true I am outraged sir
Yeah I don't believe this
So the first thing that I find troubling about this story is that a week is a pretty quick
recovery time for a kindergartner to get over pneumonia
As easy
That seems fishy
That's a strong kindergartner
Also Jordan I would ask you this question what is truancy if you're a kindergartner?
Those kids are between four and six years old so it's not like they're even able to
skip class
They stopped watching The Wire all right they turned around
If there's an unexplained absence of a child in kindergarten that's an issue with the parents
a six-year-old is not responsible for getting themselves to class like a high schooler might
be so pretending there's an equivalence in terms of truancy is just ridiculous
The kindergarten hires a guy in a van to drive around outside all 7-elevens and be like hey
you you're it's your one day you gotta be in school get in there
According to the Texas Board of Education there are a bunch of steps that are taken
before any kind of court would come into play with truancy issues as it stands now
These rules were changed to get rid of any possible criminal charges back in 2015 but
even prior to that the worst that would really happen to a student is that they would be
charged with a Class C misdemeanor
Sure
That they could get out of control and we'll discuss that in a second
Right right right
I'm not sure how I feel about any of this but I'm also pretty sure from what I've read
on the subject that this is only something that currently is done after there are attempts
to resolve the truancy issue and those attempts have failed
Sure
And it's not even how this stuff works anymore
This is one of those interesting things about Alex in the past though where he he's actually
covering a murky subject but he's sensationalizing it so far past the point where it can be taken
seriously
Yeah
So people can and should discuss what approaches are appropriate to take in terms of encouraging
attendance in school and how chronic truancy is often an indication of a larger problem
that should not be ignored and kids need help with
Yeah if chronic truancy the problem is not you're not in school often enough
Right
There's a way bigger problem somewhere
It usually is a sign of something that someone could use some kind of assistance with
Is imposing fines on high schoolers who skip class all the time a good strategy or is it
overly punitive and counterproductive?
That is a fine conversation and I think that it's worth having
Sure
Where it falls apart and why Alex is a terrible source of information about anything is the
point where he makes this about a kindergartner who had pneumonia being criminally charged
for being out of school
That's absurd and even according to the debatably too harsh rules that Texas operated under
at the time these truancy rules only applied to students in first through 12th grade
Alex is making up an extreme example of some anecdote that he's heard that's so severe
that it creates an image in the audience's head about this policy that he's looking to
demonize
He does this because that's easier than it would be to look over data and come up with
an argument against the policy as it exists
If you can just paint a dramatic overly emotionally charged picture in your audience's head you
don't have to do the work of making an actual point
Yeah
Yeah that'd be like I remember whenever they took away three three a day practices when
I was in high school doing football and I and people were all like oh no you're making
the kids soft and all of that stuff and yeah that was probably the best decision to take
that away but this would be like if Alex got on and he was like yeah they said you only
have to do two and this coach he went ahead and did three anyways so they fucking killed
him they just killed him they murdered him on the spot they're not even following the
laws anymore
There's no due process
They just murdered the coach on the field
Honestly my problem is the lack of due process
Exactly it's due process
So also by framing the issue that Alex is discussing like this he can sidestep the uncomfortable
reality that this kind of program disproportionately victimizes students without means
If you skip school and you're fined for it and you can't pay the fine what happens then?
A 2015 article on Buzzfeed discussed the case of an 11th grader in Texas who couldn't pay
and was quote offered jail credit at a rate of three hundred dollars per day
This is an incredibly flawed system and the conversation about it is done a disservice
by having Alex try to grandstand about imaginary kindergartners
Thankfully there are other adults discussing these sorts of issues in terms of reality
and adjustments were made no thanks to Alex's idiotic fake advocacy
Yeah yeah like it's such a huge issue too when you consider the school to prison pipeline
and how so many things are meant to criminalize children at an early enough age so you can
just keep them criminals forever and use them as fuel for the capitalist mill
But Alex clearly one only cares about white kids so there's a problem there
And two is just he's not dealing with any of the larger problem he's just like ah they're
criminalizing kindergartners and you're like oh fuck
I think that this has an interesting intersection of that school to prison pipeline idea which
is definitely real and an issue
Totally
And also misguided but well intentioned ideas
Yes
I do think that some people who may not be trying to criminalize children think they're
like okay if you're in high school and you skip school and you get a fine maybe you'll
be less likely to skip high school
Sure
You know encouraging the right behavior the wrong way
Yeah
I think that there is an element of that but even so no matter what no matter where more
of the weight lies
Yeah
Whatever Alex is doing is pointless
And it doesn't help solve any of the problems
Yeah no and you can totally imagine like I can get inside the mind of the person who
offered the kid like oh so we'll give you credit for doing jail and that person was
probably thinking they were a genius like see you can't afford to pay it you just do
some jail
Right
I'm helping you out instead of somebody who should have been slapped in the face the moment
they had that thought
Yeah it's
You know
Yeah
The moment you're like hey how about do some time in jail instead of paying me the money
that doesn't make any sense for you to pay me in the first place
Yeah reading that kind of stuff it doesn't make a lot of sense why you would continue
down this road of this policy
Yeah
Yeah anyway Alex mentioned a guy named Chris there and he's a guy named Chris Klicka who's
a lawyer for an organization that is a staunchly conservative Christian organization that is
all about homeschool
That's terrible that's terrible because I would listen to MC Chris Klicka instantly
I would listen to his mixtape
You would not
He drops that oh man
Here's what most of his songs are about
Okay
Those who oppose us those who are anti-parent and the pro-child forces and I don't mean
that in a positive way they're they're trying to take our children through whatever means
they can
Well let's face it there's also a big move to take people's children to give it to homosexuals
Oh yeah
Oh boy
Okay
So yeah this is this is the way this manifested in 2003
Yeah that's not as good of a mixtape as I was hoping
No
No no that was not the coloring book that was
Yeah so apparently this a lot of this stuff with these schools and the truancy and the
punishment and the that gets the social services involved and all this and part of it is that
there's a major push to take your kids and give them to homosexuals
Sure sure
Again
The homosexual agenda is running amok in 2003 because that is where the edge that the conservative
panic is playing
Yep yep these people are silly children
Mm-hmm
They it's so weird to go back into the past and listen to these people and think you're
still allowed to talk aren't you people still listen to you you listen to that and you're
like really we're doing that back then yeah and you're still around
It's pretty wild
How?
Mm-hmm
And it's just a conservative edge grift mill is just so endless
Yep
And it's the same shit
Yep it's the same it's the same shit with just slightly different window dressing
Put different little ingredients into the same stew
Yep
Shit
So if you go to the hospital and you're gonna give birth
Sure
These social service people
I'm gonna take the yeah no I'm gonna steal those kids and I'm gonna give them to homosexuals
I believe
They're very least gonna take the kids
Yeah well
Yeah this is worse than the Soviet Union
Oh yeah
You go and you have what's that already is here they're stalking the hospitals they've
got plants in there they get a cut and the people look ignorant man their kids are gone
That's right
I mean if you look ignorant man it's oh they walk in and go please sign here well what
are you doing just work with us everything will be all right you sign it they grab your
kid and go ha ha ha I mean literally
Uh-huh
I don't know and Alex does not expound on what it means to look ignorant in this in
this case
Yeah I think we
I don't know I honestly don't know what he means it it does not make sense
It's true that's true it really doesn't make any sense
Nope
I just don't you know people listen to that and they don't hear people who are whining
like crazy people like this is insane like do you know what's going on now I went to
the DMV to re-up my license and instead of giving me a new license they shit in my mouth
they shit directly into my mouth
Literally
The lid you know they put me down they held me down they had me on a gurney and somebody
shit directly into my mouth
I have documents
From it was they were on a ladder and it was it dropped for a while
I have a notarized witnesses signature
Yeah it's like what are you talking about right you sound ridiculous
Yeah
You're children
Yeah yeah it's it's pretty wild and and when you talk about that it gets into like okay
well obviously Alex nowadays would call them the devil
Yeah yeah
That's what he would do nowadays
Yep
But in 2003 people who mix that stuff up
Oh they're they're
That's the poison pill
It's too far
That's how you make the Patriots and all this look bad
Yeah
A caller calls in and wants to talk about the social service workers and he thinks that
they are demons
Okay okay here we go
Now here is Alex's response
All right
When people hear statements that these people are diabolic they are of the devil just listening
to you talk about the guidelines when you went through your training proves that they
are your first three guidelines were totally unscriptural anti-scriptural it goes against
the creator and our instructions for life and they are of the devil and Alex you're
right on the money with that these people are
I'm gonna be honest I've covered them been around them and you know this is a news program
but when you're around them they really are demonic I mean I'm gonna be I mean these are
at least what I've seen these are degenerate scum that's all I can say about them
That's kind of measured
Yeah
They're demonic that's an adjective this is a news show
Isn't that interesting
I too appreciate that
He's trying to walk a line
Yeah
He knows he knows that like I can't fucking present myself as a guy who's saying that
my enemies politically are devils
Yeah I won't be taken seriously I won't be taken seriously
Yeah I have some pretense of wanting to be respected
Yeah
Oh man I think I might be able to get a show on an actual network at some point
Yeah that is that is interesting and I mean what's kind of interesting about it is that
at the time I think he's right you couldn't be out and out the demons are coming to kill
us all
Yeah probably not
And people wouldn't take you seriously
Well I think Alex certainly didn't have a big enough career
Right
He wasn't a big enough star to be able to absorb whatever blow might come from that
And then I would say probably right around what like the tea party movement whenever
they swept in 2010 that's really when it all was like started a change where you could
just talk about demons all all you want
Well I mean what is that Hunter S. Thompson quote when the going gets weird the weird
turn pro
The weird turn pro you got it
You know when the normal is the tea party on the right
Yeah
You know whatever you are as Alex Jones
Gotta go weirder
Gotta escalate a little bit
Yep
Yeah I don't know I obviously don't know for sure if that is when sort of more overt conversation
about demons and shit happen
Yeah
Because I don't think it did I think it was later
You think so?
Yeah I think that we did not see nearly as much these people are the fucking devil when
we were looking at 2015
That's true that is true
So I think I think it might be more recent than that
Yeah
But I find I find this glimpse at 2003 really really interesting and this next clip I think
Alex has to stop himself
Interesting
From saying that these people are demons
Okay
And this clip would not stick out to me at all if I didn't know what he does now
So so what you're telling me is that like a demon trying to get out he wants to call
these people demons okay just just putting that out there
And so imagine being at the hospital you've already got your four other kids with family
and friends you're there your babies are hanging on for life and literal I'm sorry creatures
show up and are cornering you with their beady eyes what parent frankly what parent wouldn't
probably fluff out at that point
Doesn't that sound
Literal demons he was about to say literal demons
He was
About to say literal demons I'm screaming at you through the future you I mean you were
there the whole time
Doesn't that sound almost like someone had told him dude don't fucking say that you're
fighting the devil we need like Ted Anderson told him there's no way we're gonna be able
to sell gold with you yelling about the literal devil because he said sorry he said literal
long pause sorry creatures
Yep wild and see this is this is a piece of evidence circumstantial obviously yes not
definitive but it works towards answering the question that I have had for a while which
is is Alex's I'm fighting the devil thing a new thing right or is it something that
was there underneath all along and he was pretending that that wasn't what he believed
and I kind of think that this looks like
It's not smoking gun but I'll be goddamn if it doesn't really sound like you're on the
right track gumshoe
It feels like that is at least a minor indication that Alex has this idea that his enemies are
literal demons yeah and he was covering that belief up for the sake of appearing respectable
yeah yeah and I'm interested to see if there's any more flickers of that indications but
that made me that's laugh really hard
perks your ears up yeah yeah but isn't it interesting too that like that clip would
not be at all it wouldn't sound off any alarms unless you knew that 18 years later yeah screaming
about literal demons everywhere all the time all the time yeah that's so ridiculous yeah
I'm oh that's annoying I don't I don't like that he's a liar I'm mad at him in the past
for lying to me Dan you should be up front if you think your enemies are literal demons
you should tell me yeah front yeah I think it would be more responsible to the audience
yeah because don't you don't you tell me that you're hiding that there are literal demons
everywhere because you're supposed to be the truth teller right on your own show yeah and
you're pulling back whenever you know that literal demons are killing everybody don't
Trojan horse the literal demons at the talk of like the Federal Reserve and all this stuff
that's not fair to the audience totally anyway yeah Alex is a guy who's against the Iraq
war totally totally against the Iraq war but since it weirdly fine with the idea of deposing
Saddam Hussein in this next I mean you gotta I tell you what I just got I just I can't
believe it I can't believe people we had operation Iraqi freedom okay great Saddam's a thug great
can't we have operation American freedom yeah why not you know Bush wanted to turn all this
around here but he didn't he put more funding into the Department of Education all these
other groups and I can't we we have the conservative the real conservative backbone to do it how
Chris do we force the Republicans that control everything now to finally get rid of abortion
to finally just acts these social workers how do we do it so apparently we want operation
American freedom right in the mold of operation Iraqi free exactly and that involves getting
rid of social workers right abortion there we go okay we did it that is a complex series
of steps you need to get to those three things being related to each other at all I don't
like it no I don't like it I don't like these callers I don't like this guest no no I think
these people are literal demons no no I've been hiding that belief this whole time so
this caller has some bad things to say sure I'll just say bad sure sure sitting here listening
to Alex you asked him a few of the questions he answered for me one aspect about this demonic
side of it one place in the scripture where Messiah got very angry and that was when with
children he said you suffer these children to come to me for such as the kingdom of heaven
and these people are not letting them come to him they're like doing what Alex said they
learning Islam and all kinds of a multi cultural crap it's called math Virginia Chris I'm in
Virginia weird weird question that's a very strange thing yeah that's a very strange thing
to add on hey hey where are you by the way yeah I think that this is a bit more anti-Muslim
than I expected it to be yeah because I think the presentation that Alex has is very much
like and I had no problem with Islam or anything like and I think I got the sense that his
his anti-islam stuff kind of escalated yeah and to be fair you know that's coming from
his caller yeah but yeah yeah that doesn't surprise me I'm I would be Islam in the schools
saying that Islam is just multicultural crap yeah like it's what the fuck is this freedom
prize just yeah whatever you want just just fucking shut up yeah so this caller wants
to know where in Virginia Chris's organization is and they Alex has to stop now I'll tell
you they told my son to find the square root of something roots are in the backyard my
friend that's devil worship that's what I'm telling you right now go find the square root
of Vega get digging why don't you go find a switch so yeah they chat about where they
are in Virginia and Alex has to be like guys what are we doing why did you ask him so unfortunately
they end up stopping that very pleasant conversation it does sound nice to take another call that
might have been a mistake oh very good guest you got on there today I wanted to ask him
a couple of questions because I know that there is that the when we won when an American
becomes a 14th amendment citizen our status of law changes because we are no longer sovereign
freemen and have exercised sovereignty are talking about privileges instead of rights
and you only have about a minute left what's your other question well I wanted to ask him
how he approaches the legal defense standpoint for you know from that particular thing he
got asked this question a year ago on this show and he said from a constitutional perspective
correct that's right that does not answer the question no no it seems like there's a
fair amount of sovereign citizen callers at this point I like this career it is it is
funny because it seems like he also really doesn't like them the well I think he recognizes
how silly a lot of the arguments are and how they make it look bad what he's doing at the
same time he's making a show that is essentially catering directly to sovereign citizens yeah
yeah there's a lot of yeah and actually there I didn't have any clips of this because it
was just too all over the place but a good maybe half hour of this episode is dedicated
to Alex arguing with a caller about the Republic of Texas sure there's this idea that like
Texas should secede and he's like yeah I tried to support all that stuff but everybody kept
declaring themselves the president it's really funny but at the same time there was no way
to cut clips in a way that would make it work it's so funny it's so all right fine I could
just declare myself a president maybe I'm a general I don't know who to get in touch
with and he keeps calling them fruitcakes I he called he uses the term fruitcakes to
describe the Republic of Texas people like maybe five or six times yeah very specific
wording yeah made me think maybe he has a personal beef with somebody it's it is it's
kind of funny it's it's a little bit like somebody like starting a roller rink and then
like just hating people who roller skate yeah or like hating hating people who use like
uh inline skates yeah yeah yeah this is a four wheel only yes yeah yeah the law says
I have to let you skate okay this is America not according to the Magna Carta what so Chris
Chris leaves he was not that much of an interesting guest just kind of like very reactionary against
social workers pro homeschooling did not drop a mixtape did not yeah warned everyone about
the homosexuals come to take your children sure sure very different cool so Alex gets
to some headlines and this one is a load of shit we're back live we're going into a world
where you're a good decent person you're an enemy of the state because you're not you're
not a criminal they can't trust you you might fight what they're doing you might fight the
world they're setting up that's right that's what happens when the evil are in control
government lawyers say burglars need protection this is one independent by Robert Verkart
legal affairs correspondent government lawyers trying to keep the Norfolk farmer Tony Martin
behind bars will tell a high court judge tomorrow that burglars are members of the public who
must be protected from violent house holders so Alex is misrepresenting this case that
he's covering to make it appear that it the system is now just out to protect criminals
and punish the good people which is code for white Christians hey if people aren't committing
crimes you can't trust him so this is an article about Tony Martin a man from the UK who shot
at two young men who were breaking into his house which resulted in the death of one of
them the issue here isn't that Tony was wrong to practice self-defense it's that the court
didn't believe that he was acting in self-defense in the shooting the incident happened in 1999
at which point Martin did not have a license for the shotgun he used in the shooting problem
number one he'd lost it five years prior when he supposedly found a man stealing apples
from his orchard and proceeded to shoot at him leaving a hole in the man's vehicle hey
a point of order you you know added to this was Martin's very publicly known hatred of
the Romani people who which was referenced in a Guardian article from 2000 quote apart
from thieves Martin's pet hate was gypsies nor which crown court heard that the farmer
had talked of putting gypsies in the middle of a field surrounding it with barbed wire
and machine gunning them the article goes on to say that Martin had said quote Hitler
was right about these people and also points out that Martin's uncle Andrew Fontaine was
one of the founders of the straight-up fascist National Front right right right so he was
a Nazi the prosecution the problem here the prosecution successfully argued that the shooting
was not an act of self-defense but that Martin had laid in wait and shot these intruders
without first giving a warning this wasn't the sort of case that Alex is portraying it
to be where the burglar is hurt by someone practicing legitimate self-defense and then
sues the homeowner for it it's a clearly unhinged lunatic with a history of shooting at people
with a clearly racist past using deadly force against intruders to his home who had not
presented a mortal danger to him and according to the British courts that was not an acceptable
use of self-defense yeah I'm gonna go with yeah yeah so I don't know I Alex tries to
play this game where it's like yeah you know if someone breaks into your house and they
slip on a banana peel they can sue you or something like no they can't no no they really
really can't you have to kind of go way out of your way to be the one who's convicted
of a crime in that scenario and that's what this guy did yeah if someone is like presenting
a danger to you you do have the right to self-defense if someone does not and they're in your house
you have to tell them to leave before you shoot them dead I would try I would I would
open with excuse me that would be yeah so Alex has some very interesting similar problems
in his life in 2003 as he does in the present sure one is that boy these calls just don't
work out the difference though is in 2003 Alex could handle it sure grace yeah let's
just go ahead and talk to go ahead and talk to yes Mike in Illinois and then tip Oh Tim
in Texas is next okay well you know what I'm gonna do I'm gonna talk to Mike in Illinois
Mike in Illinois are you there okay he's not there who did you want me to go to Tim in
Texas all righty you're on the air Tim Alex how you doing pretty good I quit wow wow
that is such a normal that's a breath of fresh air just being like oh this is a minor setback
and we're off to the next one I quit not a big deal we're just going to rebroadcast
this is annoying but hey everybody bear with me yeah that's the vibe that I got there everybody
bear with me as opposed to doing a live radio show all failed me yeah we're doing live radio
show sometimes there's a little bit of a hiccup this happens yeah that's normal that's called
professionally Alex present-day not normal no no no so you know there was that talk with
the Texas folks about how they're all weirdos and sure one's the president yeah but everybody
can secede if they want sure Alex is very pro secession natural 2003 yeah Indiana you
know has the right to secede it's not just Texas or Hawaii Texas and Hawaii have stronger
cases because from the beginning they never signed the contracts but but but but still
sir it's a Civil War question they will send federal troops in they will lay seas they
will burn cities and the average person people were a hundred times more educated about real
politics and liberty in the 1860s and they are now that's correct in the 1860s the Confederacy
was full of New World Order moles was designed to lose from the beginning responded by the
British to break the country up both sides were controlled in that that's true so apparently
the the confederacy was full of globalists I do I do like how people who study the Civil
War so obsessively change their story all the time quite quite frequently usually when
you study something you refine it and the story becomes clearer and the picture is easier
to understand and you have a full awareness of what's going on New World Order moles whereas
it seems as though their study of the Civil War involves just rewriting it to whatever
it is you want it to be at any given point in time even if it's the same day what if
it's like you what if you find something that sounds more fun how can you be global how
can you be Confederate royalty if your royalty is just infiltrated by New World Order globalist
it's not like everybody was New World Order and how is it possible for everyone to be
just so well informed when the national rate of reading is like 10% listen it was the New
World Order was run in the Confederacy okay fair enough uh look dude false flag Civil
War that's pretty much what he said yes yeah he said it was a false flag Civil War everything
is fake nothing is real except Alex's conviction to the truth yes yes yeah yep yep wow oh boy
Confederate false flag Civil War yep should have seen it coming I should have so there's
a commercial for the Genesis Communications Network sure and I think that this I just
wanted to play this a little bit of it because it sounds really weird is mainstream media
telling you everything you should know about the war on terror what is our real interest
in Iraq and Saddam Hussein who stands to gain if we give up our freedoms in the name of
national security who's behind the manipulation of our financial markets and why we're the
jury you be the judge we're the GCN radio network are you tired of being lied to by
mainstream media well so are we and we're doing something about it we're the jury you're
the judge uh what does that mean we've already decided and you have to pass the sentencing
who's the executioner uh double back to we again also the jury doesn't talk are you like
the prosecution metaphor sucks uh your honor the jury has something to say and they say
no no the jury does not the audience is the jury you do not get to be the jury we're
the attorneys you're the jury somebody on the jury just stands up hey I think I can
do a better job of this lawyer and shit get this prosecutor out of here somebody wrote
that because like judge jury and executioner is an expression it's like this sounds pretty
good yeah uh didn't think about it for even one second no no using good job GCN Ted probably
wrote that so Alex comes back and he's got to be in his bonnet because there's a holiday
that bush right uh-huh George W the evil one yeah he's got this holiday well I mean they're
both evil he's got this holiday the whole family's dude honest it's not about them it's
about this holiday about the holiday listen to this one neo colonialism is the new world
order and they're coming right out with this in mainstream news oh don't worry the White
House is going to have loyalty day loyalty to the government day to be celebrated in
all the schools and nationwide that's terrifying it says our children will be taught that the
nation is a force for good in the world extending hope and freedom to others being part of the
Imperial Army to grab all natural resources and enslave everyone's children sure loyalty
day coach and the person that sent me this email and I went to the White House and got
the actual article that written by the White House it said when do I get my black boots
and dagger you know like the Nazis right right right right but it sounds real good loyalty
learning that we're this this good force in the world now loyalty to the government so
two things that jumped out at me there like the first is that in 2003 Alex is clearly
fully aware of the colonial exploitation that is part of our country's history yeah he completely
denies totally in the present and the second thing I was thinking is like man he would
be totally fine with a holiday called loyalty day if it was like a nationalist extreme right-wing
government everyone had to be loyal yeah yeah on loyalty day we have a big military parade
oh I love loyalty days my favorite day there's bombs yeah if it was his thing what a what
a fucked up thing to have a loyalty day do you know how that's so fucked up it would
be like if every morning kids had to go to school and recite some sort of yeah every
morning that would be so fucked up be very weird yeah loyalty day is just one yeah also
I would be remiss if I didn't point out that loyalty day is a holiday that's existed since
1921 and it was an attempt to replace the communist leaning May Day or as it's also
known International Workers Day that holiday marks the date of the Haymarket riot which
was something that the American government in the early 1900s was eager to not glorify
we don't want to talk about workers uniting we are still mad there's a weekend so yeah
they didn't want to endorse workers rights which of course was communism and so there
was this idea of loyalty day coming in on May 1st to take over for May Day yep the holiday
itself didn't catch on until 1955 during the Cold War Red Scare when Eisenhower made it
an official holiday in the United States and every president since 1958 has recognized
and proclaimed the holiday see if you can guess who said this quote now therefore I
Donald J Trump president of the United States of America do hereby proclaim May 1st 2017
as loyalty day this loyalty day I call on all Americans to observe this day with appropriate
ceremonies in our schools and other public places including the recitation of the Pledge
of Allegiance to the flag of the United States of America I also call upon all government
officials to display the flag of the United States on all government buildings and grounds
on that day who said it ah I gotta go with Clinton do so close Trump oh every time yeah
I thought you were trying to trick me nope it was not a trick so the very ideology that
created Alex Jones is the same ideology that created the idea of a holiday called loyalty
day to express loyalty to the United States in the face of a communist menace exactly
Alex understands so little about the hysteria and insanity that created his political identity
that here he is rambling about the direct result of his ideological forefathers and
pretending it's some kind of an evil event that Bush wanted to create he's much more
palatable and seems happier in 2003 and he doesn't freak out when he can't get to a caller
but he's still a total idiot yeah it's almost as if conservative reactionary ideology is
essentially an ouroboros that creates an outrage and then later on gets outraged when they're
outraged created a thing for them to get outraged about yeah and as I understand in 2017 there
was like some people who were you know like Trump is creating loyalty day is a fucked
up holiday the pledge of allegiance yeah but if you trick yourself into thinking that this
is the first one ever or whatever or you present it that way then you deprive all the context
of it yeah and you're just using it as a as a prop yeah and it's it also seems almost
a little insulting I think to to imagine that in whatever year it is that was the first
year they thought of loyalty day listen we've had plenty of fascists run in America for
a long time they've thought of loyalty day every time workers tried to unite they were
like okay here's what we got to do pledge loyalty the to the 120 hour work week like
that's what they were doing yeah it's the it's the byproduct of anti-communist freak
out yeah and so is Alex yeah exactly yeah so stupid yep so one of the other differences
that I found when I was looking at this episode between present-day Alex and back then is
he seems like to understand that movies aren't real at least a little bit interesting folks
we're in the twilight zone somebody listen to me it's it's like in the 1950s version
of the body snackers you know where the doctor goes to town they've taken over he bust out
he's running he's in traffic up the highway wake up they're after you there we're in danger
somebody listen to us oh it's so scary it's like that yes yes it's similar to this it
is not a reference the plan and they were not telling it to you by releasing that movie
yeah yeah it's uh that's just a corollary yeah there's a disconnect between this idea
that's represented in media and reality as opposed to them merging together in some weird
to use an Alex Jones word gestalt yeah yeah it's nice to hear people know the difference
between movies and realities it's comforting yeah at least because when I listen to this
I can be like all right we all agree that we breathe air yeah that's there the time
moves yes entropy is real yeah okay and that's comforting because I don't feel bad in the
present I definitely don't it is it is a real bummer going into the past and finding things
that are more positive than the present because you're like you want to live in a place where
hope exists but when we do this we're like man isn't that nice and then you remember
where it goes and you're like oh it could happen it could happen to you it could happen
to all of us at any point in time you could just forget how movies work yeah that is that
is a little bit scary it's it's humbling you know there but for the grace of uh literal
demons go high we should all be careful to not hide uh that we secretly think that we're
fighting demons if you think you are fighting demons tell someone yes you try to keep it
a secret for too long you turn into Alex Alex in the present yeah we've got a perfect example
oh boy you are what you pretend to be gonna figure out a way to make an infomercial out
of that lesson not sure or not an infomercial like uh sure what am I thinking of uh psa
that's it yeah psa yep yep so Alex believes that the us is evil sure but he loves the
united states there is a problem there I was listening to this next clip and I just got
confused this is a such an evil evil country I love this country but when you really face
how bad things have gotten and how there's this icky facade everything's good mom and
apple pie patriotism it's not real it's as fake as those plastic chinese flags it's as
fake as the boxes that said made in usa and st louis when bush gave that speech with the
made in china taped over it is a rotten facade under it is maggots and rotten meat the stench
of this thing is just everywhere it's freaking me out we gotta warn people we gotta stand
up for america we gotta fight with this country I just love this country so much I love my
family so much and I can't believe we let it get to this when Alex fake cries in 2003
he's doing a Clinton impression I was I was like is that Phil Hartman doing Clinton yeah
is that a wonder I really heard Phil Hartman there yeah when he's faking emotion it sounds
like a bad Clinton now bill I think that you're doing a great job yeah we gotta warn people
it's ridiculous it's so silly so I thought that was weird and I thought that was like
a completely artificial presentation of emotion and sincerity totally but I started to think
like okay so there's some there's some patriotism and apple pie and all this is is a facade
yeah and underneath it is just rotting maggots and what have you sure what do you love them
like what do you think he loves it's right there in the title if he's saying that like
this country is evil right right but he loves it right but it's a rotten thing like a fake
lid on it yeah isn't he is he just saying I love the lid yeah he likes the lid make
that why not make the whole plane out of the black box Dan what do you what do you not
understand I don't fully understand what it is that like he's hoping hoping to save if
it's rotting underneath with a fake yeah it seems like yeah you'd expose the you take
the lid off and you'd realize oh yeah maybe we should go I don't need I don't need what's
in this rotting it seems weird I don't yeah I don't feel fully that I understand yeah
yet from listening to this like what it is that's like what is what isn't rotten totally
to be saved right I would guess that it's guns sure property rights loyalty to your
country no absolutely not not yet yeah hating school sure sure sure whites only yeah yeah
I don't I don't have a full grasp of like Alex's entire policy set in 2003 yeah like
I think I understand a lot of stuff through the prism of like listening to thousands of
hours of his other content but like there there's gonna be some stuff that's gonna be
surprising and I don't want to make too many assumptions yeah you know I was I was listening
to that clip and thinking about all the stories of people who listen to him at this time period
and we're we're kind of drawn in by that and I was thinking about my understanding of politics
at that time like as the Iraq war is going on it totally felt like I was the first person
to discover how evil America was totally it was like I had been told all of this stuff
all the way up until I'm 16 years old and then the Iraq war happens and they're like
maybe you should read what real history is and not your school stuff and then I it really
did feel like oh man but this is before red pilling became the meme that it was but it
did feel like that and then you listen to Alex go like this is a rotting thing and you
can you can really get that sense of like yeah that's how I feel yeah I don't have sophisticated
political opinions yet I just know that this is some bullshit yeah yeah you know on a on
a pretty surface level there is a presentation that is almost perfect yes for exploiting
disillusionment yes and and that is definitely a period where there's a lot of people who
are feeling alienated and disillusioned from uh what they had the world as they had been
brought up to understand it totally and I think that you and I though we're a few years
apart we're both you know a certain men of a certain age when the Iraq war sure sure
we were not wild hogs yet we were youth yes and and that's that's a period where people
are generally they go through a period of disillusionment of course of course and to
have that compounded by something as something that should disillusion and yeah yeah yeah
yeah it's it's it's something where you know those feelings that you're having you could
see them mirrored in something like Alex talking about the the rotten core in the facade over
it yeah you could you could see that and you could gravitate towards that yeah it's interesting
to think about how much goes along with it that you might not realize that you're also
accepting yeah of course like that homosexuals want to take your children worse absolutely
yeah yeah because you that's how liberals got tricked into thinking he wasn't I mean
you're driving you you're listening to this you're you're on a 20-minute drive right you
pop on Infowars because you're like I'm disillusioned and this guy's pretty funny and and you only
get 20 minutes where he's doing the anti-Iraq war stuff and you don't listen to the half
hour he does with the gays are coming to steal your children you know and you're like arguing
about the Republic of Texas yeah exactly like you you could totally be sucked into that
and and it's it's much more believable like as like the the notion of like him having
a large audience if you listen to it in the presence like yeah fuck what in God's name
yeah it's much more believable when you look back at this totally not petulantly having
outbursts all the time right the presentation of emotion is generally within like where
he would want it to be to make a point yes yeah and he's still got that dynamic range
of like he can get it up there high and he can yeah but it's it's not out of control
yeah yeah although it is silly that when he's feigning sincerity he sounds like Clinton
that is a little bit weird I don't know yeah that was that was very strange yeah so you
know the Civil War was a false flag we we learned this yeah and it also it turns out
that you know in grocery stores they're putting in the self-checkout line sure right that's
how they steal your children right well eventually okay but first they're going to transition
these self-checkout lanes into fingerprint scanners where you're gonna have to have some
sort of a mark of the beast or whatever in order to buy groceries we're never not gonna
do mark of the beast I want to be done with mark of the beast can't we do about I'm telling
you we just got to be done with you can't do it they're gonna do this biometric scanning
stuff at the grocery store and then you're gonna have some sort of a Christian who's
gonna go bomb biometric sure natural it will be a false flag right right this is presaging
our people are going to bomb 5g towers and it's going to be a false flag yep yeah this
is not inevitable but you have to lead the charge you have to go boycott H-E-B and Kroger
and Safeway when they put thumb scanners in for self-checkout lanes because they put in
the self-checkout lane first then they tear out all the lanes and make you thumb scan
it's already happening Home Depot already starting it we're still doing self-checkers
and about six months later they put in the thumb scanner then they get rid of all the
employees make you do your own bagging but that's a sub reason why we're against it what
really against this because of the taxation the control the tracking if you go and you
fight it now we can stop it you wait till it goes in everywhere folks then it's then
the government's gonna blow stuff up and claim there's a Christian right-wing group it's
against the biometrics and so if you're protesting it you must be really with this group that's
gonna be the plan there I hate to give them ideas but they already have the idea I can
tell where they're going that's what they're gonna do you're against pro-abortion stuff
it turned out the feds have done all the bombings sure it's always the government one guy actually
did some that admitted he did it and we don't know if he's mind control or not oh okay okay
we're talking about uh sure I don't know who could be anybody just talking about there
but like yeah okay so all all the abortion clinic attacks that have happened it's all
the facts except for that one guy and we don't know if he's my we don't even know if he's
mind controlled so it could still be the feds that one's on the fence oh boy that's as close
as I get to admitting that it could possibly not be a false flag everything that was on
the foot everything's fucking fake that's that's the thing that I find really exhausting
about this uh this glimpse into 2003 is like everybody is a fucking communist and everything
is fake yeah he's talking about like all kinds of folks like uh uh joe scarbrough is an ultra
communist well that's that's turned out to be a prophetic uh prediction there who's the
other person to be labeled a communist on this episode fuck I can't remember it was
another it was another right wing guy I can't get over the pettiness of like look oh no
it was chris matthews chris matthews well but he's he's an ultra commie obviously no
I just love the like they're putting finger scanners in there they're gonna do all this
shit second problem I don't want to do my own bagging side issue that's a side issue
I'm putting that in there and no it seems petty right now compared to the fingerprint
scanner that is not the patriot's main complaint it is a complaint we do not want to bag our
own groceries it is inconvenient I always put the eggs in first I only ever get 10 eggs
I've never been trained on how to bag things these people have training um yeah silly also
great prediction uh that they put in the self-checkout stuff and then the next thing is a thumb scanner
I don't think that I've ever scanned my thumb at the grocery store I've never scanned my
thumb at a grocery store I would I would almost prefer it to scanning a credit card eight
years eight years on self-checkout uh pretty ubiquitous yeah thumb scanning not even really
in the conversation I don't think in terms of and nobody you know most people's problem
with uh self-checkout line isn't doing your own bagging it's when you get stuck behind
somebody who shouldn't be using the self-checkout when they have too many items well not just
that whenever they're clearly uh not bagging material if you will wow yeah um I don't have
many complaints about self-checkout I kind of take everything in stride sure you do so
yeah everything's false flag uh there's gonna be Christian groups that are gonna bomb biometric
places and it's gonna be all fake all these predictions have been fantastic yeah Alex
Jones is constantly right about everything I'm gonna be real mad if the when we do start
getting those biometric chips because we there are there are biometric things in little augments
that you can have you can put little electromagnets in your fingers and stuff like that yes sooner
or later we're going to have an implantable chip of some sort and some that are available
now I know but like one that will be uh that final that like ipod moment of an implantable
chip you know where all of a sudden this thing didn't exist and then it's everywhere and
it should be called the mark of the beast I think it's possible that that that technology
will go along that line but it's equally possible that it doesn't I don't know I don't know
I don't know if there will be an ipod moment like that I don't know but it better be called
the mark of the beast we got Soylent that's real yeah and we don't talk about Soylent
start uh I don't know we gotta find out but it became real so why not the mark of the
beast you gotta find that episode of Alex's show he's gotta be furious about that would
he be furious about that yeah that would be fun definitely okay next thing you know this
guy is gonna be starting a business where he uh has robot trash trucks go get the bodies
any moment now they're gonna have implantable chips and it's gonna be called the mark of
the beast listen yeah I've been taking the piss out of Alex a little bit on this episode
really just sort of mocking yeah some of this is stupid it is but you have to recognize
Alex Jones is a hero and in this last clip we learn about something that maybe isn't
in the history books but it should be Alex saved a lot of lives you laugh you laugh okay
okay where'd we where'd we save all these lives Dan you gotta stand up for this country
and you gotta do it now they're trying to pass hate crimes legislation but it's just
like the smallpox shot the truth was out on that grassroots the people refused and now
the government launching a smallpox attack which they were planning to do guaranteed
has been stalled they didn't do it Alex stopped a smallpox attack by publicizing information
about smallpox attacks he stopped it you could I mean look he said it obviously it's true
he saved so many lives I do you mock look sit here and you laugh at a hero some of the
benefits of having a narcissistic personality disorder in that you can't invent your own
crisis is to become the hero of hey it's amazing that is nice I've never felt like a hero well
quite in the way of saving millions of people from a small time maybe you should pretend
that you stopped I really think that would probably make me feel better yeah I mean if
you're doing a costume or like a pro-con kind of analysis of your career sure in the pros
are things like that yeah I'm a hero yeah I'm a hero I've saved the world ten times
over yeah no matter how many things you've bungled it's kind of easy to convince yourself
it's a net positive fake it's all worth it because I saved the world from a smallpox
attack yeah yeah love that kind of stuff nice yeah so this was this was a little bit of
a fun trip 2003 in order to you know get our toes back in the water for for what will probably
be an unpleasant present-day episode certainly disgusting nonsense spouted by a monster not
looking forward to it yeah but it will happen it's gonna now I think if I had to sum this
up like the reason that I thought that this episode was like really key sure it's that
moment where Alex says literal sorry yeah yeah when he stops himself from saying literal
demons it's so important it's right there yeah it is if we can demonstrate if we can
find more instances of Alex stopping himself from talking about the literal devil in the
past I'm I'm gonna my mind's gonna be blown so you're saying that you're gonna be the
jury and I'll be the judge and then the audience will be the execute executioners I don't know
I don't know how this works we will we will be court reporters okay and the audience could
be an audience can I can I be the stenographer I want to play with one of those ticket you
can't you can't type fast oh come on um so yeah we'll be back on Friday with another
a episode but until then Jordan we have a website we do have a website it's knowledge
fight calm on Twitter we are on Twitter said no go to bed Jordan Facebook we are this iTunes
if you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
do a God's work right now yeah we'll be back but until then I'm neo I'm Leo I'm DZX Clark
I'm Daryl Rundis I invented Liberty Day Andy in Kansas you're on the air thanks for holding
so Alex I'm a person color I'm a huge fan I love your work I love you