N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys.
Probably but not in the right direction.
I love your work, it's TimeToPray!
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding us.
Hello Alex, I'm a victim caller, I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
Knowledge Fight.
Nom nom nom nom nom nom.
Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight, I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're couple dudes, like to sit around, drink novelty beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh indeed we are, Dan.
Jordan.
Dan.
Quick question for you.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today is a little slice of life moment.
A little slice of life moment.
Little moment, just laying in bed, hanging out.
Celine, the cat, comes over, stares at me while I'm laying there.
Just like, what are you doing?
What are you doing, cat? You weirdo.
Yeah.
And then she just, she's just standing there.
Uh huh.
And then, just with no warning, plops over on her side.
Just floomp.
Just falls over.
Like a horse that was tranquilized.
Yes!
Just goes...
Ka thunk.
Yeah, okay.
Just immediately dead weight is the cutest thing.
It happens from time to time, but I really enjoyed it last night.
And then, uh...
It is like how that battery goes out.
Where it's not, it's like a sustained and then boom, it's just off.
Yeah.
And then she'll lay there for like maybe five minutes and then get bored and go lay somewhere else.
Sure, well, yes.
I understand.
That thunk moment is really nice.
It's beautiful.
I enjoy that.
How about you?
It's a lovely slice of life, Dan.
Thank you.
My bright spot is twofold.
One, Brockhampton has a new album out.
It's great.
Great.
And two, I just found out that there's this show that I've never heard of that ran for like six some odd seasons or something like that called Superstore.
And it's actually really good.
What about Walmart?
It's kind of about Walmart.
Yeah, yeah.
It's like a...
I was surprised to see how much labor issues were like...
You'd never heard of that show?
I'd never heard of that show before.
I swear to you, I've never heard of it.
It was all over the place.
Really?
Yep.
Hahahaha!
Yeah, it was...
Where?
Where was it all over?
It was probably on network TV, of course.
The place that you would normally...
The one place that I would never go, yes.
Oh, that's all dumb.
It's all dumb comedy.
I just don't have cable.
I don't have...
I'm not gonna cut the cord.
Sure.
I cut it.
Hahahaha!
But even if someone had come up to you and been like,
Hey, there's this show on basic cable that is so good.
You gotta check it out.
You'd have been like,
Oh, fuck yourself.
I'm gonna watch...
What? No!
Parks and Rec was on basic cable.
I'm gonna watch artistic prestige television.
No.
The first run of Full House was on basic cable.
These are shows that everyone enjoys.
In 30 years, you have two examples.
Yes, exactly.
Congratulations.
Yep, you got it.
Well, I'm glad you're enjoying Superstore.
It's great.
Great.
So, Jordan, today we have an interesting episode to go over.
We're in the present day because chaos is afoot.
Yes, naturally.
And we'll get into some of that chaos here in a moment.
But before we do, let's take a little moment to christen some new wonks.
Oh, that's great.
So first, Dr. Destructodome.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, Dr. Destructodome.
Thank you.
Next, I'm moving to Canada and changing my name to Joe Kickass.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, future Joe Kickass.
Thank you.
Next, Gwendolyn.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Gwendolyn.
Thank you.
Next, The Sheep Mafia.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Oh, thank you very much, Sheep Mafia.
Thank you.
And then I got a couple of technocrat shout-outs to give out today.
First, WTF is an NFT.
I'm also confused.
That's totally right.
You are now a technocrat.
And Backyard Widow Farm.
Thank you so much.
You are also a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate.
That's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right, we got to go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why are you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much.
Yes, thank you very much to the both of you.
Also, Jordan, I don't know if you know this, but there's two April birthdays.
Just me and Dr. Gums.
Yes, correct.
And also who could forget about Kelly Clarkson, Cedric, you know, Taylor Swift.
Well, no, of course, nobody could forget about those two, actually.
Well, we have one more to add to the list.
Okay.
Actually, we missed this email.
This was sent in and I missed it and I apologize.
But Rex, happy birthday.
Happy birthday, Rex.
Welcome to the pantheon of April birthdays.
Along with myself, Dr. Gums, Kelly Clarkson, Cedric the Entertainer, and Mandy Moore.
And a couple others.
I can't remember other celebrities.
Oh, Tyson Ritter.
Oh, sure.
The lead singer of All American Rejects.
Sure.
Naturally.
Everybody remembers his birthday.
Move along.
And commemorated by...
I'm sorry.
I've heard very little of what you said because I can't get past Backyard Widow Farm.
That sounds like murder, right?
I don't know.
I think it's a farm.
I like to believe it's a farm, maybe run by widows.
That sounds nice.
I don't know.
You could put an ominous or benign spin on it.
Sure, that's true.
However you want to play it.
I guess I have a bad temperament because I went ominous first.
Yes.
So Jordan, we return today to the present day of Alex Jones' content.
He's deep in rambling about the border and about that Spars document from Johns Hopkins
that apparently is a smoking gun.
Which is nothing of the sort.
I was really worried that we would get into today's content and we'd start looking at
this stuff back in the present.
It'll be so boring and repetitive.
A lot of these issues are things that we've done at least three or four laps with Alex
on before.
Oh yeah.
A lot of recycled narratives just about fairly present issues.
The words ad nauseum come to mind.
Yes.
Or as Alex would say, at nauseum.
Yes, at nauseum.
But then, Jordan.
Yes, sir.
On Tuesday evening at the end of the War Room, Alex called into his own show from home.
Oh no.
I guess the War Room isn't his show, but whatever the case.
He owns all shows.
We've got big breaking news.
Uh oh.
All right, they're bringing us in with the classic-
Song.
Slimball intro music.
Still great.
Alex Jones here, ladies and gentlemen.
On this 13th day, on this Tuesday transmission, we were going to have a special report shot
by now, but I ended up going too long.
I was going to shoot like a two minute quick video, but I ended up doing like 10 minutes.
So that'll be up in about 45 minutes or so at infowars.com or newswars.com.
So the breaking news is that Alex rambled too long in a special report that he shot
about this breaking news, so the well-produced version of it isn't going to come out for
like 45 minutes or so, and Alex is just going to have to come in and do it on the phone.
All right.
Breaking news.
I'm struggling here, if I understand correctly.
Alex is going to give us a thing that he already knew in the past.
Yeah, but he talked about it.
He meant to talk about it for two minutes so they could have a special report here on
the show, but he talked too long.
He rambled too long.
So then an hour later, you're going to see a better version of what he's going to do
for you now.
Exactly.
And it's so important that you cannot possibly wait one more hour.
No, we have to get into live programming.
This has got to be done.
We've got to break in.
This is Infowars, God damn it.
We can't wait another 45 minutes for this information.
I feel like if it was as important as he thinks, he could have kept it tight.
He could have.
So he can get this special report together.
Or he could have just spent two minutes on it in the middle of his rambles.
Also great that Rush has been dead for two months and Alex is already stealing his aesthetics.
I think it's a good idea.
Stealing his intro music.
Steal it up.
I do like that that clearly wasn't Alex's choice, though, because he calls it out.
That's true.
He's like, oh, coming in with some Rush Limbaugh music.
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
Someone else did that and he kind of ruined the illusion that they weren't stealing.
There is a secret hero on the staff, I swear.
The more music we hear at the right time, the more I'm like, somebody is watching us.
So, you know, he rambled too long in that special report that he tried to shoot, but
we don't really know what this news is that's so important.
Sure.
So let's see if he gets to it.
What's we got?
A lot of this we knew was coming.
But now here it is, Sam Montoya for us, about three years.
He's a he's a great.
My daughter just came in here.
Hello, honey.
I love you.
He just he just came in breaking news.
My daughter just came running in here.
We can't wait an hour.
I have that.
Let me just go outside.
I thought she was gonna be in the other room.
This has to happen right now.
I just got home.
Sorry.
Long story short, we were going to air in this segment.
This report, but it's not ready yet.
It'll be a band on video.
InfoWars.com and NewsWars.com here in 30 minutes, 45 minutes or so.
OK, so I guess the news so far is that Sam Montoya is a really good guy.
He's a great guy.
And that Alex, he's trying to innovate in ways he can make his show impressively unprofessional.
It's kind of incredible.
It really is.
So far, we have spent far more time talking about his daughters than we have the breaking
news that he had to call in.
Yeah, breaking news.
I talked too long about it in the special report in order to fit it into here.
Sure.
So I'm going to talk about it now.
Wow.
Yeah.
Yep.
This is good.
This is good stuff.
Oh, man.
Almost a parody.
So, you know, there is a story here.
Sure.
So let's see if we can get to it.
What do we got?
Well, we knew this was coming and I've talked to a lot of smart folks and they concur with
my analysis.
Sam Montoya, he is a great guy and he went to the Capitol that day.
He was separate from our main crew because he ended up we didn't take him on a trip with
us.
Go ahead.
Go on his own.
So he went up there to the January 6 event and then he ended up going to the Capitol
once it was open.
And once I guess the police wave, you'd be as we told me, and he got the tragic footage
of and was the first person put it out of actually Babbitt being executed, by the way,
we don't know the name of the police officer still had executed her.
But we do know the name of the police officer that just shot this guy at a traffic stop
in Minnesota during all the riots.
So just an example of how the feds and the media are all going along with this to demonize
local police for domestic takeovers is a very, very systematic criminal operation.
So here's the deal.
The story that Alex is trying not to cover is that Sam, his cameraman, got arrested and
charged for his actions on January 6th at the Capitol.
Sure.
Alex doesn't want to just say that.
So instead here he is just reiterating that Sam's a good guy and he's trying to come up
with every possible Dodge he can think of in order to not deal with the reality here.
That clip was less than a minute and here are a list of the qualifiers that Alex is
trying to bake into this story before even telling the audience what has happened.
Give me a list.
One, Sam is a good guy.
He's a good guy.
Two, Sam was separate from Alex's main crew.
Never heard of that guy.
Three, Sam went into the Capitol on his own.
I swear to you, this man, I've never seen him before in my life.
Four, Sam only went to the Capitol after police waved him in according to what Alex claims
Sam told him.
Frankly, I'm pretty sure he's a ghost.
Five, Sam was the first to get the footage of Ashley Babbitt being shot.
Incidentally, I don't think this is true.
And if you watch Sam's live stream from that day, you'll see him trying to negotiate with
John Sullivan, AKA Jaden X, who had captured footage of the shooting.
He was trying to get the footage from him.
Let me get the footage.
Yeah.
Six, for some reason it's nefarious that we don't know the name of the officer who shot
Babbitt, but we do know the name of the officer who shot Daunte Wright in Minnesota.
I have no idea what that has to do with anything.
No, it has nothing to do with anything, but it's always a good idea to jangle the keys
of racism away from the very real problems that you are dealing with.
You can see pretty clearly how Alex's primary motivation in telling this story is to make
sure the audience knows that Sam's a good guy.
Sam's a good guy.
Even if he went into the Capitol, he wasn't wrong to do it.
And if people say he was wrong to do it, then he did it without Alex even knowing or telling
him to do it.
Fairly certain I've never heard of this guy.
Alex hasn't even told the audience that Sam got arrested yet, and we already have multiple
claims that Alex had nothing to do with this shit.
This whole thing is a simulation.
I put the world on trial.
This is fucking Shadowgate.
This is bad.
This is Shadowgate.
Listen, he's a great guy.
Never heard of him.
Didn't tell him to do anything.
No idea what he's talking about.
Good guy!
Speaking of Shadowgate, I've realized that the Matt Gaetz thing could be the Gate of
Gates.
It does seem like the Gate of Gates.
It sure does.
I don't like that.
I think we're in a situation similar to that where I imagine it took Joel Greenberg exactly
five seconds to give up Matt Gaetz.
I think it might have been even less than that.
The FBI went to his door and he was like, y'all want Matt Gaetz?
Sure!
I'll give him to you.
Sam Portnoy is not protecting Alex in this circumstance.
Me and a friend had this joke that we would always tell each other, like we would smoke
together.
We'd have blunts and we'd be sitting around passing back and forth and having fun listening
to music.
Sure.
Doing the good stuff.
And one of the things we would always do is tell each other about how we were going to
rat each other out.
We'd always just joke about how if we were in public, we'd be like, officer, he got weed!
Yes.
That's how I imagine it.
That is how it's going.
Yes.
Absolutely.
We all have our way to fuck over each other.
That's how I feel like Matt Gaetz and his buddies.
I can tell you shit about Matt Gaetz that you ain't never even, you didn't even want
to know this stuff.
He got weed!
So now we finally get to the part here of this episode, or this special breaking news
where we find out that he got arrested.
Yeah.
That Sam is arrested.
Breaking news.
Long story short, I was sitting there this morning at about nine o'clock trying to get
into shape with some weights and got a call that the FBI with 30 people had raided his
little apartment here in Austin, Texas.
And that was crazy because we knew they'd already been harassing one of our other employees
named Rob, not Rob Dewey, the other Rob, who didn't even go to DC on the 6th.
And so we were just like, this is a crazy dragnet.
But Sam had gone in and the journalists, you know, there was other journalists in there
as well.
Jaden X had got $70,000 from CNN and others saying, burn down the Capitol.
But he's okay.
He's been released.
So that's, that's fine.
He, he tell, you know, lead the attack, the evidence I think is pretty overwhelming in
my opinion.
Not only was Sam arrested, but 30 FBI agents came to get him and other reinforced staff
have been harassed and Jaden X is totally free.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
I've been trying, but I can't find any proof that the arrest went down the way that Alex
has claimed.
He's shown a picture of a door that has a hole punched in it, but I don't know if that
was from police ramming it or a random person kicking it.
I have no idea.
Sure, sure.
As for Jaden X or John Sullivan, that's what's going to be Alex's main defense and the longer
special report that he rambled too long during.
Alex has decided that John Sullivan led the attack on the Capitol, which is absolutely
not true.
Sounds true.
And then he was paid by CNN to be there and he got off scot free.
That's definitely true.
All of that is bullshit.
Oh.
Sullivan has been released with conditions, but he's definitely still facing some very
serious charges and they have not been dropped.
He's, I mean, he's just out.
Yeah, no, that's, it's, yeah.
He's still in trouble.
That's part of the legal system.
You can, you can get out while awaiting trial.
CNN did not pay Sullivan to be at the Capitol.
Alex goes on to repeat the figure $70,000 as the amount that Sullivan was paid, but
this is just a misrepresentation of the fact that CNN and NBC both bought his footage from
inside the Capitol, each for $35,000.
Right, right, right.
There wasn't a preexisting contract or agreement.
It was just CNN and NBC acting exactly the way that Alex's cameraman, Sam, did when he
tried to get the footage from Sullivan inside the Capitol.
Yes, correct.
Uh, so yeah, I don't, I don't know.
According to a CNN spokesperson, quote, on January 6th, CNN was contacted by a reputable
agent regarding an eyewitness video from the Capitol Hill riots.
The company entered into a one week agreement for use of 44 seconds of key content, which
was attributed to the witness on air.
When his role in the event was later called into question, the company informed staff
to cease all use of the video.
Oh, that makes sense.
Yeah, totally.
Yeah.
So Alex's main strategy is going to be to point at John Sullivan and pretend that Sullivan
instigated the riots, that he was paid by CNN to do so, and that he isn't facing any
consequences.
And yet here poor Sam the cameraman is getting arrested just for being a good reporter.
It's all nonsense, but it's about the only angle you can take here that heightens the
feelings of agreement correctly and you can profit off of.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, I can't even really think of it because you don't want to turn Sam into a persecution
too much.
You know, you don't want to turn him into too much of a hero as long as then people
will give him money.
Well, we'll see.
Hold on.
So you don't want to give Sam defense funding.
Well, I mean like you do want to make him a victim if you can make it really all about
yourself.
Exactly.
If you can manage to do that.
Yes.
And we are dealing with a world class make it about himself-er.
I wonder if that's what the whole next episode is going to be about.
It could be.
Anyway, here's the last clip from Alex's breaking into the war room.
So we're going to have a detailed report on that coming up soon again at man.videoinfowars.com.
But this just shows you where the country is and what's going on and what's unfolding
in the persecution press.
It's not a detailed report and we're not going to listen to it because it's just longer but
about the same stuff and just kind of yelling about John Sullivan over and over again.
So now let us jump to April 14th because I wanted to see how Alex is coping with this
situation.
Sure.
One of his employees just got arrested and charged with a riot.
What's the new story he's going to tell about it?
Now one of the things that I think is really interesting is that we've been aware that
Alex had that cameraman who was inside, like we knew on the 6th.
Yeah.
We knew the whole time.
There wasn't really much of a secret around it and they released the footage of him yelling
infowars.com while he went in the Capitol.
Well that's because the FBI is just full of great investigators.
Well I actually kind of figured they probably were aware of this and it just didn't rise
to the level of someone they would want to charge.
Yeah it does seem like that.
And to me it's actually kind of surprising that there was a charge.
I don't think he's going to get in any trouble.
I think he'll be probably released maybe a slap on the wrist, who knows.
So it is kind of surprising to me that they did end up charging him but I'm not surprised
to hear that there could be a charge.
Oh totally.
Yeah yeah yeah.
So anyway Alex, I just don't, I didn't know how it was going to land.
Outside of I was pretty sure he was going to make it about himself.
Yeah totally.
And we'll get to that but before we do, you know John Bowne has been a long time boring
voice man.
Indeed.
For Alex.
He's got special reports.
Yes he does.
And Alex will play those special reports generally in the first six minutes of the show.
Right.
Get him out of the way.
Those often don't go out on the radio.
Get your vegetables out of the way.
A lot of stations air their own sort of station identification and news stuff at the top of
the hour.
So Alex has this first segment that just is kind of no man's land.
And he'll usually play some John Bowne reports there with his dumb boring voice.
But there's a guy who's been really making waves.
Guy named Greg Reese.
He's never heard of him.
He's another guy who's got these special reports that he does.
He's another little video maker down in Austin at the Infowars.
And I think he's making a run at the crown of the weird voice special report guy.
All right.
Here we go.
Immediately following the death of Nikola Tesla, Dr. John Trump, an electrical engineer
with the National Defense Research Committee of the Office of Scientific Research and Development.
And interestingly, President Donald Trump's uncle was called in to analyze the Tesla papers.
Is that interesting?
Or boring?
In a few days, John Trump officially concluded that Tesla's work was primarily speculative
and did not include workable methods.
We are then told that most of Tesla's papers disappeared, but his work most definitely
quietly continued.
All right, man.
I hear that driving music behind you.
What is this special report about?
This is about Tesla, man.
This is about how Tesla's work is the underpinning for all of our futuristic technology that
was stolen from him and hidden from the public.
Yeah, I didn't know what was going on, but I was excited.
Yeah.
I was like, this is how the show is starting?
With this special report?
This is weird.
I'm really more interested in Tesla than I am in whatever other bullshit they're going
to spout.
Sure.
So let's hear this Tesla shit.
So Greg Reese, he wants to blow some minds talking about some of this physics stuff and
wireless energy, mysterious stuff that Tesla has figured out.
The whole thing.
Teleportation.
The Palmas spinning ball experiment from 1977 is simple enough for anyone to repeat.
Two steel balls are repeatedly launched with equal force.
One is spinning.
The other is not.
The spinning ball consistently flies higher and falls faster than the other.
This is in direct violation of both Newton's laws and Einstein's relativity.
Really modern science.
You ever see a curve ball for this energy?
Yeah.
You ever see a curve ball?
You ever see a major league baseball pitcher throw a curve ball?
You know, one of those things that's on TV during the summer 162 times.
This is amazing.
Yeah.
Modern science has plenty of explanations for why this phenomenon could be seen in different
rates of speed between spinning and non-spinning objects.
The issue is that there's no difference for these objects when you try to conduct the
experiment in a vacuum.
You know, like if you didn't have other forces at play, then they would travel at the same
speed whether they were spinning or not, but because in nature, in the world, there's other
forces that come to bear on the object, and they understand that.
Yes.
Scientists are not stupid.
No.
The force that Greg Rees is ignoring here is called the Magnus effect, and it's basically
the reason why pitchers can throw bending pitches or why tennis players add spin.
The spinning object in the air exerts a force on the air that it's traveling through, and
in the process, its path of motion is affected.
This is a well-understood phenomenon, and it's completely compatible with Newtonian
physics.
Yeah.
I guess Greg Rees didn't really look into this before deciding that spinning balls are
somehow proof that physics is a lie.
It would be very hard to research the American baseball pastime.
Yeah, or you can find countless videos of people doing this, like dropping things from
really high heights, because it is really cool.
Yeah, it's cool.
It's really cool to look at.
It's cool.
Yeah.
Yes.
Is there any spinning force stuff that no one can explain?
No one.
No one can explain.
Only Tesla.
Maybe.
Oh.
But we don't know.
John Trump didn't look at those papers.
That's true.
So, John Trump's uncle is involved in a cover-up.
Did you know that Bruce De Palma is Brian De Palma's uncle?
What?
Isn't that interesting?
No.
Nope.
I also don't think that's true.
So, apparently, the spin creates this magical force.
Magic.
Or whatever.
Yeah.
This magical force somehow to create UFOs.
These patents look very similar to what whistleblowers claim have been in production for years by
weapons manufacturers such as Lockheed Martin Skunk Works.
The same UFO-like craft that whistleblowers claim are being prepared to stage a fake alien
invasion.
So, we've got a fake alien invasion coming.
Yeah.
And these spinning things.
You ever see a knuckleball, Dan?
It was an interesting special report.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I think that the music really does a lot of work.
I think the music does more work than Greg.
I think our greatest scientists are going to use a split-finger fastball to develop
UFOs.
Yeah.
That's pretty fun.
Also, I would question what this has to do with the globalist's plans.
I don't know how a false flag alien invasion fits in with the larger schemes that we're
supposed to be afraid of.
It does seem like the plan B being kill all of the people would kind of negate the need
for the UFO part.
Yep.
That would just be like, hey, look, we're going to do the super bioweapon thing, but
let's have a little fun.
I mean, you know what, I will give it up to the devil in this sense.
It does seem like he's got a lot of plans up in the air at the same time, and if he's
juggling that many plans, that's a talent in and of itself.
That's a management issue, and he's killing it.
But you know, I think back when we did stand up, sometimes you'd have somebody who's like,
I'm going to start my own show, animate a clothing line going, and then start a video
blog.
Right.
Well, you've got to brand yourself.
Well, there's a lot of plans.
There are a lot of plans.
Sometimes if you have too many plans, you're not going to do any of those things, and maybe
that's the issue that the devil's running into.
That's the ultimate weakness of the devil.
He's got the false flag aliens.
He's got the super bioweapons.
He doesn't follow through on anything.
He didn't even kill Eve, you know?
What was the point?
No.
Stupid.
Also, what do you think you should be more afraid of?
Extermination or world government?
Ooh, depends.
What kind of extermination?
Well, because I feel like in Alex's scheme now with the devil's plan, world government
is not a necessary step towards extermination.
That's true.
That is true.
So I don't know why the devil would need to push for that anymore.
Well, if you had... Okay, so if the devil obtains world government, he's gotten through
the loophole that God set that keeps him from limiting human free will, maybe?
I don't know.
Because the government can do the free will limiting, and he just gets to exterminate
people?
I don't know, man.
Yeah, this is what happens when Greg Reese starts the show.
This is a problem with both, I guess, UFOs and the Bible.
So Alex comes in, and he breaks things off with some real serious headlines.
Sure.
Let me tell you what we got for you.
Everyone is starting to call out Fauci as a fraud, and mainstream news is now reporting
that he ran the Wuhan lab, which they're now confirming is where COVID-19 came from.
Absolutely huge.
And then people say, well, I thought you said COVID's not that deadly, but they want to
own it, and they want to have version one, and version two, and version three.
They've got super deadly versions.
This was just the drill.
So Alex is just talking about a Washington Times headline that doesn't prove the claims
that are in the headline, or are speculated about in the headline.
Yeah.
I don't know who that is.
I was pretty disappointed.
He doesn't talk about it until fairly a ways later.
Right.
Well, I did see that the CIA would refuse to confirm that it wasn't created in a lab,
so people have taken that as speculation that they're probably looking into it, I guess.
But I think that all along, it's not been excluded as a possibility, but it's not the
most likely possibility, and there is not evidence that it was.
Right.
That's the issue.
There are a lot of issues, yeah.
Yeah.
Anyway, Alex-
And I don't trust the CIA.
Fine.
Yeah.
I didn't know whether or not we were going to get into the Sam issue early or late.
I didn't know.
It turns out that Alex dives right in.
The FBI yesterday morning raided one of our crew members, I'll tell you about that coming
up next segment, and the media is just in ecstasy, oh my God, we're so close to arresting
Jones.
We want to shut down Infowars.
Think about that.
It's not just take us off the internet, not try to block our bank accounts.
Now it's, we want Jones in jail.
He masterminded the capital attacks, you've been hearing that since it happened a few
months ago, three months ago, and now they're just fixing the intelligence to go in line
with all of that.
So I guess this is the first instance of him making it all about himself.
Yep.
And it happens immediately.
They got Sam, which is actually about me as always.
I wouldn't be happy about this if I were Sam.
No, no, no, no.
I would flip on him.
I would take this as an insult.
Yep.
So Alex gets to talking about his charges, what Sam's been charged with, and he might
be a little bit off.
As far as reporters, Sam arrested for covering January 6th Capitol riot Montoya.
So I talked to Sam's dad yesterday.
He was here.
Guess what he's charged with?
They said making loud utterances.
So Sam wasn't charged with making loud utterances.
The charging documents are public and he's facing five charges.
One, entering and remaining in a restricted building.
Sounds like he did that.
Two, disorderly or disruptive conduct in a restricted building.
Almost certainly.
Three, violent entry and disorderly conduct in a Capitol building.
Yeah, that's true.
Four, impeding passage through the Capitol grounds or Capitol buildings.
No other way to be a mob in front of the door.
And five, parading, demonstrating, or picketing in a Capitol building.
I could be wrong, but I don't think that Sam's going to get in any real trouble about this,
unless there's some kind of information that the state has that I'm not privy to, like
where he was in greater coordination with people than we know.
I don't know.
Unless that's the case, I would guess he's going to get a slap on the wrist and maybe
not even that.
One of the charges about disorderly conduct and violent entry is described like this in
the filing.
Quote, to willfully and knowingly utter loud threatening and abusive language or engage
in disorderly or disruptive conduct at any place on the grounds or in the Capitol buildings
with the intent to impede, disrupt, or disturb the orderly conduct of a session of Congress
or either House of Congress or the orderly conduct in that building of a hearing before
or any deliberations of a committee of Congress or either House of Congress.
Right.
You can't go in there and scream, go fuck yourself.
Yeah.
But framing that as him getting charged for loud utterances is fun because it makes it
seem like the government's trying to punish Sam for yelling, but that's not what happened.
Yeah, it makes it seem like the government's trying to punish him for yelling, go fuck
yourself to Nancy Pelosi.
Right.
Yeah.
That's not quite the same thing.
You kind of lose the context of it.
A little bit.
And, you know, Alex is just saying that he's getting charged with making loud utterances.
It's like, there's five charges.
The documents are right there.
Yeah.
Stop playing games.
They're public too.
Man, everybody's trying to jam Alex up and this is just a part of it.
Sure.
They've had all the major mainstream media, Wall Street Journal, New York Times, all of
them, uh, approach people and offer them money to lie about us.
They've had the big tabloids do it.
They have done Facebook scan searches on any body that even ever took a photo with me and
people that take selfies.
Uh, if I'm randomly at a restaurant, uh, these women will get a call from the Wall Street
Journal, the New York Times saying you have a relationship with Alex Jones.
They go, no, I don't know Alex Jones.
I mean, I met him once took a photo with him, with my husband that go, okay, well we heard
he raped you.
What?
No, this is a preposterous and we then get calls from these people and have confirmed
it.
So thousands of people are called by the Savage criminal operators of just the actual leftist
intelligence agency crime Lords.
And then they control the FBI and order the FBI to then go and reverse engineer it.
So these media entities, the mainstream media are essentially leftist crime Lords and they
run the FBI.
And so the media comes up with this stuff and then they reverse engineer an investigation
through the FBI to jam someone up.
I think, I think that Alex is used to people he knows like Jacob Wall and James O'Keefe
operating like this where they're trying to set traps and that's the news that they're
doing what we're doing, even though we're the ones doing it and they aren't.
I think that because those people that are in his sphere do this stuff that he thinks
that everybody does.
Yeah.
And I think that he thinks that's how media and news operate and that's scary.
Which is one of the big things that we can see as a problem with Jacob Wall and the ilk
there because that undermines confidence in any and all media outlets if you are so brazenly
corrupt about it.
Yeah.
And if people have it in their mind to equate the two.
Yeah, of course.
As if the people of that ilk are in any way analogous to the media.
Yeah, no.
Real journalism is lying your way into buildings to surreptitiously record people and then
edit together misleadingly.
That's what people believe.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
That's great.
That's good.
That's good for the fourth estate, damn.
Sure.
Yeah.
So there's a CNN article about Matt Gaetz, The Gate of Gaetz.
Sure.
Yes.
And...
Never heard of the guy.
Well, Alex maybe didn't actually read this article.
That could be a problem.
I saw a CNN article.
Gaetz attended parties with drugs and it'd be some huge party in Miami or a big hotel
suite party and the women went to the media to say he was really nice and he didn't give
us money and we didn't even see him using drugs.
One woman said, I saw him take a pill once, but he was really nice and the women were
all 25, 30.
But that's at the end of the article.
And then other women go, yeah, I'm getting offered money to say Gaetz did something to
me.
And it's not that Gaetz is perfect.
He's a rich kid.
He's a smart guy.
He's admitted he's a party animal.
Hell, he's for drug legalization and I'm not endorsing any of that, but I'm not a hypocrite.
I've never been a drug problem person, but I've been, let's just say it, I'm pretty much
an alcoholic off and on.
That it doesn't need to go down like this.
It doesn't.
It's unnecessary.
Why are you involving yourself in the story?
We would all be like, that's fine.
There's no way Alex is involved with this Matt Gaetz story if you wouldn't keep involving
yourself.
Hey look, I love the booze.
Hey, I'm an alcoholic.
Why did you tell me that?
So the actual headline of this CNN story is quote, women detailed drug use, sex, and payments
after late night parties with Gaetz and others.
That does seem like a different headline than the one that I was presented with.
Slightly, slightly different.
Yeah, that is a little bit different.
The article relies on the stories told by multiple women who claim to have been at these
parties.
There is a mention of Gaetz behaving quote, like a frat type of party boy, sometimes taking
pills she believed were recreational drugs.
This person saw him taking pills that were believed to be recreational drugs.
Yeah.
So the article mentions these women being paid by Joel Greenberg, but not directly ever
by Gaetz, and they quote, said they never saw anyone at the parties who appeared to
be underage.
Additionally, the women disputed the characterizations of what they were aware of happening as being
sex trafficking.
Sure, sure, sure.
Which is fine.
Could just be sex work.
Yeah.
I don't know why, like I said, Alex can't even just touch this story, get into it at
all without some personal thing about himself.
It's very weird.
Yeah, it is feeling a little like, oh no, my son is in trouble, I gotta protect this
poor idiot.
It's very weird.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I wouldn't do that.
No!
I would do anything else but get involved and then tell everyone I'm an alcoholic
on air.
Now, speaking of things you would or would not do.
Sure.
If you were Alex's lawyer, what would you tell him to say publicly about the whole Sam
issue?
Ooh, I would tell him probably to say something along the lines of, we don't believe these
charges are accurate and we are fighting against these, my lawyer has advised me to say nothing
beyond that.
Now, if you were Alex's lawyer and you advised him not to say anything, you probably wouldn't
want to hear this.
This could be an issue.
But my lawyers and people are like, I would not talk about this at all.
Oh, just so it's all over the news and they can lie and say I sent him in there and he
had flame throwers and hand grenades and cut Pelosi's head off.
I'm not going to sit there and wait for that crap.
I'm going to put out a million dollar bounty.
So yeah, Alex is going to set the record straight before people can say he had grenades and
stuff.
Yeah, okay.
Now my lawyer told me not to say anything, so here we go, I'm going to say I'm a bunch
of shit.
All right, here we go.
Shoot that shotgun of bullshit at us.
So here comes, here's what Alex is, here's his story and he's going to be sticking to
it.
I'm sure this is going to be very consistent, fully.
So here's what happened.
Um, everybody wanted to go to DC and had a carnival atmosphere.
And I told Harrison Smith, you can go on the next trip out of here.
You here to do the shows while we're all there and to cut to us life.
Well Sam, who almost fired for it, but he's a likable guy, so I didn't do it, but he came
as close.
He's a good guy and said, well, if Alex isn't going to send me, I'm going to go with the,
my pillow people.
And he got press passes, White House press passes from them for the main event.
And then I find out later he's in the Capitol that day and got the footage of like Sam got
footage of the woman being killed.
And I had a huge meltdown on the rooftop, sort of cussing at people.
I said, I didn't, I ain't supposed to be in Austin running things.
He's got footage of these.
And I go, yeah, here it is already on Twitter.
Then I go, why is it on Twitter and not on us?
What the hell?
So Alex said Sam couldn't go, Alex as your counsel, Sam said Alex can't go, or Alex said
Sam can't go.
You and Harrison Smith need to stay here and throw to us while we're there.
Gotta do whatever it is you were doing.
I know it's going to be a carnival, but you got to work.
Yeah.
Sam says, fuck that.
I'm going to go talk to Mike Lindell and apparently goes to the Capitol with Mike Lindell.
Right.
The my pillow people.
Yeah.
Okay.
Sure.
So then Alex.
Well, I mean, everybody that works for Infowars, I assume is now an independent contractor
completely.
So Alex is unaware that Sam has gone with the my pillow people.
Honestly, he's never met Sam before in his life.
So he finds out that Sam is in Washington DC when he finds out that he has footage of
the woman being shot.
But at the same time, Sam was along with Tyler Hansen at the time who was burning a Black
Lives Matter flag with Owen Schroyer the night before and had shared a hotel room with Owen.
You would think.
Seems like they might've.
They might've had text messages.
Or maybe Sam was there when they burned the Black Lives Matter flag.
Sure seems like it.
Who might've been hanging out.
It seems weird.
Yeah.
That whole burning the Black Lives Matter flag kind of puts it out of carnival atmosphere
and more into bloodthirsty mob atmosphere.
I don't believe for a fucking second that there wasn't an awareness that he was there
in DC.
Absolutely.
That's ridiculous.
No.
I don't know what it means that he went with the my pillow people.
He went with the my pillow people.
You know who you should investigate?
Mike Lindell.
That's who you should investigate.
Boy doesn't feel like that.
You should go see the my pillow people.
They're the ones.
In other words I'm mad that he didn't give me the footage.
I wish he had given me the footage until this moment when I definitely don't wish he gave
me that footage.
So the next day after the 6th on the 7th Alex is talking with Sam and he's like hey dude
shit's fucked up.
Bruh.
This was a terrible idea.
Right bruh?
Bruh.
You fucked.
You gonzo.
And Sam was like hey buddy.
I get it.
It's all good.
Look I'm with the my pillow people now.
No it's all good man.
You shit.
And then Sam talks to me I guess the next day and I go Sam.
You're probably gonna get in a lot of trouble even though you didn't do anything.
You know as a journalist did you do anything wrong in there and he goes no no it's fine
everything's fine.
I said that's not the case Sam but we'll see.
And here we are a couple months three months later and you see what's unfolding since January
6th.
Okay.
So.
Yep.
I really don't think the people on the right really understand what unfolded on January
6th.
And if they do they are lying about it.
Well I think one of the problems is the you know the ripples of the fake shit that they
came up with to make excuses about it.
Sure.
It's taken a while to catch up with the reality of you know reality keeping on existing.
Yeah it keeps going whether you like it or not.
So Alex heard that Sam got arrested.
Sure.
Right?
Yeah.
And even though he told him he was gonna be in trouble on the 7th.
Right.
And then last night in 2021.
Sure.
Last night he interrogated people at Infowars Studios.
What was Sam up to?
Get the fuck out.
So then I got to interrogate some people here last night and check their messages and make
damn sure when I tell you the story it's what the truth is and I said I thought I said they
had to stay here and run the shows.
Well he told me he was going with my pillow people and if he got footage he'd give it
to us and maybe we'd reimburse him if he asked for receipts or something and I said so again
as usual no one does what I tell them.
That's why I blow up.
Okay.
As usual when facing legal troubles I really want to check the messages and make sure I
am telling the truth and there are a few other times when I do this.
And I have literally no control over anything.
Nope.
Nobody knows what I'm doing.
I don't know what anybody's doing.
This is an anarchist outfit.
Legally no one listens to me.
Legally.
I have never met any of these people.
So it seems strange to me that Alex would have talked to Sam on January 7th and then
in April he's interrogating people and checking messages about something that he clearly knows
what happened.
Has no idea it was a cold case, Stan.
I don't understand.
He's starting a podcast to investigate Sam's involvement.
Get the piano out.
Yes, it's a new serialized podcast.
Uh, yeah, but look dude.
Sure.
I mean this story doesn't make sense.
No it doesn't.
What?
Who cares?
Good point.
Sam sucks.
Plus, Sam is not that extended.
He's not a good guy anymore?
He's a video editor, low level, camera guy, been here three years and I'd say he's, you
know, second string.
He's a great guy, but he's not gotten trained up to that point.
It takes time.
And sure enough, he went on his own volition, went in there and I don't, I don't say that.
To like me, oh, you know, I didn't tell him to go in there even.
No, I mean, I didn't, but it doesn't matter.
He didn't do anything wrong.
It really sounds like Alex is trying to be like, I didn't have anything to do with this
shit.
This is like a story that Avon Barksdale's lawyer is telling.
Like listen, my client has never been anywhere near drugs.
He's never seen any of these people before.
I don't know why you are trying to malign a businessman and large character in the community.
Quite frankly, Bodhi is a second string.
Listen, if he was part of my crew, I would tell you he was only a mid-level manager.
He didn't have much going on.
He was selling drugs on his own and even if he wasn't, then I wasn't wrong.
I don't know.
He had just got his own coroner, he was, he was moving up in the world, but he wasn't
any good yet.
I would say that if I were Sam, I wouldn't like to hear that.
I would be real unhappy.
Yeah, here I am in prison for info wars and Alex is on air saying I'm second string.
Yeah, I think we're going to see a little bit of a Shadowgate fall out of this one.
Unfortunately Sam has been let go.
If I were Alex, I would be going out of my way to say everything positive about this
guy.
Totally.
He's worked there for three fucking years.
You know, you know what Roger Stone said about Trump when he got arrested?
The nicest things anyone has ever said.
Oh my God.
He prayed for pardons?
No, and look at it the other way.
Trump said nice things about Roger.
Exactly.
When Roger got arrested.
Yes, because you don't want nobody telling nothing.
No.
Exactly.
That's what the lawyer from The Wire would suggest.
So Sam got jammed up because one of his family members tipped off the enforcement that...
They needed a family member to tip people off?
I guess they weren't watching info wars.
Oh, that's fair.
It's not something I would recommend most serious people do.
That is fair.
But Alex is all over the place talking about Sam's family.
And I was this close and I said, you know, Sam's a nice guy.
I'm not going to, I'm not going to fire him.
And then I got to learn that his family member, we know who it is because he told us how she
won't even come to family dinners because he's a conservative and his dad is, they're
big Trump supporters.
Is that it?
His family member, one of his siblings won't even come to dinner with him for years because
of Trump.
Sam's a big Trump supporter.
I mean, you see Sam at the RNC five years ago talking to me, shaking my hand in videos
that Eric Andre shot.
I mean, he's like, he's, he's, he's, he's been around, he's a big fan and so we're praying
for him.
We support him.
He's in jail.
Okay.
This is all over the place, man.
This is weird.
Yeah.
A more important person.
Perhaps somebody not on the second string would be getting a nice little defense fund
boost.
We're setting something up to help him instead.
Sam just gets a nice little, we're praying for him.
Obviously we hope he's doing well.
He will definitely be working here when he gets out of jail 100%.
I will not be firing him immediately.
We've sort of talked to his dad.
But again, it's important to remember that what's at stake here and what's real about
this story is not, it doesn't even involve Sam at all.
No.
It involves Alex.
Of course.
So we're praying for him.
We support him.
He's in jail, uh, for raising his voice in the Capitol and they've got the quotes about
woo woo, America standing up, all this stuff, but he was wearing two hats.
He's a journalist.
He had a presidential, uh, uh, uh, media pass.
He thought the president was going there.
The police opened the doors and waved him in.
That's why he went in and covered it.
He got the footage of the woman dying.
He had other mainstream media there.
So they have to all be indicted if he's indicted.
It's all a fraud in a hope, obviously, to keep him in jail for a nonviolent offense
to try to have him turn state's evidence and make stuff up about me so they can put me
in prison and shut down info wars.
And that's their admitted goal.
Wow.
So that was a lot for them to have as a goal of sure.
Yeah.
They didn't process this story except as it being part of an elaborate plan to get him.
If I were Sam, I would be a bit worried about how my arrest was being used as a prop to
justify Alex's completely out of control narcissism.
You'd think.
I want to take this clip piece by piece.
Okay.
The first little piece here is that Alex is claiming that Sam just said, woo woo, America
is standing up.
That is not true.
That doesn't sound right.
Here's some of the quotes from the charging documents.
Okay.
Quote, we've had enough.
We're not going to take your fucking vaccines.
We're not going to take all your bullshit.
The people are standing up.
That sounds like something he might say.
Quote, here we are in the US Capitol in Washington DC in the Capitol building.
It has officially been stormed by Trump supporters.
Again, the US Capitol building in Washington DC has officially been stormed by Trump supporters.
And here we are taking our the people's house back.
I wouldn't want that anywhere where people would have that on recording.
I especially wouldn't want to say be recording myself while I was saying those things.
It's not in the list of quotes in the charging document, but my favorite quote from Sam's
live stream was when he was walking in, entering the Capitol building and he does a plug for
Info Wars store.
It seems weird.
Like maybe if he was there with my pillow, he should have plugged them, but I didn't
send him down there.
I guess, I guess loyalty runs deep, but it's also a one way street because Alex doesn't
give a shit.
This dude's second string.
That's brutal.
The next piece is that Alex is claiming that Sam had a press pass.
That is also not true.
From the charging document quote, the director of the congressional press galleries within
the Senate press office did a name check on Samuel Christopher Montoya and confirmed that
no one by that name has congressional press credentials as an individual or via any other
organizations.
I have no idea what Alex is trying to claim, but there's no way that Sam had a press pass
to be where he was.
That's complete bullshit.
And there also wasn't any other like mainstream media where Sam was.
The videos that have come out have been played on other outlets or things that people purchased
from the folks who were there.
The media isn't going to be like, Hey, let's go wander inside the middle of this blood
thirsty mob that hates the media.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
Wear one of those hats with a little card from the coverage I can find in any real outlets.
It really feels like Alex is heightening this to a point of absurdity.
This is my area of interest and what I cover.
And honestly, I don't think I care nearly as much about the arrest as I do about Alex's
response.
It's complete sensation, a sensationalization where Alex is trying to walk this interesting
line where he has nothing to do with Sam's actions, but the consequences that are coming
to Sam are secretly an attack on him.
Yes.
This is how a narcissistic mind would interpret something like this.
Like Alex is blameless and all negative consequences are secretly a plot against him.
Yes.
And if I were Sam, I would realize this is a plot and I am being used.
I would immediately go, Oh, he's a vicious narcissist.
Oh, why would I think that he was anything but that who would help me out in my hour
of need?
No, but I mean, look, it's all about getting Alex.
Welcome back to the Alex Jones show.
So there are now hundreds of news articles proliferating like mushrooms going, Oh, Alex
Jones is going to get arrested.
Alex Jones is finally going to get it.
We're going to shut him up.
He sent in one of his reporters to attack the capital of the most vicious attack on
the U S since Pearl Harbor.
You know, they're actually saying that this was as bad as Pearl Harbor asinine.
Again, Alex is making this all about himself.
I failed to find any mainstream media articles that fit the description of what he's talking
about.
But again, if he actually means random tweets when he says media articles, then there's
nothing I can really do about that.
It's just the delusions of a liar.
Yeah.
Also about that Pearl Harbor thing.
This is just Alex misrepresenting comments made by Chuck Schumer after the storming quote.
It's very, very difficult to put into words what has transpired today.
I've never lived through or even imagined an experience like the one we've just witnessed
in this Capitol.
President Franklin Roosevelt set aside December 7th, 1941 as a day that will live in infamy.
Unfortunately we can now add January 6th, 2021 to that very short list of dates in American
history that will live forever in infamy.
Alex has taken this and twisted it into Schumer saying that the storming of the Capitol was
worse than Pearl Harbor when he said no such thing.
Yeah.
Interestingly, there was a recent comment about Pearl Harbor that you might find interesting.
Hmm.
Quote, we went through the worst attack we've ever had in our country.
This is the worst attack we've ever had.
This is worse than Pearl Harbor.
It's worse than the World Trade Center.
There's never been an attack like this.
Ooh, I'm going to go with Paul Ryan about something 10 years ago.
No, it was Trump talking about COVID-19 in May of last year.
There it was.
I'd like Alex's comments on that.
I'd like to see what he thinks about Trump saying that COVID-19 is worse than Pearl Harbor
in 9-11.
Well, you know, you don't need to worry about the things that Trump says.
It's more about the vibe he gives to it.
Right, right, right.
Speaking of vibes, Alex has this vibe, right?
Sure.
Sam got popped.
So Alex has nothing to do with this.
However, Sam was there the night before with Owen.
Well, I don't know.
Actually, I'm not 100% sure Sam was there the night before.
When Sam was in the Capitol, Tyler Hansen was there as well at the same place, and Tyler
was sharing a hotel room, hanging out with Owen, and burning a Black Lives Matter flag.
They all knew they were there.
It seems like there's a very clear associate chain of people.
Right, right, right.
Sorry about distracting you.
So Sam got popped, and Alex has this vibe that's like, it's unfair.
Other people protest at the Capitol, and they don't get arrested.
I don't need to say that I didn't send Sam in there because I need to protect myself.
I'm saying it because it's the truth.
But it doesn't matter because you saw Kavanaugh hearings where they took over, blocked the
halls through things, chased Congress people onto elevators, blocked the elevators, did
all that stuff, and nothing happened to those people.
But when a couple hundred people go in behind a few dozen morons that were violent and who
did do wrong, they don't all deserve to then be indicted when the police officers wave
Sam Motea in.
That's the second time Alex has gotten his name wrong.
Sam Motea.
Yeah.
The guy who definitely is a good guy.
Second string, Sam Motea.
Yeah.
Boy, if I were Sam, I would be like, I'm racking my brain for shit that's unrelated to the
six.
I'm going through any crime I can think.
I think he embezzled 50 bucks one time.
He took it from petty cash.
It was Alex.
As for the Kavanaugh protesters, it feels like no one got arrested there to Alex because
he doesn't care.
Right.
And acknowledging that there were arrests would hurt his narratives.
In reality, you can find articles about mass arrests that took place around the Kavanaugh
hearings.
CNN had an article on October 5th, 2018 about 293 people being arrested by the Capitol Police
for unlawful demonstrations.
A Mother Jones article lists the arrests at Kavanaugh protests.
And if you add them all up, not including the group one from that CNN article, you end
up with 662 arrests at Kavanaugh protests.
That's a ton.
And the main difference between then and now is that these anti-Kavanaugh protesters didn't
try to take over the fucking Capitol.
How many people did they kill?
Alex pretends that no one got arrested protesting Kavanaugh because if he acknowledged that
they did, he'd either have to argue that they shouldn't have and then be defending evil
leftists, or he'd have to accept that there are consequences for people's actions.
And currently, Sam is experiencing what a lot of others before him have.
It was a risk that he either knowingly or unknowingly accepted when he decided to film
himself going into the Capitol with a bunch of lunatics, and recognizing that dynamic
is a big threat to Alex's entire pitch about how they're all victims.
Yeah.
The right has no idea what it means to actually protest.
No.
Like, they just don't get that.
They don't understand the idea about accepting consequences when you put yourself in these
situations.
That's the point.
You are accepting that something will happen to you in order to stand beside a ton of people.
You can't take all of us.
The cause is important enough to you that you risk whatever consequence may come.
It's illegal to occupy this space and sit in the Capitol, let's say, for example.
And you do that knowing that the consequence could be that you get arrested because it
will bring attention to whatever cause you are there protesting.
Yeah, I think they're just so used to getting whatever they fucking want.
Yeah.
It's so bizarre for people who are just so interested in personal responsibility to not
understand this dynamic.
Yeah.
Oh well.
It's not bizarre.
People who are really interested in personal responsibility are usually really interested
in it for other people.
Yeah, maybe.
So mike down for this clip because it was so weird, but another defense of Sam is that
he's got a lot of hats.
He's wearing hats.
He was wearing a MAGA hat when he was there, literally, but he was also wearing a journalist
hat and also just like a, hey, I'm cool guy hat.
And he got really, really dramatic footage.
And so we left it up because he was operating as a journalist.
So they're going to try to say, well, he's not a journalist when he's making political
comments.
Well, everybody can wear two or three hats.
You can be out playing golf and then say something to the news cameras about your view on apartheid.
You know, 30 years ago, you can be at a star Wars premiere and say something about animal
rights if you want.
It's two different hats.
Okay.
I'm guessing that Alex is referencing Gary player.
Yeah, something, but man, that's a weird poll for him to make as an example of someone wearing
two hats.
I think that was on Alex's mind because Trump gave a Gary player a medal of freedom or whatever.
That's too predictable.
I hate people like this.
Yeah.
So that's weird.
I think that there's a slight difference between a golfer giving a unpopular opinion or you
making some kind of a political comment when you're on a red carpet.
I think those are a little bit different than you being, uh, in the middle of an inactive
participant in the storming of the Capitol, but you're a journalist because you have a
camera.
Yeah.
They like to pretend that it wasn't a massive bloodthirsty attempt to take over the entire
country, hopefully triggering Trump to Institute martial law.
So you have a, everything under your control, they don't like to deal with that part.
Well, the circumstances are a little bit weird to me because it's not analogous to someone
at like a movie premiere saying something political.
No, the, the version that I think would be really funny is if someone was, let's say
storming the Capitol.
Sure.
But they were wearing like Godzilla versus Kong merch, so they argued they were just
doing promotion.
Yeah.
There's two hats.
I'm a marketing major and also I am attempting to overthrow a country.
Right, right, right.
Yeah.
I think I remember that and Marquis de Sade, whenever they stormed the Bastille came out
with copies of his book and he's like, just while I'm here, look, where is there
going to be more free press attention than at the storming of the Capitol?
You want to get the word out about your movie?
That's the place.
Has anybody ever said no press is bad press, my friends, because that's the truth.
I don't, I don't, I don't think that this argument holds up in my mind that he's wearing
two hats.
How long before that's a legitimate advertising strategy, fucking Disney is like, okay, here's
what we do.
We're going to storm the United States Capitol and then after we've done all this damage,
we're going to remove our shirts all at once and it's going to be the next Pocahontas movie.
And everyone's going to blame soy bomb.
Yeah.
Yeah, that sounds right.
So I got this real sense and I think it's kind of a normal sense to get in situations
like this that Alex is obviously making this all about himself.
Sure.
Duh.
But as Alex talked more, I really got a feeling that it kind of felt like he is mad that it's
not him.
It seems like he wishes it was him who got arrested.
Good enough.
Martyr.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
Disrupting would be blocking him, blocking the door, shutting down the hearing quickly.
He's talking about when he went to Congress and yelled at Sundar Pichai.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
I don't believe you should do that, but particularly I got angry also because the, in the hearings
they'd been talking about me, they did talk about me in that hearing.
I was in there for five angry hours and they said my name at least six, seven times and
they had Congress people pointing me out in the back row with Roger Stone going, there's
the Russians, there's the spies right there.
I'm not a Russian spy, you trash.
And you know it, you're the globalist butcher in this country.
Sure.
So again, what I did was 10 times more aggressive than Sam and if he is indicted, I deserve
to be indicted for what happened.
I see, that's how I operate.
I am Spartacus.
The law is a fraud, the whole application of it's a fraud, it's garbage.
So please arrest me, please.
I want to be a martyr, it would give me so much attention.
Secondary attention is not good enough.
Uh-uh, what is this, what is this?
Just a second string cameraman that's getting arrested, I can't turn him into a martyr that
leads the movement?
I did 10 times worse.
I am the worst person here, he says confidently knowing he won't be arrested or inconvenienced
in any way.
So silly.
Yeah.
So we get now to that Washington Post, I'm sorry, Washington Times, quite different.
Yeah, hold on.
Headline that Alex was talking about earlier in the episode.
Is Dr. Fauci the father of the pandemic?
An incredible Washington Times article out just yesterday, admitting he basically ran
the Wuhan lab, it had hundreds of groups funding it, but his program with Obama continuing
under Trump till he pulled out of it two years before COVID launched, about a year into Trump,
Trump pulled out of it.
We showed you those documents last week, to his credit, that he got back into it by then
supporting their damn vaccine, it's a terrible idea, but that's the facts.
That's the facts?
Those are the facts?
What facts are those?
I think that that makes Trump look worse.
That makes him look incredibly stupid.
Yeah, if any of that were true, which it's not, that would make Trump like a willing
participant in bio warfare against the American people.
Because it's not him just letting the program continue, it's him being like, I got to stop
this program, and then a couple of years later, them being like, come on, let's kill everybody.
And he's like, I'm tired, sure, go for it.
That makes him real, real bad.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So we know from looking at past episodes of Alex's show that when Alex first learned about
Anthony Fauci towards the beginning of the pandemic, huge fan, loved him, he's a great
guy.
Didn't do him, he's a legend.
He's a man among men.
One of the best.
Trump's got him out there, he's going to- Best person to lead the fight.
Right, because he was, Alex thought that Fauci was saying stuff that worked for his conspiracies.
Right.
Turned out it didn't, so he threw Fauci under the bus pretty quick.
Also we know from listening to past episodes, Steve Pachanik used to think that Anthony
Fauci was one of the best in the business.
True.
Because they went to Columbia together.
Yeah, exactly.
Or Cornell.
Or Cornell together.
And that has changed that tone.
Right.
Turns out we have a new villain backstory.
How do I know Fauci's in charge?
He's been involved running these attacks and bioweapon attacks against Africa and others
since before Gates was even out of college.
Gates has worked directly under him.
Fauci is the guy that actually runs the operational programs.
He's been doing it for 40 years at least.
And his, because I read transcripts, his word for word stuff a week before, a month before,
a day before, will word for word come out of Gigi Pink's dirty mouth and out of the
UN's dirty mouth, the WHO's murderous mouth.
He's in charge.
He's the one.
Look at him.
He looks like an academic and we hate those.
So Fauci's been running bioweapon attacks for like 40 years and yet Steve Pachanik,
the great insider who knows everything in his overthrown countries, secretly the Forrest
Gump of world history, thought he was a great guy until like just now.
No, I would say that Steve Pachanik thought he was a great guy until he was the first
person to be infected with COVID-19.
He cured himself.
So once he got infected, he realized that Fauci had been lying to him the whole time,
even since he was young, because Fauci was actually recruited into this program when
he was zero years old.
He was grown in a lab, Dan.
Since he was zero and a half years old, he was also exactly five foot eight at the time,
et cetera.
Yep.
I think I proved it.
That sounds right.
Yeah.
I feel like the more and more you try to parody what Alex is talking about.
It's going to say it next week.
Yeah.
It's not far off enough to actually be funny.
I just don't know how far I can go.
We're just basically in comic book territory at this point.
That is true.
So Alex is complaining about this article, not really dealing with it at all, but the
headline's fun for him.
Sure.
So that's great.
Yeah.
And then Alex reads another headline.
I'm a clinical lab scientist.
COVID-19 is fake.
Wake up.
And it continues on from there.
It continues on from there.
Dan, does it continue on from there?
It does.
Would that continuation perhaps provide context for this headline?
Yeah.
That headline is just the first line of a meme post that's been going around on message
boards and Facebook since at least early December.
It was initially attributed to an anonymous doctor, but since it's been claimed to have
been written by Dr. Rob Oswald, a virologist and immunologist at Cornell University's Department
of Molecular Medicine.
Man, Cornell is out of its mind-growing lunatics at us.
Oswald didn't write that.
Oh, okay.
And he doesn't agree with the sentiment.
Sure.
But people get tricked more easily when you pretend that someone with expertise in a particular
field is saying something, as opposed to some random idiot on the internet.
I'm pretty sure Thomas Jefferson said that.
This is what Alex is covering in his stack of news.
This is something that passed the test of what should be printed off and covered on
this program, which is just pathetic.
It's a meme.
You got to share memes, otherwise they won't become powerful.
It's not even new.
New memes are just old memes waiting to be reused.
Great.
Something else that's getting reused is Norm fucking Pattis.
Oh, no.
No.
Really?
Norm Pattis.
Oh, man.
He's a lawyer extraordinaire, guy who had to sit silently and awkwardly while Alex put
a bounty out on his ass, and he hooked enemies.
There's got to be...
I think at this point, Pattis has to be in it for the stories.
You know, like 20 years from now, he's sitting at a bar just being like, I can tell you tales,
man.
I suspect that maybe he's flown too close to the sun with Alex.
And he can't go anywhere else.
Might realize...
It might be starting to realize like, ah, shit.
I don't know.
Maybe it's part of a book thing that he's trying to write.
Like, you know how some strippers or sex workers or the like, they're like, oh, I do this.
And then they write a book and they go on Oprah.
That's what Norm Pattis is going to do.
I don't know.
Because the more that I hear Norm, the more I feel like he's being more willing to say
Infowars-y stuff.
That's true.
Whereas before, it seemed like he had a little bit of restraint.
It seemed a little more professional.
He seems like a real fucking shithead in this interview.
That's not good.
Yeah.
So anyway, Alex introduces him and he also gets Sam's name wrong again.
Great.
I wanted to get Norm Pattis as a famous criminal lawyer and constitutional lawyer and also
does work for us on the first amendment issue quite a bit on, you know, he doesn't know
all the facts and this all just happened yesterday.
So he's going to be limited on what he talks about with our Infowars reporter, Sam Motea.
Wow.
Sam, you got to listen to this broadcast.
This is one that's going to change things for you.
This broadcast is going to put you on a path to a better life.
Alex is trying to do you dirty.
Yeah.
And one of the funny things about Norm's appearance here on the show is that you get a real sense
that he's kind of trying to reassure Alex that like you're clean.
Okay.
You're good, man.
What I know in Mr. Montoya's case is that he was arrested for his conduct on the Capitol
that day.
I understand he had a press pass.
Federal authorities may or may not be aware of that.
The press pass may or may not have protected him from all the consequences of what he was
doing that day.
That's a question that will have to be sorted out in a court of law.
You know, I represent you, obviously, my primary concern is you.
I do not believe there are facts sufficient to warrant a further investigation of you
or much less an arrest.
I'm prepared to wage that fight when the time comes, if it comes.
Yeah.
I don't know, from everything I can see publicly available, Norm's probably right.
Like, he was promoting Infowars while he was live streaming going into the Capitol.
Sure.
But who's to say if Alex asked him to do that or is even aware that he was doing that?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that is something that will have to be seen.
But it is interesting that there's like, yeah, yeah, he's gonna have to go to court.
You're cool.
Yeah.
Hey, buddy, buddy.
My primary concern is you.
He's not my client.
He doesn't pay me.
You do.
And let me tell you something right now, you keep saying what you're saying, you never
met the guy.
You're cool.
We're gonna have a good night.
So they get to talking about the shooting of Daunte Wright in Minneapolis, or in Minnesota.
Yeah, sure.
I want to get my lawyer buddy on to do that, yeah.
This takes a turn for the uncomfortable.
Let's talk about this.
This is just now breaking.
We know the name of the female police officer who said, get ready Taser.
And then she shot and killed Daunte Wright.
He's in the middle of rioting.
He's got a warrant out for armed robbery.
The city's burning, the police station shot up.
He's kicking police flailing.
She absolutely shoots him in the fog of war.
That's what happens.
I'm not glad it happened.
But he's a thug waving guns around on the internet.
You know, all this, he's dead.
Now, what does he expect?
You go to a riot, you're probably gonna get killed by somebody.
Surprisingly, one person got killed.
Fox is making up almost all of the details of this shooting.
Daunte wasn't at a riot.
He was pulled over for having expired tags on his license plates and having hanging air
fresheners that blocked his mirrors.
Very minor things.
He wasn't fighting with the police, though it does appear that he was trying to get back
into his car before he was shot.
There was a misdemeanor warrant for Wright's arrest, but it was unrelated to an aggravated
robbery charge he'd gotten in December 2019.
It had to do with missing a court date for a misdemeanor of carrying a pistol without
a permit, something Alex should not think is a crime.
There's a conversation to have about this shooting, but it's literally impossible to
deal with any of the real underlying issues if you're like Alex and you insist on creating
a completely fictional version of events to tell your audience.
It's important to understand that Alex does this all the time.
Real events become fiction, with his addition of tons of details and subplots that aren't
real.
And it's critical to understand how he uses fictional augmentation of real stories, because
it's one of the easiest ways to see his biases.
When it's a black man who's killed, the story is supplemented with all sorts of extenuating
circumstances and details that make it so sad that the guy kinda had it coming.
We've seen this play out over and over again recently with George Floyd and Ahmaud Arbery.
The opposite is done when it's a white person who's killed, as we saw so grotesquely in
the case of Kate Steinle.
In reality, an immigrant found a gun wrapped in a rag that he didn't even realize was a
gun, he picked it up, the gun discharged, and a ricocheting bullet accidentally and
tragically hit Steinle.
Alex's retelling of the story became a tale where this immigrant saw Steinle with her
dad who the immigrant thought was her older boyfriend and the immigrant was jealous that
she was with, he was with someone so beautiful and he couldn't have her so he killed her.
These strategies are intentional because reality isn't what's real to Alex.
What's real is this white supremacist ideology and archetypes that he can try to justify
by using real life events and tragedies as props.
And you see that and it's very, very obvious.
So I mean, one of the things that I think is really important whenever we're talking
about Alex Jones and the things that he does is often times it's less important to look
at what is being done as like the structure of why these things are being done.
Alex is creating side stories and details about the story of this shooting in order
to make it more palatable for his audience to not care.
And he does the reverse when it's a white person who has been shot.
It's just very obvious whenever Alex says something like, where, how am I racist?
This is a key example.
This strategy and this tactic is a fingerprint.
Yeah, I mean it's immediately obvious simply because his argument, even if he says it's
not okay for the cops to kill people, his argument always boils down to it's more okay
for the cops to kill black people than white people.
Yeah.
His behavior dictates that that is his position.
That has to be true in his situation.
So there you go.
You're a racist piece of shit.
Alex is taking issue too with the fact that the name of the police officer in Minnesota
was released and that the officer who shot Ashley Babbitt in the Capitol has not been
released.
Sure.
And then Norm chimes in.
The department of justice closes investigation, the death of Ashley Babbitt.
And they say, since when do you have an investigation?
Like it's national security, like it's the CIA and we don't even, they've closed the
investigation and we don't even know the person's name.
This is a very dangerous precedent here, Norm.
What do you think is going on here?
I have no idea.
I mean, and that's the problem.
It's not transparent.
I know that had she been black and there were no charges, no transparency, there might be
more riots in the streets and then we'd be talking about the need for a so-called racial
reckoning.
Are you a lawyer?
Man, you know, the past few years have really made me think that passing the bar is not
as hard as it has been advertised.
Cool, Norm.
Jesus Christ.
Wow.
A racial reckoning.
Yeah.
He's saying that the reason that no one is concerned with who the Capitol police officer,
and I don't even know if I'm going to allow that stipulation to stand, but he's saying
that we would ever want to be up in arms if it was a black person who had gotten shot.
That's wow.
This guy's a lawyer.
That's not good.
Nope.
So if there's ghosts in the neighborhood, there's something strange in the neighborhood.
Sure, sure, sure.
Who are you going to call?
I would call the Ghostbusters.
That is correct.
Who would other people call?
Now, if there's a rustling in your house at night, maybe if it was a burglar, who would
you call?
I would still call the Ghostbusters.
Those proton packs are fucking powerful, man.
Do they affect people?
I don't know.
I've never...
I mean, if you cross them, they'll make something come to life, I guess.
You'd call the police.
I would totally call the police.
Yes.
And in that, you and Norm...
Wait, what?
No, I would never call the police.
I would die before calling the police instantly.
Norm would call the police.
Calling the police is essentially attempted murder at this point.
But I'll tell you something.
If I hear a rustle at the door tonight and somebody's trying to enter my home, I'm calling
911.
I'm not calling Black Lives Matter.
That's the kind of statement that I hear and my only response is, okay, all right, all
right, man.
Yeah.
Cool.
Why would you call Black Lives Matter if someone's breaking in your house?
They're not a police organization.
They're not law enforcement.
I don't know.
I just don't...
I just don't know.
Are you really going to use that as a thing that's acceptable to say?
Well, it's really bizarre because I think we might be dealing with a Norm who's trying
to get into a second line of work.
Oh, he's looking for that Milly Weaver slot that opened up.
No, I think he's trying to get into standup.
Oh, no.
I tried my debut at standup comedy the other night at a small club in Connecticut and I
ended my riff with the following, hey, you know, I tried to buy woke insurance the other
day.
The crowd looked at me.
What's woke insurance?
Well, woke insurance is what you need if you're a white man because I'm reading the paper
and everything that's wrong with this country is my fault.
How am I going to pay for all of this?
I need woke insurance.
And we're at a point where that sort of humor isn't necessarily farcical any longer.
He's going to fit right in and stand up.
Wow.
Listen.
He's not funny and he is a bitter white dude.
He's going to go straight to the top.
Or at least straight to every single open mic I've ever been to in my entire life.
Yeah.
Then the bitterness is going to keep on growing.
Oh, it's never going to stop.
Wow.
It's never going to stop.
I don't know.
I feel like if I were interviewing my lawyer and they decided to get into racist, hacky
standup, I might be considering a change in representation.
Yeah.
I guess I'm going to call Saul Goodman from here on out.
Better.
This is not good.
No.
Don't tell me.
Don't tell me that you started doing it.
I don't want anyone to tell me they started doing standup.
No.
Especially not Norm fucking Pattis.
Definitely not Norm Pattis.
Not a good bit.
Oh yeah.
Are there problems?
Yeah.
I would go with the structure.
So if you're buying woke insurance, let's explore this.
Okay.
Let's do this.
So let's say you're a woke insurance agent.
Right.
I'm a door to door woke insurance salesman.
So you come to my door.
You're white.
Right.
Okay.
So I need woke insurance.
Right.
What does this protect me from?
It protects you from if people are rioting.
So flood insurance.
Sure.
That is like, okay, so if my house floods, this money that I pay when it doesn't flood,
so whenever it does flood, if it does flood, then you can have money to fix my flooded
house.
Sure.
So woke insurance, it's got to be something where you pay.
Totally.
That's what's happening.
I agree with you.
I don't know.
Scream the N word at people.
Now.
That doesn't protect you from that.
It only protects you from the racial reckoning, dad.
So if a racial reckoning occurs, you're going to want woke insurance.
Okay.
So you're immune from this quote unquote racial reckoning if you've paid your dues to your
woke insurance.
Of course.
Why would we have woke insurance?
What do you think this is?
Some sort of scam?
I don't understand what it's for.
You're a white man and you need it.
That's all I need to tell you.
The world is changing, Dan, without this woke insurance, you could be left in the dust.
I think a better way to tell this bit if the way that Norm wants to do it would be something
like a protection racket.
You know, it's not insurance.
It's insurance, like the mob kind of insurance, right?
Sure.
I mean, isn't that like more the vibe he's trying to give?
Hey, you don't buy this insurance.
We're going to say that you said the N-word in public.
If you don't pay your woke dues, they'll come and get you or something like that.
Isn't that more the bit he's trying to do?
It would make sense because it does seem like it's-
I don't understand what woke insurance is and his conception of it.
I mean, I think it protects you from being dog piled on for being a racist is essentially
what he's saying.
How?
Well, if you get dog piled on for being racist, there's a potential loss of income or of course
a potential gain of income.
I mean, how does the insurance work?
You pay money a month and then whenever you get dog piled on for being the racist piece
of shit you are-
The insurance company comes around and is like, oh, he's cool.
We'll be like, hey, no, hey, no.
This guy gets a free rental car.
We cover those.
And then, but no, they have to, the insurance company would have to be like, it's cool.
It's cool.
Stop the dog pile or whatever.
Sure.
Well, we can't do that.
But then that implies, or it has to imply that the people who are doing the dog piling-
Right.
That's the work for the insurance company.
If you haven't discovered this yet, the Woke Insurance Company runs the world.
Yeah.
This bit could use some work.
Probably.
His delivery could use some work.
Yes.
Telling people a standup joke outside of the context of a comedy club is a bad idea.
It is.
Yeah.
So Norm goes on from bad standup bits to biblical analogies.
Now I heard you say before the break-
Sounds like my standup.
I asked your listeners to go to the Gospel of John chapter five.
And that's the story of the sick man at Bethesda.
Jesus went to the fountain.
There was a man laying beside the fountain.
He was ill.
Should have had fountain insurance.
When the waters would rise, they had healing power.
He was begging for somebody to move him so that he could be touched by the water.
And Jesus said, why are you here?
I want to be into the waters, he said, but every time the waters move, others beat me
there.
Jesus looked at the man and he didn't create an affirmative action plan.
He didn't create a program for a racial or disabled reckoning.
He looked at the man and said words that I don't think we say often enough to one another.
Pick up your bed and walk.
And the man did.
He had the power within himself to take care of his own situation, as I believe we all
do.
So my view is the next time somebody asks you for something on account of their skin
color, tell them.
I'm up here working on a Thursday night in mid-April, 2021.
I am almost glad that he got cut off by the break and we don't know what he suggested
you tell people.
Yeah.
That's, that's good.
So when you are a lawyer, you do realize that other people do not have the capacity within
themselves to defeat the law.
Does that make sense?
Take your bed and walk.
I feel like that's, you are abdicating any and all personal responsibility.
Go ahead and take your bed and walk.
I also, I just don't see Jesus seeing a man who can't walk and thinking this requires
a top-down structural change.
I think the whole point of Jesus was the bottom-up kind of stuff.
Also wasn't the whole thing about Jesus is that he did miracles?
Isn't it, isn't it?
No, no, no.
It was the water.
But, but like people got healed by touching him and stuff.
Sure, sure.
That did happen periodically.
Well, he coated himself in the water.
Okay.
He was always covered in water.
He was, it's left out of the Bible, but Jesus was a very wet man.
I would say that basically what Norm is doing here is using a biblical story to get the
message across to people to stop complaining.
Hey, you know what?
I think if you ever see, if I saw a slave, Dan, obviously I would go up to the slave
and they would be like, Hey, we need some structural changes here because I'm a slave
and that's wrong.
I would look at him and I would say, get your bed and move.
See?
Everybody has it within themselves to solve their own problems, Dan.
There's no doubt about that.
Take your stick and get the fuck out, is what Jesus said.
So we have one more clip here from the time that Norm is on and Alex is talking about
a story about Patrisse Cullors, one of the co-founders of Black Lives Matter.
Apparently some attention has come to the fact that she's bought some houses recently
and Alex has this to say.
Well, I mean, now the Black Lives Matter lady that their own people are calling for investigation
looks like embezzled tens of millions, 10.6 million given to Black Lives Matter causes
last year.
She's calling it white supremism to investigate her.
I mean, no, you moved into all white neighborhoods.
You have a private airfield.
Turns out you've got like six houses, tens of millions of dollars.
And then she says it's white supremacy.
If she's so afraid of white supremacy, why are all her houses in the most white neighborhoods
I've ever heard of?
Because she's trying to recolonize the continent that was stolen from Native Americans and
to disconfit her neighbors by showing that we're here and we matter.
Wow.
Oh boy.
Kind of feels like Alex's question answered itself.
Segregation now, segregation forever is what you might as well have just said.
He's kind of saying like, if this person's so worried about white supremacy, why don't
they just leave our all white neighborhoods alone?
That does seem like nuts.
It does seem like the point he's trying to make is if you're worried about white supremacy,
you should leave our country.
So Patrisse Cullors released a statement on Instagram about this sort of questioning of
her money.
Sure.
And you know, she said that she has a number of different careers and revenue sources,
but they quote, I do not receive a salary or benefits from Black Lives Matter Global
Network Foundation.
She didn't say that investigating her or questioning her is white supremacy.
She did say, quote, this effort to discredit and harass me and my family is not new, nor
is it acceptable.
It's taken away from where the focus should be, ending white supremacy.
And that's been twisted by Alex to saying like, it's white supremacy to investigate
me.
Sure.
So Norm takes off and I think that was one of his worst appearances.
And that was one of the most blatantly racist things I've heard Norm say.
Yeah.
I mean the standup bit alone is graceful and that's like maybe third on the list of problems.
So Alex comes back and he decides he's going to take matters into his own hands about this
whole thing, about the non-releasing of the name of the cop.
Yeah.
See, if he wasn't such a, such a bad lawyer, I would say Norm Pata should be there for
that part.
No, no.
Norm had to get out of there.
Yeah.
And I think it's our moral responsibility to release the name as best we know, the man
is a capitalist officer.
Oh, that's not good.
Don't do that.
If he's not the officer that did it, that's fine.
Don't say it as best we know.
They can contact us and let us know.
But it came out, you know, that the internet believed they knew who it was and the name
and the information.
That's not good.
And so I believe the public has a right to know not to go after this officer.
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
I believe that.
Yeah.
I would say that generally speaking, if you just have a hunch that somebody is the person
of interest in this case, don't report that.
Here's what happens a lot.
Whenever somebody reports the name of somebody accused of murder and says, as best we know,
this is the person.
Right.
A lot of the times it's not the person and you really fucked up their lives.
Yeah.
It's something that you can't really take back.
Never.
You can't really predict what the audience's response to your shitty reporting will be.
Totally.
You don't know what you expect people to do.
Even if you are correct, you're like, I don't want anyone to go after this person.
What else could people do?
Yeah.
Why would you give them the name?
I don't understand.
I look, the people have a right to know exactly the person.
I totally don't want you to target.
I am however, giving you the name.
I'm strangely enough, I'm going to read off the address as well, but I don't want people
to bother this person at all.
I am getting a sense that Alex is pissed off that he is not being oppressed like his buddy
Sam is.
Yeah.
And so he's going to throw a wild curve ball and try and dock somebody and see if it gets
him in trouble so he can be the real victim.
Yup.
And also he wants to be clear, this is just because he believes that the capital officer
is black.
Okay.
Yeah.
That makes sense.
He takes careful aim and kills her.
Okay.
That's what he did.
And the grand jury didn't indict him, so whatever.
All I know is we know every white cop that kills a black person's name, but when a black
person kills a white person, we don't hear about it because the media wants to act like
it's only white people killing black people.
And that's not true.
Holy shit.
I would say like the most impure of motives are being expressed here in terms of Alex
wanting to say this person's name.
Openly.
That's, that's one of those things where it's like, you can not say things.
Yes.
And you can, you can, you can not say this person's name because you can't prove that
it is the right person.
Which makes it a very bad idea to single them out.
Second, you cannot say on air that you're really just pissed off on a race issue.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Your white aggrievement is, is...
I don't know why people call me racist.
Anyways, I expect different treatment for black people.
Jesus.
Anyway, it gets racist more, I guess.
So when a white police officer or Hispanic police officer shoots a white person, a black
person, a whatever person, it's instantly on the news every time.
But when a black man shoots a white man or a white woman, it's never on the news because
only whites do bad things.
You've heard we're evil.
So our intent exposing this is not to say black people are inherently bad or that what
one black person does reflects on others.
It's just, we're going to be fair here.
We're not, listen, we're not saying insert the only reason we would be saying this.
We're not saying it because of that.
We're definitely not saying it because of insert the only reason anyone could say this.
That's not why we're saying this.
It's outrageous.
No, we're not saying it because of this.
The only possible reason we could have for saying this.
We're saying it for a different reason.
Now, all right, look, I think Alex wants attention.
He wants this to blow up, get him in a little bit of trouble, but he doesn't want that much
trouble.
So he has a fall guy.
He's never met Sam before in his life.
He has a fall guy and it happens to be the guy who was in the Capitol with Sam.
It was not.
Get the fuck out.
Tyler Hansen.
Jesus Christ.
Tyler Hansen has been a pretty good investigative journalist over the years and he's been on
the show before and he and others say they have the identity of Ashley Babbitt's shooter,
which in the three plus months, the feds never released and now they cleared the police officer
without saying his name of it.
You don't normally see that.
Do you?
Like some citizens shoot somebody in their backyard.
Later, you hear they were indicted or they were cleared, but you heard their name day
one.
So is he in the new royalty?
Sometimes you don't.
Sometimes names aren't released.
You know, I don't know.
I think that the sound of a whooshing, fast moving vehicle that meant to carry a bunch
of people that Tyler should be hearing right now, because it's coming and Alex is throwing
you the fuck under it.
Not good.
Nope.
In case Alex gets in any trouble, don't worry, I'm just repeating what Tyler Hansen told
me.
Yeah.
Okay.
So Hansen also the guy who burned a Black Lives Matter flag with Owen Troyer the night
before January 6th.
He's a very good investigative journalism.
Cool guy.
Well, no, Alex said he's pretty good.
Pretty good.
He's a pretty good investor.
That's faint praise.
I mean, it's kind of so fucked up that it's like, if I have to explain to you the difference
between a cop running down and chasing a child and shooting them or fucking choking a man
to death versus a mob of people storming the fucking Capitol building, trying to tear down
the walls, running with people with fucking guns and goddamn everything.
If you can't see the difference between that type of shooting and not, there's no point
in talking.
No, you're being intentionally obtuse if you don't.
There's just no way for me to communicate with you if you don't see the difference.
And, again, assuming that the person who was the police officer in the Capitol was black,
trying to pretend that the relevant difference between those two issues is a racial one is
absurd.
Yes.
That is...
Absolutely absurd.
But it's what employers would want to do, because it helps with the white-agreement
narratives that are the fuel that the machine runs on.
So Alex is going to name this guy, and I want to leave it in just because I looked into
it and you can find it being like, it all goes back to Tyler Hansen, but he tweeted
it out and it's out there, it's public, so it's not like...
If it were something that I couldn't really find easily, I might bleep it just because
I don't want to add to this, but just for the sake of demonstrating that Alex is completely
and unconfidently not knowing at all if he's correct naming someone as a shooter here.
Not good.
Now, maybe he's not the officer, but for months his name has been known, so if he's not the
officer, let us know, or we're going to do a foyer, I assure you.
A foyer?
I've asked my lawyer to do it.
Foyer.
You've asked your lawyer to foyer?
Because we have a right as the press, a right to know.
The identity of Ashley Babbitt's shooter is Lieutenant Michael Leroy Byrd, says Taylor
Hansen on Twitter.
So again, throwing Tyler Hansen under that bus.
Hey, Hansen said this name that I'm not saying for any of those insert reason...
Yeah, yeah.
I have a way larger platform than Tyler Hansen, and I am going to rely on his reporting, but
I'm also going to say that maybe it's not the guy, and hey, if it's not him, maybe he
could call in and correct me about it, because that's the responsibility of the people that
you accuse of things.
Totally.
Look, we're just asking questions, and if these people would come forward and tell us
the answers, we wouldn't need to ask any more questions.
This is definitely not something we're saying in bad faith.
You've never heard this before.
Not once in your life have you heard us say something similar to this in bad faith.
Right.
This is like Alex claiming that Bill Gates is in the Council of 12 or whatever, because
he said it on air and Bill Gates hasn't corrected him.
Totally.
If he wasn't in the Council of 12, he would have called into my show.
I would have been incredibly deferential towards him because he's powerful and I am a coward.
This is not how shit works, man.
I like the idea that he does call a FOIA a FOIA, which is fine, whatever, it's his accent.
His lawyer's getting a FOIA.
Whatever.
So he understands that that's something that you might be able to do in this case, because
the investigation has closed, and so there may not be a legitimate law enforcement reason
to not release the name of the person, and you might be able to get that with a FOIA
request.
Possible.
Now, if you do that, you could report the name.
Exactly.
You can't do this and then be like, hey, if he's not the person, he should tell us, meanwhile
the damage has been done by me saying that it is the person, and also eventually we'll
do a FOIA request that we're never going to do.
We'll absolutely confirm this later on with a FOIA request, something that we do so often,
I pronounce it correctly.
So Alex, like I said, it's just too clear that his entire premise here is that he's
just mad that the white cop's name got revealed.
Again, they won't say his name, his reported name, but again, we do know Kim Potter's name,
and she's had to evacuate her house and the police station's been burned down, but that's
okay because she's a white devil and she deserves it.
So there you go.
I mean, it's just too obvious that what is animating this and what's motivating him to
behave in the ways he is.
Even without that motive, this behavior is unacceptable.
But having this kind of a reckless, irresponsible behavior going on while it's being so obviously
motivated by feelings of white identity, insecurity, and victimhood, it's just multiple layers
of unacceptable.
I can't believe he's this transparent.
Yeah, I mean, but it is kind of a truth that if you cling to whiteness, eventually that's
the only thing you're going to have left.
Like clinging to the color of your skin as something important is going to push everybody
out of your life eventually.
Or it's only going to unite you with other people who are clinging to whiteness.
And until you find a difference between you.
Yeah, exactly.
Until it's time to shut them out for not being white enough for...
Right, wrong color hair, something.
Wrong religion, whatever you want.
Yeah.
I mean, I think in many ways it comes down to just having a mentality that is so entirely
based on exclusion is going to exclude.
And it's going to just, it's going to go that way.
That's how it works.
Yeah.
So now at this point, Alex goes to Owen Troyer, who's down by the border trying to get more
footage of stopping smugglers, I guess.
That's where I would want to be.
I would want to be near the US Mexico border if I was Owen Troyer, just in case.
Just like, oh, I'll take a little step over here and now I'm not in trouble, no border.
Come and get me.
Yeah.
Come on.
Suck it Biden.
You want to get to extradite me for this?
Come on.
So yeah, I didn't care for any of that.
I'm not going to play this dance.
No.
And I got really mad.
I got really mad at Alex.
One, because of how disgusting this display has been for most of this episode.
Absolutely.
But then second, because here's a clip from the first hour that I got really excited about
and he just fucking teased me.
And then separately, I'm mixing it into my stacks and I can't find it because I was about
to hit it.
Will you guys get me the new John Hopkins cyber collapse document that Jamie White wrote?
I've got the document, but I can't find, always on the bottom I did find it.
Cyber polygon 2021 globalist run simulation of coming cyber pandemic to prepare for economic
reset.
This is the blueprint.
I'll tell you, John Hopkins is like the main horse in the fight now against this.
All the globalists do their tests, their drills, they agree at committee what they're going
to do.
And it's given to these academics and business people and top scientists and in the top of
their fields, academia, banking, computer science, weapons, psychology, psychology.
Then they launched the attack.
I'm going to be hitting that as well.
I've got to hit that.
You got to hit it.
You have to hit that.
You got to.
You literally have to hit that.
And then he didn't.
That's the most important story I've ever heard.
Cyber polygon 2021.
I got to know.
It's so great.
The great reset is happening and it's through the cyber polygon 2021.
So I found the documents and everything, and then Alex never brought it up.
So I don't get to talk about it.
Damn it.
Anyway.
Look, someday soon.
Look, it's yeah, we will talk about it once he talks about it.
We'll get there.
The thing that I struggled with is like, I got really excited.
There's primary documents here.
It is actually something that interesting maybe we could talk about, but I'm not going
to debunk things Alex doesn't even get to.
Yeah, that's not fair.
No.
That's not fair.
You can't pre bunk things.
I don't actually even know what his angle is outside of that vague nonsense.
Exactly.
Anyway, once he talks about cyber polygon, I'll be very excited.
We'll get to it.
I have a lot to say about it.
It's good that you've got it in the can though.
You know, it's always good to be one step ahead of, uh, of the roadrunner.
It's unsatisfying though, cause you know, I'm listening to this bullshit about Sam.
Sure.
And then Alex and Norm getting racist as hell and I'm like, at least I've got cyber polygon
to look forward to and then it just doesn't happen.
Oh man.
Bullshit.
I, I'm telling you, I think second string Sam should have been on the second string
for this episode.
Should have been cyber polygon 2021 all day.
If I were Alex, I might've spent more time on that than trying to make Sam's arrest about
himself.
Yeah, that would be smart.
But narcissists got to do what they got to do.
It does seem like it.
Um, so yeah, I think that, I think this is, um, you know, one of the first times that
we've had an active Infowars employee get arrested and so that's kind of interesting
and that was one of the reasons why I was like, we gotta, we gotta get into this.
Well, Millie Weaver got arrested, but she was, I think that was unrelated.
No, it was totally unrelated.
And she was not, uh, she was an independent contractor, honestly, never met her before
in my life.
Yeah.
And she, she was fired pretty quick.
Yeah, very quick.
Um, and then like Joe Biggs got arrested, but he's a former employee.
Sure.
That's true.
Um, Roger Stone, but you know, he's, he's Roger Stone.
He's Roger Stone.
I guess a lot of them have been arrested.
Wow.
All right.
I like how felons can't vote, but they can work at Infowars.
Yep.
So, uh, Jordan, we'll be back, uh, with another episode, hopefully covering Cyber Polygon.
Yeah, no kidding.
We got something to do.
We got to do something with that.
Yeah, that's going to be my big tease from now on eventually we'll get to Cyber Polygon.
And we're going to hit Cyber Polygon 2021.
Um, but until then we have a website, Jordan.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yes.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledgefight.com.
Go to bed, Jordan.
We're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook.
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work right now.
Uh, we'll be back, but until then I'm Neo, I'm Leo, I'm DZX Clark, I'm Daryl Rundis.
Jordan, I place you under arrest for loud utterances.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
Thank you for being with us today, and we'll see you next time.