I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying, we are the bad guys.
Thank you.
It's time to pray.
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes.
Like to sit around, drink novelty beverages,
and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are.
Mr. Freezin'.
Mr. Holmes.
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today is granola, baby.
Ooh, what's that say?
Lure Crunch?
This is Love Crunch.
Love Crunch.
Founded at the store.
This is espresso vanilla cream.
Granola.
Oh my God.
What do you have to have to name your business Love Crunch?
Jordan, this is so good.
It's inspired by the Italian affogato,
which is made with espresso and ice cream.
Oh, okay.
It's very good.
It's nice.
I'm trying to, I had like this period,
I think I talked about it in some previous bright spots,
where I was going for these bizarre ass cereals,
you know, like the fruity pebbles with marshmallows.
Oh yes.
We, the Dunkin' Donuts.
The coffee Dunkin' Donuts ones.
That's gonna happen, yeah.
And I'm trying to get back onto a more like,
all right, I've indulged my inner child a little bit here.
Sure, sure.
And even this, I'll admit, this is, I mean,
it's an espresso vanilla cream situation.
So it's not like it's the hardest core granola,
but I'm working in that direction.
I feel like my breakfast could be better served.
I'm glad it's based on an Italian something
as opposed to affogato.
Cause it sounds a little bit like a song
a hair metal band would have released in the eighties.
You know, like, love crunch, love, love crunch.
Isn't that Nazareth, love hurts?
Could be, could be, something along those lines.
So what's your bright spot?
Oh, my bright spot, Dan.
I'm assuming some people have found out by now.
We were in the New York Times.
How fun is that?
That's nice.
Super bizarre.
That's fun.
If I hadn't like been aware that this was coming,
I would be like, this is, I can't, I.
Yeah, yeah.
It's very bizarre.
No, this is.
Very bizarre, thank you to.
It's fun, it's fun, it's silly, all right.
So Jordan, today we have an interesting episode to go over.
We're going to be talking about April 16th, 2021.
Blackjack.
Ah, shit.
This is Friday's episode of Alex's show.
Okay.
And you know, it's not, it's not great.
It's not, it may not be the most groundbreaking of episodes.
Sure, sure.
But there are a couple of things that happened
that are breathtaking.
Okay.
That are amazing.
All right.
And a good teachable moment.
So. Okay, good.
We'll get down to business on that here in a second.
But before we do, let's take a little moment
to say thank you to some folks who have signed up
and are supporting the show.
Oh, that's great.
So first, the Reverend Dr. Sorrow.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, RDS.
Thank you.
Next, 1776 was a false flag.
The British are the globalists.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thought-provoking.
I think Alex might agree with half of that.
I think he might have said that.
Yeah.
Borderline, yeah.
Then a couple of technocrat shout-outs
to throw out William V.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat and Thomas C. Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate.
That's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
We got to go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why are you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you, Willie, and thank you, Tomas.
Yes, thank you very much to the both of you.
So Jordan, I had to cut the wonk shout-outs a little bit short
on this episode because we have another little bit of business
that we have to get to.
It's very important.
Of course.
And that is that tomorrow, Tuesday, is 4-20.
Right.
And that means that it is the official end
of the year of the Seltzer.
That's true.
It is the official end of the year of the Seltzer.
Where did we wind up?
You got 3-50, right?
Yeah, right around 3-50.
That's great.
For people who maybe have found the podcast more recently,
last year, around 4-20.
You've got lore to catch up on.
I decided that I was going to drink 500 Seltzers in that year.
It was kind of something just to put a smile on our face
because it seemed like there was going to be this period where
there was the COVID.
I didn't think it was going to go as long as it did.
I did not either.
I just kind of thought like, yeah,
this will be a way to kill some time.
I'll drink a bunch of La Croix and all
these weird flavors of things.
And look, a year's too long for a novelty goof.
It was very much an emotional rollercoaster ride
because it started off as a goof.
Then a few weeks later...
It started off as a goof with a lot of energy behind it.
That's true.
No, well, a few weeks later, what I'm saying
is you got into it.
And all of a sudden, it started being a lot of Seltzers
just popping up all over the place.
And then, what was it?
Probably about six months ago.
I got a hot tip on a Seltzer.
We got to go to the south side to find it.
It was about six months ago that your enthusiasm
dropped down, and then there was a little bounce back.
It was like the stock market.
It dropped farther, there's a little bounce back,
and then it's gone.
Well, I can say that a big part of it
is the difficulties involved with COVID.
And then some personal life stuff kind of
disenchanted me a lot over a period of months.
And look, a lot of Seltzers are not very different.
Yeah, I think you could make it to a year and 500
if you were on a Japanese game show where
you had to live in a place where there's nothing
but Seltzers for a year.
If someone brought me all of the Seltzers,
and I was like, sip it, and they're like, oh, 50.
Who gives a shit?
Like, in those circumstances, I definitely
could have tried 50.
But after you try so many, it's like, I don't know.
This is fine.
It sucks, but it's not that bad.
It's not great.
You really lose the enthusiasm to hunt
down new Seltzers.
And once you've already had everything
that's at every store within a couple miles of your house,
and you can't find anything else on Amazon,
it just becomes a real stu-
I mean, it was a stupid idea from the beginning.
No, but I mean, you know, all of our ideas
are somewhat stupid.
Yeah, and I'm glad I tried.
I learned a few things.
One is the wide, wide world of these Seltzers.
There's so many.
And the ones that are more tea-like are better, I think.
I enjoy them more.
They have more depth of flavor.
And so, hooray.
And in honor of ending the Year of the Seltzer,
I'm ending it with my novelty beverage for today,
which is a listener, Amani, sent some Sunwink
Sparkle Herbal Tonics.
And I've tried the one that is, I believe, turmeric-related.
And that one was all right.
It's got a little spice to it.
Is it turmeric or turmeric?
I think it's pronounced turmeric,
but there is an R in there.
That infuriates me.
Yeah, it might be a silent R.
We can continue.
So this is Sunwink Lemon Rose Uplift.
I feel like now is a good time for some uplifting.
No, Lemon Rose, taking a sip.
I noticed you playing around with that bottle
before the show.
And normally, you have a bit of an energy drink going on there.
And how did you do?
It was really good.
It was really good?
Yeah.
Nice.
Yeah, that's very tea-like.
It's reminiscent of those ones that had flour.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, I guess rose is the flour.
Well, that would make sense.
Yeah, good.
Those were real good.
Yeah.
So thank you, Imani.
And thank you, everybody who has enjoyed
the year of the seltzer.
I don't know if I'm going to do a year of anything else
ever again.
I doubt it.
I learned a valuable lesson.
There's definitely that.
It's humiliating.
Think of it.
You got to round 350 seltzers.
If you had set your goal for 300 seltzers,
you wouldn't have made 350.
500 was such an attractive number, though.
It's a nice round number.
Yeah, I mean, look, I achieved something.
Indeed.
Maybe?
Probably.
Let the viewer decide.
Sure.
Anyway, Jordan, today, April 16th.
Indeed.
Ides of March.
I'm still writing June on my checks.
So here we go.
We're going to start off with Alex
talking about some headlines.
And then getting into something that is very bad news for us,
as you know, we are the chat guys.
Now, they denied all of this in mainline publications
until a few years ago.
And now they run the same headline every week.
For the first time, animal human clones have been made.
That's always, it's in the test tube, it's embryonic.
And that's just a condition, condition, condition,
condition.
The CIA was quoted in the Washington Post back in 1999
that, oh, we're funding the body modification and tattoo
and earring movement.
Doesn't mean it's bad or good or anything.
All the things you said, all the things you said.
To get you ready for implantable chips.
I mean, this is all actually in different publications.
They admit all of this.
Yep, the CIA encouraged everyone to get earrings and tattoos.
It's really weird for the CIA to finally start admitting stuff
and choose the stuff that I guess
would take them down the most.
Yeah.
But, you know, what are you going to do?
Yeah, I don't know about this.
Also, so the latest news in the animal human hybrid front
is that there was an article published in the journal Cell,
where researchers injected human stem cells into monkey embryos,
which then they observed growing.
Three of the embryos survived up to 19 days,
but they didn't create clones or anything like Alex is saying.
This is a field of study, but it's not
what Alex is describing.
And the scientific community is far
from reaching a consensus on it.
There are tons of debates that go on about the ethics
or even the need for such research.
And you can find people who have informed opinions on both sides.
Alex is not one of them.
Yeah, but, you know, once I saw that you could transfer
the bioluminescence trait to another creature,
I was like, well, get rid of all other research.
Until I can glow in the dark, all science should stop.
Until everything.
Until everything can glow in the dark.
My buddy Dr. Gums used to get furious with me,
because I would constantly demand
for him to explain to me why we can't photosynthesize.
Like, why can't we get a human that has photosynthesis?
I would like to know that.
I feel like we should.
I really think he had a compelling, full answer,
and I was too high to remember what it was.
Well, of course.
I don't remember.
Considering you've heard it many times, too.
Yeah.
So this story, you know, the whole thing
about the human-animal hybrids and stuff,
this is something that people like to take as an example
of actually, Alex, he's right all along, man.
But the important thing to remember is that his version
of this research, it doesn't match what actually exists.
The stories that he tells are different than reality.
Just remember, we were talking about fish-human hybrids
in tanks with sad human eyes.
Exactly.
That's the kind of stuff that Alex talks about.
And he claims that he's seen them.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's pinned to the tanks.
We're not talking about injecting embryos.
We're talking about full-grown fish men wandering
around our seas.
Yeah.
It's very attractive for people to take headlines and then
sort of out-of-context snippets of things Alex said,
and he's like, yeah, he's been right all along.
Showed you.
It's not really accurate.
It's a fun game, though, and I applaud people for playing it.
So if you want to be someone who plays this game that Alex
is right about everything, I have bad news.
We will all be dead soon.
Oh, no.
There is a scientific global dictatorship
that is breaking away from humanity,
and that as it breaks away, it extracts
all the resources of the old civilization,
poisons us, dumbs us down, divides us, and conquers us,
puts us back into the jungle, the urban jungle,
and then wipes us out.
We've got fun and games.
And by the time that they finally wiped everybody out,
which is coming very soon, in a cascade of crises
they orchestrate but pose as the saviors, those of us
that haven't joined them, it'll be very hard pressed for us
to survive without joining them.
And those of us that haven't joined them
will still only survive because the global has killed everybody.
So we're not on their side, but if you're
able to make the right moves and be prepared,
you might be able to survive and not join them.
But I think God isn't going to like that.
God doesn't like cowards, so I think it's just surviving.
We have to stop this thing from happening.
This is very weird.
Well, I mean, it seems strange for him
to say that God wouldn't like that,
considering the most popular Christian book
series ever written was about the small number of survivors
who made it through the evil apocalypse.
Yeah, that was globalist shit, though, man.
OK, well, that's fair.
Kirk Cameron's a globalist.
My bad.
Nope, I fucked it up.
Yeah, it's an interesting version
of Alex's fear narratives.
It's like, OK, so a kill-off event is about to happen very
soon.
Naturally.
Because the globalists are taking over
and the blah, blah, blah.
Any moment now.
So it's coming up almost immediately,
and you are probably going to die.
But if you make the right moves, there's
a way that you can survive.
Now, some of the right moves that are the wrong moves
are joining with the globalists.
Of course.
That's bad.
But you could survive if you did that.
Even though, why would you, since everybody you've ever
known and cared for is dead?
I don't know.
Fair enough.
But you cannot join the globalists and still
survive if you get really lucky and do all the right moves,
but God will be mad.
But then you're going to hell.
God's going to be mad.
So you can die in the apocalypse,
or you can survive it for a little while with no one
you've ever met.
But either way, you're going to hell.
But I guess that this implies that there
is a fourth, fifth option, and that
is fighting to stop this.
Somehow stopping it, yeah.
But it doesn't matter.
The globalists have a plan B. Alex
has already explained that.
Yeah, it doesn't seem to be a good fight at this point.
No, this is really dumb.
So I think that there are jobs in the world that have
more staying power for people.
Careers.
Sure, if you're in a career that takes a long time to master,
let's say, maybe there's a lower turnover
than some unskilled professions maybe
have higher turnover rates.
Comedian, high turnover rate.
Quite.
Very high turnover rate.
Although it should be higher.
Much, much higher.
What do you think about the high ranking globalists?
What's their turnover rate?
Yeah, what do you think about that?
Oh my god.
It has to be, here's what I think.
I think it's got to be like the Politburo level of like.
It's got to be zero.
Backstabbing, no, no, no.
Backstabbing murder all the time.
You're wrong.
And I can tell you the globalists have major turnover
with their higher level people.
Because they really understand, even once they have all
the money and the power, that it's empty.
And if they haven't totally turned their souls over.
They get to keep all the money and power?
They then turn against it.
But then those people don't have a voice.
They get shut down or they get killed.
Oh, OK.
That's convenient.
So the globalists and the high ranking levels,
they constantly have crises.
Right, they have crises of conscience
and realize, nah, fuck this noise.
Alex is right.
So they quit, but then they get killed.
So what are you going to do?
Hey, it's as everybody knows from watching our government
function, obviously the people who run the world
have consciences that they've been to at all times.
I don't know if I can think of any examples of anybody
that Alex has ever discussed who was a high ranking globalist,
who turned on the globalists, and then got killed.
Although, again, it's a fun story.
It is a fun story.
And it does explain why there aren't
defectors of the globalists.
Sure, sure, they're dead.
Except for, I guess, Leo Zagami, which maybe he should be dead.
Right.
If this makes sense.
I don't know, Mike Lindell got rich and powerful.
So he's probably turned against the globalists.
I bet he was a high ranking globalist for a while.
He had to have been, right?
I don't know.
Otherwise you can't get money and power.
His point is you can only get money and power
if you join with the globalists.
Or I guess if you sell supplements.
Or pillows.
Yeah.
I don't think Mike Lindell's with the globalists.
I doubt it.
No.
Also, the topic of Alex's employee
who got arrested at the Capitol does come back up a little bit.
OK.
My pillow storyline is not brought back up.
No longer brought up.
It might still be there, but it's not front and center.
So here's the thing.
These globalists who have high turnover rates
and then end up having to kill the former employees,
they're only going to kill you if certain conditions are met.
That's nice.
If you've ever worked for the New World Order
and never signed the contracts with them
and ever actually run their operations,
then they will kill you if you sidestep them
or don't follow their orders or ever try to leave them.
But if you've never sold out to them, it's metaphysical rules.
They'll just try to get other people to kill you,
but they won't give the order themselves.
Or they will try to kill your name or discredit you
or put you in prison.
But they don't often kill you unless you've
been involved with them and made some deal with them
at some level.
And that's why I've never made any deals with these guys.
That's a protective instinct on his part.
I.
Yep.
So yeah, you've got to make deals
or else there's going to be some kind
of an infringing of metaphysical rules that sound really dumb.
I have a lot of problems with this.
Yeah.
If the metaphysical rules that govern the universe
are so dumb that you can ethically sidestep
murder by convincing somebody else to kill somebody,
and then you have a totally clean slate,
I don't think that these rules are good.
I think that they're ungrounded.
Give me a second.
Are you telling me that Mark Richards
is innocent of all crimes according
to the metaphysical rules of the universe?
I think there might be a flaw in this metaphysical rule.
You bet.
Yeah, I think there could be.
Yep.
I don't know what I feel about this other than any time
he brings up these metaphysical rule ideas, I just,
I want to know more.
I want him to actually get into the ethical underpinnings
of this and really break down what must be
true within this ethical system.
Oh no, if he were capable, the one thing
that I want from him is a full accounting
of his metaphysics beliefs.
It's just brought out whenever things are convenient.
Yeah, I want a book of him like codify,
I want Alex Jones' version of the Bible.
That's what I want.
I don't.
Oh wow, that's fair.
I definitely don't.
That's fair.
All caps.
So Alex has all these ideas about how
the news about human-animal hybrids and stuff,
it's not what they're saying.
Of course not.
It's not that there were human stem cells and embryos.
No, fish people.
No, no, no, no.
Fish people in the oceans.
Technology is 50 years ahead of where it actually
is, all this stuff.
And you know what?
You know who thinks they know what's up but don't?
The globalists?
Fucking military intelligence.
Oh, those idiots.
People talk about army intelligence
or the military intelligence.
They don't know any of this.
That's an oxymoron, am I right?
This cute stuff at the highest level
is military intelligence.
That's totally compartmentalized to archaic weapons.
Atomic weapons are 120 years old.
They had all the equations 120 plus years ago.
That's all tinker toy stuff.
That's all that's being phased out.
They're getting rid of the human military.
By 2030, there really won't be very many humans
left in the military.
And they have all these Hollywood movies
about super soldiers, these really cool bad ass guys.
And you know, like the new movie, Nobody.
You know, he's so tough.
None of that exists.
It's all gone.
It's all over.
It's all robots.
It's all clones.
It's all robots and clones in the future.
Fun.
All right.
So I guess you saw Bob Oden, Kirk, and nobody.
Yeah.
So that's nice.
It's a good movie.
I bet it is.
I think Bob Oden, Kirk has a lot of range that's been unexplored.
And I'm excited for him.
He's incredibly great.
I think, you know, it's kind of an interesting dilemma.
Because you do see the possibility of a future
where a lot of warfare is done by way of robots.
Sure, of course.
You know, drones certainly are a big problem.
Yeah, we're already there to a smaller extent.
But if things escalate towards the point
where actual troops are robots, then eventually you're
going to get to a point where a negotiation between countries
that is robots fighting robots is really
just a financial thing.
It's like, I'm destroying more of your property,
which is robots.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, it's.
And then it almost has a potential to be like, well,
we could negotiate through this easier than fighting.
So I don't know.
I haven't fully thought it through.
But it's an interesting thing.
It almost seems like it would lead to a vast reduction
in war.
Well, I mean, I think there have been
a lot of really interesting, because that's something
that I've read about.
That's one of those things that futurists
have been describing since Kurt Vonnegut,
like that kind of stuff.
And there's a lot of people who are like,
war doesn't mean anything if there aren't people dying.
So you can't really do it.
You know, it would be like a video game at that point.
It's just like, are you better at video games?
I have 100 more robots than you, so mathematically I
win before we even fight.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess it doesn't relate to robot drones and stuff
like bombing apartment buildings or something.
Exactly.
It doesn't relate to that, my thought.
There's still a devastating human toll
associated with that.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know about the clones part.
What would clones be doing in this scenario?
I don't know.
Have you seen the prequels, the Star Wars prequels?
I mean, yeah, but ultimately clones are not as good in war.
You know, if you're going to build.
Seems like a massive investment if you're
going to use them for warfare.
No, it's like, look, but here's the thing.
If you're building robots, you know,
we're not thinking about AT-ATs, because those are stupid.
They're giant lumbering moron machines.
I have bad news.
I am thinking about AT-ATs.
Small, small, quick mobility, all of these things.
Human beings don't stand a chance against those.
Those terrifying things you see videos of every now and again.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yep.
So Alex has some complaints about the pope.
Sure.
Pope Francis, those full communists
are sharing prosperity is not communism,
but pure Christianity.
But they're going to direct how you share.
And of course, all the big bankers pay no tax,
but they'll lecture you all day.
No idea what the bankers have to do with the pope's opinions.
I mean, I guess they don't pay taxes at the Vatican either.
Also, I have great news for Alex.
What's that?
The pope was arrested a year ago.
He was.
According to Steve Pajetnik.
He's been gone for a while.
This is the fake pope that Alex is complaining about now.
Don't worry about what this pope is saying.
This is a puppet.
Francis is behind jail bars.
Naturally.
So Alex gets to talk in here a little bit
about the old COVID vaccines.
Sure.
And I think he says something that I
find flagrantly irresponsible.
You've got all these countries that
have stopped the Pfizer shot, all these companies that
have stopped the AstraZeneca, all these ones that
have stopped J&J. You've got all these deaths, not one death.
They'll go, one woman died.
You actually go look at the reporting system.
It's like 3,000 here, 2,000 there, 5,000 there.
They estimate between 1 in 10 and 1 in 100.
They're not sure.
It varies.
Country to country are actually reporting the deaths as COVID.
But it is COVID vaccine killing them.
This is a gigantic unsupported claim that Alex is making.
If he has some kind of evidence that the COVID vaccines are
responsible for a high number of deaths
that are being called COVID-19 deaths,
then he can't just assert it and wave
his hand to some vague unspecified statistics that
varies from country to country.
He knows that he can't back this claim up,
which is why even what he's saying
is a meaningless nonsense assertion.
The difference between 1 in 10 and 1 in 100 is huge.
That's an irresponsible spectrum to be pointing to.
It might be a little bit.
Anyway, I'm going to need to see the sources on this.
And until I do, I'm going to go out on a limb
and assume it's his dumb imagination, as usual.
It's either 10% or 1,000% more.
No idea which.
Could be anything, honestly.
So on our last episode, we got a meeting
of the minds between Alex and fresh, hot on the scene
comedian Norm Paddis, lawyer.
He's finally breaking out of this law game
to pursue his real passion of stand-up comedy.
He's not even going to be able to be the funniest lawyer,
because every comedy scene already has that.
We've already got a funniest lawyer in Chicago, at least.
So not to be outdone by the shit-headery of Norm
coming on, Alex's other lawyer buddy, Barnes,
is going to be on this episode.
Oh, yeah.
You can't have Paddis on without Barnes being like,
you got to book me soon.
Yeah, so he's got to come on.
And this is where Alex teases that they're
going to talk about how the Chauvin trial is nonsense.
No.
Coming up today, Robert Barnes is
going to be looking at the insane Chauvin trial
up in Minnesota.
And when he thinks that's going to end, and no doubt,
every major city is going to be lit up like a Christmas tree.
And they're not the type you put cookies and milk out
for Santa for.
It's going to be lit up with fire.
And why are the communists doing this?
It's part of the takeover of the police.
They're not getting rid of the police.
They are bullying them using any bad event that happens.
Oh, my god, we've had three days of riots.
And a guy, an armed robbery suspect for robbing a woman,
waving guns around everywhere, is then attacking the police.
And in the melee, the cop pulls the wrong weapon
and shoots him.
What do you think happens when you go into riots
and high-speed car chases?
But now, you see, we've got to have more riots for that trial.
We've got to have more.
It just goes on and on.
But if you're a good globalist police department,
if you do everything the New World Order says
and arrest their political enemies,
become commissars under strong cities initiative
that Obama launched, directly directed by the UN,
well, then you're in like Flynn.
So that's coming up.
Separately, ladies and gentlemen, where is it?
Here it is.
This is your last three-day chance
to get the really highest quality liquid multivitamin
mineral system with amino acids as well.
There's going to be riots and fires all over the city.
Got it.
Add pivot.
Yep.
Fun.
You know, you work people up about, hey,
this ain't the fun Christmas tree with cookies and milk.
And separately, let me get these vitamins.
Hey, listen, don't turn around, Dan.
Der Kommisar is in town.
Uh-oh.
Yeah, we're in trouble.
So Alex has a story that he hits on a number of times
throughout the show, and that is that Maxine Waters apparently
told Jim Jordan to shut his mouth
seated in the chambers.
It's a very un-congressional language.
I would have preferred she beat the shit out of him
with a cane, because we've got one.
There is a precedent to that happening, I guess.
OK, I think there's an even, look, we've got one.
You get to beat an anti-abolitionist
to borderline to death in Congress.
That's the rule.
I think Alex might have the wrong angle on this.
Uh-oh.
Let me do this.
I want to get into this Jim Jordan thing,
and Maxine Waters telling him shut up.
In fact, let's go to the end first.
Let's go to her telling him to shut up.
And imagine if a white guy was telling a black lady shut up.
That's like half of Alex's show.
Yeah, I was going to say, you are always
telling black women to shut up.
It's the most important thing to you.
Yeah, any time there's some kind of social justice-related
activism, it tells people to shut up.
Just shut up, yeah, yeah, just shut up.
Can you imagine if there was some sort of football
player who was blackballed from the league for speaking out
very obvious truths that seem so obvious that no one should
be even borderline punished for them?
Imagine if a white guy told that guy to shut up.
People would be furious.
We're going to get some flagrantly racist stuff
about Kaepernick a little bit later.
Of course we are.
Why wouldn't we?
It's funny you should bring him up as an example.
While we're here.
So back to COVID matters.
Here's Alex saying some dumb shit.
And even a year ago, they admitted 94% of COVID deaths
were something else.
It's the same thing in England.
It's the same scam everywhere, because it was never
really COVID, folks.
It was pneumonia or the flu.
So in 6%, it was an actual virus.
In 94%, it was heart attack or cancer.
But the hospitals coded as COVID to get the $53,000.
So this is just Alex misrepresenting
how there was a figure that came out where it was like 6%
of COVID-19 deaths didn't involve a person who
had an underlying condition that might
have contributed to the death.
Sure, sure, sure.
Considering that things like obesity or smoking
could be underlying conditions, this isn't surprising.
Alex and his ilk have just used that stat incorrectly
for a year to argue that the death numbers are artificial.
Right.
Now, I was thinking about this.
And that idea that the hospitals are in on a get-rich-quick
scheme because there's a certain amount that they get paid out
by Medicare, Medicaid, based on COVID-19 patients.
Yeah, that tremendously stupid idea about that, yeah.
I was just thinking about it, and does Alex
think that those hospitals don't get payments
for other conditions?
Does he think that someone getting,
like if they have an aggressive cancer that they need
treatment, does he think that these programs don't also
pay out?
What you're not understanding, and I
don't know if you've been to a hospital in a while,
they pay everything on a flat $100 fee.
So if you've got cancer, you're taking all kinds of stuff
and they pay $100 for it.
It's been a while since I've been to a hospital,
and admittedly, I don't have cancer.
They switched it.
It's super weird, but it's $100 for everything but COVID.
Yeah, it's one of these days I'm actually
going to sit down and try and figure out
like what other payouts are.
Yeah, yeah.
So you're like, all right, here we go.
Let's do this.
But that may be needed for another day,
because today we're going to get in to Operation Cyber Polygon.
Ooh, now you're excited.
I'm also lying.
He doesn't bring it up at all.
God damn it, Dan!
You son of a bitch.
No, no, Alex doesn't bring up.
You always have to then, like when you're excited
and you get a letdown, you have to just pass it on to me.
Yeah, it is a little bit mean of me,
and maybe I just want you to feel that disappointment.
Yeah, no, no, no.
We got to share in it.
We're a team.
We're partners.
We got to share in that disappointment.
So instead of getting into that, Alex just
complains about things he imagined
that Anthony Fauci said.
Sure.
You can play the clips.
Once you're vaccinated, you can go out and not wear a mask
and go to restaurants.
That's Fauci.
That's what they all said worldwide.
Oh, sorry, doesn't work, because they've
had you under their control for a year.
They've doubled their wealth.
They're taking over.
They're not going to stop.
They're bad people.
So this is mostly about defending
Tucker Carlson about attacks that
have been made against him for his segment
that he had where he was talking about like, hey,
I was told that we could go back to normal
once people were vaccinated.
Oh, OK.
I thought he was talking about the white replacement one.
No, no, no, no.
We've moved on from that?
You can just get white replacement for like a week.
He lets Harrison Smith defend that.
That's fair.
So I think people might have gotten the sense that things
would immediately return to normal
after a vaccine was released, but that's not
what was being said by experts, including Dr. Fauci.
This is a straw man position that the right wing media
types like Alex and Tucker have been using recently
to argue against vaccination while pretending
that they have some kind of a principled point.
It's basically a child whining that their parent promised
to buy them a pony if they got good grades when
the parents said no such thing.
Yeah.
In December 2020, Fauci said, quote,
let's say we get 75%, 80% of the population vaccinated.
If we do that, if we do it efficiently
through the second quarter of 2021,
by the time we get to the end of the summer, i.e.
the third quarter, we may actually
have enough herd immunity protecting our society
that when we get to the end of 2021,
we can approach very much some degree of normality
that is close to where we were before.
So that's what he was saying at the end of 2020.
No, at every point in time, they've
said even after you've been vaccinated,
continue to wear a mask, not least of which
to stop the spread, but also just to make it fine for people
to wear masks outside.
In September, Fauci told Healthline, quote,
we can be greatly helped by vaccines,
but it's not vaccine alone.
Let's assume that we get a reasonably effective vaccine,
not measles vaccine where you have a 98% effective.
I think that would be too much to ask for.
But let's talk about 75%, 80% effective vaccine, which
would be really good if we did that.
If we did that and we ultimately got
everyone who should be and could be vaccinated,
I would think that together with not necessarily abruptly ending
measures like masks and physical distancing,
if we could get the majority of the community
to adopt those health measures together
with a reasonably effective vaccine,
then we could get the level of infection
down so low in the community that by the third quarter
end of 2021, we could start thinking in terms of normal.
Alex and his idiot friends don't live in reality.
They've fabricated a fake one that adheres to the storylines
that they want to tell and that they profit off of.
Alex's story about the vaccine is
that the globalists are trying to force it on everyone.
So it's essential for that story to involve an explicit promise
from the villains of the story that if everything will go back
to normal just as soon as you take my evil vaccine.
That's not the actual messaging that people like Fauci
have been engaging in, but it's how it feels to Alex
because that's the story that he tells for a living.
You can see by the false portrayals.
Yeah.
Silly.
What a dick.
Yeah.
So I think it's important to recognize a few things.
One of them is that I'm willing to address and talk
about like factual issues like, you know,
cyber polygon if you were to bring it up.
Or these other big operational lockstep nonsense.
SPARS.
SPARS, sure.
That was recent.
Yeah.
I'm very happy to engage in those things.
But I will also say that anybody who
wants to take Alex Jones as someone who
is a good purveyor of information
will also have to explain this kind of thing.
And I know God's real.
I'm going to leave it at that.
I have always had a connection to God.
I was born again when I was probably about eight,
nine years old.
But I have been having experiences now
that I'm going to keep private.
But I'm going to tell you are biblical.
You hear about the Holy Ghost, the Comforter,
and all the rest of that.
I am now routinely having experiences
that now I would be pleased to be crucified upside down
or tortured for five years for this.
OK, I mean, I can just flip a switch in my brain
now and go right to Valhalla.
And so I am transcending these Satanists.
And I am so thankful to God because I've
been in a lot of pain and really upset over them
and really taking on and getting very depressed.
And I just prayed to God the last few months
to take the worry away.
And I'll fight harder than ever.
And I've done that.
And now I am really now experiencing the Holy Ghost.
And it is un, oh my, oh, it's so good.
Wow.
I mean, we're talking 50 times what I ever experienced.
Because I mean, you start crying getting near God
and close to the door.
But man, I've gone in the door now.
And I mean, I've, I'll tell you part of it.
I mean, man, I have these dreams now
that are just intense ecstasy.
And I'm in heaven.
And I, trying to describe the beauty of it
and the purity of it and the level of this
is just like you're in God's mind.
It's all good and well to have like religious beliefs
and stuff.
It's not normal to believe that you're
having visions of being in heaven when you dream.
Everyone, everyone, I am waking up having just been
sucked off by an angel.
Are you shitting me?
This is ecstasy.
I thought women were great.
This is lunatic level behavior.
The Archangel Michael visits me at night and gives me handies.
I've been in the God's mind.
It turns out all angels are gay, by the way.
I think that this is silly.
And I think this is stupid.
And anybody who wants to take Alex
as any kind of sincere good faith actor
in the sense of like the conversation about ideas,
let's talk about this being the way he sees himself.
But even that's kind of, you know, maybe a personal attack
and what have you.
Well, all I heard him say was, I am having good dreams lately.
Sure.
So that's also, that's nice.
But he puts so much more import on it than just someone saying,
I've had good dreams.
A little bit, a little bit.
And then the other thing about it
that I think is much more functional and grounded
is Alex says at the beginning that he was born again
at eight or nine when we know that he was a Satanist.
Yup.
To his teens.
When you were born again.
This timeline doesn't work.
When you were born again, at eight or nine,
had you already paid for the abortions
or would that come later?
Yeah.
Is this before or after the Satanists tried to lure you
and you were a functional Satanist until you were 18?
Listen, I was a Satanist for a while.
I was born again at eight or nine.
I was a Satanist.
Look, if you're not a Satanist when you're young,
you have no heart.
The problem with stories like this that are obviously
fucking artificial and not true and played up
for the presentation of this, the person
that Alex wants the people to see him as,
is you can't keep it straight.
It just doesn't make sense.
No.
This timeline is ridiculous.
So yeah, he was born again at eight
and then went to the devil for a little while
and then came back.
I don't know.
That's why all mythologies wound up in books,
because they were like, eh, I'm telling you,
I think Zeus did it this way.
And somebody else is like, nah, nah, nah, Zeus is crazy, man.
Yeah.
Eventually, you've got to put it in a book.
Otherwise, nobody's going to agree.
Oral tradition has a way of changing stories
a little bit over time, because of the different ways
the different tellers would tell stories.
You got it.
So this goes on.
Alex keeps talking like a deranged lunatic.
Well, we have different words.
Well, that's fair.
And it is just, I mean, last night, man,
I woke up really upset about 2 AM and everything.
I'm like really upset about the world and really upset.
And I said, I said, God, I'm going to pray.
I'm going to go back to sleep.
Please, please help me.
And man, it was just, it was just unbelievable.
There's no way to describe this.
And I've never seen any of this in art and literature,
because a lot of stuff I've seen,
I've seen in movies and culture.
Other humans have seen that archetype.
I'm seeing stuff that has never been seen on this planet.
And you can say, oh, your mind created that.
Well, then, wow, that's quite a mind.
But I'm telling the Satanists, you are missing out.
You have no idea what you're missing out on.
I just, it's unbelievable.
All right, I'm getting metaphysical.
I'm going to stop right there.
All I'm saying is I want to stay on air.
I need the temporal funds to do this.
And we spend a lot of money running this operation.
I pay the crew pretty good.
And I don't want to have to do a lot of things here.
I don't want to cut back.
I want to expand.
So go to mvollwarstor.com.
That's the end of his long rant about the God giving him
visions and stuff.
Satanists have no concept of what it's like.
So what I'm going to do is immediately
take the Lord's name in vain and ask for your temporal money.
I am going to tell you all about how great the Lord is.
And how I'm special and have visions inside God's eye.
And when I go to bed, when you go to bed,
you just maybe have a memory that you replay in your head.
No, I go to heaven.
Absolutely.
And in heaven.
And I need money.
And then I come back down and I break commandments left
and right because I'm so good.
It's great.
It's really great.
Also, I love the idea that he's seen things that
have never been seen on earth.
I want to know what those things are.
That's like a Lovecraftian description of something.
I enjoy that.
Art in literature does not contain these archetypes.
I get what you're saying, but also describe
what it looked like.
It does not belong in Euclidean geometry.
I imagine if he described what it looked like,
I could probably find some literature or art.
Yeah.
I think he saw an angle that looked acute,
but acted as if it was obtuse.
I looked at the standard model, and it turns out
there are more particles.
So Alex gets into talking about COVID
and how it's a globalist attack, right, of course.
Sure.
But one of the things I really appreciate about Alex
is that he's a man with good priorities.
And he knows what, like, if you're going down a track
and something more important comes up,
kind of got to go for it.
Italian lawmaker calls for the arrest of creepy Bill Gates
in charges of crimes against humanity.
And more and more scientists, more and more lawyers
are coming out and saying, that's
what this is, is a medical weaponized globalist takeover.
And the sooner we rake up the horror
and that our acquiescence to tyranny
encourage these monsters to launch this,
the sooner we're able to stop it.
That's coming up.
But Brian Stelter is one of the nastiest people on Earth.
And he's a liar.
What?
He's an anti-American.
He's a defamer.
He's somebody that goes around against people deplatformed,
like myself.
He literally stalked 20-plus advertisers
and ran them off by threatening to do pieces on them
and call them white supremacists.
He's a terrorist.
Sure.
Economic terrorist.
And what he is is a sack of garbage
who acts all powerful and manly.
He is America's enemy.
OK, all right.
Thought we were going to talk about COVID.
Turns out you're mad at Stelter.
I do appreciate that, of all people, Brian Stelter
is our big bad today.
You know, it's super weird to me that you
have such a hatred towards Conor Friedersdorf.
You complain about him so much less than Alex
does about Brian Stelter.
I haven't talked about Friedersdorf in a year.
That's what I'm saying.
I'm Frieders free, OK?
That's what I do.
Alex needs to take some cues from you and let it go.
Just let it go.
You don't need to read it.
You don't need to be so mad at Stelter.
Although, if you believe Alex, then his anger and hatred
at Stelter is actually paid some dividends.
If anything was ever an enemy of the country,
it's Brian Stelter.
And I can tell you, my rant from four years ago,
calling him enemy of the people, I didn't know this,
but a certain national talk show hosted others,
sent it around everybody, and Trump got it,
I recently learned, and that's where
enemy of the people came from.
So I am kind of the unofficial speech writer,
I guess, at some level for a lot of folks,
which I'm very honored to do.
OK.
So Trump took enemy of the people
from Alex when he was talking about the press.
Look, a phrase like that has never
before been uttered in literature
or in any kind of art.
No archetypes.
Nothing.
That is brand new, straight from Alex's mouth to Trump's ears.
I don't believe this, first of all.
But second of all, if true, not something necessarily
brag-worthy.
That's kind of a pretty bad thing.
No, I gave him a phrase.
So Alex is complaining here about some stuff.
Sure.
And mic down for this, because I actually
think that this is really hilarious.
This is one of the funnier things I've heard in a while.
I know the average man's watching baseball,
his buddy's eating pizza and drinking beer at a bar tonight.
And that sounds great to me, too, OK?
In fact, if we weren't in so much trouble,
I'd be buying season tickets to baseball and football
and the NBA.
I love it all.
I like basketball.
I like boxing.
I like the Olympics.
Man, I'd be happier than a pig in you know what if this wasn't.
But I can't do it, because the whole thing's
coming down on us.
So what I'm doing at night is reading the UN documents.
So here are the reasons I find this hilarious.
The first is that Alex constantly
pretends that he hates sports, because it's just
the media's way of pacifying men's instinct
towards conflict in battle.
I was going to say, that blew me away.
I was like, you hate sports.
He gives a speech about it every single Super Bowl Sunday.
Every one.
It's ridiculous.
The second thing that's really funny
is how long it took Alex to come up with UN documents.
What is it that I stay up late reading?
I am reading.
Fuck.
Finally, this is hilarious, because this entire show
is based on the idea that nothing is ever
going back to normal.
And yet here, Alex is decrying how the average man is watching
sports at a bar with their friends,
which Alex can't do because he's too busy with UN documents.
Should the average people he's mad
at not be able to go to a bar and watch sports
because of Fauci's dictatorship?
See, what it is is the government has you.
They've been keeping you inside for a year,
and they want to keep you inside for a year.
Now obviously, everybody's out and about tonight.
They have a great time.
Everybody's having a great old time.
This might sound kind of like nitpicking,
but it's really more something that I
want to use as a demonstration about how deeply
seated Alex's narcissism is.
His presentation of himself as a superior person
because he fights imaginary globalists
is more important to him than staying consistent
with his ideas that people can't do normal things like go
to bars with their friends anymore.
You see the priorities there.
Yeah, when anything gets in the way of Alex saying
he's exceptional, it is out of the way as soon as possible.
Alex will give up on any narrative
for telling you how great he is.
So Tucker Carlson is coming under fire
from Chelsea Clinton about these vaccine comments.
And Alex does the whole like, if you're vaccinated,
why should you care if I get vaccinated routine, which
is very dumb, but it works on folks.
So he's doing that.
He's going through this.
And then he remembers the George Carlin bit.
Oh, no.
And this is one of his suggestions.
Bring Pattison to deliver it.
Actually studies it's swimming in swamps
in the area you live in, and that means in sewage.
Is that what we think swamp is?
It's where the bears and the bees
and the buffalo and the deer and the bobcats and the fish.
That's the flora.
You basically, that's the inoculation is Mother Earth.
Don't swim in sewage.
This is not good advice.
All right.
This is not revolutionary.
You should not, instead of getting vaccinated,
it's not a good idea just to jump in.
So what you want to do, all right,
you get this little cocktail.
You put some Ebola in it.
You're immune to Ebola.
Makes sense.
I shouldn't expect much more from somebody who thinks
Mike Adams is a good doctor.
Yeah.
But yeah, don't jump into sewage tanks.
No.
It's not good for you.
And swamps are an ecosystem, not just a toilet.
Right.
There is that as well.
There's more than just the toilet of swamps.
Yeah, yeah.
Swamp thing wasn't poop thing.
Shit thing.
So this next clip is a little bit rough.
It's a little offensive.
Alex has found a clip from a protest.
And I don't really know what all the circumstances are in it.
But from what I can tell from the limited amount of context
that's in the clip, it appears that some organizer
at a protest took issue with some
of the behavior of one of the white participants
of the protest that was probably not
in line with what the people who were doing the protest wanted
to be how things were presented.
Look, there's a reason people teach you
how to protest at these things.
There's a way.
Yeah, and it can be disrespectful to the larger
point of the protest if people are working across purposes.
And that's what it seems like is going on in this video.
Alex takes this and gets wildly racist.
I don't hate white people because there's
some racist white people.
I don't hate black people because there's
some racist black people.
I judge people according to what they do, who they are.
That's common sense, like Martin Luther King said.
That's why America believed in what he said,
because it was true and brotherly love
that Christ talked about.
But I have dozens of videos just today
of whites being shot, stabbed, beat up because they're white,
told you're not welcome here because you're white.
And the hatred of these young black people's faces
is palpable.
But I notice most of the time, and I've
looked at some studies on this, they're not even Africans,
but where they're like 100% African.
Oh my god.
They're usually mulatto.
They're usually part white.
And now we learn, like Kaepernick and others,
their parents are white liberals and have basically
done this to them.
Like, why is it always white skinned black folks that
are being really anti-white?
There's some really black folks that are doing this.
That's because they have white parents.
They're either adopted or one of the parents
is white.
And the left has done this.
This is their communist revolution
hidden behind black people so they
can do this in claimants for black people's empowerment.
So that's pretty offensive just on the surface level.
And I don't feel like we need to break down exactly why that's
incredibly fucked up.
I mean, if you want me to just scream for about 15 straight
minutes, yeah.
I also think that if people who've been listening
to our show for a while, they'd recognize
this isn't necessarily an uncommon sentiment for Alex
to express, despite it being horrible.
I mean, it's, yeah.
You know, if this were the first time that we heard him say that,
well, go back and listen to the first times
that we've heard him say stuff like that.
Jordan started barking and dove out my window.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So the reason I pulled this clip is because the mentality
that Alex is espousing, that these people who he's
determined are not really black enough
are being used to push a communist agenda
to attack white people, is exactly,
and I mean exactly, the argument that his spiritual predecessors
like Gary Allen made when they opposed
the civil rights movement.
Yep.
Allen's book, Communist Revolution in the Streets,
lays out this mentality, and it's clear
that Alex subscribes to this explanation
of any kind of social justice-related activism.
That's not interesting on its own.
Alex is a dumb bigot, but what's fascinating
is how Alex isn't stupid enough to argue against the civil
rights movement, because he knows that he couldn't back up
that kind of claim, and it looks a little bit too transparently
bigoted through present-day eyes.
Yeah, that's what I was saying a week ago or whatever,
is like you can measure the same ideology being forced ever
so slowly to be like, fine, you won on civil rights.
Fine, we don't get slaves anymore.
Fine, I'm still going to say the same shit, though.
I'm going to do it.
The book, Communist Revolution in the Streets,
is mostly an attack on Martin Luther King Jr.
So forgive me if I think it's a little bit funny for Alex
to signal some imaginary support for King's ideas
while using the exact same playbook his heroes used
to attempt to discredit and demonize King himself
while he was alive.
This is bullshit, but it's important to recognize this.
When Alex has glimmers like that, there is severe racism,
but it's also these same ideas that
have been bubbling under these hard-right forces that
were in favor of segregation.
They were against the entirety of the civil rights movement.
Yeah, no, absolutely.
And it's that same mentality that still underpins Alex,
but he's smart enough to know that he
would be called some horrible, accurate names
if he argued like that.
But even then, it goes all the way back to fucking slavery.
It goes all the way back to being like, oh, well,
see, whenever you allow miscegenation,
the ones who are more white are more likely to cause it.
And it's just fucking, it's slavery.
It's the same shit.
Yeah, there's that sort of influence
and then this other influence that comes in.
Yeah, it's all just very, very shocking and horrible.
Anyway, that's, you know, who Alex is.
Yeah, yeah, he's shocking and horrible and a bigot.
It's not necessarily news, but it's
important to recognize these things when they're here.
Shocking, horrible bigot.
Yeah.
Also, he's been in God's mind.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Hey, I wonder if it's all white in God's mind.
I bet it is.
I think it might be, Dan.
So you might notice from watching Alex's show
that all of his guests are complete lunatics who
believe mostly the same things he does
and say, not only that, but Alex, hey, aren't you great?
And they like to flatter him, yeah.
Love to.
Love to flatter him.
That's how you win.
And you might think, like, why doesn't he
have other guests on the show?
For many reasons.
Well, I have a lot of great guests on the show.
We invite communists and globalists on.
They won't come on, but everybody we have on regularly
are smart.
But right up there at the top is Robert Barnes,
great lawyer.
Barnes, so smart.
Yeah, so commies and globalists have
been invited, but the RSVP comes back not attending.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, I believe that.
I don't know.
I've been saying good work Barnes very dismissively.
But now that I know Pat has tried stand up,
he might be the dumber lawyer at this point.
Yeah, it's neck and neck.
Yeah, that's tough.
Trying stand up comedy really lowers your.
You know what's interesting is I do
think that Alex does invite some people on.
I don't know when lately there's been
anybody who would be an interesting booking.
But you know, you have the people like David Rothschild
or like the weatherman.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The moment you ask me for a poll, it's gone.
I could have pulled it two seconds ago.
Yeah.
Bill.
Bill Ayers.
Yes.
Yeah, so there are those interviews that have happened
and like Alex comes out looking terrible.
Oh, yeah.
And so like, yeah, I guess maybe in the past
he would have put out more feelers for globalists
and commies in his definitions.
But they don't go well.
Those interviews are embarrassing.
No, and you can't do them now because if somebody comes in
and he starts getting religious, boy, it's going to get bad.
Yeah, imagine if you had David Rothschild on now
and Alex is just screaming about the fucking devil.
The real fucking devil.
I mean, Bill Ayers would be like, whoa,
and then just leave.
You're a Satanist.
You're the devil.
I am with God.
I've seen his mind.
Oh, click.
Wow.
Yeah, right.
OK.
So Barnes thinks that the Chauvin trial is a show trial.
Nice.
And he has a reason.
Oh, he's starting to stay.
Why are you saying this is such a fraud
and where do you see it going?
Two parts.
One is that Chauvin had agreed to plead
guilty to third degree murder before the trial.
And so that put him in jail potentially for 20 years.
And it was Bill Barr who blew it up.
And so if they were serious about getting an outcome that
could meet the facts, they already had that in the bag
and they chose not to.
So this is very much a Soviet style show trial
simply because they refused to do a reasonable plea deal.
And the trial is for public consumption almost entirely.
So Derek Chauvin had offered to plead guilty
to third degree murder and William Barr did reject that.
But the details of the situation aren't
being captured by super lawyer Robert Barnes.
One of the primary issues is that according to an ABC News
article Chauvin, quote, asked to serve his time
in a federal prison and wanted assurances
that he wouldn't face federal civil rights charges.
Because he was asking for federal guarantees,
the deal needed to be approved by the Department of Justice.
But Barr, quote, wanted to allow state prosecutors
to make their own decisions about how to proceed.
Seems like that state autonomy thing Alex and his buddies
yell about all the time being put into action.
Yeah.
And also Barr being like, I don't want to touch this.
You guys deal with it.
Also the fact that Chauvin was willing to plead
to third degree murder is probably not a great sign.
No, if you say he's willing to plead to third degree murder,
wouldn't you want to then defend the murder
charge instead of being like, the whole trial's
illegitimate.
Also the way that he's presenting
is it's a show trial because they didn't accept
what is a reasonable plea.
And that's your determination Barr.
You have determined that this is what
would be a reasonable plea.
That's not necessarily what the prosecution believes
or the state.
Yeah, justice doesn't exist unless it's equally applied.
So that's it.
So the real issue, though, is that this trial
is just happening because it's a demonstration
that the left wants to put on, that they
can do whatever they want.
Sure.
So let me ask this.
We've got a minute to break.
What is the left looking for?
Just rubber stamp what they want?
I think the left wants him hung.
The left wants him legally lynched.
And the left wants to show they can use and weaponize
the prosecutorial process to validate and vindicate
their media narratives to help push
a particular politicized agenda.
Sure, so like anybody they want burned, they can burn.
Exactly.
That's the point, to show this is what we can do.
Y'all need woke insurance.
We can do it any time we want, any place we want,
even to a police officer.
I think that there's other issues.
Like a guy died.
Well, there's that.
I don't think it's anyone, any time.
I think there's specific circumstances that are.
I would imagine that in this case,
committing a murder is probably more important for the left.
Well, I mean, look.
That he committed a murder, not we want to commit a murder.
They can burn anybody they want at any point, no big deal.
As long as you murder somebody, we can burn the shit out of you.
Anybody who murders, even cops.
As long as there's a body, they can just jam you up.
Just lie about how you murdered somebody, you know?
So, you know, we got on the right, we have a lot of groups,
people like the Oath Keepers, people like the Proud Boys,
certainly.
But Brian Stelter is a terrorist.
Definitely.
Yes.
But you have these groups, and there's
been pretty well-documented interaction between them
and law enforcement, some overlap even.
But Robert Barnes wants you to know that people like Antifa,
they are actually the Nazi brown shirts.
That sounds right.
They want to triangulate BLM Antifa and the FBI
and use the military on the people.
Don't they get that will cause an internal civil war
guaranteed?
Well, I mean, the real model they're looking at
is not so much the communist Soviet model,
but is the fascist model of the 1930s.
Sure.
They want to know the long knives.
They want to, yeah.
Yep, you have your paramilitary supporters
that are outside of the governmental structure that
can do things that you can't do that you can use
as a pretext and a predicate to do what you want to do.
You create false flags events, you stage events,
or you exaggerate events.
I mean, I mean, the amazing, the January 6 event
is basically being treated like the Reichstag fire.
So it's the same, except there was less violence and less
damage.
You know who the only person I've
heard call that the Reichstag fire?
Fucking Alex Jones.
Yeah, you would think.
Alex spent like a week talking about inaccurate information
about Hitler's rise to power and the Reichstag fire
and how it was the January 6th storming of the capital.
They were the same thing.
Now Barnes is trying to say that the left is doing that.
That's what the left does.
Fucking nonsense.
That's what we do, Dan.
So stupid.
That's what the left does.
I just, I have very little patience
for this direct pretending that that's not his entire strategy.
Yeah, you know, it is so fucked up
that they apply to us the characteristics that most
define their thought process and then describe that thought
process as disgusting.
So it's like, hey, if they did do what we were doing,
we would really hate them.
Because it's evil.
What they're doing that sounds like what we're doing
and how we think, we'd be pissed.
Totally.
If they did the things that we think.
Now let's interview Stuart Rhodes.
Let's go ahead and get the people who
decided to overthrow the capital.
So you know, there have been some unfortunate things
that I've seen popping up about the idea of like an America
First caucus.
Sure.
Certainly there's no historical precedent of this being shit.
Just call yourselves the Know Nothing Party
and never read history.
Just do it, fine.
It's a little much.
You want a bunch of white men running around rioting
and oppressing people.
You're the Know Nothings.
Let's go.
It's a little bit frustrating and scary.
And I hope that it fizzles.
That would be nice.
But Alex is on that tip.
He's on the vanguard of America First.
Sure.
He also knows nothing.
So is Robert Barnes.
Man, these are America First kind of guys.
That's what caused Russians in the early 60s to defect to us.
Because they saw Khrushchev acting like a maniac.
Our leaders are acting worse than Khrushchev right now.
By far.
By a long mile.
Putin looks completely reasonable compared to the way
Biden is behaving.
Putin's not changing his mind every other day.
He's cutting defense budgets.
As Navalny dies.
He's asking for Jay time.
Great.
Exactly.
Yeah, so they're getting into some pretty serious,
like, oh, Putin's the best.
As Navalny is literally starved to death
and his body is falling apart and shutting down in prison,
the main political rival of President Putin
is being murdered by President Putin as we speak.
To be fair, he's been consistent on that front.
He's really been consistent.
It's kind of a thing.
Yeah, America First.
But also Putin's much better than our leaders.
Putin's much better than our leaders in America First.
Yeah, America First.
And Alex, I would take this more seriously
and actually discuss some of the issues
around maybe international relations.
Sure, sure, sure.
But I don't feel like Alex's positions deserve the respect
of being taken seriously.
I mean, listen to this nonsense.
And by the way, I don't even respect a lot of generals
and a lot of top people.
Some I do, but at least they've been like in 20 tours
and combat and kill people.
It's all a bunch of weird Harvard women
want to have war with Putin because they're
going to show a man.
It doesn't even make sense.
It's insane.
It's like putting a woman in the ring with Mike Tyson in 1989.
It's kind of a silly way he's trying to format,
formulate this thing.
Or it's like, ah, yes, these women who have feminism
run amuck.
And that's why they're mad at Putin,
because he's too much of a man.
Yeah, I despise educated women leading a military.
What I want is bloodthirsty murderers
who went over to a different country on a lie
and killed people for no reason.
That's who should be running things, Dan.
Sure, sure.
And if Alex is going to insist on disseminating
this kind of an idea, and I found myself
having a very similar response to a lot of stuff.
And this episode's a little bit shorter,
because there's a lot of stuff that I was like, nope.
Yeah, yeah, that's a big nope.
And that's one of them.
That's a big nope.
It's like, nope.
And I was kind of expecting that we
were going to get into fucking cyber polygon.
I know.
It was never going to happen.
Yeah, it infuriates me.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Niall, why am I apologizing to you?
That's a good question.
Anyway, Alex has some more things to say.
Sure.
This is the last clip.
Him and Barnes are having a little discussion
about how great Russia is.
Sure.
And Putin.
Yeah.
Deeply nationalistic country, deeply proud of their country.
That's who Putin really is.
He's Russia's version of Trump.
That's why the deep state hates him.
And it's just insane.
We should be aligning with Russia on key foreign policy.
I agree.
And I feel the danger for my family.
And it pisses me off, Barnes, that we're literally having.
We're having some type of pissing contest
with these weird liberals.
Just Putin's Christian, and Russia's Christian now.
So they see it like the Midwest.
They want to blow it up.
This is all just essentially projecting identity politics
onto anybody who has a critique of Putin.
They hate him because he's Christian,
or it's just weird women who think he's too much of a man.
Yeah.
And yeah, it happens to be all of the identifying identity
signifiers that Alex has.
So he feels himself under attack when people criticize Putin.
And again, it's just like a rank level of narcissism.
It's not geopolitical analysis.
It's not meaningful in any way.
It's just he identifies, feels himself.
Yeah, I can't think of any reason
why people would be mad at what is functionally
the richest man in the world.
Yeah.
Even if you're just Alex and you're like,
hey, I don't believe in dynastic rulers.
Sure, yeah.
I'm into democracy.
I hate dictators.
And I definitely don't want anybody
to rule over a country for, let's say, more than two terms.
Yeah, it seems like he should have just
an elementary problem there.
But he doesn't.
Nope.
And I don't know.
I think that if you look at it realistically,
I think that what it mostly is is
Alex sees a lot of his identity mirrored in Putin.
Yeah.
A lot of those things that are the surface level,
I am a white male Christian.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I think that he sees a strong person there
that he lacks that as someone to follow.
Yeah, performative masculinity is
what he's really stoked about.
Yeah.
That's not to say that he's going
to become Putin's number one guy.
No, I doubt that.
It's just a continuation of these longstanding trends
that he's had.
It was pretty overt, though, just the love fest
of these America Firsters.
Yeah, it's hard to go back and see
the vehemence with which he despises Putin
and then get to the present day where
it's like, Putin's probably the best thing we've got,
second, of course, to our God King Trump.
Well, but he's Russia's Trump.
Well, yeah.
So I guess he's the God King there.
And I wish we had him God Kinging us America first.
Yep, it feels that way a little bit.
Stupid.
Yep.
Anyway, Jordan, this episode's a little bit shorter,
and I apologize.
But you know, it is what it is.
Yeah.
We'll be back.
Indeed.
For another episode in the near future.
That's the plan.
And we'll see where the wind blows us.
We may be back in the past.
Let's hope for Cyber Polygon.
Fingers crossed.
I've got it open on my screen right here.
I was going to say, you've got that locked and loaded for sure.
Anyway, we'll be back.
But until then, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yep, we're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledgefight.com.
I go to betjordan.
We're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook, and if you could,
please find a local charity or bail fund in your area
to help out people still protesting, still fighting.
Sure.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZXClark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I'm the Juiciest Ice Cube.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.