it's a downward slide. It's a downward slide is it? A couple of
greasy overgrown man-children. They have a podcast called
Knowledge Fight. Alex Jones's podcasting hecklers knowledge fight
calm. They're doing research you ever listen to the show
Knowledge Fight? Knowledge Fight? Oh, a couple of neck beards
indeed, they literally just make stuff up. They don't appreciate
literally just make stuff up.
They don't ever talk about
what Alex Jones actually talked about.
They don't actually say what he actually says.
They don't actually delve into his sources of information.
Mr. Friesen, Mr. Friesen.
I was live, you numbskulls.
They're in the league with some sort of cult leader
called Selene.
Knowledge Fight, mocking Infowars every single day.
It's really just incredible.
It's almost hard to comprehend.
Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes like Sir Raptor,
Donald T. Crouches, and talk a little bit
about Alex Jones and his sources.
Oh, indeed we are, Dan.
Shout out to DJ Dan Arkey.
Oh, of course.
Thank you so much for whipping up that.
Fourth or fifth absolute banger of a track.
We're gonna close the episode
with a little special DJ Dan Arkey track also.
So stay tuned for that at the end of the episode.
It's incredible.
But yeah, hey, what's up?
Oh, that's right, Dan.
Jordan.
What's your bright spot?
Why don't you go first?
I have a little thinking to do.
I will tell you, I had some stressful times
past couple of days, and then last night
my partner was like, I'm just vibrating
with fury and stress and all this stuff.
And she's like, you know what you should do?
You should take a bath.
So I took a downright ecstatic bath.
I absolute.
This makes me furious.
Incredible.
So what I did, I used a whole thing of bath salts.
That's twice as much as you're supposed to use.
Maybe, I mean, depends on the size of the bag.
Deep relaxation is what it was called.
I had that, I had the Cubs game on my computer.
I could watch that.
And I had my vape pen to my left hand.
It was the best.
Nice.
I'm happy for you.
Although this really, really sets me off
because I do feel like.
You don't own baths.
No, no, no.
That's not why.
Oh, okay.
I'm happy for you to enjoy a bath.
Okay, thank you.
But I do have visceral memories
of me telling you, yeah, baths are great.
And you judging me for it.
Of course I did.
And now your partner comes in and she's like,
hey, come on, why don't you take a bath?
We both haven't matured over the years.
Bullshit.
I've come more towards your direction on baths.
Yeah.
I guess, what's your bright spot, buddy?
What might my bright spot be?
I don't know, man.
I've, I don't know.
I guess not caring.
Is that kind of a bright spot?
I would say that's kind of a bright spot.
I don't give a shit.
Like, okay, here's what I would say, I guess,
in terms of a bright spot.
Hey, there's nothing left to lose.
There was a, you know, I had a lot of anxiety
about the prospect of Knowledge Fight getting noticed.
Sure, sure, sure.
Usually by Info Wars.
There's something that was kind of,
it was always in the back of my mind
as like being a little bit like,
oh, that's kind of scary.
And it doesn't matter if nothing happened.
Nope, nothing happened.
Nobody cares.
It's fantastic.
It's great.
Best case scenario, we got a new theme song out of it.
That's all we needed.
Yeah, so like some kind of like fear that I had
about the acknowledgement.
Sure, sure.
And granted, maybe I'll be killed
by an Info Warrior tomorrow.
Well.
At this point, you know,
there's been a couple of harassing emails
and they're all from the same email address.
I found the guy's address really easily, so.
So if you're listening, buddy.
Yeah, congrats.
Just do a little bit more security on,
don't send threatening emails
from your personal email account.
Try a proton mail account.
Yeah, yeah, something like that would be good.
Go for it.
Yeah, I mean, I'm not too worried about this nonsense.
It's great.
I think a lot of people are probably tuning in
and hoping to hear like sort of a deconstruction of that.
Naturally.
That's kind of, you know, that's kind of a big deal.
And I think they will be-
Everybody likes feuds, you know?
Sure.
Yeah.
I think they will be sorely disappointed.
Super.
I have no interest in really talking
about Harrison Smith's breakdown of-
Not at all.
And part of the reason is
because he wasn't critiquing our show.
He was critiquing an article that we didn't write.
Yeah.
I don't care.
No, I don't give a shit.
Give a shit.
Yeah.
So anyway, I figured the only thing we can do
is move ahead and do the stuff that we do.
And that is, we're going to be talking
about April 20th and 21st, 2021, Blackjack.
Oh, wow.
Man, now you see, you were doing updated 2021.
I almost did.
You almost did.
You can't surprise me with a bit change mid-bit.
I surprised myself.
Yeah, so we're just going to do business as usual.
We're going to be talking about-
And I was going to, my birthday is this weekend.
It is.
And so one of the things that I was going to do
is I was going to treat myself to going back to 2003.
Mm-hmm.
But I just felt like, you know,
we've got the issue with the Chauvin trial.
Sure.
And I think that it probably is more important
that we go ahead and talk about that.
Yeah, yeah.
And take care of some of this present day business.
Not a bad business.
And what better present I could give myself
than to do some work?
As usual.
So Jordan, we're going to get into business on this,
but before we do, you take a little moment to say,
hey-o, what's up to some new wands?
That's a great idea.
So first, Paul Joseph Watson's laminated map of solitude.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Hey-o, Paul Joseph Watson's, et cetera.
Rude.
Next, Bigsby Smalls should point out that's a dog.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Hey-o, Bigsby Smalls.
Next, Rachel.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Hey-o, Rachel.
Every time you shake your head, it gives me hope.
Like I'm fed by it.
I'm growing stronger when you shake your head.
Next, this one's actually possible.
There's two possible names, so you
could choose which one you prefer at the end of it.
OK, all right.
First is The Most Delicious Hamburger in the Galaxy.
And the second is Simon's Disappointed Dad.
First or second?
I'm going to have to go with second, just
for non-personal reasons.
All right, Simon's Disappointed Dad, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Hey-o, Simon's Disappointed Dad.
I gave you eyebrow raise that time.
I know, it might be the last time.
Next, it's pronounced A-T-A-T, not At-At.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Hey-o, Mr. At-At Imperial Walker.
That was straight at you, Jordan.
Yes, it was.
And I'd like to give a little technocrat shout out
to a couple of folks out there.
Tom and Kelsey, thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat, or two technocrats in a pod.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate, that's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right, we got to go full tilt boogie on this Watson,
all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why are you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much, Tom and Kelsey.
Yes.
Two peas in a pod-lacy wonk.
I would call them a dick-tick in the porse.
Policy wonk force?
No, lost it.
Lost it.
OK.
I was trying.
So hey, this weekend, not only my birthday
coming up, very excited about that.
But also, I should tell you that coming to theaters and VOD,
the Mortal Kombat, we're sponsored by Mortal Kombat.
We are not sponsored by Mortal Kombat.
Please no.
Jordan, Shang Tsung got in touch with me.
He sent you an email from shangtsung at gmail.com.
It's a real threatening email.
All this publicity you've been getting.
You will take your soul.
All this publicity you've been getting,
you guys got to promote the movie.
No, also this weekend, though, very exciting.
Yes.
Now, I want to call myself out on this just right off the top.
Of course, naturally.
I made an incomplete note about what kind of shout-out this is.
So on the 24th, this Saturday, this is Shan and Jay, right?
They either have an anniversary or they're getting married.
Or.
So that could be your 0th anniversary.
Or they're going to a dog marriage.
No, no, no.
It's one of the two.
It's either their wedding is this Saturday
or it's their anniversary.
I think it's their wedding.
All right.
If this is your anniversary, cut this out, play it next year.
If it's your wedding, cut it out and play it
at your goddamn wedding.
Congratulations, either way.
Yes, yes.
And thank you for helping me remind myself.
I've got to write more specific notes.
Jeez.
I like the idea that you, like when
you said I wrote an incomplete note,
I had this mental picture of like that Civil War note
where the guy is being murdered.
It's like, ah, right at the end.
That's what I was looking for.
So Jordan, today, like I said, 20th and 21st of April.
Sure.
But before we get into today's episode,
we have a out of context drop.
And it comes in the form of the game show
that is taking over the country.
OK.
And that is, who is Alex going to tell to burn in hell?
Is that taking over the country?
We've done it a couple of times.
Can I get three, can I get R, S, T, L, N, and E?
None.
OK.
None of those.
OK, fine.
I was going to try.
Yeah.
You're going for Wheel of Fortune shit?
I was going for Wheel of Fortune shit.
None of those letters.
OK.
Do you have a guess?
None of those letters?
No.
Burn in hell, CIA.
Burn in hell.
Damn it.
How was I supposed to know that it was those letters?
Well, it wasn't any of the ones you said.
It wasn't any of the ones I said.
So he wants the CIA to burn in hell.
Man, I am bad at Wheel of Fortune.
So Alex gets to talk in here.
We're going to start on the 20th.
And this is a day where, of course, in the afternoon,
the Derek Chauvin trial's verdict comes out.
But there's a good bit of anticipation surrounding that.
People were kind of aware that closing arguments had been done
and the jurors had been deliberating.
And Maxine Waters had come out and made some comments
that Alex isn't happy about.
Oh, of course not.
This will take up quite a bit of the show.
Yeah.
And then Alex.
But he doesn't have a problem with black women speaking.
Not at all.
No, no, no, no.
Not a pattern.
It doesn't matter in the scheme of things about George Floyd
or about Chauvin.
They're both humans.
They both have red blood.
God made them both.
I mean, they matter to God.
But to the globalist, they don't matter.
They're just pawns in this game.
I guarantee you George Floyd didn't
want to get addicted to methamphetamine
and to fentanyl.
And I guarantee you the cop that turned out was friends with him
and worked at the same club with him didn't want to kill him.
But they're humans.
And so we're flawed and things go wrong and bad things happen.
But now the media can sit there and divide and conquer us
and control us.
Turns out they've gone to the former home.
I'll cover next segment.
Guys got my article out there in the printer.
Thanks.
Of one of the defense witnesses.
Went to his home, hadn't lived there in two years,
threw a dead pig head on his property,
on the former property, and spread blood all over it.
We'll show you all that coming up next segment.
There's some of it right there.
Barry Brode's former residence.
And they went to the other jurors' homes
because CBS doxed them yesterday.
CBS said, here's who they are, so you can go harass them.
The Maxine Waters commentary is going
to be a major part of this, but where Alex begins
is this pig's head and the idea of CBS doxing folks.
So I've seen that story reported in other outlets than Infowars.
I'm going to go ahead and assume that this act of vandalism
towards the defense witness's former home
did happen more or less at the same time.
Although Alex does still seem to be embellishing it a tiny bit.
Like, blood all over.
Yeah, well, come on.
It's a better story.
To be clear, I am against this kind of thing,
and I feel like it's counterproductive
to the ability of trials to proceed.
According to an NBC News article,
the people responsible are being sought and are, quote,
accused of felony vandalism.
So there's a decent chance someone's
going to get in trouble for that.
That being said, I would be remiss
if I just let Alex play this game of fake outrage.
In November 2012, the NBC News article
showed that in 2020, Roger Stone was on trial.
And in case you don't remember, Alex
spent a couple of days on his show
trying to dox potential jurors in that case.
Alex didn't even know for sure that the person
he was naming on his show was actually even a potential juror
in Roger's case, but he was still going to go ahead
and put a target on them.
And so nobody else will release it.
That appears to be who it is with about 99% probability.
Oh, hey, it just appears to be who this person is.
Right, right.
I still really feel like once you have put out a bounty
on somebody, you don't get to be like,
and now they're mistreating the jurors.
You don't get to do that.
After you do this whole big thing where it's like,
this is the name of Roger Stone.
Exactly, yeah.
No, you lose.
You lose forever.
Goodbye.
Naturally, Alex felt a little bit insecure
about his actions because it's a very clear attempt
at jury tampering.
So he even addressed that on his show on November 6.
Keep in mind that Roger wouldn't be found guilty
until November 15.
This trial was still ongoing.
And then Media Matters goes, Jones
should get arrested for jury tampering and harassing jurors.
It's completely legal and lawful when someone's a public figure.
What if Brad Pitt was on the jury?
What if Obama was on the jury?
What if it was Robert Mueller?
What if?
What if it was Hillary Clinton?
What if it was Chelsea Clinton?
Oh, she got called.
Oh, she's on it.
Oh, Chelsea Clinton's going to sit
on the jury for Roger Stone.
You'd say, that's crazy.
Get her off.
It's the same thing.
It's one of their minions.
And we've got her name.
And we're going to release it.
Oh, boy.
Because that's what the press does.
I know there's a war on the press.
It's an interesting strategy to claim this juror that Alex was
talking about as a public figure on the level of Brad Pitt
or Hillary Clinton.
But that was just desperation talking
because he knew that Roger was guilty as shit.
Oh, she had a lot of hits in the late 90s.
She was really killing it.
She got her big break with Thelma and Louisa.
It's so convenient whenever you can just redefine public figure
to be suspected minion of my imaginary enemy.
Anyone that I despise.
If the people who threw a pig's head at that house
had thrown it at the house of a juror,
or if one of the jurors on the Chauvin trial
was being targeted, then I wouldn't
be OK with that at all.
That would fall into the same kind of category
as Alex's behavior.
But what did happen is a little bit of a gray area.
And again, I'm still against it.
But the person whose former house
it was was a witness for the defense who'd
already given their testimony.
You could argue that it was a retaliatory vandalism.
And I suspect that's why it's being considered a felony.
But I do think that that's different than trying
to intimidate jurors, which is what Alex was very publicly
doing like six months ago.
Yes, very much so.
CBS also didn't dox anyone.
The local Minnesota affiliate published an article
that discusses the jurors, broadly speaking,
just vaguely in details like their age and information
about their perspectives.
CBS, damn them.
This is not the same thing as what Alex did.
If Alex can show actual instances of people showing up
at the jurors' homes, he should do that.
But I can't find instances or any evidence
of that being a real thing.
I suspect he's just taking that defense witness story
and then making up another story on top of it
because it's more fun.
I'm a huge fan of people who have really taken to heart
all of the historical lessons about intimidating witnesses
being a thing that puts you on the side of good.
I think that's really, you know, history judges people
for intimidating witnesses very positively.
That's kind of history's thing.
So Roger, when he was on trial, Alex did this whole thing,
this whole nonsensical display on his show.
Yeah.
Interestingly, he doesn't bring this up
when talking about the efforts that some people have made
to intimidate jurors.
That is surprising.
Instead, on his show here on April 20th,
he's just talking about how, like,
when he's been in trial situations-
Sure, sure.
The globalists have tried, or the, I'm sorry,
the media has tried to intimidate these journalists.
The evil CBS media.
I've been involved in jury trials.
I've been involved in situations we later learned
where the media got involved in contact to the jurors
and said, if you don't do the right thing,
we're gonna dox your ass.
That's how corrupt the corporate media is.
They're not media, they're terrorists.
They're the enemies of this country.
So I guess Alex thinks he's a terrorist.
Yep.
I think Alex should think he's a terrorist.
It's interesting.
So, like I said, one of the big things
that goes throughout this episode
is critiques of Maxine Waters-
Sure.
Having some public statements about the Chauvin trial.
And Alex is kind of mad.
He's kind of mad that she grandstands on issues like this,
but won't take on some of the bigger issues
that Alex cares about. No, no, no, no.
And Maxine Waters said,
well, that's what civil rights looks like.
But she doesn't say a word about
three million Muslims in death camps,
a million Christians in death camps,
a million Buddhists in death camps.
Uh.
No, no, no, no, no.
She'll pick one of the 14 black men killed each year
in a wrongful situation out of 350 million people.
And she'll make a huge deal about that all day
and act like that's all the world's problems
to distract from the fact that she's a monster
that sold out to China 30 years ago
and deindustrialized this country.
And that she promotes planned parenthood
that was established to kill black people.
Can you imagine if I set up a group
that's mission was to quote, kill black weeds,
kill black sub-humans.
That's who she works with.
That's who she really funds.
Isn't the Republican party exactly that?
I see what they've done to black people
and everybody else for that matter.
They just started on them.
So they're farther down than us.
You think I feel strong as a human watching them
brainwash me?
Strong as a human watching them brainwash, dumb down,
drugged out, dying, killing each other.
It makes me feel like a sack of garbage.
But to people like her and the Democrats and Joe Biden
that passed the laws to,
if a black guy gets busted with drugs,
he gets three times the sentence of a white person
to those real elitist,
cause they're beyond racist, they're elitist.
Is that beyond racist?
They see us as animals.
They see us weak and falling apart
and dying and going bankrupt.
They see that and it makes them feel big inside.
Makes them feel strong.
Cause the truth is they're falling and they're ugly
and they're stupid and they're bad.
These globalists, they're black, they're white,
they're Christian, they're Catholic, they're Jewish,
they're Muslim, they're Chicom, they're everything.
I thought they were Satanists.
They're from all our groups,
but they're of their father, the dirty,
lion, stinking, loser ass devil.
There it was, my bad, I spoke too soon.
My bad, my bad.
That's a loser.
He's a loser.
I take it back, my bad, that's on me.
He's a loser, the devil.
Yeah, come on, man.
I know, I should've, I should've known
he was gonna pull it home.
Yeah, I mean like, I do appreciate how,
you know, conversations about issues
like the carceral state or China end up becoming rants
about how they're all from the devil.
They're all children of the devil.
The literal Christian devil.
Who I should point out is a loser.
Yes.
That loser ass devil.
I thought he was doing great so far, to be honest.
Also, incidentally, Maxine Waters has spoken out
consistently about the human rights abuses in China.
On September 30th, 2020, she spoke on the House floor
in support of the Uyghur Forced Labor Disclosure Act of 2020
saying, quote, the government of the People's Republic
of China falsely refers to these concentration camps
as vocational camps or reeducation camps.
Make no mistake, the truth is that today in 2020,
one million human beings are being held
in concentration camps where they're beaten, starved,
and forced to work long hours in conditions
that can only be described as inhumane.
And we haven't even gotten to America yet.
Their relatives often have no idea where they are
or whether they are alive.
They're dying each day due to the cruelty
of their living conditions and the brutality
of the Chinese government,
which executes them with impunity.
Incidentally, that bill had five co-sponsors,
all of them Democrats.
Some of the notable Alex-friendly folks in the House
who voted nay on that include Louie Gohmert,
Paul Gosar, Jim Jordan, Devin Nunes, and Steve Scalise.
That makes sense.
Alex is making up that people like Maxine Waters
don't ever deal with the issues
that he wants them to deal with
because that makes it easier for him to trivialize things
like the George Floyd killing.
The reality is, however,
that Alex is just making up everything he says.
He has no idea if Maxine Waters has spoken out publicly
against the Chinese human rights abuses,
but the idea that she hasn't is the only option
that fits into how his content is supposed to feel.
Totally.
Because that feeling is more important
than accurate reporting.
That feeling is reported as fact,
and this is just bad work.
This is how he operates.
It is the most infuriating part
of the right-wing bullshit sphere
is that it's like, we only pay attention to these people
whenever they do something we don't like,
so we have honestly no idea whatsoever
if she's ever spoken about China.
No clue, no clue, doesn't matter.
Wasn't paying attention when she did that.
I am only mad whenever she speaks out
about something that I care about.
Wait, what is the Uyghur Forced Labor Disclosure Act of 2020?
Totally no clue, no clue, no clue.
So, you know, sometimes the world opens up a little bit.
You know, like, I think that now that vaccines
are going around a little bit more,
we're getting to a point where there's a possibility
of like meeting a friend for dinner.
And it's kind of exciting,
or being able to go over to a friend's house
for a barbecue or something like that.
There's a ball game in my future, and I'm very excited.
It's kinda nice.
It's very exciting.
Unless.
Very bad.
You're like Alex.
Uh-oh.
And you go out to dinner with James O'Keeffe.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
I had a really great evening last night.
I had like a two and a half hour dinner
with James O'Keeffe and his fantastic crew.
And it's just an honor to be around these types of souls
who love liberty, who are indomitable,
and who have a fighting spirit.
It just makes me feel strong, and it was really great.
And O'Keeffe turned to me after dinner and he said,
hey, we're gonna give you a big exclusive tomorrow.
We're gonna actually let you break it at 11 a.m.
And it's another terrorist.
They caught at the border and a coverup of what happened.
They were given the internal documents.
That is breaking in 10 minutes at infowars.com.
James O'Keeffe operates on one thing and one thing only,
and that is attention.
If you're ever in a position where James O'Keeffe
is offering you an exclusive,
you need to ask yourself some very serious questions
about the legitimacy of the story
that he's trying to give you.
I am 100% sure this man,
whose entire career is based off of lying to the people
that he is speaking to at any given point in time.
For the sake of attention.
For the sake of attention and profit,
I am sure there's no way he would backstab Alex.
I'm not saying backstab necessarily,
but you gotta be asking yourself,
does he just not wanna stand behind this story?
As it turns out, it's not an exclusive.
It's a video that's up on Project Veritas
that Alex just plays.
Sure, of course.
He's calling it an exclusive.
It doesn't fucking mean anything.
No, of course not.
I don't even believe they had dinner.
How is it possible that you can,
like, the Infowars itself is blackballed
on the major right-wing conservative news networks,
but O'Keeffe can hang out with Alex
and then still be like, Fox News is like,
look at the new O'Keeffe masterpiece.
To be fair, we don't have corroboration
they went to dinner with us.
That's true, that's true.
That is true, that's true.
Alex does say a lot of shit.
You can't trust him bullshitting about that.
He also said this is an exclusive,
and it's fucking not.
It's true, that's true.
So let's get to that real quick.
Here is the scoop that's not.
Project Veritas exclusive,
Department of Homeland Security insider leaks,
quote, significant event report
showing suspected terrorists being tracked
and apprehended on US-Mexico border.
This is the third one in a couple of weeks
and they want this shut down,
so folks get the article out.
I don't care what Project Veritas does,
but also even if everything that's being said here is true,
then I don't care about their scoop.
A suspected terrorist was tracked and arrested
when they tried to enter the country.
That's just a story that tells me that border security
is pretty all right in catching terrorists.
No, no, it's not working.
It's a failure.
Biden's administration is ruining everything
by catching terrorists whenever they cross into this country.
Also, if I were James O'Keeffe,
I'd probably shy away from stories like this
about terrorists and the border.
They run the risk of reminding people
about that time in 2014 when he dressed up
as Osama bin Laden and walked across a stretch
of the Rio Grande River,
supposedly illustrating how easy it would be
for bin Laden to sneak into the country.
It was super embarrassing and he got dunked on pretty hard,
so I'd be careful about reminding people about that video.
I would say go for it, O'Keeffe.
I think this is a great idea.
You're gonna get all the attention in the world
and absolutely you should dress up like Osama again
and then die in the ocean.
I will say that the sort of like flare for costuming period
seems to be over in James O'Keeffe's career.
That could be.
He seemed to love to dress up earlier on.
You know, when you're young, you like to dress up.
That happens.
You get older, you know, you put away childish things.
Now he just likes to wear a suit,
act really dramatic.
Oh, I hate him so much.
Interview weirdos.
I hate him so much.
Who maybe used to work at Facebook.
Yeah, he's the worst.
Yep.
So we got a new instance
of social media censorship going on here.
This one doesn't quite fit all the usual suspects.
It also probably isn't true.
Meanwhile, Facebook removes posts by Breonna Taylor's mother
criticizing Black Lives Matter
saying they never helped her and they're full of crap.
Wow.
So now the mother of Breonna Taylor who was killed wrongly
and Senator Paul passed a law
to try to stop the no-knock warrants being used too much.
He gets beat up for passing a lot of protector.
It's all upside down.
So you can see here
Alex's position on the killing of Breonna Taylor has changed
now that there's an angle he can use
to attack Black Lives Matter.
Yeah, fuck, I wanted, oh my God, oh my God.
Because he's using the mask
of being sympathetic about her death
to make his attack on Black Lives Matter more palatable.
Oh my God, you fucking opportunist, bullshitting,
oh, fuck off.
This is shady as hell and I have zero respect for it.
A couple of quick fact checks here though.
Taylor's mother did not say
that Black Lives Matter was a fraud.
She was commenting on the Louisville chapter
of Black Lives Matter
which she said she also has never dealt with.
Also, there's no indication that Facebook took down her post.
It's entirely possible that she removed it herself.
There's no verification on that.
Also, Rand Paul was beaten up by his neighbor in 2017
and reports on the neighbor's trial have called it a fight,
quote, over a lawn care dispute.
Breonna Taylor was killed on March 13th, 2020.
So unless this neighbor attacked Rand three years in advance
as retaliation for passing laws limiting no-knock warrants,
then what Alex is saying makes no sense
and he's just grasping at straws.
Also, Rand Paul's bill, S3955, was read twice
and then referred to committee
where it has been since June, 2020.
It is a dead bill.
Rand Paul has not succeeded in doing the thing
that Alex is giving him credit for
which his neighbor apparently beat him up
for three years prior.
I would, I think that's a fun, a lawn care incident.
I think if Rand and I were to get into a fight,
it would be like, they would be described
as an existential incident
insofar as I do not appreciate his existence.
So that would just be my, that would be my excuse.
Sure.
That's what I would have.
I feel like you might be the sort of cat who would like,
you could get in a lawn care dispute with him.
I could find a lawn care dispute.
I could find any kind of dispute.
I just feel like it would be,
you'd like put poison on some of his yard
so it would spell out something really offensive
maybe in the grass.
No, but what if he has a dog that ate it?
I would never, ever, ever hurt a pet
despite it being Rand Paul's pet.
That is still a good pet.
Trim his bonsai into a offensive shape
out in front of his house maybe.
Oh, I think I could probably get a crane
and then, you know like that gag
where you've got the bottle of,
or the bucket of water on the door
and you like open it and then somebody gets,
oh, that's terrible.
I get a crane, but like a really tall one.
Okay.
And then when he's walking out of his house in the morning,
I just pee right on his head.
Hmm.
And then whenever he's not sure what it is
and he looks up, right into his mouth.
No way to kill the dog there.
That's how I do it.
So that I think you're safe. Exactly.
Yep.
I would say that if you were doing that,
you'd be playing with fire.
Possibly.
And now the globalists want to burn down America.
They want to hold the police
and all the governments hostage
so they roll over and a lot of them are.
But don't play with me.
They're playing with fire.
Cause you're playing with fire.
Playing with fire now, aren't they?
Fire has a way of getting away from you.
Way of blowing back.
Burning you real bad.
That's why I don't play with fire.
Is it?
Don't you?
Cause what did old George Washington say?
Old George, our leader.
What'd he say?
What did he say?
He said, fire is a dangerous servant
and a fearful master.
This isn't a real Washington quote.
I was going to say that's not a Washington quote
by any shot.
The structure of discussing fire
and this exact construction
with the servant master dichotomy
was traced back to at least 1637
by the website quote investigator.
And the same idea and quote,
but being applied to water
was traced back to 1562.
The first time this turn of phrase
was credited to Washington was in 1902
in an article in the Christian Science Journal.
And it's not even been consistently credited
to Washington since then.
It's just another example of Alex
thrown around fake quotes.
Man, I think that one probably goes
all the way back to like 150,000 years ago
whenever it was just like ugh
and that meant it's hot.
Run away.
You can use fire for things,
but also it can fuck you.
Exactly.
So I was listening-
Don't touch it, it's hot.
I was listening to that clip though
and I got really excited
cause you know, every now and again,
I hate the doors,
but every now and again,
I'm in the right mood for that playing with fire.
Sure, sure.
I don't know.
I'm just in the right mood.
And the way that Alex was doing the like,
don't play with fire.
I learned not to play with fire.
Fire has a way of biting you.
I got really excited
and then when he said this,
I got even more excited.
You're the ones playing with fire.
You're the one letting it out of the box
and you don't control it.
And those that release the fire
are almost always the ones burned by the fire.
That doesn't sound true at all.
You must respect the fire
and you must keep the fire at arm's length.
But those of you that embrace the fire
of 666 will be burned by the fire.
You cannot contain the fire.
You are not in command of the fire.
You wanna play God?
You're not.
I wasn't ready for the fire to be the devil.
I really wasn't.
Oh man, oh boy.
I thought it was just about taking chances.
See, now who got tricked by it
winding up being the devil?
Yeah, I know.
I was hoisted on my own petard.
I was playing with fire, if you will,
and I got burned.
Do Christians not know how silly it is
to use 666?
Ooh, it's three numbers.
I also do like the idea that Clank's like,
you have to respect the fire.
You gotta respect the fire.
Wait, the devil?
You gotta respect the devil?
Keep the devil at an arm's length.
All right, you don't embrace it,
you respect the devil.
And when he was saying you gotta keep the fire,
I was thinking of that Kenny Loggins song.
Well, I was thinking of that too.
So yeah, that little diatribe was a little fun for me.
Yeah, I always appreciate it
whenever he really loses the thread
while trying to do lyrics.
And then he's like, what if I combine the two
and then I'll have a thing to say?
What if I turn this into a block of content?
Then I have to do less work.
Then I have a good excuse
to have not covered any news stories.
Dumb asshole.
Spoken word album is coming our way
once he's off the air.
Anyway, Jordan, this clip,
this for me is just like every now and again
you need like that cute moment.
Sure.
And I think that this is really cute.
Because there is a war on for your mind.
No, no.
There are a lot of diseased,
crazy people who always seek to destroy innocence.
And when we bow down to them, well, we get destroyed.
He can't stop himself, he can't do it.
He can't.
He can't do it.
It's too catchy, Dan, I almost started whistling.
It's too catchy.
He has to start whistling in the middle of a sentence.
He can't stop.
It's amazing.
That, my friend, is a human moment.
That is very cute, that is very cute.
Yep, so not so cute is Alex's story corner on this episode.
Oh, no.
Except a little bit of a story.
About something that happened when he was getting divorced
from his wife.
Okay.
I think.
How is it possible to turn this racist?
Because I feel that's where we're going.
It's not going racist yet.
Okay, okay.
We'll get pretty deep into that later.
I'm sure.
This story in particular is more,
I don't even know what it is.
I think the story Alex is trying to tell
is a couple of really high-level stories.
A couple of really hot ladies
after he was getting divorced, right?
A couple of hot ladies.
All right.
Invited him to a drag show.
Okay, yeah, okay.
And here's what happened.
And I don't know what it is about women liking this.
When I was getting divorced,
a couple of gorgeous women that lived in the condos with me,
well, one of them did, one of them didn't live there,
said, hey, we want to take you to this drag show contest.
And I'm like, I don't really go to topless bars.
And they go, no, no, no, this is tasteful.
It was in North Austin.
I lived in downtown then.
I was like a year into my divorce.
I wasn't divorced yet.
I'm like, okay, I mean, I'll go with you.
And there were two gorgeous brunettes took me.
And I get there and I go, what the hell?
This is like, half of these are men.
And the smell of the hormones, I was sick.
And then they all got mad at me that I was there.
And we were there like, well, you're right.
We didn't know it was all men.
We thought there'd be a few here, let's go.
What?
But I remember, and we were there like 15 minutes.
This story makes no sense.
This is incoherent and insane.
Yeah, I wonder what the reality of the story is
if he's just making all this up.
Yeah, I mean, it rings true in the sense
that I have no doubt that at a certain point in his life,
someone invited him to a drag show.
Sure.
That I would believe.
Well, yeah, it feels strange that you accept
that invitation. I would also believe
they would be incredibly,
it doesn't sound like he knows what a drag show is.
It's possible.
I think he thinks that it's a burlesque show.
Maybe.
And it's not a drag show.
It's tasteful.
Wow, man, isn't that sad?
There's a certain part of me that finds it so sad
that if you're a conservative Christian white nationalist,
you can't enjoy a drag show,
which is one of the most joyous places that I've,
there's, everybody's happy at a drag show.
There's a lot of happiness.
There's, it's so happy.
I think that this story may or may not actually be true,
or it might be greatly embellished,
because I think it's really just an avenue for him
to get into bashing drag queen story out.
Yes, of course.
And so one of the things that I've noticed
that he does all the time is basically says,
he says that he, his reporters have captured
like pornographic footage of kids with like naked men
and stuff like that.
Sure, sure.
And it's like, no, you haven't.
Not, if you had.
It would be everywhere.
These people would be arrested.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Absolutely not.
And so would you for playing it on your show.
No, no, you can't play it on the show
because the local affiliates complain.
That's what I'm saying.
That's what he, that's what he's saying.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He, this is just nonsense.
Yeah, this is some footage in Austin
where the station's complaining about this.
So don't, don't show the part with a guy
totally naked with glitter with children humping him.
I mean, but it's like a dude with a major slong
and there's kids riding him,
but he's got glitter on his genitals.
So it's, oh, it's covered.
I mean, this is all illegal.
And so I just couldn't imagine being a child
and being around these.
Cause it's, it's a pack of lunatics.
I mean, they're all on drugs.
They're on all sorts of crazy hormones.
They're doing all sorts of insane things.
And I've been around it for 15 minutes
and it made me physically sick.
Talking about that drag show that he went to
with those two very attractive ladies.
Wow.
For 15 minutes on that one.
So, so much of that doesn't need to be part of the story.
Nope.
So much of it is like,
those details don't help with your story.
It doesn't matter how big his slong was.
No, that is weird.
Were that the case?
It's, any size slong, it's still illegal.
Let me, let me tell you this.
I don't know if he was saying it was a big slong.
He said it was a major slong.
That's true.
That means it's one rank away from giving him information.
Yeah.
This is not a Lieutenant Colonel slong.
This, yeah, I don't know.
I don't, I don't buy any of this nonsense.
No, no.
So Alex gets back to talking about the Chauvin trial.
Sure.
The anticipation is building.
Maxine Waters has, you know,
said some comments that Alex is not into.
Sure.
But the judge, you know, he's not,
he's not interested in making this a mistrial.
You see that judge up there.
Well, we don't just listen to a Congresswoman.
You know, we don't, we don't need a mistrial.
No, you just have the jurors,
people going to their houses the last two days,
CBS news doxing them.
You got people going to the,
where one of the witnesses lived two years ago
and putting pig blood and a severed pig head
on his property.
No, you just got the media saying
they're going to burn down everything
if you don't send him to prison.
This isn't about that cop.
It's about lawlessness and terrorism and this mob,
this French revolution, Maoist, Bolshevik revolution,
October revolution, takeover.
Alex has yet to demonstrate or show any instances
of jurors being doxed or harassed.
So I'm not taking him repeating that claim
any more seriously than I did the first time.
There's another interesting thing here though,
which is that the media didn't say
that there would be protests and fires
if Chauvin was found not guilty.
Alex has played some clips from newscasts,
but there are interviews with civilians in Minneapolis
who are expressing that are likely beyond rest
if Chauvin is acquitted.
There's a really important difference here
and it's one that I think Alex refuses to acknowledge.
If the news goes out and interviews people
and they say that they'll likely be protests
if Chauvin is found not guilty,
does Alex think that the news should pretend
that they didn't do these interviews?
If the goal is to represent the opinion
of persons on the street that they talked to,
it would seem like an irresponsible level of censorship
to just edit their responses
to reflect what you would want them to say,
but that seems to be what Alex wants to happen.
Well, the, okay, so the person being interviewed
said specifically that if justice in this circumstance
is denied when it's so overwhelmingly obvious
what the verdict should be,
then I'm going to help people, quote,
no longer have a police precinct for a little while.
And then if that was edited, it would be like a,
bah, zh, bah.
Well, I mean, like, I think that really what's going on
is essentially that this is how Alex creates content,
and so he assumes that everybody else does.
Yeah, of course.
Alex only puts like blurbs in and stuff that makes him,
you know, like he has these-
It tells the narrative he wants it to tell,
so he assumes.
Super cuts of Owen Schroyer dunking on libs
and stuff like that.
Do you think the right wing has actually convinced itself
that the other side is doing what they're doing?
I think Alex has probably thought that all along.
Yeah, it has to be the only justification
for their horrible, awful behavior, right?
Yeah, I think so.
Also a small point,
but Maoism and Bolshevism aren't the same thing,
and they have some pretty salient differences.
I think Alex just picks and chooses commie words
that he thinks will scare the audience.
Communism is a single block.
I would love for him to try and explain
what he meant by the end of that sentence.
That would be amazing.
Yeah.
So Alex is not a racist, as we've discussed many times,
but usually in the reverse.
He is a racist.
Yes.
And one of the ways that you can tell that
is when he says things like this.
But in all these BLM events,
it's like 20, 30 white people
and three or four black people
who they have at the front of the line,
who they admit they use at the front of the line.
And then the black controllers trained as Marxists
even say white allies in the back
because they don't want them seen.
They want it to look like it's blacks doing it.
To scapegoat the blacks while they start the race war.
Wow.
So I'm smart enough to play chess
while their folks are playing checkers.
Really?
Wow.
That was your chess game right there.
4D.
Ah, yeah.
I would say three moves is all it takes to defeat him.
So Alex seems to be hitting this note
a little bit more regularly in recent days.
This idea that social justice causes
are meant to incite racist backlash from white people
and are orchestrated to do that by white people
putting a few black scapegoats at the front of their actions.
This is a pretty outrageously racist idea.
And as I've mentioned in the past,
particularly on the last episode,
this is very much in the same tradition
as Alex's forefathers who fought
against the civil rights movement.
I realized in hindsight that maybe I should explain
my point a little bit further.
And now Alex has kind of given me an opening
to do just that.
Yeah.
Alex's favorite book,
the one that turned him on to the new world order
was called None Dare Call It Conspiracy by Gary Allen.
Apparently Alex read it at 12 and his mind was blown.
Although he was still a Satanist a few years later
and got a bunch of people pregnant,
but honestly the timeline doesn't matter.
Let's not worry about that.
This book is a primer that has been cited by many people,
not just Alex, but people like Richard Belzer
as being like a revelation to them.
Wow, the bell's tolls.
Mm-hmm.
Gary Allen was a longtime member of the John Birch Society
and None Dare wasn't his first book.
Previously he'd written a book called
Communist Revolution in the Streets,
which was a scathing and very racist attack
on the civil rights movement.
There are a lot of arguments made in the book
that look very bad in hindsight,
but one of the predominant themes in the text
is the idea that black rights organizations
were secretly not actually black rights organizations,
but actually communist fronts,
typically run by white people.
Just in case any white people reading this
are concerned about unequal treatment,
let's just 100% get rid of that idea
that race even exists at all.
It's just white people versus white people.
From page 33, quote,
We arrive at the interesting possibility
that the black Muslims were started by the communists,
knowing that the majority of American Negroes
felt no kinship with Soviet Russia.
By establishing a pseudo-religion
based on Negro racial supremacy
and annihilation of the blue-eyed devils,
a revolutionary cadre could be built
within the United States without the majority of people
realizing its true significance.
Probably not surprisingly, Allen never actually justifies
this quote, interesting possibility,
because as he goes on to say, quote,
If the black Muslims were a communist setup
from the beginning, it's doubtful that any
but the very top oligarchy were aware.
That's some classic Infowars-style proof right there.
That's great.
This thing is true, and I can't prove it,
because only the top level of the conspiracy
that I swear is real has that proof.
And you can trust my credentials,
because my previous and former professors,
all of whom top professors,
I mean, you could, look, you can interview them,
all of them are dead, but you can trust that I'm great.
Right, you understand this construction
that he's using is basically,
in order to prove the basis for my conspiracy
and the suspicion that I have,
you have to assume the existence of the very conspiracy
that I've failed to prove exists.
It's circular.
It's kind of, yeah, no, it's him saying
that if I'm right, you would already know,
or if my information was public by them,
you would have already, yeah.
This runs constantly throughout his book.
Quote, The real cause of the riots is agitation
by revolutionaries, power-craving civil rights leaders,
and vote-hungry politicians who are willing to trade
a citizen's safety for the vote of a minority bloc.
Every group is a front,
every event is incited by communists,
it's all very boring.
On page 48, Allen lays out
what is essentially an overarching thesis.
Quote, The communists have been working for over 30 years
on mass recruitment of Negroes in America.
Their efforts have usually failed
because Negroes have proved to be loyal Americans,
but this has not caused the communists to slacken,
because they see civil rights as America's Achilles heel,
and the Negro is the sacrificial cannon fodder
for a communist-instigated revolution.
This is the exact same rhetoric that Alex Jones uses now,
which is being deployed by Gary Allen
to attack the civil rights movement
and Martin Luther King back in the mid-60s.
I would challenge Alex to reflect on this more or less
one-to-one overlap between his rhetoric
that's being used to attack social justice protests
of the modern era, and the rhetoric that Gary Allen used
to attack social justice protests
from our country's recent past.
I mean, you could, again, this goes back to slavery.
This goes all the way back to them being like,
well, there's no way that slaves
could ever organize on their own,
so it must be white people agitating the slaves,
and it's probably poor white people,
because they don't like us having all the money.
It goes all the way back.
It's there.
There is that.
I choose to focus this towards this,
because this is part of Alex's intellectual tradition.
Right, right, the anti-communism hadn't been attached to.
And this is the worldview that Alex espouses very deeply,
this anti-communism stuff, and this rooting of it
is something that he needs to understand
and stop obfuscating.
It's nonsense.
You can't play the exact same game that your forefathers did
against the civil rights movement
and pretend like that's not what you're doing.
It's not about communism.
No, of course not.
So Alex won't do any of this reflection,
and everyone in his orbit pretends
like books like Communist Revolution in the Street
don't exist, because they make it too obvious that,
like I said, this isn't about communism.
It never was.
That's all just a mask that they use to hide behind.
Yeah, absolutely.
Whenever the communists was used as an excuse
to blackball Jews in Hollywood, it's
not like J. Edgar Hoover was like,
this will never work against black people.
Yeah.
And just to give you some idea of how
little people want people to read books like this,
it was very hard to find that book.
I believe that.
I had to get it on loan from another university's
private library that I got it for like a week
and was able to photocopy it.
It's out of print.
It's buried, probably because it's super offensive.
It is a terrifyingly racist thing.
I've read, you've given me one page,
and I was like, Jesus Christ.
Yeah, it's terrifyingly offensive and very similar
to the rhetoric that Alex Jones uses now,
vis-a-vis things like Black Lives Matter.
Any white replacement theory in there?
Yeah, probably.
Yeah, we'll get there sooner or later.
Yeah.
So Alex goes to calls, and he wants
to talk about what do you think is going to happen
with this verdict, ma'am?
What do you think?
OK, so number one on the verdict,
I think it's going to be a hung jury.
I think a lot of people got scared about the Maxine Waters
comment.
Even the defense lawyer brought it up
that his phone was blowing up on the trial.
And that's what I think.
I think they're going to be hung jury,
and it's going to be a retry him.
I think they're going to try to keep this going all year.
That's my thought.
Yeah, I think Maxine's totally controlled.
She's a demon.
I think they told her to go do that too, hang the jury.
I agree.
To cause the blow up.
OK, so there's going to be a hung jury,
and it's going to be Maxine Waters has come out
and said these things in order to precipitate that.
Here is my educated guess.
That way there's going to be a riot afterwards
because people are going to be really upset about that.
They're going to be pissed.
Yeah.
So that's where we're at here, and that
seems to be fairly consistent.
Not hard.
Now, this caller has another thing to bring up.
Boy, things change real fast.
OK.
I just want to know, did you see that Omar segment
where he pretty much told his audience
that the liberal media has been lying about COVID
the whole time?
I just want to know your thoughts on the Bill Maher
segment because I haven't heard talk about that yet.
Well, I think Omar is very talented, very watchable.
I don't agree with a lot of what he said.
What the fuck?
I think he got smart.
Yeah, he said COVID was basically a giant hoax.
And a fraud.
Oh, and I forgot that he had that.
I hate you.
I hate you so much.
Bill Maher.
Bill Maher is now a secret patriot.
I hate him.
I can't.
No.
That's a bricking.
I just think he's fucked pretty much.
He's not going to become like a regular Democrat on the left.
He's going to have to come out as a libertarian
or they're going to start calling him a fraud.
Oh, actually, they've been demonizing him before this,
saying, stop burning down random neighborhoods.
Stop shooting random police.
That's what bad guys do.
Yeah, no, he's, look.
I can't think of anybody.
The word is he's more like Tucker Carlson.
He's just, he won't be on air if he doesn't tell the line.
So he has to make some false statement
and make a true statement.
But I'm rooting for Bill Maher to go all the way.
Thank you so much.
I have bad news for that caller, and that
is that Bill Maher is self-identified
as a libertarian many times in the past.
His exact political philosophy is kind of tough to nail down,
but libertarianism is one of the titles he's used before.
The only reason anyone would think
that he's some kind of a super liberal
is if they only know about his positions
from listening to Alex yell about him.
Also, Alex can fuck right off with this stuff about Maher
being basically like Tucker Carlson,
but he knows that he needs to say some things to stay on air.
For years, Alex has used things that Maher has said
and pretended they were globalist positions.
The whole thing about how the globalists
wanted to crash the economy to hurt Trump,
that was entirely based on a joke
that Bill Maher said on one of his shows.
Alex has used Bill Maher's comments
to such a prominent extent in his conspiracies
that Alex had to explain Bill Maher's role
in globalist operations like this.
Here he is on the same show, Bill Maher.
When he talks, that's a globalist mouthpiece.
So it's like Satan's puppet, his little, sitting on his lap,
a little, one of those things, ventriloquist dolls.
Yeah, he's basically a globalist ventriloquist doll.
He lays out the program.
I was just gonna say,
whenever he said some people have been,
I'm like, that has been your job for five years.
Jesus.
This is a stunning reversal for Bill Maher.
If I believed a word that Alex said,
Bill Maher should be super worried
about globalist assassin squads
coming to get him for betraying his contract
as a ventriloquist dummy or some dumb shit.
But all of it's made up, so it doesn't matter.
Isn't that something that he said on his last episode,
is that the higher ranking guys
eventually leave the globalists
with all their money and power,
and then they get killed.
Yeah, Bill Maher is gonna get assassinated soon.
That should be what you're saying.
Yeah.
Anyway, we get a guest at this point,
and it's Norm Standup Comedy Patches.
Does he have a new bit for us?
No, but he has.
If he did Lumerics, if he just out of nowhere
started doing Lumerics, that's a full circle for us.
Isn't Schachter's name Norm too?
No, Marty Schachter.
No, it's Marty, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I will say that Norm doesn't have a new bit,
but he does have an old one.
Okay.
I mean, I'm sure not gonna call Black Lives Matter
if somebody's breaking my door down tonight.
I'm dialing 911 and hoping somebody like Derek Chauvin
responds to the call.
Again, great bit.
I mean, you would if you were white.
And I do love the idea that he's insistent
on making sure people know that Black Lives Matter
does not address burglaries.
Yes, yes.
Just to make sure everyone knows.
Thank you, Norm.
One, the number for Black Lives Matter,
significantly longer than 911.
I also wouldn't call the police to deal
with like racial injustice issues.
Nope, nope.
So I wouldn't call them to deal with like advocacy
for causes.
Uh, yeah.
Woo.
We've made an amazing point.
I think it's good.
It's so good that Norm had to do it again.
Yeah.
The same fucking point on my back to back episodes.
Mic down for this.
Cause Norm's gonna lie a little bit about the idea
of reassignment surgery for minors.
Oh no.
But that's less important than the exchange
that happens at the end of this clip.
Okay, okay.
Cause it is so heartbreaking.
Okay.
It is so sad.
We cherish difference for the sake of difference.
We're in a situation where parents could be accused
of risk of injury to a minor by not heeding
their minor children's desire for sex change operations.
I mean, it's just absolutely insane.
And I don't really know who benefits from this.
It's hard to imagine that anyone does.
Satan.
Well, yeah, you know, that would be one candidate.
Oh my God.
You're a fucking lawyer.
Who benefits from this?
Satan.
Oh boy.
Your honor, I ask that this case be thrown out.
Seeing as how half of the jury is Satanists.
How embarrassing would it be to be like,
well, maybe we used to be taken seriously.
Now I'm sitting here with this dumb fuck Alex.
He's telling me the answer to Qui Bono is Satan.
And I have to be like, well, that's one option.
That's a possibility.
To take this bullshit seriously.
At no point in time could I consider that perhaps
somebody would benefit from not having their emotional life
destroyed by their real identity being denied them,
but it's gotta be the devil.
So I think that Alex has a disease.
I think he has a compulsion, sickness and addiction.
And that is whenever Norm Pattis is on the show,
he can't help himself,
but make declarations that involve a million dollars.
Probably put her face up.
She's under lights, like 10 lights
that are on her at a press conference.
And she's got almost pure pupils.
Talking about Maxine Waters.
Yeah, I put that together.
From my research, you've got to at least,
we're talking 10 lines of methamphetamine,
cocaine or LSD to do that.
I mean, those eyes are, she is jacked.
What the hell is she on, man?
She's, I mean, she's on self-righteous fumes.
No, seriously.
Look, I'll bet anybody a million dollars.
You can't shine bright lights in somebody's eyeballs
and have them be 95% pupil.
I mean, look at that, God almighty.
I don't understand enough of the physiology
of pupil dilation.
Let me get into this flash.
Any police training, let me tell you.
I, it's remarkable.
I mean, once is a, I mean, it's still not a pattern,
I guess, but Norm has been on for two instances
of Alex offering million dollar bounties on things.
If it were Norm, I'd be like, is it me?
I do appreciate it.
Is it something about me?
Am I so boring that Alex needs to spice this up
with millions of dollars on the line?
I do appreciate that Norm is like,
well, I think she's on self-righteousness
because I am not going to insist that she is on drugs.
That's not what I do.
You already pimped me out into saying
that maybe the devil.
Maybe it was the devil.
You forced me to say that.
Yeah. Yeah.
So, man, interesting.
Norm, not Norm's appearance, very boring.
No, of course.
But what is interesting is that immediately after this,
Alex has Barnes on.
Why?
His other lawyer friend.
You always have the double lawyer attack.
I think it's because it's the law day.
Well, that's right.
Chauvin trials going on.
Chauvin trials, yeah.
You might as well have as many lawyers on as you can
and there are only two who will.
Yeah, but I might have accidentally skipped a minute
or something because Alex was in the middle
of talking to Norm and then he's talking about
how Barnes is the smartest lawyer that he knows.
Oh, boy.
And I'm like, did he just say that but he meant Norm?
I don't know.
I couldn't tell until Barnes started talking to himself
and I'm like, okay, I guess they just had them back to back.
So maybe we just stroked out for a minute there.
Yeah, but as soon as he was on,
I kind of figured out what was going on.
The whole point of a jury trial
is to not have mob justice.
It's the counter to mob justice.
It's the opposite point to mob justice.
It's the remedy to mob justice.
So by trying to create mob justice inside the courtroom
and convert the jury into a mob,
they are completely defeating the entire point
of jury trial justice and maybe their goal,
much like with policing,
will be to ultimately replace juries.
Exactly.
Why the bold assault?
Why are they so arrogant?
How do we counter this?
Because this should really threaten all Americans.
This is just as bad as going after free speech or guns.
But one of the greatest protection
against total control by the state is the jury system
because it's ordinary, everyday people coming together.
It says the power of the judiciary lies with the people.
Absolutely.
The power of the state is in the power of the jury.
And it's a check on politicians.
It's a check on abusive state actors.
And the media wants the power to misquote, misphrase,
misscript, misrepresent, and then the media wants the power.
Like, what we say juries gotta do.
So I found this really interesting.
So what's going on here is that Barnes
is coming on the show here towards the end.
And the game that they were playing,
I thought was really overt.
What's going on here is, so for a lot of the show,
the fear that Alex has been building up to
is one of a hung jury or an acquittal,
which is what the globalists want
because then there's gonna be riots in the streets.
Naturally.
This trial is essentially an elaborate setup
to get people riled up to the point
where there will be riots.
That's what Alex's callers have suspected
and Alex has mirrored this sentiment back to them.
He's even said that he believes
that Maxine Waters' statements were intentionally made
to cause a mistrial so there would be riots.
But what if that doesn't happen?
You don't wanna put all your eggs in that one basket,
so here comes Robert Barnes
to provide the alternative narrative.
In case things don't go the way Alex
has been saying they will this whole episode.
Yeah.
In case Chauvin is found guilty,
Barnes has the narrative in place here,
that Maxine Waters' comments were essentially
the creation of mob rule within the courtrooms
in order to replace jury trials with mob justice.
Until the verdict is read,
if you're a listener of Infowars,
you're being asked to believe
that Maxine Waters' comments were simultaneously
an attempt to replace juries with mob justice
and also a needlessly complicated conspiracy
meant to cause a mistrial that'll lead to riots.
Infowars needs both of these to be true
until the verdict comes.
It's a game of Schrodinger's bullshit.
Yeah.
I do appreciate how his audience,
in fact, maybe how all of conservatives
view everybody on the left
insofar as never speaking to them,
they know exactly what the left is going to do.
It's kind of amazing that if you never learn anything
about your political enemy, quote unquote,
you can make them say whatever it is you want them to say.
True, yeah.
So Infowars have these narratives established
and they're ready to push their worldview
and pretend that they were right
regardless of how the jury decides.
The act of the verdict being read
actually determines which of these ideas
they have to accept as truth moving forward.
Yeah.
If Chauvin is not guilty,
Alex will say that Waters caused that to start the riots,
but if he is guilty, that angle will be quickly forgotten.
The reverse is true of the mob rule storyline.
Yeah.
This is an important point to recognize,
that reality doesn't matter to someone like Alex.
Real life events are just things
that he incorporates like props
into the story that he decided to tell long ago.
Yeah.
And the story with the Chauvin trial
is that there's no outcome that's actually good.
They're all just useful.
Yep.
To Alex.
It is, yeah, it's very annoying.
It's very annoying that they can just fucking,
it's like they're pre-writing a choose your own
adventure book based on the story, you know?
Like they've already got where they're going to wind up,
just they just have to give you
the different like pathways to go down.
And if they choose page 19,
then you have to start over at page two
and be like, okay, well now they're gonna start
a race war next time.
But this time it was a Maxine Waters mob rule.
Well, it's basically like, you know,
insistently saying both A and B,
which are contradictory things.
Yeah.
And then B happens.
And then someone criticizes you for talking
so much about A and be like, no, I said B.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You said both.
Dick.
Well, A squared plus B squared equals
either A or B squared, I believe is how the, yeah.
So Barnes, he has some comments that he wants to make
about how society got to the point that it is now,
where you have such a nanny state.
Does he say that it's his fault?
No, although Alex should probably be mad at him.
What did we do to let these lunatics get to this point?
And how do we counter people like this?
Well, it sort of starts with the culture itself.
The politics is downstream from culture
and the sort of the entire safe space movement
that arose out of sort of the moral panic
about kindergartens at elementary schools
and daycare centers in the nineties,
going to, you know, all of those range of cases
where a lot of stories were told by the prosecutors
that ended up being false,
created sort of a playdate culture
where we weren't allowed to let our kids go out
in the street and just play with random strangers.
You're saying the nanny state has created
a lot of neuroses and now they can leverage that
at anything they want.
Correct.
No, he was saying that's a satanic panic.
So Robert Barnes' main contention
is that conservative right-wing outrage
towards an imaginary problem
led us into a circumstance
that is almost entirely conservative outrage
at a made up problem?
Yeah, more or less.
That does make sense.
But the reason that Alex should be mad about this
is that Robert Barnes is saying that like the things
like the McMartin School trial and stuff,
there were things that were alleged that weren't true.
Which Alex has often said are 100% true.
He believes that Ted Gunderson
is the most reliable source ever
and Barnes is saying literally the opposite.
This is silly.
Both can be true.
Yeah, and I do, I wonder if Barnes was stopping himself
because you could hear him say mmm
and he stopped himself from saying McMartin.
Like maybe he just didn't want to be too specific
or whatever, like at risk of pissing off Alex.
I think there's a rule of like don't tread too closely
into Alex's zones, you know,
especially not with specifics.
Yeah, especially when you can't bear the indignity
of agreeing with Alex's stupid position on it.
Well, it could be the devil this time, Alex.
Norm got trounced.
So look, Robert Barnes, noted gambler on politics.
True.
This guy loves to make a bet.
May make some money, yeah.
So Alex wants to know what.
You know how it's great if your lawyer
is also gambling on the side?
You know how what you want from your lawyer
is also gambling?
Yeah, so Barnes is the kind of guy
who's gonna make a definite stake
in terms of like what's gonna happen with this verdict.
Is he gonna put a million dollars down?
No, he's not, Alex.
Oh, damn.
And I think that there's a decent chance
that we get an acquittal.
My view is there's about a 50% chance
of an acquittal in this case,
and that's gonna shock the media,
that's gonna shock a lot of people
who didn't watch the trial,
but it would affirm the confidence that people rightly have
in the authority of the court.
And I agree, because I think the last straw
is threatening the jury.
People go, wait, we're the bad guys?
We're being honest here, I'm a good person.
I wanna do justice.
You're saying I'm bad, I better do what you want?
That would make me, you know,
if I was on the knife's edge of which way to go,
that would make me acquit.
So Alex is talking about thinking
that Maxine Waters has threatened the jury.
So if I understand Alex correctly,
were he on a jury, the main thing
that protects us from a mob rule system,
were he considering the actual justice,
he would take somebody, anybody's comment in the media,
and use it as justification for his spiteful decision
to exist entirely within oppositional defiance.
Oppositional defiance would rule his decision-making,
not the facts of the case.
The only thing protecting us from mob rule.
Look, I'm pretty sure this fucking person's innocent, but.
Maxine Waters said some shit.
Bill Maher said.
He was talking shit.
Wait, Bill Maher's cool now.
Oh shit, who am I mad at?
Who do we choose?
Jimmy Kimmel?
Oh my god.
Yeah, also, congratulations Barnes
on your 50-50 bullshit.
Yeah, yeah, well, it could go one way
or it could go the other, or there's a third possibility.
Wishy-washy nonsense.
So I found this very bizarre,
but not really all that bizarre.
There was this phenomenon going on
where you had these two possibilities
and these two narratives that were built up,
one at the beginning of the show
and one towards the end of the show,
where you have Maxine Waters is trying to cause a mistrial
in order to get rights in the streets.
And then Barnes, she's doing this to create mob rule
in order for the jury to be cowed into voting guilty.
And I was like, both of these things are kind of,
it's tough, you have two disconnected threads.
And then what I thought was really interesting
is in this next clip,
you can kind of see Alex tie them together.
Really?
Yeah.
All right, I'm listening.
Believe it.
So bottom line, do you think threats to the jury backfire
and they acquit or do they bow down?
I think that's an open question.
I think it worked with some jurors,
didn't work and backfired with other jurors.
And the question is who wins out in the end?
So now what Alex has done is he's taken these two things,
he's woven them together under a similar umbrella
and he's made it feel like they're connected.
Alex has decided that the deciding factor in this case
is whether or not these threats to the jury
have been successful,
which is already an outrageous assumption for him to make.
What this does is remove any reality
of the facts of the case,
or even the possibility that any of the jurors
could find Chauvin guilty unless they were doing so
as the result of bowing down to threats.
There's no such thing as the merits of the case.
None.
By framing the conversation this way,
the conclusion is that the right verdict is acquittal,
that's just assumed.
And the explanation for a guilty verdict
is that the jury was afraid of the threats,
which is nonsense.
I said this makes Alex's narratives
feel like they're connected,
but they're actually not if you take a closer look.
This new, cleaner framing leaves out the entire thing
about Maxine Waters specifically making the comments she did
in order to cause a mistrial so there would be riots.
Right.
This is not the same thing as threats backfiring
and leading to a...
An acquittal.
Yeah.
One of the differences between them is really major, too.
You would think,
because it's part of the globalist overarching plan,
that's the problem here.
Why are we adding this element that destroys the plan
that was already working?
Yeah, I guess.
Yeah.
So in the conception of how Alex was talking
about the verdict earlier in the episode,
it was pretty clear that the globalists wanted an acquittal
because their goal was to incite street riots
and burning the cities.
Right, which you're not gonna get with a guilty verdict.
If that is the case,
then these alleged threats to the jury
have to have been meant to be so over the top
that a mistrial is guaranteed and the riots happen.
However, in the new framing,
it appears that the globalists actually want Chauvin
to be found guilty.
It's the mob rule.
These threats are either successful,
in which case the verdict is guilty,
or they backfire and the verdict is not guilty.
But the reason that the threats are made
are in service of achieving a guilty verdict.
Right, if you pay close attention,
over the course of one show,
Alex has completely changed the primary motivation
of his imaginary villains
because he's just making this up as he goes along.
None of this means anything.
This whole thing is basically just a lazy idiot
engaging in an act of really long,
really bigoted improvisational storytelling.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, basically.
And having weirdos like Robert Barnes
help him out along the way.
Oh boy.
So that was the tale, I think, of the 20th.
And then in the evening of the 20th afternoon,
depending on time zone.
Sure, sure.
Maybe morning, who knows, maybe you're overseas.
What you gonna do?
Chauvin guilty.
Yes.
Also Ted Nugent got COVID.
Other news.
Is he on the 21st?
No, he doesn't.
He should go on.
He doesn't come up.
He's gotta go on.
He's gotta go on with COVID, that's gotta happen.
Sure, yeah, and lick Alex.
And absolutely find a way to be like, this isn't real.
So we come in on the 21st now
after the verdict has happened.
Yeah.
And you can tell a little bit of a different tone.
Oh, you think?
A different vibe is happening in Info Wars Studio.
We have to reach out to God to open our hearts
and our spirits and transcend all the evil.
What is wrong with you people?
All the evil, poison we exhumed out by Satan's slaves.
Thank you for joining us on this live Wednesday,
April 21st, global transmission.
It's a Lana Del Rey kind of day.
It is, I just, it's Europe.
Ah, we watched him murder somebody.
It's not an attack on whiteness.
It's not even, it's not an attack on whiteness.
Why do they all have to make it an attack on whiteness?
There are so many reasons to attack whiteness.
We didn't need this one.
You know how you were saying
that you enjoyed that nice bath?
I did, loved it.
I think that Alex was in a similar place
that you were before the bath
because of this quote unquote attack on whiteness.
Yes, yeah, yeah, sure.
And the only thing that he could have,
he couldn't have a bath,
so he had to listen to Lana Del Rey.
He loves this album, man.
I'll tell you what.
Well, her new album's even better than last.
Amazing.
Cool album.
Great Christian album, but you know,
I'm sure it's not one of the things you'd ever see.
It's a real Christian, not a fake one.
Sure, sure.
Avant-garde, the cutting edge, the future.
Get behind me, Satan.
I'm guessing that Alex just saw
that one of the titles of the songs on Lana's new album
is Tulsa Jesus Freak.
Yeah, I was gonna say, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He just decided this is a Christian album now.
Absolutely, yep, yep, all he needed to see.
Has Alex forgotten that just three years ago
he was spending quite a bit of time on his show
yelling about how Lana Del Rey was a witch
who'd used evil spells against Donald Trump
because she'd said in an interview
that she used witchcraft against Trump?
Yep, that does sound right.
Does he now remember how the entire right wing
was up in arms about her breakthrough album
being called Born to Die?
That was the other outrage machine time.
That was back then when the outrage machine
was cranking out that bullshit.
It's just, it's so interesting.
I feel worried for him when he's playing
a bunch of Lana Del Rey.
Yeah, I don't appreciate that it's okay
for him to love Lana Del Rey publicly,
but he can't admit that he fucking loves Star Wars.
Yeah, he still feels the need to be like,
I don't even like those dumb movies.
It's so infuriating.
Now let me reference an obscure character.
Yeah, exactly, someone you would only know.
Someone who only exists in the books.
An immediate pull from something
it would be impossible to immediately pull from.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, can't do it because Star Wars is not Christian
like Lana Del Rey's new album.
Oh boy.
So in Christianity.
How's Christianity doing, still kicking it?
Well, God's real, Satan's real.
Yeah.
Well, I guess that means Christianity
is having a great time, there's right.
Satan is real and God is real and you are real.
And this is not a simulation.
That sounds like something a simulation would say.
This is the great test of consciousness.
That's exactly like what somebody
in a simulation would say. Consciousness
or the seed of the universe,
the seed of infinity is not just given away freely.
You must be tested.
I must be tested.
And so when you see the Nancy Pelosi's
and the Maxine Waters and the Prince Phillips.
What?
And the David Rockefeller's
and the Bill Gates's of the world.
These are people that failed the test.
These are people held in mindless clown-like bondage.
Did I mostly keep that clip in for the turn
of phrase clown-like bondage?
Ah, it's a good one.
Possibly.
It is a good one.
Clown-like bondage is not bad.
That's very evocative.
Yeah. Also, I mean, it's just indicative
of like kind of this mood that Alex is in
at the beginning of the show, like over Lana Del Rey
he's talking about Satan and like God
and he's in a very, very deeply spiritual.
Yeah, it does seem like we're going to get
into more esoteric Christianity for a little bit.
Yeah, lest we deal with the covering the verdict.
No, we don't want to do that.
No, there's a lot of racist things that you would say
if you were to cover that verdict and you were out.
You should probably just talk about Satan.
Satan's a real good guy.
We are in the process of not humans' extermination
but the slow destruction of all carbon-based life forms
on this planet is the goal of Satan.
Does that matter?
Because God created this carbon-based system.
We are made in the image of God
and Satan hates our supremacy.
Why?
Humans are incredible when we're unchained.
We are beautiful.
We can experience the universe
and communion with the creator.
We're like rods and cones in the eye of God.
We are God's vessels, God's tentacles, God's probes
God's system experiencing consciousness.
I don't want to be any of that.
And nothing Satan can do will ever change that.
What?
I don't know.
I feel like maybe he should have gone to college
and got high.
Maybe you would have worked some of this out of his system.
Like having like really annoying conversations with people.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Cause that's very simple.
Okay, so you're telling me that one, this life.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hit it again.
One, one.
I got to break out the ball.
Yeah, you're going to need it.
This life is a test, right?
Consciousness is a test.
And that's all it is
because God is testing you to see if you can come
and hang out with him.
I guess.
Right.
But Satan is the person or entity doing the testing.
Sure.
Thus he is part of God's plan.
Right.
And if you're like Pelosi or Prince Phillip,
you have failed the test and you're in clown-like bondage.
You're in clown-like bondage, naturally.
But I mean, it's like, he's been doing this for,
you know, thousands of years.
Why is he still taking it so personally?
You know, the devil is like, I'm already part of the plan.
And God's like, he's not going to succeed
at destroying all of the people.
We've got Alex fighting him.
It's because the last 999 years of this thousand year plan
has been all leading up to this.
Well, that's why God gave us Alex.
There's this sort of bias that people have
about like immediacy or currency.
Like the time right now is the most important time ever.
And every generation thinks they're the last generation.
Exactly.
And obviously there's reasons to feel that way sometimes,
but Alex suffers from that in a way that intersects deeply
with narcissism and kind of scary.
Yeah, it's not good.
So yeah, I just, I remember,
I had a lot of conversations like that.
Like maybe when I started to like, I don't know,
explore some of the elementary ideas about
Gnosticism or something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, like, oh, blowing minds.
Yeah, that's when you should have that,
your head is empty, you're a big dumb dumb.
You should be smoking weed and having dumb conversations.
But at the same time, when you're not smoking weed,
you should be reading books
and struggling with reading comprehension.
And then you won't have to have
those conversations ever again.
I love of never having those conversations, Dan.
So one thing that I thought was really bizarre
and maybe off-putting was where he goes immediately
after this conversation about how we're elements
of God's eye experiencing things for God.
Also tentacles.
Mic down for this, because this,
I want to see if this hits your ear
the same way it hit mine.
We're like rods and cones in the eye of God.
We are God's vessels, God's tentacles,
God's probes, God's system experiencing consciousness
and nothing Satan can do will ever change that.
So don't let the enemy get you down.
I know it gets me down, it's sad.
And don't let their religion of race war
and their religion of worshiping black people
on the surface when they're doing the opposite
or killing them ever get you down.
Ever get you down.
That really felt weird.
Do you, do you, do you?
I don't feel comfortable.
No.
No, that makes me feel very uncomfortable.
That's really weird.
That's really gross because now you're transforming
the fight for even the slightest modicum
of racial justice into a holy war against anyone
who would try and get a modicum of racial justice.
Try and get a modicum of racial justice.
Yeah, there's some of that.
And also the pronouns that are used
are a little bit strange.
He's using we a lot when he's talking about
the eyes of God and what have you.
And then them when he's talking about black people.
It does seem like what he was doing.
It does seem to be a little bit of a disconnect.
I think he has a very different view of people
based upon their skin and appearance.
And that's just me, that's just me, I could be wrong.
I'll tell you what, that seemed very strange.
That hits my ear very weird except
there's a very easy explanation
that would not make it hit my ear very weird.
And that is if Alex knows that he's just talking
to white people.
Yes, yes, then what he said makes total sense.
Makes perfect sense, yep, yep.
But if he thinks that he's talking to a diverse audience,
that's weird, that doesn't make sense.
That's not cool.
The structure of that sentence is bizarre.
I would be more careful if I were him.
Anyway.
What I'm saying is that we denizens of the great Rhodesia
and, wait, wait, I shouldn't have said that.
Well, I mean, we Christians.
Alex's buddy Gary Allen loved Rhodesia.
It was surprising.
So, you know, I always like to find these kinds of moments
where there's olive branches, where there's a possibility
for Alex and I to agree on something.
Sure, we want reconciliation as always.
I mean, even if it's superficial, I'll take it.
Sure.
I kind of thought that maybe Nancy Pelosi's
very unfortunate and poorly constructed comments.
Oh boy, boy, boy, boy, Nancy,
you're really putting your name at the top of the list
to go fuck yourselves.
Nancy Pelosi came out and referred to George Floyd's murder
as a sacrifice for justice, which was real shit.
Woof.
I thought that maybe there would be an opportunity
for Alex and I to come to some sort of an agreement
that, hey, that was not good.
Yeah, it seems like it wouldn't be hard.
That's the level of shit that if I was Nancy Pelosi's aide,
I would immediately tackle her off the stage.
I would be like, everybody will like you more
if you get hurt for this.
And then come up with an excuse of, like,
I saw someone, a threat.
I ate chili, just anything.
Unfortunately, this would have been a layup for Alex
to get me to agree with him,
but somehow he manages to not only miss the shot,
he broke his ankle midair.
Critical failure.
Let me see Nancy Pelosi say we'll play it in a moment.
She said yesterday, breathing through her face diaper,
huffing and puffing at 82 years old,
with her tenuous grasp to life,
as her spirit begins its descent to her master,
and she thanked George Floyd for his sacrifice,
like he was a veteran, like he was Jesus on the cross,
like he was a Messiah.
Oh boy.
A drugged out,
male prostitute,
devastatedly unhappy,
possessed by the spirit of the world
until the moment he died.
Just missed it.
Just missed the mark.
Just incredible.
Something so...
So easy.
He's too racist to even criticize Nancy Pelosi
when she's being racist.
Yeah, yeah.
Wow.
Remarkable.
That is a level I just didn't expect.
I just didn't expect it.
Yep.
I mean, there's disappointment,
and then there's disappointment.
And then there's that.
Yeah.
Not you, like, Alex,
you can't even clear that incredibly low hurdle
of critiquing Nancy Pelosi for that kind of a bungle.
How dare she not be racist enough for me?
Yeah.
That's not good.
No.
Nope.
So the feds, they're taking over policing,
which means actually the UN is in charge,
and uh-oh, we have no government.
Okay.
And there is
Pelosi announcing the globalist,
UN-controlled federal,
and the feds are run by the UN now,
meaning UN takeover of our police,
just like they control our medicine and our speech
and policies of our military.
We are now a conquered nation.
And until we realize we're a conquered nation,
we have no hope.
But if we unified against their evil,
we could easily take back our government.
This is just about the Department of Justice
opening an inquiry into the Minneapolis Police Department.
Alex is such a dramatic little baby
that he's turned that into the UN running the country,
and the only people who can stop them
and take the country back are him and his buddies.
Yeah.
It's ridiculous.
You gotta escalate things a lot quicker
whenever your big bad is the devil.
You know, you can't be like, this is just going to,
he couldn't even possibly be like,
they're just going to root out the patriots
in the police state, and that's why it's bad.
It has to be a complete overthrow
of the United States government.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah, gotcha.
So, I don't know if you're aware of this,
but we live in a multiverse.
I am aware of that.
Do you know that we live in those universes simultaneously?
It has to be true.
It's real heady stuff.
Yeah.
We do not just live in one dimension.
We live throughout the multiverse.
I want to open the phones up
until the bottom of the next hour
and the constitutional lawyer joins us, Norm Pattis.
I'd like to shift to dimensions.
Yeah, I would very much like to not do that.
Yeah, how do I live in the dimension
where Norm Pattis isn't coming back on the show?
How about that, you dick?
Yeah, what's the quantum suicide thing?
Can you just quantum suicide
until you get into a good universe?
How do I get to the universe
where you have a better fucking booking agent?
Yeah, no kidding.
It's ridiculous.
Too much, Norm.
Nope, can't do it.
So, I want to tell you in advance here,
this is not a good clip.
This is a bit racist.
Oh, well, if you're saying that now after where we've come.
Well, this has to do with a lead-in to conversation.
He doesn't actually have much of a conversation
about the Bryant shooting in Columbus.
Sure, sure.
But the way he does get into it is not good.
It's already been at historic highs, black on white crime,
because a lot of black young people
are buying into the lie and doing it, and it's terrible.
But they're highly impressionable,
and they're being told that this is what you should do.
And I just saw a video of this morning.
It's an article on Infowars.com.
We'll play it next hour while we take your calls.
Columbus, Ohio, a quote,
little black baby, the media said.
She's a big girl for 15.
Looks like she hasn't missed out on any cheeseburgers.
How fucking dare you?
She was stabbing a white woman and a black woman
with a eight-inch knife.
It looks like a short butcher knife.
Black people called the police.
She gets there and she keeps stabbing people.
And so they were stabbed, two people were stabbed.
And because the white devil shot the black angel,
Black Lives Matter's protesting and rioting.
There's a lot of details that are yet to be sorted out
about this shooting.
And I don't feel like I have an ability
to fully assess the situation yet.
I'm gonna leave that to more information to come out,
time to process and what have you.
I wanted to play this clip, however,
to demonstrate how open and shut things are for Alex
and how coverage of this story begins by discussing
how impressionable black youth are
and how they're being taught to attack white people.
The actual details of this case are secondary
and not nearly as important as how explicitly racist Alex
and his show are.
This is outrageous.
That is so fucked up.
I just don't know.
Black youth are very impressionable.
How can, I don't, I will never understand
quite how easy it is for white racists to get to like,
well, if you're 15 and black though, you're big.
Right.
You're bigger than 15 year old white people.
So whatever happens is fine.
I just, how, how do you get there?
Like, it's just unconscionable.
It just really is.
I don't disagree.
Like for all they're screaming about pedophilia,
it's fine if teenagers get killed though,
because they're black and that means they're bigger
or whatever, fuck off, unreal.
Yeah, it's pretty breathtaking.
And the ability for content that is this racist
to not be like, it's amazing that it exists.
Yeah, it really is.
It's shocking that it exists and isn't dealt with
in the proper context.
You know, like it's not related to as like,
this might as well be a Klan show.
No, it's 100% a Klan show.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
Granted, sometimes it's a milder Klan show.
Sometimes they talk about other things.
Well, I'm sure the Klan had to talk about like anniversaries
and oh, like we have a new kid, you know, like that kind of.
Bitcoin comes up from time to time.
Sure, sure.
But man, this is, this is some pretty,
pretty out in the open racist shit.
That's unreal.
Yeah.
That's just unreal.
But if you were to ask Alex,
he has a completely different idea.
He thinks his show is like full of sophisticated information.
Really?
I've always believed in the people.
And that's why I-
You said you hate them.
This broadcast is a populist program
to just put out very sophisticated information,
but also simple truths at the same time,
believing that if you up the level of information,
that ups the level of understanding,
not dumb the information down
and dumb down the population of feedback loop.
Wow.
But that said, when I do this governmental briefing style,
PowerPoints and guests and just go over documents,
that is extremely effective, not just with like General Flynn
but I can tell you prime ministers, world leaders,
they had CIA boardrooms two weeks ago in our spars,
2025, 2028 report because it was done in a briefing format.
Not a fucking chance.
I feel like this is a simulation
because there's no way a human being
could possibly be that unself-aware.
Well, I think he is self-aware.
I just think that's the image
that he wants the audience to have of him.
He can't possibly fucking believe
that anybody took that shit seriously.
Cannot possibly believe that.
That spars video that he did
was so fucking offensively clunky.
It was so dumb that Mike Guy was a total weirdo.
They were taking lines completely out of context,
making completely false assertions about the document.
Anybody who actually read it without just already
pre-deciding that Alex was right
would come away from that like,
this doesn't say what you say it says.
Yeah, that's true.
There's a CIA fucking boardroom.
Oh my God, not a fucking chance.
Here's the thing that I have to say.
Sure, sure, sure.
I do like the idea that Alex thinks
that he has another speed.
Right.
I do like that idea because I think it's funny
when he does that.
Yes, it is very funny.
I think it's really funny when he tries.
He thinks he's ramping it up.
Because it's very bad.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And he just doesn't have it.
He doesn't have that pitch anymore.
Maybe never did.
No.
But he was certainly better at looking
like he did earlier in his career.
Right, right, right, right.
But I like that because I would like for him
to take this way more seriously,
because I will too, and I do.
And I don't want to talk about conceptions of the devil.
I don't care.
Right, right, right.
I don't give a shit.
You don't even know how fast your fastball goes.
Yeah.
But you've been hanging around 75,
like sooner or later he's going to get better
at batting practice and it's just not happening.
It's not happening.
No.
Nope.
It's just, it's frustrating.
And I would like you to do some CIA boardroom shit.
Yeah, that's kind of interesting though,
because once you find out like the FBI
was listening to Joe Biggs on like Antifa protests,
you realize like, oh, these people are morons.
You know, like I could buy that the CIA had meetings on it
because I don't know if I trust any of them
to do a fundamental Google search at this point.
Let me actually.
They're all insane.
Let me say this.
Yes.
If I worked in the CIA,
I might want to have a meeting on it too,
but just for a day off.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey guys.
Get some pizza.
Guys, we got a new Alex.
We got a new Alex, guys.
Get in the boardroom.
We're going to, we'll put it on the big screen.
Ain't no way this is going to turn into any work.
Yeah.
So anyway.
Yes.
It's time for the big enchilada.
Okay.
Let me just give you the big enchilada,
then I'll go to your phone calls.
The globalists with their money have got the universities,
the banks, the medical system, the media system,
the world council of churches.
Almost all the churches are just
country club feel good groups.
I don't care if it's Protestant, Catholic.
It doesn't matter.
They've got Hollywood.
They've got the EU.
They've got radical Islam and Orthodox Islam.
They've got Israel.
They've got South Africa.
They got everybody.
Wow.
There's one thing they don't have.
You?
And that's the US military.
Okay.
Now the US military has got its own stuff going on.
It's got its own problems.
Believe me.
It's getting a divorce.
But it's still men and chivalry.
And to operate at that level,
some form of honor, even though it's predatory.
And so the globalists want to intimidate it, attack it,
cause race riots, to selectively demonize
the military and police with these purges
to get control of them.
They don't need to.
They have a plan B.
There's a fucking super bio weapon release
that they can do.
None of this makes sense.
Why would they have?
They don't need to take over the police.
Also, if Alex's beliefs mean anything,
they don't have Russia, right?
Like he, what?
No, they've got everything.
They've got everything except the military
and the police.
They've got everything except the United States military
The fact that you're putting those two together
kind of makes you realize what the police is.
Don't you?
I mean, like this is so ridiculous.
I just, I have a hard time like even taking this seriously.
The good news is there's still plenty of white nationalists
in the US military and the police.
Still a lot of heavily armed weirdos.
We got plenty of white nationalists really rooting
for us to kill people.
So we got that.
Yeah, I don't know.
This is just, it feels like it just felt like
that was what was gonna like work for him to say.
Yeah, yeah.
And it just doesn't match with any of the stuff he says.
Normally, it doesn't make sense why the globalists
need the military and the police.
Yeah, you know what I feel like?
I feel like if you're somebody who identifies
with the police and the military, you're a fascist.
That's what I would go with.
Again, this is just like improvisational storytelling.
And one of the things that keeps people excited
in storytelling is like, you know,
sometimes the hero is doing well.
Sometimes the hero's doing poorly.
Yeah.
And when the hero's down, you gotta cheer
for him to come back up.
Absolutely.
The hero's journey.
Come on, it's 12 steps or whatever it is.
I think it was a couple weeks ago
that Alex was riding pretty high.
They were defeating the globalists.
Sure, killing it.
Unfortunately, they are now losing.
Ooh, that's trouble.
I wanna give you the honest prognosis.
I'm not like the Q people that tell you everything's fine.
We've won the war and just don't, no, no, no.
We're losing and everything's collapsing
and we have no future unless you get upset
and speak out and take action.
Now it's because we were winning culturally.
There was a huge awakening, great victory.
But now the globalists have taken their whole plan
and launched it and accelerated their timetable,
which is extremely reckless.
They were 10 years behind.
God, you just can't not hear this
over and over and over again.
Wow.
He's gotta get a new bit.
Because this bit is tired, stale.
I just don't feel like I can handle this infinite battle
between Alex and his evil enemies.
And everybody is either accelerating
or decelerating their plans at all times.
Nobody's ever like, let's put our chip,
yeah, nobody's putting their chips on the table.
Let's fucking do this.
Well, apparently they have.
So if it doesn't work this time,
I guess they've been defeated.
Well then, what are they gonna do next?
I don't know.
Eh, me neither.
It'll probably be boring and not real.
That's true.
This next clip, I would say
that this should get Alex institutionalized.
Okay, all right.
There's a lot of things that he says
that are like, you know, offensive.
Like really offensive.
Yeah, they should get him shunned,
but not institutionalized.
Maybe Bood.
Yeah, Bood is a good one, yeah.
This, if he really believes this,
he should be put in a padded cell.
Okay.
But I have decided to be Christ-like,
and I don't mean that blasting me, I'm serious.
I have taken on the sins.
I have taken them on.
I am in a poison vision of the enemy
so I can see the enemy's operations.
So Alex has taken on the sins of humanity.
All right.
So he can see the globalist's plan.
Like he's taken on the role of Jesus.
Right, right, right.
He's basically Jesus against the globalist.
I was gonna say.
This is not blasphemy.
Alex is very close to declaring himself the new Messiah.
Well, I mean, it's an interesting progression
because he was like sort of getting more and more
comfortable with talking about himself as a prophet
over the last six months or so.
John the Baptist and Trump was the, yeah, yeah, of course.
And now that is not satisfying.
Nope. At all.
I've gotta take that next step.
Yep.
I must make myself the Christ.
Look, you can only be a three-star general
for so long before you want that next star, baby.
Anyway.
Okay.
Alex takes some calls.
I am the new Messiah.
Anyways, let's go to the phones.
Let's go to the calls and let's see if we can talk
to a fucking dumb racist.
Mainly, I want to get this out of the point.
It's overwhelming to finally talk to you
because for decades, people have been telling me
I was too volatile and paranoid
because I've been telling them about all this stuff
except the pedophile stuff.
I didn't have your connections, but about the
we're all slaves and China's evil
and how everything's propaganda against the white man.
And everybody thought I was, I'm talking about all the way
back to the nineties and everybody was just telling me
I was crazy.
Well, what they do is they brand freedom and guns
and private property as the white man.
And then communism is the black man.
And they go, the black man's good.
The white man's bad.
When it has nothing to do with white men and black men
it's all branding.
Does that make sure?
Does that make sense?
Yeah.
And it's been, I mean, even in commercials, you know
the white man's always an idiot or, and then, and
I was always showing people how, you know
always shows people like abusing white men
and women hitting them.
And just, it was just always just-
Sure goes back to married with children.
Every white man on TV is an idiot.
And then, and then several years ago
I heard you for the first time.
And I realized I'm not the only person that sees this.
You know, I thought I was like cursed with this site.
Oh boy.
So I think the trope of the bumbling husband
probably dates back a little further
than married with children, but whatever.
I guess it's better than if they were like
I think we should go back to the honeymooners
when it was fine to beat your wife.
Also if Alec has a problem with the character trope
of the dumb husband, he's going to really hate
when he learns about all the other historical characters
of people who weren't white.
Oh boy.
In terms of just explaining a little bit of this
one of the reasons that there's such a large number
of husbands and fathers who are kind of idiots
is because it's the easiest way to make
their character lovable and flexible enough
to fit into the comedic premises that are required
for a sitcom to work.
Most of the situations the characters get into
probably wouldn't happen, or if they did
they would be resolved in way less comical ways
if one of the characters in charge wasn't a goof.
You could make every show like Father Knows Best,
but guess what?
Father Knows Best sucked.
It's a trash show.
Also, it's just.
You know what, I also hate the depiction
of white people in films being stupid,
which is why I hate Breakfast at Tiffany's.
Do you know what I hate about Breakfast at Tiffany's?
The way they treated that poor white man
who was definitely meant to read as white, 100%.
Yeah.
This is not an attack on the white man,
but it does make sense that this guy
would have these clearly racist feelings towards media
and everything that he experiences as an attack on whites,
and then he hears Alex and he's like,
I've found my people.
Of course, no shit.
Yep.
I mean, it's like.
It gets a lot worse.
How can you, white people have had it
so fucking pathetically easy for so goddamn long
that the idea of one appearance in movies or film
where the white guy is the bad guy is like,
how could anybody do this?
Well, look, you're saying that white people
have had it so easy for so long.
Alex would beg to differ.
Oh, I'm sure.
Based on his own.
Millions and millions of dollars.
Brother, I mean, listen,
there's not any black people that have been attacked,
let's not exaggerate, 75 times by white people I have,
but I actually enjoyed it.
I mean, I grew up with black folks trying to kill me
and I learned how to fight really good.
I mean, in fact, people ask how Alex Jones did all this.
I owe this to black races beating the living shit out of me.
I mean, I have just,
and I started hospitalizing a lot of black people
and they pretty soon started, you know, appreciated me,
but, and I love those folks.
I love the ones even I put in comas.
Yeesh.
I wanna go back to whistling.
Do you remember when he whistled, Dan?
I appreciated the whistling, that was great.
If, oh, that's what they should do.
If he gets on too much of a racist rant,
they should just start playing the Andy Griffith theme
and they'll be like, okay, I'm Andy Blackman.
And they should get like one of those
intermission type images and it's just.
Let's all go to the lobby.
But no, it's Photoshopped Alex's face onto Andy Griffith,
holding hands with young Richie Cunningham.
Yes, yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's great.
Little Opie carrying a fish and pole.
What a piece of shit.
Yeah, he's the worst.
Absolute piece of shit.
He is the worst.
Hey, I'm a huge racist,
but also I'm gonna brag about how good I am
and about how I defeated them in fights
and put them in comas, sure.
It's very strange.
What a fucked up dude.
But I'm just saying, I wouldn't be who I was
if I wasn't put in the hospital and broken legs
and broken arms and subdermal hematomas
and stabbed and everything else I did.
I really wanna thank black people
for what they did to me, I'm serious.
All right, I'm not gonna pretend to not understand
the point Alex is trying to make here poorly.
Oh boy.
This is the old idea of being like battle hardened
and Alex is thankful for the struggles that he went through
that made him who he is today.
Boy named Sue.
You hear variations of that from all sorts of people
and I think generally, you know,
there's a fine version of it.
Sure.
But what's not fine is the way Alex is ascribing
the series of beatings that he got when he was younger
to quote, black people.
Yeah.
As opposed to quote, specific people he got in fights with.
This is generalizing to the larger black population here
in a way that is incredibly fucked up.
From listening to this, I'm not actually even sure
if Alex realizes he's doing what he's doing,
but man, it is embarrassing and real racist.
Yeah, that's, this has been a real fucking highlight reel.
This is, this is a...
It's not been, it's not been really good.
No, no.
I would say that you might as well just come out
and be like, yeah, I guess I'm a racist.
I feel like I can't be too far off now.
Yeah, it's gotta happen.
It's like, and he can try and justify his racism,
but you can't pretend that you're not.
It's too late for that now.
Yeah.
We have one last clip here and it's to get a little bit
of a, you know, a little bit of parsley perhaps.
Sure, sure.
But Alex has this caller who's calling in from Brooklyn.
Right?
One of the last holdouts in Brooklyn.
Okay.
A stronghold.
Yeah.
Read that how you will.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I live in Bay Ridge, Brooklyn.
It's an Irish, Norwegian, Italian, German area.
It's like the last Republican stronghold in Brooklyn.
So what they're doing is they're sending people
from Park Slope, other places in Brooklyn,
to come in and try and take Bay Ridge over
and make it a liberal town.
Also, what they're doing is they're shutting down restaurants.
They're shutting down all the restaurants
and they're letting illegal immigrants sell products
in the street, which is crazy to me.
Elaborate on that.
Yeah.
Ha, ha, ha.
There it is.
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Been a little while since we've heard Alex eating lunch.
That's a good one, that's a good one.
So that was enjoyable.
Yeah, that was nice.
Yeah, I mean, look, I don't think that there was anything
else you could really expect from this period
other than like some pretty-
Brutal racism.
Some pounding racism.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I think it was interesting the way it manifested,
you know, like I don't think it made sense
based on real life conditions.
No, no.
And yeah, it sucks.
I'm going to not listen, or I'm gonna listen eventually.
Sure, sure, sure.
For our next episode, I am gonna go back to 2003,
because that way, over my birthday weekend,
I can spend my time in the past as opposed to
focusing too much on the present.
That is my gift to you, dear.
And that's my compromise.
But yeah, this sucked.
Yeah, that's, man, it's like that violent candle, you know?
Like it's got, in order to move forward,
we have to get rid of this bullshit.
We gotta not do this anymore.
But while we're fighting it, they're fighting so much,
so fucking hard, it's insane.
It's insane.
Yeah, I don't know what to do.
Fuck racists.
So, we'll be back, but Jordan, until then,
we have a website and all that stuff.
Indeed.
But more importantly, let's go out on a positive note.
Ooh, we gotta hear it.
And this is another track from DJ Danarki.
DJ Danarki, hell yeah.
Thank you so much for creating this.
We'll catch you next time.
Daryl Rundis, blah, blah, blah.
Thanks.
We are the bad guys. Knowledge Fight. Knowledge Fight. Dan and Jordan. Knowledge Fight. Need
Money. Andy and Fansy. Andy and Fansy. Stop it. Andy and Fansy. Andy and Fansy. You're
on the air. Thanks for holding. Hello Alex. I'm a huge fan. I love your work. Knowledge
Fight. Knowledgefight.com. I love you.
You're on the air.