N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledgefight, knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying we are the bad guys.
Knowledgefight.
Dan and Jordan, Knowledgefight.
Riddle her, riddle her, riddle her.
I need, I need money.
Andy and Candace, Andy and Candace.
Stop it.
It's time to pray.
Andy and Candace, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a first-time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes.
I like to sit around, drink novelty beverages, and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh indeed we are, Dan.
Jordan.
Dan.
What's up?
I have a quick question for you.
Yeah, what's up?
What's happening?
My question for you today is, stayin' humble.
Hashtag stayin' humble.
Oh boy.
Look, I don't know a whole lot about classic rock.
Sure.
And apparently I really stepped in it, I thought, I said that, so I'm playing with fire by the
doors.
Yes, many people have pointed that out.
Yeah, boy.
I'll tell you what, a lot of backlash whenever you misstate something about music, and hey,
you know what?
That's on me.
I don't know a whole lot.
My parents were pretty restrictive with music growing up.
That's true.
As I've brought up in the past, my first album that I ever bought was Alanis Morissette's
Shagged Little Pill.
True, delicious.
And my mom made me return it, because it was a bad influence, and I think probably everything
by the Rolling Stones was a mysterious thing to me.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I discovered some Beatles songs from Beatles Rock Band.
I was gonna say.
That's the kind of level of naivete I have about that stuff.
If Alanis Morissette is a step too far, then I would imagine that the Rolling Stones' earlier
work is off limits.
My dad might be fucking around with Pete Seeger or something, you know?
That's where we're at.
You know, I've always put your dad in the secret prog rock genre of just like somebody
who when no one's around is like, time to listen to Yes, I'm gonna get in my favorite
chair.
I think he might like Steely Dan.
We'll have to talk about that.
Sure, sure.
As you can recall, his first concert was Blood, Sweat, and Tears.
He did like Chicago and some of that horn rock.
There was a time.
But I think it was because he, I don't know, was he in the marching band?
I can't remember.
Anyway, my point is I'm sorry to everybody who I disappointed by my non-knowledge of
songs.
It's okay, it's okay.
I will stand by my position that I don't like The Doors.
You know, I actually went back and listened, and at no point did you claim the song was
The Doors.
It could very easily have been a completely disconnected thought.
I was thinking about trying to play that game, but in the sake of sincerity and being above
board, I have to admit that I did fuck that up.
Anyway, Jordan, hashtag staying humble.
I have a simultaneous bright spot in Darkstone.
Dan, we had a lovely time.
We got together and watched Mortal Kombat.
Sponsored content.
Fantastic time.
And I have decided that it is the worst movie ever made.
I don't think it's the worst movie ever made, but I was disappointed as hell.
Yeah.
No, not because of the movie itself.
Oh.
But, and this is how I'm thinking of it, all right?
Godzilla versus Kong.
Do you know what I got?
I got Godzilla versus Kong.
Right in the name, right in the movie.
There it was.
It promised and it delivered.
And when I hear Mortal Kombat, I want a goddamn tournament, Dan.
This was what I was screaming most of the movie.
This was most of the movie.
Where is this goddamn tournament?
Yeah, and spoiler alert for Mortal Kombat, there's no tournament.
It's not a spoiler.
It is a warning.
Yeah.
And the thing that really bothers me is like, okay, I get it.
Some of these movies are such that like maybe the tournament will be in the third movie
or whatever.
Yeah.
I think that's cheap.
It's terrible.
But whatever.
Yeah.
It's not fair that this movie opens up making a big deal about how the fate of Earth depends
on this tournament.
On the tournament?
There is no tournament.
No tournament.
Infuriating.
It is infuriating.
We are going to lose that sponsorship money.
I don't think we're going to keep it.
The next MK12 video game will not be announced through us.
It was still fun though.
You know, I like the idea of getting overly excited for no reason, almost as a bit about
a movie coming out.
No, it was great.
And it was fun to do that and to watch a movie that was new.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's been a very long time.
We haven't watched a movie together in a long time.
It's been forever.
And this was your idea.
You were like, we're watching Mortal Kombat.
Not only my idea.
I insisted.
Yes, you did.
Yeah, it was great.
It was a great time.
Sure.
Yeah, it's not a terrible movie.
It's the worst movie ever made.
Oh boy.
Okay.
So Jordan, today we're back in the past.
As promised.
Good.
We're in 2003, continuing our march through that time to see what we can learn.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I realized as I was listening to this, that one of the things that I obviously am the
most interested in is seeing if that sort of bizarre Christian extremism exists within
him back then.
Sure.
He thinks he's fighting the devil.
Right, right, right, right.
That seems to be what I'm most interested in.
Yes.
Because if that's been going on for 18 years, someone should have, you know, taken care
of it.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
We should have a societal understanding that this guy thinks he's the fucking Messiah.
It has nothing to do with banking.
Totally, totally.
No, no, no, no.
The Fed?
Nuh-uh.
It's fighting the devil.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's complete nonsense with a little thin veneer of political intrigue in order to trick
people into thinking that what they're involved in isn't extremist religion.
Exactly.
So I was interested-
And we've seen signs and there have been simmering tensions, slight little bits that if you were
being ungenerous, perhaps you could put that in the holster.
Yeah, so I'm interested to see what happens here on May 6th, see if we can find any more
clues.
Ooh, that's nice.
And get a better picture of what's going on.
Let's see what happens.
First though, Jordan, we've got to give some shout-outs to some wonks.
Oh, that's a great idea.
So first, Joanna, and then the message here is that Jordan needs to livestream some Chrono
Trigger pretty please, you're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much!
And that's a good idea.
That's a great game.
We've got a request for you to stream.
Yeah.
Yeah, also scream some Chrono Trigger.
Next, if it's pronounced A-T-A-T, then TIE fighters are now T-I-E fighters.
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, but also, I don't want a flame war developing through this, this is not how
we do this.
Simmering controversy.
This is not how we do this.
Ed H., thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
That's actually pronounced E-D-H, Dan.
Thank you very much, Ed.
And then, I'd like to give some shout-outs to some technocrats.
First we got Joel C., thank you so much, you are now a technocrat.
Dan, I love you, but the Rolling Stones wrote Play with Fire, not The Fucking Doors.
Thank you so much, you're now a technocrat.
And Brian...
You're now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate, that's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
We gotta go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, alright?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much, Joel, the music scolder, and Brian Seltzer.
Thank you very much to all of you.
I think I'm gonna change my bright spot to just now you staying humble.
Oh, you're great.
Thanks.
I love you.
So, Jordan, today, like I said, we're in the past, here is an out of context drop from
today's show.
Yes, I'm a maniac, yes, I love freedom, thanks for putting up with me, folks, I, uh...
So that's an out of context drop, you know, he's saying I'm a maniac, but he's not being
a maniac.
No, no, no, no, that's almost more terrifying of just somebody in a monotone, yes, I'm a
maniac.
No, but he hasn't been earlier in the episode before that, either.
Oh, not at all?
No.
What?
Yeah, like if you listen to present day shows, you'll be like, this guy is so subdued, and
he's like, I'm sorry, I'm being crazy.
No, you're not.
Wow, that's interesting.
This is the first serialized content we've got, where he's referencing the fact that
he has been a maniac in the past.
At least we're aware of the past in this time period.
In the future, I will be so nuts that I have to apologize now.
Yes, exactly.
So he starts off the show, and I honestly think, I'm working on a theory, this is another
thing I'm tracking as I'm going back to the past, and I think Joe Rogan might have ripped
off Alex.
All right, my friends, we have a powerful broadcast for you today.
Just masses of vital information developing on the police state, on the thought crime
front here in the home land.
We also have Bechtel, that wicked organization, it's now coming out in the mainstream news
that Bechtel is big with the bin Laden's.
Well, of course, you don't build anything in the Middle East unless you are with the
CIA.
And you became the bin Laden British intelligence family.
So I think Rogan might have stolen calling his show powerful from Alex.
This is 2003, this is before the Rogan experience started.
Oh yeah, for sure.
The powerful Joe Rogan experience.
Powerful Rogan.
Got a powerful broadcast here.
Oh boy, I don't think so.
So let's talk about the Bechtel group.
Sure.
So the story here that Alex is talking about, it begins with a piece by Jane Meyer in the
New Yorker, where she covers a connection between the bin Laden family and the Bechtel
group.
Quote, the global construction and engineering company to which the US government recently
awarded its first major multimillion dollar contract to reconstruct war-ravaged Iraq.
This was because the bin Laden family had invested about $10 million in a company called
Fremont Group, which began as a subsidiary of Bechtel, but had been a separate entity
since 1986.
Some of the board members of Bechtel were also board members of Fremont, but they weren't
connected businesses, so an investment in one isn't necessarily an investment in the
other.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's a lot of reasons to point fingers at Bechtel and suspect they're not above board
in their dealings, but this tenuous connection to the bin Laden family is not one of them.
Even if you connect them concretely to Fremont, then you still need to demonstrate how the
money the bin Laden family invested in Fremont has any connections to the actions of Osama
bin Laden.
Yeah.
There's so much work that you still need to do to make this a sensible conspiracy, and
all Alex is doing is just pointing at someone else's headline and then misconstruing it.
I can't think of anything more like, oh, I heard that the Bechtel group was into some
shit or I'd be like, oh yeah, of course they were.
Most businesses commit financial crimes of some sort.
I don't think they're financing terrorism.
That's more expensive than just committing financial crimes.
Well the conspiracy that they're sort of trying to dance around without explicitly saying
it is like, so this Bechtel group, they do a lot of construction projects, multi-million
dollar reconstruction projects.
So Osama bin Laden, they built the twin towers and they were actually fake and they were
made, and it was a small model that was, no, no, okay.
It's that like the Osama bin Laden funding of this is related to causing the need for
the construction.
Sure, sure, sure.
You have a closed loop of investment.
I gotcha.
That's sort of the conspiracy that's being hinted at without actually overtly saying
because it's like, okay, no, hold on.
If you were to actually assert that, people would be like, you can't prove any of this.
That's outrageous.
Yeah.
But if you hint at it like Alex is doing, then you know, you can kind of get away with
it.
Pretend you've proven a case when you haven't done anything of the sort.
Follow the money.
There's a few million invested in a small company and that's terrorism.
Okay.
All right, fine.
Yeah.
Okay.
So Alex is this guy who has always been right about everything and he's just like just waiting
to be proven right all the time.
All the time.
Also, a passport will carry eye prints.
We'll get to that.
Even WorldNetDaily admits it.
I wasn't going to cover it yesterday when the Toronto Star was saying it because I knew
it would come out in other conservative publications.
We like to go from it from that angle because we know how the liberals are.
Turns out what we told you about a month ago was completely true.
So it's interesting to see how clearly above the left-right paradigm Alex is back in 2003.
Can't trust any liberals.
No, totally seems like a guy who is consistent about how the left-right thing is just an
illusion.
Unfortunately, he doesn't seem like a dishonest, manipulative, extremely right-wing asshole.
The truth is that Alex does dislike the left and the right at this point in time.
You can tell that.
But it's important to recognize what his complaints are.
He hates the left because he hates them.
He hates the right because he doesn't feel like they're far enough to the right and that
they're secretly on the left.
Right.
Also, 18 years later and our passports do not include eye prints.
Chalk that one up in the column of things Alex has not always been right about.
Yeah.
So in this time period, Alex wants to hear George W. come out and be like, segregation
now, segregation then, you know, and then he'd be well above the left-right paradigm.
Certainly beyond it.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
So we have another echo of the past that certainly plays in the present day quite a bit and that
is the idea that if you pay with cash somewhere, you're going to go to prison.
Well, sure.
So paying cash triggers alert for terrorism in the new world.
This is out of the Virginia pilot.
Paying cash anywhere is now a terrorist act.
They'll be phasing it out soon.
So that has not happened yet.
I mean, didn't India phase out all the paper money?
Didn't Narendra Modi just be like, one day he was just like, no paper money.
I'm not sure if that's been a full and total phasing.
Yeah, well.
I know that during COVID, there's been a lesser use of money.
Well, for sure.
We still use paper money.
We do still use paper money.
Totally fine.
I used it earlier to purchase the drink that I am enjoying right now.
Yeah.
I was kind of suspicious about this and it takes him until the end of the episode to
actually talk about what this article is about.
Well, sure, sure.
So I'm just going to jump forward now so we can close this with.
Okay.
So we're doing this in what it sounds like a really poorly written attempt at humor,
but also no, but also at like, like a editorial kind of thing.
Sure.
And here's basically what's going on, but a polite equivalent of your money's no good
here.
Arrived in the mail the other day in the form of a note from the Sachs department store
folks.
The only reason we have an account with them is that my wife once said she wanted to get
some Sachs and I hardly agree, only to learn that as a mutant Midwesterner, I'd once again
misinterpreted her soft Virginia accent.
Those women in Virginia do have pretty voices, fine Southern ladies.
Anyway, the note from Sachs said that henceforth, it would not accept cash as a form of payment
on store accounts in any form over $300.
So that's the story.
Some guy was, he learned that at Sachs, they don't accept cash on things over $350.
I'm so infuriated by that.
And there's a little bit of a, that's how with sexy Alex's show used to get.
That's so fucking annoying.
I just can't imagine one opening something from Sachs in the mail that goes in the garbage.
Sure.
That's too caring if you can't buy something more than $350 with cash.
That's fine.
Yeah.
That's totally fine.
Sure.
That's slightly annoying to people buying things more than $350.
It's also, if I were someone who was running a store like that, I might be suspicious of
someone paying a thousand dollars for something in cash.
Yeah, of course.
I might be.
Of course.
Why wouldn't you be?
I mean, I wouldn't judge them too much, but I'd be like, this money might be dirty.
No, I mean, if somebody walks up to you, they're like, Hey, I want to buy this car for 20,000
cash and I don't want you to give my name, you would be at least a little suspicious.
Yeah.
There might be a reason.
Right.
So Alex gets to talking some more about the Bin Laden family.
He does not cover this story about Bechdel in depth or anything, but he does ramble a
bit about the Bin Laden, how he's CIA.
I love the song, I love the song Ramble On.
Do you know who did that?
Doors.
It was the doors.
One would have to hide on the dark side of the moon to not know that Bin Laden is CIA,
to not know that his family, it was set up by British intelligence over 70 years ago,
that they carry out dangerous missions for the new world order all over the world.
And that if you want to build anything in the middle East, you go one place, the Bin
Laden, and that you're not allowed to build any type of military structure or pipeline
anything unless you go through the CIA and Her Majesty's Al-Qaeda.
That's a lot of stuff being said.
It does seem like there's a lot going on there.
Yeah, so there's this claim that Bin Laden is CIA, and you have to be on the moon to
not know that.
No, he's committing worldwide wet work as we speak.
I would say that Alex can't prove this at all.
Oh, you don't think so?
You know, the most he could probably do is say that people have theorized, and some believe
quite strongly, that Bin Laden received some training from the CIA back in the 1980s when
Bin Laden and the Mujahideen were fighting against Soviet communists.
You could even be pretty reasonable in assuming that some of that financial support from the
US did find its way to Bin Laden and his fighters in that period as part of Operation Cyclone,
aimed at fighting communism abroad with the help of proxy armies.
A strong argument could be made that the formation of Al-Qaeda was at least partially the effect
of blowback from these behaviors and operations.
The thing is that one can accept all the conventionally understood history of Bin Laden and his connections
to the US and the CIA and still recognize that the claims Alex is making are unfounded.
Saying that stupid geopolitical decisions inspired by the anti-communist hysteria of
the Reagan era led to unforeseen and severe consequences is not the same thing as saying
that Osama Bin Laden was in the CIA.
It's very different.
Yeah, it's wild to me to go to like, Osama is still working for the CIA, instead of immediately
assuming that the CIA made a stupid and short-sighted decision that is perfectly in line with literally
every decision that the CIA has ever made.
Yeah, yeah, it's pretty-
It makes sense.
There's narrative consistency there.
Yeah.
So the second claim that Alex is making in that clip is that there's no construction
that happens in the Middle East without the involvement of the Bin Laden family, which
is nuts.
Why?
How?
Well, Saudi Arabia is the majority owner of the Bin Laden Group Global Holding Company,
formerly known as Saudi Bin Laden Group.
They do have interest in a lot of construction and some incredibly high-profile projects
like the Jeddah Tower, but it's a little much to pretend that they run a complete racket
of all these construction projects in the Middle East.
I mean, he does not want to learn about sovereign wealth funds, I'll tell you that right now.
A Forbes Middle East estimate recently put the total value of projects in the Saudi Arabian
construction market at $1.2 trillion, and that's not even considering like 713 billion
in UAE projects, 578 billion in Egypt.
It's a fun story to tell that the Bin Laden family has a stranglehold on the market and
no one makes anything without their approval and that of the CIA, but it's not real.
It's just a cartoonish exaggeration of the news that was reported about the ties between
the Bin Laden family and the Bechtel Group that Alex is trying to inflate into being
something completely different than it actually is.
There are problems with the interconnectedness of these boards, and you can make some good
arguments about the way contracts are baited on and doled out, and the sort of conversations
are completely impossible.
If the point that you want to start from is that Bin Laden is CIA and his family runs
all this construction in the Middle East, it's a dead end if you're trying to understand
the real world, and that's what Alex is ushering his audience towards.
And also, like, the biggest construction groups in Saudi Arabia are run by the government.
It's not the Bin Laden family.
An incredibly corrupt government using this for their own personal gain in a way that
makes perfect sense if you know anything about the history of that government.
So Jordan, we've heard a lot about Alex predicting 9-11.
Sure, he nailed it.
We know that about a month before he did, Bill Cooper was saying the exact same stuff
on his show.
Sure.
Well, I mean, and several times before that, Osama himself was saying it, which is probably
why you could assume that it was a smart prediction.
Alex in this next clip talks a little bit about where he got some of his ideas that
the...
Osama bin Laden?
Nope.
Oh, okay.
Gary Hart, one of the chief neo-cons.
I mean, he's a great Democrat.
Of course, he's a leading neo-con now on the board there with the CFR and with Rudman.
And they said, they said, we're going to be hit by terrorists when big, tall buildings
are going to be in trouble.
He sat on hardball, 4-9-1-1, started laughing.
Chris Matthews laughed.
It was a CFR moment.
Lots of giggling around the table, lots of smacking, lots of rubbing hands together.
And I got on the air and I said, look out, New York's about to get it.
Call the White House, tell them to stop, to call off the attack.
So Alex saw Gary Hart and Chris Matthews having a moment.
Yeah.
Was this a segment on the show back then?
The CFR moment?
Yeah.
And that's your CFR moment for the day.
It was like the Daily Show at the moment of Zen.
Exactly.
Yes.
Chris Matthews had the CFR moment.
The CFR moment.
Yeah.
He had this blatant CFR moment happening in public, and he knew that there was going to
be...
Absolutely.
Unfortunately, if you listen to him in the present day, it's a slightly different story.
There's a different story?
Let me tell you, folks, I told you they were going to blow up the World Trade Center and
blame it on bin Laden.
God gave me a vision, and that's the little added ingredient of M4s everybody knows about.
It's not just that I know how to politically analyze all this stuff.
I can get on my knees and go to that place, and then the problem is you're just in God's
presence.
You don't care that now you can actually see everything going on in the universe, plugging
directly in to the source.
And there was that time that he went on Rogan's show and said that he got it from a dream?
Yes, there is that.
Well, there was a two-hour thing I did in July 25th, 2001, where I went ahead and went
on air and said, they're going to blow up the World Trade Center, blame it on the CIS,
have been live, then launch all these wars.
And I said, oh, I just got this from analysis information, but I kept having the dream of
the towers, smoking, all the rest of it.
I love the idea that in the present day, when he's talking to Rogan to try and be interesting,
he's like, I claimed back then that it was based on analysis, but I just had this dream
over and over again.
Now we're looking back at 2003 and it's him saying that it was based on analysis, based
on analysis.
So we can only conclude that in 2003, all this episode talking about the CFR moment,
he's lying.
Yes.
He's just had dreams.
100%.
Yep.
Wow.
Well, I mean, that's strangely conclusive proof that maybe he wasn't lying in the present.
He was, hey, hey, I was lying in the past, okay?
I'm coming clean on this one.
No matter what I do, it's based on a lie.
Yeah, I don't know.
That's so funny.
Did you ever notice how narcissists, as time goes on, the people in their stories tend
to disappear and it's just them?
You know, that whole Gary Hart thing just disappears into the past.
The CFR moment.
Yeah.
Is but a dream.
No, not a worry.
Not a worry.
In the present day, it was all me and God, baby.
God gave him a vision of literally everything that was going to happen because he was so
spectacular.
He gets hand jobs from the arcane angel Michael, yeah.
So we have this interesting dynamic in the past here where Alex is still trying to do
that whole pretending the left and the right are the same kind of game.
Yeah.
I think it's a choice to get into that a little bit, and I think it's a little silly.
Look, I've tried to explain the real political paradigm, okay?
If you're on the far left, you've got police and black ski masks, giant prisons, incredible
taxation, regulation control, a few strong men running things.
That's socialism, communism, whatever you want to call it.
That is what they do to us.
On the far right, police and black uniforms, giant prisons, a few strong men running things,
total control, high taxation.
Sounds like the past five years.
Look, until 100 years ago, the universities taught liberty, freedom, Magna Carta, Bill
of Rights.
It was a discussion of liberty versus tyranny.
It wasn't a discussion of left and right.
They've learned how to give you false choices.
They go, oh, do you want the left and the right when there's no difference in substance.
What?
I do like we can kind of boil it down to the conversation is still between liberty and
tyranny.
I'm not just pretending that the right doesn't associate with tyranny.
That's kind of your problem here.
You guys just tried to institute a theocracy.
I think we know what the left-right paradigm is, liberty versus freedom.
Yeah, it's a little bit strange.
I would say that that's a superficial analysis at best.
The way he's trying to depict the left and the right as the same is essentially meaningless.
And also, I don't know how he knows what they were teaching at universities 100 years ago.
Sure.
I would say that he is not somebody I would take as a credible source on that.
So yeah, that assessment I don't care too much about.
The left and the right, it's just simplistic.
You can take left-wing governments that have eroded into dictatorships and right-wing governments
that have also eroded into dictatorships, and then you can find some superficial similarities
between them.
Sure.
And I think that they're all the same.
For a policy wonk, you'd think that he would bring up specific things that they agree on.
No, just superficial things like there's big jails and people and police in black uniforms.
Okay.
All right, well, they solved it then.
Also, I want you to keep this in mind.
Typically speaking, if someone is trying to tell you that there's no difference between
X and Y, there's a really good chance that they're super on the side of X or Y.
Yes.
They're usually not in the middle or neutral.
It is strange.
They're usually an extremist for X or Y.
Usually they go from there's nothing between, there's no difference between X or Y, and
then they push you strongly towards X or Y.
Yes, it does seem like that is a pattern.
Yeah.
So Alex is trying to make this point that like the left and the right are the same,
you know, blah, blah, blah.
Sure.
Fascism and communism, same thing.
And here is how Alex makes that argument.
There's no difference in substance.
So call it fascism, call it communism.
It's all command and control, maybe a little bit different implementation system, but yeah,
you got Bush's grandfather getting detained and having to pay a million plus fine, Prescott
Bush for running almost all Nazi operations globally, over 53% of their steel production,
you name it.
Prescott, the Senator.
No help at all.
You've at the same time got the other families funding the communists.
I mean, this is what they do, folks.
So Alex is really bad at his job in clips like this.
Yeah.
Like what does he mean by Prescott Bush?
We're in almost all the Nazi operations globally.
Did he run the cloning program in Brazil too?
Totally.
Okay, good.
If you pay attention to that clip, you see one of the ways that Alex lies.
He takes something that is true, namely that Prescott Bush did indirect business with the
Nazis and then he embellishes it in a completely insane way, like claiming he ran almost all
their operations globally.
The assertion that Alex is making is nonsensical.
He's saying that Prescott Bush profiteered by trading with fascists and that other rich
families have profiteered by trading with communists, thus they must be the same.
Same thing.
It means nothing and is a silly argument.
No difference.
The argument that fascism and communism are the same because Alex believes them both to
be command and control systems is equally meaningless.
Alex throws out that term a lot, but it really is just a military term that the Joint Chiefs
of Staff defines thus, quote, commanding control is the exercise of authority and direction
by a properly designated commander over assigned forces in the accomplishment of a mission.
The term has a broader understanding outside of strictly military situations to mean someone
directs other people to get a task done.
It does seem very self-explanatory whenever you just think of words and how they mean
things.
If this is the big similarity that Alex has that he thinks makes communism and fascism
the same, I have a short list of other things that also must be the same as the Nazis.
School.
Yeah.
Any job where you have a boss.
True.
Hospitals.
Yeah.
Firefighting.
Construction.
NASCAR pit crews.
Nailed it.
Any sport that has a coach.
Correct.
Any form of acting where there's a director.
Every country in the world.
This list goes on and on.
Well, you didn't need to add that last one.
Sure.
By focusing on what he thinks is the only relevant factor in these two systems, Alex
is actually obscuring the much more real and much more important differences between them.
I think what Alex is trying to express is that communist countries have what's known
as a command economy, where the government decides what should be produced and how much
as opposed to letting the market decide.
This is a defining aspect of communism as an economic system.
The problem is when you try to juxtapose that with fascism, which isn't an economic system.
If you look at the fascist countries during World War II, for example, you can see massive
differences in the economic models that they employed.
What Alex is trying to express is that communism by definition involves a command economy and
that the Nazis also had a fairly command-based economy.
The difference is that within communism it's an element of the economic ideology, but in
the case of groups like the Nazis, it was just used because it was necessary to run
an economy almost entirely based on war.
We did the same thing during World War II.
Yeah.
It was a great idea.
It worked out for everybody involved.
This is not a meaningful, substantive connection between these two things.
As I was listening to this episode, I was trying to give Alex a fair reading, and it's
just what he's saying doesn't make sense.
No, I mean, based on his definition of command and control, the fundamental idea of laws
can't exist, because that is a designated body telling you what you can or cannot do.
That simply cannot exist in his concept of both.
I think if you went too far with it, yeah, you probably could get to that argument.
I think I could get him to that argument.
I don't think it would be hard.
Oh, another thing that's command and control.
Judges.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're right.
All laws should be abolished.
Okay, Alex, that wasn't quite my point, but fair enough.
So the thing, though, is that socialism always leads to fascism.
You want to use these half-baked political terms, communist, socialist, fascist, I'll
use them.
Half-baked?
And to use them, and more accurately, socialism leads to fascism.
Over and over again, the bankers fund a socialist communist movement to consolidate power to
get a big government, to get people dependent, and then it is transferred, once they're dependent,
to a fascist government.
Now that's what happens over and over again.
That's just not true.
But this conversation's probably impossible to have, because I don't think Alex is using
any of these terms in the way that anyone else would use them.
I don't know.
This is a completely made-up claim that Alex is peddling that he can't back up at all unless
he uses completely absurd definitions of the words socialism and fascism that I don't think
anybody would agree with him on.
Socialism is whatever it is he doesn't like, and if you can define it as something different
from that, he will tell you that that's the secret way they talk about it, to cover up
that what they actually mean is socialism.
Sure.
Yeah.
So Alex, one of the big breaking points in his career, one of the times that he...
Also, real quick.
Yeah.
He realized the idea that communism is half-baked.
One of the most documented and argued about in books over and over and over again, refined
and reinterpreted things, is half-fucking-baked.
Karl Marx made it through three-quarters of Das Kapital and was like, eh, that'll do.
Look, I tried.
Yeah, exactly.
I'll put it out there and everybody else can finish the last 40 pages if they want.
There's a salient difference between I disagree with this and it's half-baked.
Yeah, it's half-baked.
Yes.
That is fake.
Sorry.
I needed to beat that dead horse real quick.
Hey.
I say nay.
No.
So Alex broke into Bohemian Grove, right?
Sure.
Yes, he did.
And you know, we've heard a lot of stories of him talking about his heroics.
And now that we're in the future, he did it completely by himself with no other journalist
there whatsoever who were also documenting the situation.
Oh, you might be surprised to hear this then.
Oh.
I mean, you can't write stuff this crazy.
I didn't believe in Bohemian Grove.
I'd read about it.
I'd heard about it.
I didn't believe it.
I'd read mainstream news articles.
The British media says, Mr. Jones, we'd like to get you to sneak in.
We really can't do it.
But we're afraid to do it, Mr. Jones.
We know you do things like this.
Would you like to sneak into the Grove?
I snuck in and I saw it, folks, okay?
I saw it with my own two eyes.
I got video of it.
Alex in the present day would like to say that he was the first person to ever break
the story wide open.
Oh, of course, of course.
Here he is in 2003 talking about how he'd read about it in the mainstream news before.
And in fact, the British media approached him to do the story.
He did not think of this by himself whatsoever.
Hey, Alex, we hear you're a weirdo.
He would never do it had he not had the push from the British media.
Yeah, these are just some of these little differences between past versions of stories
and present.
Yeah, it seems like things change.
Sure.
Alex in the present is weird sponsors.
Alex has a herb store or like, I don't know, I guess they have some colloidal silver and
stuff that they sell that he's running an ad for.
And it ended in a way that shocked me.
Sign up on the website and receive our 104-page catalog and a current Herbal Healer newsletter
free.
Simply log on to herbalhealer.com.
Check out our online member testimonials and our hundreds of exceptional products.
We have been working hard since 1988 to save the remnant.
That's herbalhealer.com, your website for safe, effective, natural alternatives and
education.
What?
Is this a Christian identity herbal shop?
Oh, no.
We're going to send you our 104-page catalog.
Also, we've defeated the Zardons and if you call this number, we will be able to send
you this catalog.
Wait, you shouldn't have thrown the Zardons in there.
What did you just say?
Yeah.
We're trying to save the remnant.
That's interesting code to be in this commercial this far back.
It seems like maybe Alex was, I mean, why would you have that as a sponsor if they weren't
like a Christian identity type of herbal shop?
Sure.
Yeah.
Natural place for us to advertise.
Why would you shoehorn that into your commercial?
Very weird.
Yeah.
I can't get over the idea of like Kellogg's just... Cornflakes, they're great.
The thousand year war almost ended and if you want more Kellogg's cornflakes, like,
wait, what did you just say?
We will defeat the devil with my lucky charms.
You can't just toss that in there, man.
What are you doing?
It is strange.
So Alex is having a tough time with the Iraq war and all this, partially because he hates
the people who were doing it.
Sure.
Vis a vis George Bush.
Naturally.
And all that.
And I think that by free talking a little bit too much, I think that Alex reveals certain
ways in which his ideology is inconsistent with what he wants the audience to believe
it is.
I mean, the government was leaving us alone and not trying to dumb our kids down and not
trying to ship heroin and cocaine in and not doing all these things.
They wanted to go invade a bunch of countries and, you know, bring them real republics and
really have elections.
I'd go, well, man, you know, maybe so.
Violates what George Washington said about, you know, staying out of other hemisphere,
but okay.
But no, you don't destroy everything that makes America America.
So Alex seems like he's fine with the idea of colonialism.
Yeah, it does seem like that.
Regime change, installing democracies abroad.
Sure.
Only in the case that the government wasn't doing the things that he doesn't like.
Right, right, right.
So I guess his opposition can't possibly be to meddling in the affairs of other countries
or regime changing nation building.
That is something that he is hypothetically okay with.
But he will pretend that he's not.
Yeah.
I would be interested to know what Washington would consider a hemisphere.
Alex's argument against the Iraq war seems to be vaccines.
Yeah, I was going to say, it does not seem to...
This is not sensible.
No, no, no, no.
It doesn't seem like he's like, hey, hey, we should be colonizing Central South America
is what we do.
No other hemispheres, Washington.
No, I think he's saying that if our country was run the way I want it to be, we could
go ahead and put in democracies around the world.
Sure, of course.
I just don't like these people.
It's an incoherent and silly ideology that runs into problems really fast.
Yeah, it is.
It's the same thing with him wanting to buy Greenland when Trump is in office.
For sure, for sure.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's just steal it.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's that kind of nonsense of like, oh, that is kind of what you believe.
As long as it's your idealized Christian authoritarian government, you'd be totally fine if it was
one world government.
Of course.
You'd be totally fine with all kinds of colonial expansivism.
Well, then everything's one hemisphere, Dan, if it's all America.
Don't care at all about the idea of freedom or self-determination and bullshit.
It is like, okay, I get that we both don't want the Iraq war, but I don't want it because
millions of people are going to be slaughtered for no reason, and you don't want it because
you don't like the guy?
I don't think we necessarily agree.
I don't like tax.
Yeah.
I don't think that's a good... So Alex does an ad pivot here, and it's very
sensible.
It makes sense.
This is kind of how... I'm not offended by this necessarily.
Because what he's doing is advertising his products, which are like his DVDs and stuff.
It makes sense for him to be like, there's more information on this.
It makes more sense than him constantly throwing to pill commercials.
Yes, it does.
Because at least there's still hypothetical information to be found here, although I think
he's lying.
Well, some of us aren't afraid.
We'll stand up for humanity because it's people like us, the only reason we still have humanity,
to counterbalance the just insane filth out there.
Before I end this shower, if you believe in what we're doing, you want to fight the New
World Order, you want a tool to fight the New World Order, get my videos.
I produced eight of them, and we proved the globalists carried out 9-1-1, and we proved
they're going to carry out more, and we proved that they're enslaving you and your family.
So on his documentaries, he proved that the globalists carried off 9-1-1, 9-11.
I don't recall that.
But do you recall when he did that interview a couple years back with Patrick Bette-David
and Patrick Bette-David asked him who did 9-11?
I do recall that.
Who was really behind the 9-11 with what you've studied over the years and what you've spoken
about?
I don't know who's behind it.
Oh, well, you should watch your DVDs then.
You should watch the proof that you made.
It seems like you would stick to the proof.
Yeah, I would say that maybe you were wrong, or maybe you didn't prove anything.
No, I'm just trying to, okay, my documentary's going to prove everything.
The World War is coming.
Now, I mean, obviously the capital gains tax should be about 40, 50%, and that's why
we're like, wait, no, no, no, you threw the snot sequitur in there.
It's fun.
It's fun for him to forget that he proved who did 9-11.
Yeah.
It seems like a big thing to remember.
Oh, well.
Who did it?
Alex doesn't know.
I think I've watched those DVDs, and I don't think I know either, based on his proof in
quotes.
Yeah, I would like those redacted pages is what I want, Dan.
So here's our first indication of something not being quite right in Austin.
Sure.
Alex is going out to break, and he says this.
Again, that's 888-253-3139, defending the Republic against the forces of Satan.
Uh-oh.
Okay, there it is.
The forces of Satan.
And you could pull that off as being like, oh, look at him, he's making that exaggeration.
Ah, come on, we've all used flowery language.
Yeah, and it's going out to break on like a pump-up kind of thing.
Yeah, totally.
It sounds like a reasonable thing that you would say if you were just pumped up.
And it also does feel like this is a little bit more than I've been giving a pass to a
lot of stuff.
It seems like I'm fighting against the forces of Satan.
He's not as literal, he's not saying that as part of a 15-minute rant.
Sure, sure.
It is just going out to break, but it made me worry.
It could be hyperbole, of course.
Of course, however, you can't miss the forest for the trees, if you will, Dan.
Yeah, yeah.
So Alex goes to calls, and I think I've brought this up before, but there's such a sensible
formula to his show at this point, and that is that he'll rant about something for a little
while, and then go to calls, and then maybe the caller says something that he can talk
about for a little bit longer, he'll read a headline or two, then go to a call, get
maybe a reaction, that'll lead into a rant.
There is just a fluidity to it that makes sense.
Whereas now, it's such fucking long chunks of him saying nothing.
Stream of consciousness chaos, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So it is, it flows much easier.
And so this caller that Alex goes to at this point in the show brings up Rush Limbaugh.
What do you think Alex thinks about Rush Limbaugh?
He's grateful for someone giving him something to steal.
Nope.
Oh.
I was listening the other day, driving in my car, and I happened to turn on Rush Slackjaw,
and he was talking about it.
You turned into the ultra-liberal, and the neo-con, and Bush is a communitarian.
You know what the dictionary 20 years ago said about communitarian?
No.
One who promotes communist systems.
Bush's press release for the election, I'm a communitarian, what do the communitarian
Rush Limbaugh say?
So apparently Rush Limbaugh's a commie.
Yes, the communitarian Rush Limbaugh.
Yes.
Noted.
The left commie Rush Limbaugh.
The leftist among leftists, Rush Limbaugh.
Right standing next to Bill Maher is people who are leftists beyond all reason.
Yeah, see, I mean, you get this sense of like, okay, here's where the denial of the left-right
paradigm is.
Rush Limbaugh is a fucking commie.
Yeah, just take a hit at somebody on the right, and then you're good, you know?
And it doesn't have to be a substantial hit, you can just be like, that guy's a real dick.
Hey, I'm above the left-right paradigm.
So Alex is talking to this caller, and they bring up going to the World's Fair in the
70s, I think.
Sure.
And they might have seen some Russian propaganda about ecological efforts.
Okay, okay.
I don't know.
I don't know what's going on anymore.
Talking about your lies and propaganda, I remember in 1974 I went to the World's Fair,
and the theme of that World's Fair was ecology, and the worst exhibit there, the most propagandized
exhibit was the Russian exhibit at that World's Fair, and you go through the Russian exhibit
from one end to the other.
All they said was how wonderful it was in Russia, there was no pollution, the waters
were clean, the air was clean, all this stuff, it was exactly the opposite of what was reality.
But now we're turning into the same kind of a system that I saw in 74 in the World's Fair
in the Russian exhibit.
Well, I'll be honest, if it was a new world, I'd leave, but I love America.
What did you just say?
And my family's been in the Texas independence fight, and for the battle for independence
in 1776, but I gotta tell you, I'd be moving down there, I'll tell you.
Well, I'll tell you, we need some states to break off, break away, get out of this thing,
and get back to America, call it the real United States, because this isn't the federal
government.
Why?
People running the federal government, they are the enemy combatants.
Yeah, the federal government's enemy combatants.
Sure.
Now, the thing that I think is interesting about that clip, and the reason that I pulled
it out was because this caller is expressing this idea that they saw this Russian display
at the 74 World's Fair, and it is a delusional portrayal of what was really going on in the
Soviet Union.
And one of the things that he brings up is, like, there's no pollution, and then you flash
forward to the present day, and Alex talking about how coal power plants are all totally
clean.
No pollution, yeah, Russia is just a perfectly clean thing, yeah.
It's so interesting to see Alex becoming this thing that this caller is describing as being
this horrendous act of propaganda in 1974 that he still remembers in 2003.
Just don't care.
Alex is completely delusional about accepting and recognizing and dealing with the sort
of more bad history of the United States, to the point where he's even worse than probably
whatever that Soviet Union Russian display was.
Yeah, that is one of those things about fascists, is that once you're in power, all of the past
is changed to whatever you want, you know?
As long as Trump is running the United States government, the United States has never ever
done anything wrong.
And saying so is an attempt to undermine Trump.
Exactly, yeah.
Oh, you're gonna bring up slavery again?
It's America, come on, man.
You're trying to ruin the exuberance that is being felt.
You're screwing up our good time, man.
We're trying to slaughter innocents, and you're really making us bummed out.
Yeah, it's very strange.
By that I mean it's not strange at all.
So hey, we got this idea that, left, right, same thing.
Sure.
Last two presidents, Clinton, Bush.
No difference there.
Both puppets.
Sure.
But were they equally responsible puppets?
That's, what?
What?
Again, I have nothing really against Bush.
Bush is more of a puppet than Bill Clinton.
Bill Clinton was really in there, enjoyed all of it.
Bush is really just reading off a teleprompter, and hey, thanks daddy, it's great to be able
to preside him in the new world order in the end of America.
So yeah, we've got these two presidents who are both puppets.
Right.
The left and the right.
Sure.
But somehow still the one that's on the left is worse.
Right, right, right.
Because he enjoyed it.
So we're in a Pinocchio situation where Clinton is when Pinocchio was turned into a donkey
for a while.
Sure.
And W is still the puppet, but he is not yet a real boy.
And then Trump is the real boy?
Yes, I guess.
I think that's what happened.
I think I've figured it out.
Yeah, it's just remarkable to look at this and be like, oh yeah, this act of the left
and the right are the same is so thin.
It's so transparent.
Yeah, you've already done it over and over and over again.
Almost any time there's a comparison between someone who's on the left and someone who's
on the right, you can see like some sort of derision towards both, but the left is way
worse.
Oh yeah.
He enjoyed it.
Their inclusion is what makes them evil.
So Bush, he gave a warning to the U.S.'s supposed enemies and Alex believes that these are actually
the globalist's enemies and here we get another wonderful prediction from Alex.
Also Bush fires warnings at U.S. enemies, you mean globalist enemies, saying that other
countries are next, so if they are going into other countries, they'll need to be a convenient
terror attack.
Blamed on someone though, don't worry.
Much larger Gary Hart and other CFR people have told us with total confidence and then
we'll call them profits when Dallas or Denver or Cleveland get hit by smallpox, as Gary
Hart said on national television on hardball, well he said that before 9-1-1, he just said
that on Hattie and Combs.
So this is one of the problems with relying on quote-unquote CFR moments and that sort
of thing as being predictive of what's going to happen in the world.
When Gary Hart says something like we're worried about smallpox cases in an American city,
and you read that as there's going to be, to justify another war, you're just making
shit up.
And that's what we see here.
No, and it's the most powerful type of making shit up propaganda, wherein somebody trying
to protect you from a thing that's happening, you have turned into the person trying to
cause the thing that's happening, thus ensuring that the thing they're worried about almost
certainly will happen, and then you get to bitch about how they didn't see it coming.
And then you have these kinds of instances of things that just litter Alex's career,
that just things never happen, and we're just totally talking out of his ass, he just pretends
that that isn't a bulk of his career.
Well the last time I visited Denver, there were about four people there after the smallpox
epidemic destroyed most of the city, but they were really cool to hang out with.
There's only lone survivors.
They did try and eat my leg.
So look, we get another caller.
Sure.
This guy's got an interesting idea.
Naturally.
And by interesting I mean very stupid.
Terrible.
Yeah.
So stupid that Alex has to end the conversation by saying, I don't speculate.
No.
Let's talk to Andrew in North Carolina, Andrew you're on the air, welcome.
Hi Alex, how you doing?
Good sir.
I had an idea, I don't know if you'd support me on it, the idea popped in my head a while
back while I was tying down a little glass.
Anyway, the idea was how much of a coincidence that a little girl gets kidnapped in Utah
and just so happens that her last name is Smart.
And the fact that there's a Smart Chip out there and now her parents and Amber's parents
have signed the Amber Alert Bill, which turns over all radio, TV, billboards to FEMA and
they're now flashing report terrorist, report guns.
And then it turns out that she's related to a Congressman and all this other stuff.
And then there's some weird freak weather.
And yeah, the whole thing stinks to high heaven, but I don't know, sir.
I don't speculate.
You were just speculating.
Wow.
Hey, listen, I'm going to take your wild, insane speculation and I'm going to speculate
on that, but listen, I don't speculate.
I'm going to rattle off things that are meant to give justification to speculation, but
man, I do not speculate about whether or not the Elizabeth Smart kidnapping was an elaborate
globalist plot to put chips in everybody.
I would never speculate on that.
I mean, obviously that plan is in play and they could do it at any point in time.
And you know what?
I was told there were going to be Silicon chips, turns out they're going to be made
of Amber.
Yeah, exactly.
Amber.
Smart chips.
Fine.
Yeah.
I think that's the type of theory if somebody comes at you with, you just have to roll up
a newspaper and be like, no, bad.
I think that I would love to just like, God, my dream job at Info Wars just keeps changing.
Now it's, I want a clip of Alex saying, I don't speculate.
And then every time you start speculating, it's going to hit a button.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't speculate.
The big red button.
Boom.
Uh oh.
Stop it.
It's just a repeat until the speculation ends.
Yeah.
So 9-11 was proven by Alex to have been carried out by people who can't remember who they
are though.
That was in the past.
Yep.
But there are some signs, there's some telltale signs of how you know that the man was behind
it.
Sure.
Why else would they have the Chicago Mercantile exchange on 9-1-1, the one year anniversary
come up 9-1-1 point zero zero zero zero zero zero.
What?
I saw the article that said 9-1-1 point zero.
I went and looked up on the Chicago Mercantile, the close of that day.
The zeros went on basically forever.
That's never happened.
That's impossible.
But what you're thinking, that was just a fluke.
Oh, it came up 9-1-1 at the New York Lottery on 9-1-1, one year anniversary.
Just their little mark.
Hey, we control the lotteries, we control the exchanges, the speculation exchanges,
down to the point they close it.
So I'm not sure that they, I believe this, it sounds like an urban legend kind of situation.
It does.
For one thing, according to the CME website, which is the name of the Chicago Mercantile
exchange when they're listed as a publicly traded entity, the CME group, they didn't
go public until December 5th, 2002, when they had their initial public offering of stock.
They wouldn't have even been a stock price for CME on September 11th, 2002, since it
wasn't traded.
Oh, that was a real sneaky move by the globalists.
Yeah, I don't know what he's referring to.
They really nailed it.
I don't know.
I think he might have seen a meme or something.
This level of bullshit might as well, oh, okay, okay.
Did you see that George W. Bush has been complimenting people a lot lately?
Yes.
Another word for that is lauding.
Do you see what I'm saying?
Oh shit.
So, and he's been doing it repeatedly over time, so you could say he's been lauding people.
What does that mean?
We nailed it.
It means something.
He is been lauding.
So people have looked into the lottery thing, and that one actually is true, but it doesn't
actually mean anything.
The state lottery in New York does, they pick two, pick three winners each day.
The numbers.
Sure, sure.
The sets of three numbers.
Yeah, yeah.
And the other combination coming up is one in a thousand.
Because there are two drawings, the odds of 911 hitting on any given day are one in 500,
which really, it's an interesting coincidence, but it's far from proof that the globalists
did it to show that they control lotto numbers.
Yeah, it's fun, but you might as well use that as also like, oh, I had to call 911 that
day.
It's a miracle.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's just weird how much of Alex's supposed proof of things relies on just denying that
coincidences exist.
Yeah.
Well, they don't.
It's a little annoying.
There's no such thing as a coincidence.
Because there's no real way to argue that.
You could be like, well, the statistical odds of that coming up are not really that insane,
and I don't know what you're talking about with the mercantile exchange.
Sure, yeah.
But yeah, all right, go off.
Anyway, Alex is talking to this caller, and they got into an argument, this caller and
someone in their life, because they didn't agree on the Federal Reserve.
Sure.
Right?
Well, who can?
Well, there was an interesting theory about what was going on there.
You guys were having a boring conversation?
You bet.
They don't need any facts.
They just need to feel good.
Exactly.
Yes, and the conversation I had, I was basically being yelled at and told.
I tried to tell this guy, you know, because it went in so many different directions at
one time.
I was telling him, you know, your income tax monies go to the IMS and Federal Reserve and
so on and so forth, and no, no, they don't, no, they don't, you know, it's just a loud
vehement denial makes it true.
And uh...
Now, wait a minute, though, if he didn't have some problems subconsciously, the subconscious
is much more powerful.
What is happening?
It's a powerful processor, God gave us, it knows the truth, whereas the conscious doesn't.
Don't do this.
This guy, if he'd laugh at you if it wasn't serious, you know, me thinks they protest
too much.
Why do they get so excited then?
So I guess...
Because you guys are the worst to talk to!
I guess anyone arguing with you is an indication that you're right now.
Yeah, exactly!
Because if you're wrong, they'll just laugh at you.
Somebody says no.
What?
Oh, God.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
That's outrageous.
Yeah.
So this guy, this caller, he was told by someone to just believe the news.
Sure, sure.
And I bet that's not what this person said to them.
It's doubtful.
But Alex's response to it is so telling.
I wanted to lay a quote on you from this guy.
I believe in too many conspiracy theories, and you just gotta watch the news and believe
it.
That's what he told me.
And he's a successful businessman.
That's right, I'm successful, I'm important, I'm part of this power system.
You just need to watch the news and believe it, and be part of it.
I'm reporting you, you're with Al-Qaeda.
Nazi Germany, Nazi Germany.
So, I don't believe that this caller is reporting things accurately that his friend just said,
watch the news and believe it.
Kind of doubtful.
But, you know, let's imagine that that's actually someone's position.
Sure.
That is a crippling level of naivete and lack of critical thinking that you're approaching
information that's coming to you with, and I would be opposed to what this supposed person
said.
You know what, I would even argue that I would be above the left-right paradigm in saying
that that is a bad way of consuming media.
Sure.
Now, Alex has a couple of options in terms of addressing the situation.
You could say something like that, like, hey, your friend should engage more critically
with the information that's coming to you, and you should as well.
Or he could have blanket defiance.
I think that would be a better way to go.
Which I think is just as stupid.
I think it's just as stupid to mock the idea of ever listening to the news and being like,
it's Nazi Germany.
It's not, it's the pendulum swinging too far the other direction.
And that's what he wants.
Yeah, it doesn't matter how you get to consume whatever it is uncritically, whether it be
eating it or denying it.
Yeah, whether it's CNN or World Night Daily, like, he wants them to accept World Night
Daily uncritically.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah.
Of course.
And hostility towards things that are saying the other.
Well, you can trust them, and you can't trust anybody else, because it's Nazi Germany day.
Sure, sure.
Yeah.
It's not a bad path, and I would say that he's not setting up his listeners for success.
It's a strategy that won't get you into a better engagement with information.
It'll just make you believe something else.
You'll be tricked by something else.
It'll make you a captive to your information source, and then you'll be like, oh, I should
give him money, because he's saving me from the rest of the evil media.
And then all of a sudden you're going to start believing that he's the Messiah, actually
fighting the literal devil.
And then he will believe that.
And then we're all out of control.
So Alex is right about something in this episode.
Interesting.
He is right that it's stupid that people say that they would die for George Bush.
I think that is stupid.
Mike Hanson does some camera work for me.
He got some video that I just finally saw this week.
He's had it for a month.
They were having the pro-war Bush rallies downtown in Austin.
They had like 30 people there.
Mike walks up.
I wasn't there.
I was with one other person and says, hey, why are you for the war?
And the guy just screams, Mike Hanson, you're with Alex Jones.
I will, and he bleep, bleep, you're, you're hined in if you don't say you're for George
Bush and started threatening to assault Mike.
This is on tape.
And Mike goes, hey, you're on camera.
And he goes, and Mike goes, wait a minute.
So what do you think of George Bush?
I'll die for him, I'll die for him, I'll die for him, I'll die for him, I'll die for him.
I was like a Iraqi just screaming they love the leader because the media said so.
And, you know, they're mindless slaves of the media and the neocons are controlling
them.
Jump into a time machine with me, Jordan.
Come to the present.
Yeah.
They can put a gun to my head and say, if you don't come out and say you hate Trump,
we're going to blow your brains out.
And I'd say, pull the trigger.
Okay, Alex, calm down.
Yeah.
Also, I love how dainty he's being.
This man was threatening to fight me.
He's threatening my camera man.
He came up to me and he used curse words and he said that he would hurt me physically.
I can't repeat these things because it's a family show and I actually kind of mean it
back at this point.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
God.
What a dick.
So Alex has another caller and this guy, he had a similar vibe to me as that, that one
caller who was like, it's 8 a.m. in China, time to get up.
Gotta drive to work.
Alright, alright.
That guy.
He's got a, he's got a Matthew McConaughey kind of vibe to him.
It's not the same vibe, but this was a caller who was like, I want to listen to you talk
some more.
Alright.
In the same way.
Larry, you're on the air.
Go ahead.
Hey Alex, good day.
How you doing?
Did you hear Jeanette Hanson this morning on the Peacock Channel?
Well, they call it the Peacock Channel, but if you strip his wings off, sure looks like
an oblique view of a horned owl to me.
Get him!
I love it.
Who the fuck are you, man?
That is great.
I just imagine that guy writing that out while he's on hold.
I was gonna say, that's not a turn of phrase that one just pops into mind.
Oh, the Peacock Network, it looks like an oblique horned owl to me.
That's well practiced, sir.
Yeah, that was, that's either a mirror or a thing you have said to a lot of people to
bore them.
Yeah, I wish his call was more interesting, but I did enjoy that.
That is nice.
He came out swinging.
Yeah.
Ah, that's good.
He gets to talking about a story that his cousin told him, and I don't know if this
is Buckley.
I don't think it is.
It could be any cousin.
Yeah, it must be another cousin.
And unfortunately, all, well, you'll see.
Okay.
My cousin, two Mondays ago, was sitting in my living room, been in the Army for 20 years.
He's an officer.
They were given a briefing this year.
They're all getting microchips, the entire armed services.
And then it goes into the general public, and they're telling them brace for more terror,
we'll have to give up all our rights, the Army's gonna run our lives, but the border
will stay wide open.
Okay, so 18 years later, the military isn't all chipped, right?
They are all chipped.
Ooh.
Yes.
So Alex was right about this?
Or was he wrong about this?
No, 100%.
Every single military member is chipped upon introduction.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know those guys, the recruiters at your high school?
Yeah.
And when they shake their hand, they are implanting you with a computer.
They have one of those little assassin's blades?
Exactly, yeah, yeah.
No, it's like a clown buzzer, you know?
But you get it, and they're like, ha ha, wasn't that a funny joke?
And then they stare deep into your eyes and program you.
Right, right.
And then, to get you out of your trance, a flower on their lapel squirts you with water.
Yes, it squirts you in the...
Yeah, yeah.
That's how you wake up.
And then, naturally, they slip on a banana peel, walking away from you.
Of course.
So everybody's getting chipped.
Uh-huh.
They're all getting this one to come around.
Right.
But this caller has verified Alex's story, because they have also heard that a military
friend of theirs is talking about how everyone's getting chipped.
Military friends are popular these days.
And Larry in Louisiana was saying he just talked to an E-8 that got back from North
Korea who said they're all getting their chipped, got the same briefing.
You know, that's Twilight Zone, folks, but you're not patriotic if you're against it.
Let me tell you what the tactic's gonna be.
The globalists are gonna blow stuff up and claim that anti-chipping, anti-biometric groups
are doing it.
And so if you're anti-chip, anti-world leader, you're with the terrorists.
Larry, you can see the script, can't you?
Yes, I see it exactly.
So, I mean, this is what I'm talking about when I say that this is just interactive improvisational
storytelling.
Yeah.
Alex is just coming up with a story for them to get excited about on this day.
Yes, I know exactly what you're talking about.
Now, the globalists are scripting this stuff, so that's how I can predict it.
I know that this is what's gonna happen, they're gonna blow up stuff and blame it on the anti-chip
people.
Naturally.
Okay.
Yeah.
Yep.
Anti-chip people.
Now, here's what's interesting.
What's interesting?
I think I would be opposed to mandatory chips.
Oh, yeah.
I haven't given it enough thought to really have a strong position on it, let's say, but
whatever direction I would fall on it after giving it some thought, I'd have a pretty
coherent position on it.
Yeah.
I would want a couple of assurances like mind control.
First question.
Are you gonna mind control me?
Right?
You can't ask that.
I've gotta ask that.
What else would I ask?
Well, I mean, obviously the answer is gonna be no, even if it's yes.
Yeah, but I gotta look them in the eyes.
Right.
I'll know if they're lying to me.
They're evil eyes.
Exactly.
You gotta look into the evil eye and then I can tell.
Yeah, sure.
Mind control, no good.
Yeah, exactly.
What else?
No mind control.
Electroshocks, no good.
No, I think I'd be fine with a little electroshock here and there, you know, but as long as it's
not somebody doing something, doing it for weird reasons.
Ooh, I think you're going to have to really litigate what's weird.
Well, again, we're going to sit here.
We're going to talk about it.
I'm going to look them in their evil eyes and we're going to hammer it out.
Our next bonus episode can be going over the conditions under which you approve of chips.
Yes, exactly.
Well, I'll have a full-
We'll really work this out.
Right out of contract.
But for Alex, he's supposed to be totally against it.
Yes.
He thinks that it's like the mark of beast stuff.
It's the mark of the beast.
Unfortunately, he's inconsistent as hell.
To be in the army, they want someone who will take a microchip.
I mean, I am some weird one, you know, you can see special forces getting one, but no,
the entire troops all for their identification, no, no, this is setting the precedent.
Wait, so, but why wouldn't special forces getting it be setting a precedent?
Well, you got to mind control special forces, Dan.
But you understand, this is silly.
This is nonsense.
I am staunchly opposed to giving microchips to people in the military unless they're in
special forces.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, obviously you want Green Berets to have computer chips.
That's just, that just makes perfect sense.
I don't understand why.
I don't get what the relevant differences between people in special forces, if the argument
is that Alex is trying to make, which is a big part of it, which is they give it to the
military.
That normalizes it.
So then it becomes something that goes to the citizens.
Right.
Now you could just take one step further and be like, they give it to special forces.
That normalizes it for the military and that normalizes it for the population.
No, no, no.
Slippery slopes only work if you start where I say this top is.
It doesn't make sense.
No, no, no, no.
Just cause we're starting in the middle of the slippery slope, meaning that we've already
had to go from somewhere to get here.
This is pretty dumb.
Yeah.
So 2003 was a very different time in the anti vaccination community.
Oh, that's good.
No, it wasn't.
No, I didn't think so.
It wasn't great then either.
No, I doubted it.
So some of these ideas about autism links with vaccination and like mercury and the
preservatives and stuff, it was a little bit less uniform in the anti-vax community.
They hadn't had a lot of the other, let's say maybe even stupider ideas shot down.
Right.
Was this...
Jenny McCarthy was...
I'm not positive about her timeline.
Yeah.
I don't know that either.
I'm not sure, but I do know that at this point there are anti-vax proponents who are making
the argument that mercury in the preservatives has a link to autism.
Sure.
Now at this point, Alex doesn't think that.
Alex is trying to stake a claim on something weirder in anti vaccination.
All right.
Okay.
That he will not stand by today, I don't think.
Boy believes a mercury-based preservative added to the vaccines during the 90s may have
caused the autism.
Uh-uh.
That's the cover story.
It's the hormone designed in a brain development hormone to attack cerebral cortex development.
Most of you just get an IQ reduction, people that compromise immune systems get severely
retarded or autistic.
Little gift from your government.
So Alex doesn't say what this hormone is, and I'm not sure.
I'm not going to go on a wild goose chase and then just assume that I found whatever
he's talking about.
But if he does get into this, we'll talk about it in greater depth.
But yeah, so the argument is being put forth to him that there is mercury in the vaccines
and stuff.
That is pretty close to his current position on anti vaccination.
Right.
Right, right, right.
That is safe territory for him now.
Sure.
But back then, he didn't have that.
He wanted another, he wanted his own version of this.
Yeah, he had to jump it up.
It wasn't just mercury, which is a natural occurring, it's a naturally occurring element.
You can drink gallons of that stuff, they're fucking with you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, what it is, is they grow hormones in labs for brains to then put in there and that's
what does it.
Yeah, I think that's interesting.
I would like to know what he feels about this now.
That would be interesting.
He believes that there's some weird hormone that's actually behind, and I wonder if he'd
like to interview some of his weird anti-vax friends about that.
Oh, that would be interesting.
See if they stand by that nonsense.
Yeah, what do you got?
So Alex gets a caller.
This made me so happy.
God damn, did this make me happy.
Was this back when Young Man House Phone was around?
No.
Oh.
This caller is the same person who called and Alex argued with him about the Republic
of Texas.
Okay, okay.
And Alex is clearly annoyed with this guy.
Sure.
And you don't really get, like, it doesn't become clear that Alex knows who he's talking
to until the end of this clip.
And that's when it just, this is great.
This is just so good.
All right.
Later on when this crap goes down, this bad stuff goes down, we need these people on our
side.
So just real quick as a sort of introduction, this caller has said that he took one of Alex's
films to the Aspen Sheriff's Department and he woke up the sheriff and everybody on the
force.
And so, like, now Aspen-
That really does sound like it happens, though, doesn't it?
I don't think so.
It feels like that's how they get-
I think it might happen where someone is like, hey, did you watch that DVD?
Blew my mind, man.
Real good.
Yeah, it killed it.
It was great.
Gotta go.
So anyway, that's what the beginning of this call is.
Well, we do.
I mean, I have nothing against police.
Standing with a constitutionalist and standing against the New World Order and the deception,
the lies, and the fraud.
I heartily agree with you.
What you did was just so- is this Aspen, Texas, or Aspen, Colorado?
It's Aspen, the Republic of Texas.
They call it Colorado, but it still belongs to the Republic of Texas.
No, I understand.
But-
The Northwest Territory.
So where is this in Texas?
This is up in the Rocky Mountain.
Yeah, that's what I said.
Is this in Texas, or is this in Colorado?
Well, they call it Colorado, but-
I understand, sir, but-
It belongs-
Okay.
Okay, Alex?
No?
Okay.
I know.
I think he called about this earlier a few days ago.
He did.
I like the thread that's going through these episodes that I'm getting to enjoy where Alex
is pissed off by Republic of Texas people.
It is nice.
I do appreciate that.
Because he has this whole thing that's like, Texas is its own country, it gets a seed.
But these other people are like, yeah, Texas is a country, and it involves a bunch of place
to the north.
Yes, I do.
I do.
We got most of New Mexico, Colorado.
I don't appreciate how that community is still allowed to have people that are too far out
there.
Y'all are crazy.
Don't judge them for being like, and also the Northwest Territory is ours too.
You are mad because your ideas look just as ridiculous as theirs, and theirs make you
feel ridiculous.
Yeah.
I think that is a part of it, and I think that something that I really enjoy is Alex's
ability to sort of play with the guy back then.
Yeah, that's true.
Like, Alex could not do that now.
No.
The idea of him sitting there and being like, is that Aspen, Texas, or Aspen, Colorado?
Yeah, him doubling down on like, hey man, just go ahead and say exactly what you and
I both know you're about to say.
I recognize your voice.
You know that you're the guy who pisses me off about the Republic of Texas.
Yep, yep.
I know, I'm gonna ask you this leaded question.
Hey buddy, hey buddy, Aspen, I know, I've heard a name of Aspen before, and is that
a city in Colorado, buddy?
Nope, Texas.
No, Texas.
So we get another caller, and this fella is really lauding Alex, been lauding him.
Nice.
About opposition to the Patriot Act.
Yes.
There have been some places that have passed resolutions, some cities, city councils, and
what have you.
If you listen closely to this clip, though, this caller is congratulating Alex for doing
something that he himself is literally saying was done by communists.
Well, the Democrat socialist, Steve Leal, the resolution's primary sponsor on the city
council, said if the EPA were talking about lessening water's quality standards, we'd
think it was a city issue, but if they're polluting our rights, it is also a city issue.
So this guy, you know, you did some good, and I wanted to commend you on it, and they
got your resolution, because I know at least a dozen people that send your resolution to
the city council and also to the county.
And so you got some positive results, and we want to thank you for it, and I'm really
proud that my communist city government decided to support the Constitution of the United
States.
Oh, isn't that cute?
He's calling these people super-left socialists who wrote the resolution.
You can't do that.
And the communist government passed it, but somehow Alex is responsible for this.
It's outrageous.
This is kind of amazing.
You know what?
I get it.
Every time something good happens, it's because of the left ideas, but you can't just allow
them.
What's done by actual activists, primarily on the left, is sometimes yelled about and
taken credit for by people who yell, like Alex.
Yeah.
I mean, that's all he does.
He just yells.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, once something becomes popular, then it's the conservatives who did it, like, oh, man,
Social Security, Medicare, we can't let that stuff get out of hand.
I mean, naturally, when it was being passed, we would have called it a communist land grab
trying to kill us all and steal our money.
But now that it has, now that we have it and it works, wow, it's our favorite program.
Yeah.
Yep.
There is that phenomenon.
So Alex, towards the end of this episode, gets a little bit into his own head, and he's talking
a bit about how, like, people ask him why he's not dead, fighting the globalists, and
what have you.
And he talks about being ready to die for freedom.
I mean, if they put a gun to my head right now and said renounce freedom, renounce your
family, renounce God, or we'll kill you, I'd say pull the trigger, bud.
I mean, I would.
Go ahead.
It's remarkable how that's almost exactly mirrored by if someone had a gun to my head
and told me to denounce Trump, I'd say pull the trigger.
Yeah.
Freedom, God, family, all that, just sort of Trump.
Oh, boy.
It's kind of depressing.
It's super depressing.
So we have one last clip, Jordan, and in this clip, Alex is in a bit of a rant about being
alive.
Right.
And he has felt things.
I suppose that I will accept that as a premise.
And I think that this is getting a little bit closer to that territory of religiosity
that we might be keeping our finger on the pulse of.
That sounds right.
If you don't know how evil they are, if you aren't burning with desire to expose the New
World Order, you're nuts.
And if we just have this upfront, ready to sacrifice, ready to stand up attitude about
defending America, this New World Order would not be here.
We become fat and decadent and always about the next pleasure.
And so we're dead on the inside.
So you know what?
I have really lived.
I can say that I have lived.
I have been so alive, it hurts, okay?
I have had understandings that are painful.
I have plumbed the depths of the New World Order.
I can't even articulate it.
And I know a lot of you have too.
And you have perspectives that I don't have and a lot of you are smarter than I am.
But I know this.
I am on my course and I'll tell you this, we're a lot safer standing up and speaking
out and being bold and depending on God's preservation, depending on God's providence
and God is real.
I have had experiences.
I know God is real.
I have faith.
And God isn't on the 700 Club, folks, I'm sorry to tell you.
God isn't in these big churches.
I'm sorry.
He's not, folks.
God is in your heart if you simply let him in.
And that's what we're talking about here.
And I'm telling you, if you don't hate evil and are not disgusted by it, something is
wrong with you and you are not alive.
There is not even a question.
Frankly, there is not even temptation anymore.
When you go this far into the fight against the New World Order, it is a total commitment.
You will be so alive.
It will completely consume your life because you will be fighting pure evil.
You must join in the fight against the New World Order.
That's one of the things that I always love, the idea that Alex brings out that it's like,
I no longer feel human emotions.
Yeah.
I have no longer drawn to sin.
I have progressed beyond that which other mortal men know.
Because the fight on the globalist is so strong in the New World Order.
I found that clip to be really on the line.
Yeah.
Because I do think an argument can still be made that a lot of that is, you know, it's
just kind of Christian-ish.
Yeah, I think that's-
God's in your heart, he's not in the 700 Club.
Sure.
That's not as extremist, certainly, as a lot of the stuff we hear more recent days.
Right.
And when he says that you're up against pure evil, that could still be metaphorical flourish.
Sure.
As opposed to what we know he believes now.
Naturally.
No.
That's what he believes.
Yes.
Invading people.
Yeah.
Yeah, that is true.
I do think that should come out much sooner in a conversation and it should be something
that you have to lead with.
Like if you're doing Alex's show, you should have to lead with like, I believe that our
political enemies are literally controlled by the devil like every day.
Yeah.
Just like if when I meet somebody, they're like, you should have to tell me if you believe
that the biblical flood story is 100% true.
And then I can be like, okay, fine.
Then you don't get an opinion on vaccines.
You know, like just get it out of the way so we can move forward.
I don't need to know anything else about you.
I think, I think it's more like a situation where, um, if, if you're gonna like, let's
say start dating somebody or whatever, and they don't tell you that they think the earth
is flat.
Yeah.
It's rude.
That's kind of irresponsible.
That's rude.
And I, yeah, I think, I think that Alex as a person who's conveying information, I think
it is, it is relevant if you believe that the devil is behind the gears of your enemies.
I think you should be upfront about it because it gives people the ability to consider that
in the totality of the information you're presenting and taking it more seriously.
I honestly can't quite tell yet.
Yeah.
Um, no, I agree.
I've heard, but there's more indications than I was expecting necessarily.
And I think it's probably not coincidental that like this, God is real.
God is there.
Right.
Is at the end of his episode.
I don't think that he would leave the episode with it.
No, I would doubt that.
I think that's there for the, the stalwarts, the people who are, who are in.
Yeah.
If you have a disclaimer for like a video game trailer, that's like, some scenes are
not actual gameplay.
You should at least have to have a disclaimer for like, also believes that the devil is
real.
You know, like that should be there.
Yeah.
Somewhere.
I mean, his bumpers coming in from break are like, you know, like, do you want to fight
corruption?
Well, so does he.
Like, that's not what this is about.
No, no, no, no.
Yeah.
Do you believe that you're a crusader against the literal Christian devil?
That's this show.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Well then now we get it.
Do you think that demons jump into people and make them go bleh?
Yes.
Yes, I do, sir.
I will listen.
Well, so does Alex.
Yes.
There we go.
Yeah.
I mean, it's, uh, it's an interesting, it's an interesting progression and I'm fascinated
by this and I, and this is so much more listenable, uh, in the past.
Like it's totally, totally, it's, it's absolutely, and these callers are weirdos in a fun way.
It seems like a show.
Yeah.
What we listen to now is not a show.
That is just a man unraveling.
Well, you know, too, like one of the things that's really fun and creates comedic tension
in like Frasier is that some of the callers are annoying to him.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Of course.
It's a fun show.
There's this tension.
You don't know what you're going to get.
Yeah.
It's this Republic of Texas person keeps annoying.
That's so funny.
And, uh, yeah, I enjoy that and, uh, I hope that every episode I listen to he gets into
a fight with somebody who believes just slightly the wrong thing.
Yeah.
Just, oh man.
It's so ridiculous that you think that the Magna Carta is still the law of the land
unless you're in capital letters and it's a corporation.
Now obviously the literal Christian devil is sending demons into people's brains to
control their actions.
Tell me.
Sure.
Yeah.
Um, anyway.
Jordan, this has been a, an episode.
Indeed it has.
Uh, we will be back checking in on the present day, I believe on our next episode.
But until then, we got a website.
We do have a website, Dan.
It's knowledgefight.com.
We have a Twitter.
We are on Twitter, Dan.
It is at knowledge underscore fight and at go to bed.
Jordan.
Yep.
We're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook.
And if you would like to download the show, please go to, and if you could please find
a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people doing God's work.
Yeah.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I'm a peacock that looks like a horned owl.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.