N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledgefight, Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying we are the bad guys.
College fight
Dan and Jordan, Knowledgefight.
R eternal
Need, need, need money
Andy and Kansas
Andy and, Andy or
Stop it!
Andy andforming
Andy and Kansas
Stop it!
It's time to pray.
Andy and Kansas you're on the earth, thanks for holding.
Hello Alex I'm a sister in color I'm a huge fan.
I love your lot.
Knowledgefight.com
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes that like to sit around, drink novelty beverages, and talk a little
bit about Alex Jones.
Scratch that.
We're a couple dudes that like to sit around, worship at the altar of Selene, and talk a
little bit about Alex Jones.
Jordan!
Jordan.
Dan.
What's up?
I got a quick question for you.
What do you got going on?
One, who's the deity you worship?
And two, what's your bright spot?
So Selene, of course.
Naturally.
And second, my bright spot, I feel like, look, I took a lot of beating from people about
this whole doors thing.
Okay.
I do, look, we're in straight up Alex ad territory, where you immediately started with look.
Look assholes.
Took a lot of pummeling over that, perhaps well deserved.
Sure.
So I've decided to open myself up to even more criticism.
Okay.
All right.
So I went down the street the other day and I got it in my head that I was like, I haven't
listened to methods of mayhem in a long time.
Sure.
You remember that?
The Tommy Lee rap rock project?
Yes, I do, Dan.
I happen to remember that that exists.
I haven't listened to that in a long time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I wondered if it held up.
And let me say.
How does it hold up, Dan?
Well, I listened to three songs.
I wondered if it held up.
It never held up.
It was like a shelf that was on the floor.
I liked it.
It didn't hold up.
I liked it when I was younger.
Okay.
I didn't have good taste.
I had a Kid Rock period.
Okay.
Look, I grew up in Missouri.
No, no, I'm sorry.
That was an overly aggressive reaction.
Sure.
So I listened to the Kid Rock song, New Skin.
Not good.
Also, it seems like there's a theme to the song that is supposed to be about like a new
beginning and like sort of like finding a new piece.
Sure.
Tommy Lee's famous for metaphor.
Kid Rock did not get the memo on that.
Oh, no.
Nothing to do thematically with the song.
Second song I listened to was Get Naked.
And that song is embarrassing.
What?
Oh, no.
No, Dan.
I know that's your response, but it's more embarrassing even than that, like how you're
responding.
Of course it's embarrassing.
You would still be like, oh my God.
I will tell you this.
I have not revisited it.
No plans.
It's gross and weird.
Sure.
I think I'm somebody who's all kind of, you know, I'm sex positive.
I think everybody's cool.
Sure.
Did the nudes do a guest verse on it too?
Is that how creepy it is?
No, no.
That would have been a different kind of embarrassing and uncomfortable.
Okay.
All right.
No, it was just.
There's a song on there called Proposition Fuck You.
I think that one was actually, that actually holds up.
Oh, does it?
Yeah.
Is it about like Prop 21?
What are we talking about?
No.
It's tied to the boys in blue running up on your crew.
You know what to do.
Tell them, fuck you.
All right.
Well.
It's a proposition.
Fuck you.
So the whole thing was about like, hey, yeah, I got a ballot measure for you.
How about you go fuck yourself.
Okay.
See now, now I understand that previously you said that this song was good.
I think it holds up.
And then you just sang me a little bit of it.
Uh-huh.
I beg strongly to differ.
I feel like it's, I'm sure it wasn't intended as satire of political outrage or like an
expression of like some kind of, I don't know, there wasn't a greater statement other than
fuck you.
What if we were a fourth rate rage against the machine?
Look, it works on that level.
Anyway.
No, that's fair.
methods of mayhem, my bright spot.
What's yours?
Uh, well I have a hard time with this as my bright spot because it is going to be unrevealed.
But I have completed a new project that I will be working on.
Please be a rap album with Tommy Lee.
I will not be a rap album with Tommy Lee, it will be a sex tape with Tommy Lee.
And yeah, I'm very excited about it.
It's a whole new thing for me.
It's something that I've wanted to try for a long time and I've finally stepped up.
I think I know what you're talking about.
I think you do as well.
I'm excited about this project as well.
You know, I was a little worried that you wouldn't be excited about it, but I'm excited
now that I know that you're pumped.
And also I'm excited because it does not involve more work for me.
Exactly.
In fact, this will be almost a complete reversal of fortune where I will be planning on doing
all of the work.
This kind of sucks a little bit for the listeners in as much as it is like a huge tease.
It's a huge tease, but that's what I'm in here for.
The payoff will be great.
I hope so.
And I think everyone will love it.
Or it'll be a disaster.
Oh yes.
It'll be a future bright spot or a methods of mayhem.
Let's see.
Yeah.
So today, Jordan, we are back in the present.
We're going to be talking about April 26th and 27th, 2021 Blackjack.
I was ready for it that time.
Shit.
I had the B first, but I think you said the word faster.
We tied.
That was a tie.
So what I wanted to do for this episode was I wanted to do more of the week, but I got
kind of caught up in some of the Alex stuff at the beginning of the week.
And I didn't want to get mixed up with the Giuliani got raided kind of news of the end
of the week.
I thought like it would all be too much to cover in one.
So the end of the week we'll cover on Monday, beginning of the week, we're going to cover
today.
Um, and uh, yeah, the knowledge fight, your source for breaking news yesterday's bullshit
tomorrow.
We'll get, uh, get that on a shirt.
Yesterday's bullshit next week.
But before we get to the episode, we've got to give us some hellos to some walks before
that.
I have a one out of context drop because I have two today, so I'm excited to spread them
out.
Here's the first one.
Oh, here comes the sex robots.
Here comes the sex robots.
Now I have a question.
Does this involve also the Daleks with guns?
Because if you could combine the two, you're unstoppable.
I was thinking about introducing our, uh, shout outs with, and now here comes the sex
robots.
Um, so first, uh, Ville, I don't know how to pronounce that V-I-L-L-E, Ville, whatever
you want.
S uh, last initial.
Thank you so much.
You are now policy wonk.
Your birthday was on the 29th.
Shout out.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Ville, Ville, or Ville.
Yes.
Next.
Jordan Holmes, non-binary twin.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
My non-binary binary twin.
I forgot to put an apostrophe on there and I confused myself reading it.
Yeah.
That sounds like Jordan Holmes, the non-binary binary twin, which would be a good nickname
for me.
Uh, next.
My wife says she has nightmares of Alex Jones voice because I listened to your podcast too
much.
Uh, you are now policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
And as always, let's remind you that if you are listening too much, we are fine with you
taking a break.
Please stop.
It's bad for you.
Um, then, uh, get to some technocrats here to give a shout out to first we got will and
thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
Uh, Preston L thank you so much.
You're now a technocrat and Bob, the human animal chimera.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey mate.
That's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right, we got to go full tilt boogie on this Watson.
All right, let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin while you pimp so good.
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you all.
Yes.
Thank you very much to the three of you.
Now, Jordan, we've got one little special thing, um, on, uh, on, uh, our last episode
right after we finished recording right after we finished.
I got an email.
Of course.
I had an email from my Ashley.
We wanted us to give a birthday shout out to, uh, to Matthew.
His birthday was on Tuesday.
We weren't able to do it.
We can't do that.
I felt like shit.
It's not your fault.
So now in the past, Matthew, I know your birthday was on Tuesday, but I hope you had a good
one.
Hope you had a great one.
And I hope things are going great.
And, uh, that, uh, you, you got to, I don't know, I want to know how old Matthew is before
I hope.
27.
I hope he had an okay birthday.
Hmm.
I'm just hoping for an okay birthday.
27, 27 is a year where you usually have a let down birth.
Also got a young one on the way.
June coming soon.
Uh, shout out to this baby.
Like a new sneakers dropping guys got a birthday and a new baby dropping baby.
First thing.
Don't listen to any Tommy Lee albums now or in the future or otherwise.
I hate to say it, but I mean, if you want to base your political identity on a proposition,
fuck you.
Maybe there's something to it.
Well, you know, I'll side with you on that though.
Um, so, uh, happy birthday to you, Matthew.
Um, Jordan, here is our next out of context.
Stop before we get to today's show.
You know, I know a major cattleman.
I served under major cattleman.
You sir are no major cattleman.
Okay.
All right.
Here is the beginning, uh, Alex opening up the show here on April 26th and it is a bummer
or I took off Saturday and Sunday at least about 90% actually unplugged myself from the
computer.
It's been more time with the family and it just intensified my clarity about where we
are and what we're facing.
Are we getting our neighbors dead species on this planet and the big transformation
for the worst that is taking place.
And here's the final equation.
If we don't have a total awakening to the fact that we're under threat and we're under
attack at the globalist, you're building what they call a posthuman world, then we don't
have any shot at changing this or we're fixing this and it's been the process of industrialization.
It's been the process of modernization that has really turned us into these domesticated
ignorant creatures that don't even know how to defend ourselves, take care of ourselves
and each generation going forward is less human.
Let me tell you about the candle.
Alright.
Yeah, yeah, the force of modernity has made us less human and each generation subsequently
will be less human because of computers.
Unsurprisingly, Alex is that guy at a party.
Listen, look, I'm not saying that the Unabomber was good, but if you've read his manifesto
I'm not saying he was wrong.
He's got some stuff to say.
I don't know.
He's a smart guy.
He built his own bombs.
You gotta be smart to do that.
That guy at a party is a bummer.
That guy not at a party, also a bummer.
Let's remind ourselves.
Always a bummer.
So yeah, Alex is in a weird mood.
Sure.
Unabomber is a weird mood.
Yeah.
So we heard on our last present day episode that Bill Maher, secret patriot.
Yes, I'm hard time fitting that into our canon.
It was quite a shift for Bill.
He really got an upgrade from ventriloquist dummy of the globalists to basically Tucker
Carlson.
Here's the other reason that I know for a fact Alex is a huge fan of Star Wars.
Rhett Conning is his mate Raison Detre in many ways.
The man absolutely refuses to stick to canon.
Yeah, that is true, especially when things are convenient for him.
Yeah, yeah.
I have bad- Ray is not a Palpatine in my world.
Anyways, sorry.
I have bad news.
What?
We are back to Bill Maher being one.
Oh, okay.
I've gotten to the point where I can't watch a CNN piece or even a Bill Maher piece or
any of these propaganda pieces because I see the writing that's involved in it and I see
the multi-layered deceptions that are involved.
The level of propaganda has gotten even more sophisticated and these are very skilled,
very destructive people doing this.
Bill Maher's secret patriot run lasted two days or something.
That was honestly not a bad run for Bill Maher.
What the fuck?
I was expecting almost less than an hour.
So stupid.
So that's good news.
Oh, you think that's good news?
He's gotten to the point now where he can't watch a Bill- when was he not at that point?
A couple weeks ago.
Okay, well that's fair.
Yeah, he could watch a Bill Maher report.
That's fair.
He can see the scripting, man.
Okay.
He can see all the propaganda.
All right.
No, but he can't watch it because the secret patriot is too secret in this circumstance.
Yeah, or maybe he was just talking shit the other day when he was like, I've heard from
higher ups that Bill Maher is actually kind of like Tucker.
He's like a good guy.
That sounds more reasonable.
So anyway, there's good news in the world amidst Alex's inability to watch news anymore.
Sure, sure.
You know, there's also a lot of positive things happening because there's always for every
action opposite- Wise.
An equal reaction.
But I've really, I don't want to say transcended, but I have risen above my enemies.
I've always been disgusted by them, I've always disliked them, but I haven't wanted to defeat
them so that I could be the top dog and be above them in this pile of skulls they sit
on top of.
I mean, I transcended them a long time ago.
I guess from the time I was born, the time spirit entered my body, but now I've really
transcended them.
Oh boy.
So the good news is that Alex has transcended his enemies, although he did transcend them
when he was a baby.
And now he's really- Sure, sure, sure.
So we're on the same path as like David Lynch here.
Now we're into trans- What you need to do is transcend- Okay.
Yeesh.
Yeah.
I was like, this is a mood, this is a- Unifomered to delusions of grandeur.
This is something- There's something there.
It's an interesting way to start the show.
And Alex pivots this talking about how he's really transcended now into saying that the
answer is transcendent.
Oh, okay.
We all just have to transcend.
Okay, that's nice.
Because the answer is transcending these people.
We have to really transcend the new world order- Work for you.
And still resist it and still say no to it, but not even give it energy when we do it.
These are like sad, mad dogs with rabies foaming at the mouth out in the street.
And you know they're already done for and it's over for them.
So you need to just stay away from them and just try not to let them bite your children.
And I think that's really what it comes down to.
So I guess that means communes?
Is that what he's trying to say?
Because if all of the world and the globalists and all the minions are all mad dogs out there-
Yeah, yeah.
Then you just gotta keep them away from biting your children and stay away from them.
They're gonna die of their own illness or whatever.
So yeah, communes?
I don't know.
Alex got a phone call from Michelle Obama and she was like, listen, Alex, I know you've
never tried this before, but when they go low, all right, we transcend.
That's what we do.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It sounded like communes.
Yeah.
And I doubt there's gonna be technology there based on his earlier statement.
It does seem like he's trying to go back to a pre-industrial world.
So not only that, he's also gonna shake up the transmission.
And I will say that if he had actually done this, he'd make a better show.
Okay.
But he doesn't.
No.
He does not shake up the transmission.
Well, that sounds right.
And I'm your host, Alex Jones, promising you that this already important, informative avant-garde
transmission is now going to go to the next level.
And I'm gonna shake the transmission up with more of your calls, more quick guests, and
more special reports and more live, commercial-free podcasts.
You got my commitment that here in the home stretch of going into the next level, that
I will work even harder because things are moving very, very quickly and it is essential.
And because I'm gonna shake things up, something I never do, I always come on the show and
hit the big stories and dive right into the breaking, censored and suppressed information,
the systems fighting to make sure your family and others don't get it, then I usually just
barely plug at the end of the hour.
But a couple of big things have happened.
A, you need these products, they're amazing, and B, if you don't buy them, we won't be.
Really shaking up the show.
I'm shaking up the broadcast and I'm gonna listen to a bunch of stuff that I'm not gonna
do.
However, I just want to let everybody know, I'm gonna need to do more ad reads.
I'm going straight to it.
I'm going straight to ads from now on.
I'm gonna shake up the broadcast, I'm definitely gonna go to more calls.
Maybe not.
I'm gonna do more quick guests.
Probably not.
I actually don't think he took any calls on this show.
Why does that not surprise me?
I wouldn't describe any of the guests as being quick.
Yeah, but he did go to a plug real fast.
That's nice.
I got that weird mood that he was in and then right to a plug, I was like, this is fucked
up.
We're gonna be in trouble.
This is gonna be a ride.
So Alex gets to talking about some news and it's sort of what I believe is the new development
and evolution of COVID conspiracies and narratives.
In Europe and the UK, they're still almost completely shut down.
Tens of millions extra, it's just a footnote, have starved to death in the third world,
in Africa, in India, even in China, in Latin America, in areas of Asia, the Middle East.
We've got those numbers.
When people get malnutrition, any virus will kill them.
So if any virus, any virus.
If Alex has specific data on this, he should really discuss it because he just references
having this data and actually talking about it could be really illuminating.
I suspect he doesn't have any actual information.
He's just winging it and riffing off comments that were made by David Beasley, the UN food
program executive director back in September.
This is definitely a serious issue and it's one that Alex is definitely right to call
attention to.
But the way he calls attention to the problem of food insecurity in the developing world
does a disservice to the idea of actually helping understand or solve the problem.
And that's because Alex doesn't care about the actual problem.
He cares about using the impression that he cares about it to attack people who believe
that COVID-19 is an actual problem.
Food insecurity around the world is a complicated picture and you can't just say that lockdowns
in the US or Europe directly leads to worsening conditions in other countries.
For instance, this past year, countries like Kenya, Ethiopia, Uganda, India, Pakistan and
Somalia have seen incredibly severe locust swarms that have had nothing to do with coronavirus
or any country's response to it.
COVID has affected the world's situation and made things worse, but there's a larger picture
than just what Alex wants to cover, which is essentially if all the businesses would
just open back up, everyone would be fine.
It's really troubling to see Alex try to get into the game of pretending that COVID deaths
are actually starvation deaths that are being covered up.
The basic problem here is that Alex is just making that up as a way for him to continue
his denial of this major pandemic.
But even beyond that, the numbers just don't work.
Concern USA released a list at the end of 2020 of the countries facing the greatest
food insecurity.
And if you compare that list to lists of countries and their COVID fatalities, you don't come
away with the conclusion that Alex wants you to.
Chad is the country facing the most food insecurity, the most severe food insecurity, but there
have only been 170 deaths from COVID there.
Timor-Leste is number two on the list, where there have been three COVID deaths.
Madagascar is number three, where there have been 614 deaths from COVID.
Haiti is number four, where they've registered 254 COVID deaths.
Only numbers nine and 10 on the list, Afghanistan and Nigeria respectively, have over a thousand
deaths total from COVID recorded.
Until early March, the US was seeing more COVID deaths per day than any of these countries
have had throughout the entire pandemic.
If Alex tries to redefine COVID deaths as secretly being starvation deaths, he's essentially
trying to use people's deaths as a political prop for his own narratives.
This behavior is nothing new to Alex, but it should be recognized as ghoulish, and people
should understand the disrespect that he's operating with towards people's humanity.
Yeah, you cannot, you just can't trust anybody who, when you're talking about engaging with
a serious issue, just goes, no, we don't need to do that.
What about this?
Because then what's the point?
We're always only ever going to be talking about whatever it is that you think is important,
and no matter what I say, it's going to change based on you not wanting to engage with what
I'm saying.
So how are we supposed to talk?
So this is primarily being deployed right now, this narrative, because there's a lot
of news coming out about India and how drastic the situation is there.
The devastation, yeah.
And so Alex, I wouldn't say he's doing a great job.
They're starving to death in Africa, they're starving to death in India, and when they
starve to death and die of malnutrition, when you look at the Indians dying, tens of thousands
a week right now, extra, they all look like concentration camp victims.
And the common cold is killing them, and then the media tells you that COVID-19 did it.
And India is starving to death now.
You can argue, well, there's a billion, 300 million Indians, there's too many of them.
What?
Well, ladies and gentlemen, they've always had outdoor cremations, they've always had
mass cremations for the poor, that friends and family have gone to India, there's documentaries
about it, CNN complains they should be able to burn their dead outside, it's bad for carbon.
What are you talking about?
What is happening?
Yeah, how does that even-
What are we even doing?
What Alex is saying there about Indian deaths from malnutrition being called COVID, it's
not based on anything other than his own feelings and guesses about things.
The situation in India with COVID is really complicated, but there are a number of driving
factors that people point to in terms of what's making this period right now incredibly horrific.
The first appears to be a level of unpreparedness.
Healthcare journalist Vikas Dandekar wrote a piece recently in Stat News that explained
this element of the situation like this.
Quote, India's early success in nearly flattening the COVID-19 curve in 2020 may be the cause
of the current calamity.
Despite a rickety and funding-starved healthcare infrastructure, the country's ability to manage
the first wave of COVID-19 looked laudable as the United States, Canada, and countries
in Europe reeled under second and third waves of the pandemic.
Then things went awry.
The turnaround raised false hopes that the virus had run out of steam in India and the
country would be spared a second wave.
That left people unprepared to deal with the heavy blow that was coming.
Modi declared victory and held massive political rallies.
At the same time, Hindu pilgrims amassed at the Ganges River where, quote, as many as
2.5 million people took part with scant attention to COVID-19 safety protocols.
By the time an avalanche of criticism cut short the festival, the virus had infected
thousands of pilgrims who took it home to their neighborhoods and villages.
These types of massive gatherings of people allowed for a broader spread than would have
happened otherwise.
Add to that the discovery of that new strain of hyper contagious virus in India a while
back and how the healthcare infrastructure is pushed to its limit and you end up with
a situation like we're seeing now, which is terrible.
There's a humanitarian disaster going on right now and the people of India need all the help
that the international community can provide.
But trying to pretend that the deaths you're seeing are just malnutrition deaths that are
being secretly listed as COVID, that is fucking disrespectful to the people of India and what
they're going through.
There should be no greater thing that, no greater red flag than any right wing reactionary
politician declaring victory over any worldwide problem.
That should be the immediate sign for everybody in that country to be like, oh, we're fucked.
We're fucked.
This is the worst thing that, we're going to die.
That's the first thing I scream whenever I hear a politician say mission accomplished.
What I see with Alex is a complete need to justify this to his audience.
Because it can't be possibly COVID.
No, and it's India's Trump too.
So we can't be, yeah.
But what I fail to understand, and I would love for Alex to explain this, is what's the
Indian government's motive for supposedly calling these malnutrition deaths COVID?
I understand that Alex thinks that the US hospitals were in a get rich quick scheme
where they called other deaths COVID because Medicare pays them a certain amount for COVID
treatment.
But does he think that's the case in every country?
Does he think that doctors in India are scamming Medicare?
I assume the globalists have a profit sharing program for this kind of scam.
He must think that.
It's really, really bizarre.
And when you start to look at what's actually being said, it just doesn't make any sense.
And it's dark.
It's dark.
Right.
And I suppose in his conception, any and all profiting or carpet bagging goes into one
big pot for all the evil global scams around the world.
So it's like, you know.
All scams are fungible?
I guess.
I guess that's what has to happen.
That's dumb.
That's real dumb.
So anyway, look, there's people starving, I guess.
According to Alex, all these people have malnutrition and dying.
And also in Venezuela, people had malnutrition.
But are there more people dying in India?
Yes.
Of malnutrition.
You know, in Venezuela, it was a thousand, five, six years ago, dying a day extra than
it was 2000.
Last numbers that came out were estimated at 5000 people a week starved to death in
Venezuela.
But the government passed a law that you can't call it starvation and you can't gather those
numbers.
If you're a physician or a doctor, you'll be arrested and they don't even call it malnutrition.
So that's how they work.
So I would like to challenge Alex to produce any of that information.
I kind of have a suspicion that he's making all that up and all those details up to try
and bolster this imaginary argument that malnutrition deaths in India are being called COVID deaths.
I think that's what's going on here.
Yeah.
Also, food insecurity is a very real issue in Venezuela.
And again, the particular contributing factors are complicated.
However, it's important to recognize how even if all of Alex's imaginary conspiracy was
actually happening, the numbers don't make sense.
Venezuela has recorded a total of just over 2000 COVID-19 related deaths.
Shouldn't the number be much higher if Alex's dumb conspiracy were real?
I mean, roughly 250,000?
It's important to recognize what's going on here.
Alex is trying to argue that the deaths listed as COVID in India are actually just malnutrition
deaths that are being mislabeled.
In order to defend this baseless claim, Alex points to Venezuela, where there are apparently
tons of malnutrition deaths.
In order for Alex's argument to make any sense, it would need to be the case that these malnutrition
deaths in Venezuela were being reclassified as COVID-19 deaths, because if that weren't
the case, then bringing up Venezuela means absolutely nothing in this context.
Alex's brain works from memes, not information.
When there's a story about malnutrition in the right wing media, the meme the audience
has been trained to respond to is just bring up Venezuela.
Alex has no point that he's even making here, but he knows that if he just says it's like
Venezuela, the listeners will just nod in agreement, thinking something was said.
Those lawless, socialist monsters in Venezuela.
Yeah.
Now, lest you think that Alex cares.
I would be hard-pressed to get to a point where I do, but-
Well, this will vaccinate you from that impression taken hold.
Oh, look.
The Indians are starving to death.
You could even find aid groups saying they're starving to death, but by the time it hits
CNN, look, there's mass graves.
They're burning people outside.
That's how they get rid of people over there, and anybody that has any knowledge knows that,
but not the average CNN viewer.
So it's lie upon lie upon lie upon lie, but let me get back to what I was talking about.
We haven't had bodies, our ultimate turmeric formula, in five, almost six months.
Wow.
What?
You know, here's just such a simple fucking, go fuck yourself on this shit.
Like, okay, if you're going to what about me with the Indians are starving, and we even
know aid groups are saying that Indians are starving.
All right, so you're going to tell me that that's an issue you fucking care about, that
the Republican party cares about.
So if the Republican party is in power, they should at the very least mention that they
care about while they are in power.
But when they are in power, they sure seem to forget all this bullshit.
They do.
A couple of quick clarifications.
Sorry.
One, it's very important to recognize that right now, Alex's brand is moving away from
the Republican party, because it does not look like a Trump nominee.
It's going to be the 2024 candidate that people are going to coalesce behind.
So I believe that there's that fracturing happening, and Alex is soon to be above the
left-right paradigm.
Sure, sure, you know, we'll get back to that.
Oh, that motherfucker, if he wriggles out of this bullshit.
So whenever you want to say complaints about the Republican party, yes.
Absolutely valid criticism, although Alex will be deflecting that in the future.
Trumpist party, the Patriot party, whatever the fuck you want.
Until they have an official name, it's going to be difficult to make these darts hit the
right spot.
I'm going to call them no nothings until further notice.
That's fair enough.
Yeah.
But yeah, I also like the idea that Alex is talking about real world stuff, or presumably
real world stuff.
Yeah, the important shit.
And then he's like, let me get back to what I was talking about, that's a weird transition
into the ad.
Listen, listen, sorry I took that tangent about important shit, did you know what else
we've got in our store?
We have, dumb pills.
So this next clip is fun.
This was something that I decided to have a little bit of a, dig to the bottom of a
hole on.
Yeah, sure.
And it's Alex reading a headline.
Health experts encourage CDC to implement permanent mask mandates.
That's an Infowars.com article, and it links to BBC, CNN, all of them.
Well, I could have told you that.
Bill Gates said last year, over a year ago when it all started, he said, oh, it's never
going to end and masks will be like wearing seatbelts.
This is a Paul Joseph Watson article on Infowars, and I found this to be a great opportunity
to illustrate how Infowars misleads and doesn't actually cover the news that they're even
pretending to.
The second half of this article that Paul wrote is just the standard anti-mask stuff
that you find in pretty much any article on their website that has to do with masks.
So I'm just going to ignore all that.
The actual headline is, quote, health experts encourage CDC to implement permanent mask
mandates.
This article does not link to the BBC or CNN.
In fact, the entire story is based on one article from the Providence Journal.
This is an outlet from Rhode Island published in December 2020 with the headline, quote,
thinking about life without a mask?
Think again, say Rhode Island experts.
Is that where North Korea hid those ballots?
Must have.
Must have been in Providence.
Yeah.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Leaving aside the fact that this is almost five months old as an article and Infowars
is pretending it's news, if you look deeper into how the original article is misrepresented,
you get an even better sense of the propaganda that's being deployed here.
The two experts that were consulted for this Providence Journal article are Dr. Nicole
Alexander Scott and Dr. Leonard A. Murmill.
Neither of them at any point seemed to be encouraging the CDC to make mask wearing permanent
or mandatory, as the headline might lead you to think.
You would think that's where they would be going, right?
Yeah.
Here's the part of the Infowars article that quotes Dr. Alexander Scott.
Quote, we have seen benefits of masking that occur, health director Dr. Nicole Alexander
Scott told the Providence Journal.
So there may be a new form of normalcy where masks don't necessarily have to go away.
This is all good and well, as that passage does appear in the actual article.
However, consider that Infowars lead.
Their first line of the story is quote, health experts are insisting that the CDC should
implement permanent mask mandates even after the COVID-19 pandemic ends.
That doesn't seem like Alexander Scott is insisting that the CDC implement anything.
Just commenting that there may be a utility in continued mask wearing, obviously to cut
down on transmission of annual flus.
This sensationalizing of almost half a year old comments made by a Rhode Island doctor
that Alex and Paul Joseph Watson have never heard of before.
That's bad enough.
But if you go read the actual article, there's another quote from Alexander Scott that Paul
is intentionally leaving out of the article because it doesn't serve the purposes of the
propaganda.
She was like, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Before you take me out of context, I know Paul Joseph Watson is reading this.
That would be great.
I can't hang.
From the Providence Journal article, quote, Alexander Scott said state health officials
have much to consider before taking a final position on whether mask wearing should continue
after the pandemic.
Quote, I want to reserve the ability to research and see what are some of the things that we've
introduced because of the pandemic that are valuable to continue.
She said, adding she hopes the public would see the benefits of mask wearing if its continuance
is recommended.
Quote, my hope would be that folks would see the value of continuing that, she said.
It's unlikely to be a definitive mandate, but we want to be driven by the data and the
science.
Yeah.
That's like, what if your heartless, soulless, monstrous corporate boss forces you to go
to work regardless of whether or not you're feeling ill, perhaps instead of the old ways
before the pandemic where you would just show up to work and sneeze all over everything,
you should try wearing a mask.
Or if there's no reason for you to need to go into work and you can work remotely, why
not?
Why not work remotely?
If you're feeling well and you can be just as productive at home.
Seems fairly simple.
Right.
Sure.
Yeah.
Any of these things are possible implications or ideas of what she could be talking about.
Seems like it would work fine.
And it's important to recognize that she's very clearly talking about being driven by
data and science.
Yeah.
So that's clear, you know, that she's saying that it could be advantageous.
There's not likely to be a definitive mandate.
Sure.
That position clearly articulated in the original article is completely misrepresented by the
Infowars article because they are liars who are doing this for profit.
The second expert in the article is Dr. Mermel.
Here's what Paul includes of his comments in the Infowars article, and it begins with
including a mistaken reference to Dr. Alexander Scott as his.
Oh, no.
Quote, his sentiments were echoed by Dr. Leonard A. Mermel, medical director of epidemiology
and infection control at Rhode Island Hospital, who said making people wear masks all the
time was worth it to stop the spread of the viruses other than COVID-19.
Quote, within the lifespan system, we're seeing far fewer of the respiratory viruses than
we are used to seeing at this moment in the calendar year.
So it's impressive.
The COVID preventative strategies are having an impact on other respiratory viruses, which
just makes sense.
They spread in a similar fashion, said Mermel.
Quote, it would not surprise me if that became a recommendation from the CDC, he said.
It's a pretty low price to pay to try to reduce the risk to oneself and particularly loved
ones who may be at a particular risk for these sorts of infections causing harm, he added.
It would not surprise him if the CDC made a recommendation to continue wearing masks.
Does that justify the lead?
Quote, health experts are insisting that the CDC should implement permanent mask mandates
even after the COVID-19 pandemic ends.
Does that justify that?
You didn't hear the tone of voice with which he said it.
He said, A, wouldn't surprise me if the CDC made these mandatory forever because I was
insisting in behind closed doors.
My question about whether or not that's justified is not rhetorical.
It does.
It's not.
This is bullshit.
That's fair.
And it gets even worse in the case of Dr. Mermel as well, because he also said some
stuff that Paul is just conveniently ignoring.
From the Providence Journal article, quote, flu has dampened significantly in the southern
hemisphere in those countries that had aggressive public health measures to reduce COVID risks
such as social distancing and masking, Mermel said.
The southern hemisphere acts as a sort of time machine with its winter and flu season
coming six months ahead of the winter in the northern hemisphere.
Preliminary data shows the United States having a quiet flu season with recorded cases lower
than each of the last six years at the same point in the season, Mermel said.
Quote, at the moment what we're seeing mirrors what we've seen in the southern hemisphere.
Let's hope that continues to be the case.
No guarantee, he said.
Quote, right now we are for this time of year seeing very low prevalence, but again, it's
very early, so it's hard to know what to make of that.
Uh.
Wow.
In the underlying article that Paul is covering dishonestly, both of the experts cited gave
very general comments to the effect that it's possible that wearing masks could be helpful
at lowering cases of the flu, but it was too early to say and that we should let data lead
us to our eventual conclusion.
Neither of them were saying that the CDC needs to make mask wearing permanent.
No one was demanding any kind of mandatory mask laws.
Yeah.
This is pretty much always the case with InfoWars articles.
There may be an actual news outlet story that they're basing their coverage on, but the
version they're covering is a funhouse mirror of the real thing, distorted so it'll fit
the bullshit narratives they want to push.
I chose to cover this one a little more specifically because it's pretty glaring and it's super
embarrassing that Paul didn't check the date on the Providence Journal article before cranking
out his outrage blog post.
It's honestly hilarious.
And here's another paragraph from Paul's article, just because I like to poke.
Keep in mind that experts that he's referencing are two doctors in Rhode Island who spoke
to a local paper five months ago.
This is from Paul's article that came out this week.
So let me set the scene, all right?
So we've got these two doctors.
They're on the phone with a local Providence, Rhode Island Journal.
They're busy.
They're at the hospital.
They're dealing with shit.
They're talking to this person.
They might decide to set a block of time aside.
Then cut to five months later.
All right, here we are.
Quote, medical professionals are still attempting to have mask mandates become part of the new
normal despite Dr. Anthony Fauci acknowledging yesterday that it would be common sense for
the CDC to start relaxing measures.
Wait, so now Fauci is- No, no, no, but do you understand what's
going on here?
There's a time warp going on.
Yes, I understand.
This article's five months old.
This article is far older.
He's comparing their comments to something Fauci said yesterday in the present day.
No, I'm recognizing and understanding this.
Sloppy shit, man.
You know how sometimes I'm like, Dan, we can't let scientists name stuff because they accidentally
name it really intimidating things, or we can't let scientists talk to journalists the
same way they would to other scientists because other people will twist it because they can't
really quite comprehend it.
It's not their fault.
It's just they don't have that same kind of social education, that kind of thing.
In this circumstance, fuck it.
There's nothing you can do.
Well, no, I agree, because the doctors did not convey information-
No.
... poorly.
They just were taken- They did it every-
Yeah.
I mean, if you want to really make it so you can't do the stuff that Paul does, it's like
no one can ever talk again.
Exactly.
Yeah.
There's no saving this one.
They'll just splice things open.
Yeah.
It's not like she named it murder town is what we're going to go to.
No.
It's not a fictitious presentation of something that did happen in as much as two doctors
in Rhode Island talked to a local paper five months ago.
No.
It's fanfic.
Yeah.
This is 50 shades of bullshit.
But it's fanfic that gets people hurt.
Yeah.
Naturally.
Well, like 50 shades of gray.
Alex, on the show here in April 26th, he has some other sources.
I'm sorry.
I said I'd just read you the headlines.
Stanford study result face masks are ineffective to block transmission of COVID-19 actually
can cause health deterioration and premature death, but who cares about the facts?
New studies suggest wearing a mask is ineffective.
New study highlights face mask problems with safety and efficacy.
Oh, really?
It's a total damn cult.
If you're paying attention, you'll notice that these headlines, these three headlines
are all just different dumb blogs writing their own headline about the same underlying
story.
Yeah.
A supposed Stanford study that says that masks are bad.
If you're not paying attention, as Alex's audience almost never is, it might appear
that there's a flood of studies showing that masks are dangerous and you were right all
along to be against them.
Three studies at least.
He's just named them.
Just today.
That's the impression Alex is trying to create by repeatedly hitting the same story as if
it's three different stories.
Also, this paper about masks was written by a guy named Baruch Vainshelboim, who is a
quote, visiting scholar on matters unrelated to this paper between 2015 and 2016 at Stanford.
Other than that, he has no connection with Stanford and Stanford has requested a correction
to take their name off this bullshit.
This is an important point to bring up.
People like Alex and the right wing media hate authoritative sources.
The mainstream media is the enemy of the people and the universities are just full of liars
trying to push the globalist agenda.
And yet, whenever they have the opportunity to pretend that one of their narratives is
backed by the authority, top scientists, top scientists, top scientists all over this place.
Whenever they can back their thing with the appealing to the authority of a real mainstream
or academic institution, they trip over their feet trying to associate their ideas with
a respectable source.
Of course, that's a real respectable source.
That's not the bullshit we normally talk about.
Anyone who thinks that people like Alex are legit should really question why they do that.
This paper was published in a journal called Medical Hypotheses, which is basically exactly
what it sounds like.
An outlet for fringe nonsense and unsubstantiated ideas.
This paper is trash and the conclusion runs at odds with dozens of other more rigorously
designed studies and it's being falsely attributed to Stanford in order to elevate its credibility.
This is basically the norm when it comes to information sources that Infowars uses.
Yeah.
Because it's nothing.
Because the underlying unspoken thing they're saying there is, look, even people who do
work believe this, even people who work on this shit believe.
If I reference the Washington Post, you know it's true because they actually have to work
on it.
Yeah.
That's bullshit.
They have standards.
Yeah.
So you're saying whatever you don't, you're immediately implying that you're lying all
of the time except, I hate it.
So I want to hear another lie?
Yes, of course.
Why did Merck pull out three months ago?
They said you cannot produce a safe vaccine for the cold virus.
If you do, it causes autoimmune responses, an allergic reactions in a large number of,
because they said, we don't care if you wave lab to test, we're doing lab test.
And even corrupt Merck said, we suggest you don't take vaccines and you just get herd
immunity.
Oh really?
Because if you make a vaccine that is broad enough for the protein that's in a cold virus,
then it's going to attack your own damn body.
This isn't true.
Alex is just making up this entire story about why Merck decided to spend their efforts to
develop a COVID vaccine.
In reality, if you actually read their statements, it was a situation where they had two candidate
vaccines, which the test subjects responded well to, but quote, the immune responses were
inferior to those seen following natural infection and those reported for other SARS-CoV-2 COVID-19
vaccines.
The idea of trying to start from scratch on new vaccine candidates when there are already
other promising vaccines coming to market, that would have been a waste of resources
for them.
So what they decided to do was adjust their research strategy to focus on therapeutics
that they might be able to develop.
Sure.
All of Alex's story about them saying you shouldn't take vaccines and a vaccine for
COVID is impossible, that's just completely made up from his imagination.
And it's fun.
I'm sure the audience enjoys it, but it's not real.
Yeah.
Anyway, just bullshit.
Why would anybody trust him when he says anything about viruses?
Like, honestly, just tell me what a virus even looks like before you're telling me what
viruses do.
Give me an idea of what it looks like.
You think I don't know what a virus looks like?
I really don't think you do.
They're about yay-bing.
They are not about yay-bing.
They're red.
They are, some of them are red.
They have horns.
That's true.
They have a pitchfork.
That's all such-
It's the devil.
It is the devil!
Shit!
You nailed it.
Alex, I would say that probably his main narrative is trying to rationalize the COVID deaths
in India and recontextualize them as what he's calling malnutrition deaths.
Right, right, right.
And it's nonsense.
Don't worry about this.
Worry about that.
David Beasley, he's the head of it.
We have to clip him in a moment.
Wards of dire famines in Africa, Mideast, Asia, if COVID-19 supply change damage continues
and also in India.
The reality of COVID in India right now is really scary and it should be something that
creates feelings of concern and care for the people in India and also creates a real sense
of the stakes that people are facing when it comes to the virus.
These realizations are dangerous for Alex because his entire last year of work has been
dedicated to minimizing the COVID pandemic for profit and to help his God King Trump
not look bad.
The Infowars audience cannot be allowed to think that the human tragedy in India is real
because that threatens the bottom line of Alex's operations.
Thus, you see what you see here.
It's a complete rewriting of the situation.
You can keep the feelings of concern and care for the people of India, but you're being
lied to about why you should care.
It's not about the virus, it's about malnutrition.
You can keep that human empathy, but Alex has to protect the business.
You can see a slight of hand really clearly here.
In order to make his argument that all the COVID deaths in India are secretly just malnutrition,
he's referencing a May 8th, 2020 article published by the Atlantic Council warning of the possibility
of famine due to supply chain breakdown.
The actual headline is, quote, world food programs David Beasley warns of dire famines
in Africa, Middle East, if COVID-19 supply chains damage continues.
But you see how Alex amended the headline to add India in there because he needs to
make it look like that for the narrative to stay.
The word India doesn't appear in that article at all.
And even this article isn't just about COVID, it's also about other influences on food insecurity
like the flooding that was happening in Sudan and the massive locust swarms.
It's a complicated humanitarian issue that demands attention, but Alex is attempting
to hijack that attention and use it as a prop for his COVID denialist narratives, which
is ghoulish.
Yeah.
Ghoulish, I say.
Yeah, the fundamental thing that the right wing has to do first is, you know, everybody
knows, your family members, people you know, you're like, how is it that these people who
are in person and in conversation, so empathetic and caring and kind, how is it that on large
national issues, they're fucking monsters?
And it's like the right wing has to redirect that empathy.
Otherwise people will never buy.
People are never going to be like, hey, yeah, I think we should steal money from the poor
and kill them.
You know, you have to redirect it so they don't even care.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yep.
And it's, it's just so...
And that's what you see being done here.
Yeah.
And it just destroys people's brains.
It really destroys them.
Yeah.
And the whole end result is a crippling of your ability to care for other people in a
meaningful way.
No, a borderline pathological apathy.
Yeah.
And it's held up and supported by constant misuse of information.
Yep.
And Alex does that again with another article.
Coronavirus, India's lockdown turning into humanitarian crisis, German news, DW.
That's from six, eight months ago, admitting mass starvation, millions already starve to
death.
Alex is lying about that article.
Yeah.
It's a real, and it is a real article from DW, but it's about a desperate situation that
many migrant workers in India were experiencing due to COVID lockdowns.
Many who found themselves without work due to business closures, and they were far away
from their homes and villages outside major cities.
To add to that difficulty, trains had been closed, and although there was eventually
a plan put in place to help transit, you know, stranded workers back to where they were going,
it was not smoothly implemented.
This article doesn't admit that millions had starved to death.
It's a report that's meant to bring attention to an issue that some might not be aware of,
and Alex is lying about it to defend his indefensible narrative that all the COVID deaths in India
are a hoax.
That's what he's doing.
Wow.
Yep.
Man, you know, guess what, Dan?
It's just as horrific whenever he's doing it about a different country.
True.
It never changes.
I don't feel different about it because he's lying about India instead of the United States.
Nope.
Fuck him.
So this clip is, we're jumping to another topic.
I don't know how to set this clip up other than just like, this is weird, man.
I don't wish you any harm myself.
I'm not calling for violence against you.
It's already weird.
Bill Gates should publicly hang himself.
I think Prince Charles should publicly hang himself.
I think Ted Turner should publicly hang himself and that they would all go to one of their
ranches and just have a public international thing and say, we want to kill you.
We want to save the earth.
We're going to start with ourselves and if Bill Gates just took an ice pick and just
started ramming in his throat, hey, humanity with blood spewing, I would say, well, I respect
that man.
Maybe he's right.
Then we can have the drones launch with the nerve gas and start the operation, which is
the final mop-up operation, which I told you about a long time ago, now they're admitting
it.
The drones are ready with the nerve gas.
We're in your family.
We'll be right back.
Is that plan C, the drones with nerve gas?
Because that's not a biological weapon.
That's a chemical weapon.
I'm surprised by the drones with nerve gas.
Yeah, apparently Alex just made that up to throw in.
You know, I was, I was going along with him.
I was like, this is a bit macabre, but ultimately, yeah, I'm fine with that.
I don't give a shit.
But then we got into the, then he was like, and if they killed themselves, then I would
agree that so everyone else should die.
That's weird.
That's kind of, that's what he said, right?
Yeah.
I understand you're creating terms of the secondary part that are never going to happen.
Of course not.
My political positions and my beliefs are not influenced by public spectacles.
If my political enemies kill themselves, I will join their team is his point.
I respect the hell out of that.
I respect the hell out of anybody who'd kill themselves.
I got to, listen, my beliefs are so fungible that that's all it takes.
Trump like gets up there and slaps himself in the face.
He's like, don't you see what I do for this country?
What a hero.
Oh my God.
This is, they look, now that he's not president, he has finally become the president of the
United States.
What the hell is this?
I mean, I obviously don't believe him, but he's still saying it.
Yeah.
It's weird.
That's a weird thing to say out loud.
Yep.
So we have high minded issues to cover on this April 26th show and actually it was kind
of interesting.
So far it feels like I disagree with you, but keep going.
Oh, it's going to get worse too, because that was me being decisious.
I'm pretty disconnected from pop culture as a whole.
Sure.
And I didn't actually even realize the Oscars happened.
Right.
Right, right, right.
Until they had happened.
Sure, sure.
I heard about the Anthony Hopkins sort of kerfuffle.
I have no interest in the Oscars, didn't before, don't now, and I really hate Oscars drama.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's not something that is necessarily a huge part of stuff that takes up space in my mind.
Totally.
Alex hates the media.
He hates movies.
He hates Hollywood.
He thinks about it so much more.
All the time.
It's the most important thing in the world.
He was almost in Guardians of the Galaxy.
He's so mad.
So let's start playing some of these clips.
This is Regina King, some actress that won an Oscar who's all pissed off up there with
an angry looking face because she's a good person and she's up against those bad white
people.
And I tell you, if there hadn't been the proper ruling, she'd have been putting her boots
on to march against those white people.
She'll never march against Bill Gates or Hollywood.
She'll never actually stand up for any black people.
No, she'll just make millions of dollars and wear fancy $5,000 dresses and drive around
in Ferraris and fly around in private jets and then bitch about evil America that produced
so much wealth.
She lives like this while Africans are starving to death by the tens of thousands every day.
You can see how Alex's criticism of Regina King is 100% racially based.
No.
He doesn't know anything about her as a person or what sorts of charity work she may be involved
in.
All he sees is a black woman saying something that he doesn't like and his response is racist
outrage.
So in her intro speech, King mentioned how difficult the last year has been and how if
the Chauvin verdict had been different, she might have traded in her heels for marching
boots.
Yeah.
This statement is experienced by Alex as her saying she would have been marching against
evil white people because everything in his life is filtered through the lens of white
victimhood.
Yeah, it does seem like the people, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's not good.
Also don't come after Regina.
Regina King is not somebody you want to come after.
She's amazing.
Um.
She's great.
I don't think Alex knows anything about her.
I would argue he knows nothing about her.
So he also doesn't even know who this next person is.
Okay.
All right.
He's declaring an idiot.
Okay.
Here's another one of the idiots up there getting an award telling people that there's
an epidemic and disproportionately police shoot black men when it's actually the other
way around.
On average, the police in America every day kill three people, which amounts to about
a thousand people a year.
And those people happen to disproportionately black people.
And you know, James Baldwin once said, the most despicable thing a person can be is indifferent
to other people's pain.
And so I just ask that you please not be indifferent.
Please don't be indifferent.
I mean that guy's literally up there wearing a clown suit.
I guess Alex isn't being indifferent to people's pain as much as he's being hostile towards
it.
Reveling in it?
Denying its validity.
Yeah.
I think that might be worse.
Enjoying watching people's pain.
Alex is wrong about those statistics because of the very important word he doesn't understand,
which is proportionate.
Exactly.
Yeah.
He refuses to approach statistics in context because if you do that, his arguments fall
apart instantly.
Also that was Travon Free, the writer-director who won an Oscar for best live-action short
for Two Distant Strangers.
To Alex, he's just another idiot because he's a black man attempting to appeal to the better
side of people's humanity.
It's almost comically racist behavior on Alex's part, and it's not surprising at all.
I mean, it's just astonishing how important skin color is to him, while at the same time
how vehement he is that he's not racist.
Like if you bring up the color of someone's skin that much, yeah, yeah.
So he does spend a little while complaining about the Oscars, but-
Well sure, there were black people represented at the Oscars, and we can't-
Yeah, yeah.
He's not so into that.
Where was- Back in my day, you used to win an Oscar for films like Birth of a Nation
because they changed film cinema forever, and that's why.
The only reason that I let that film- Sure, sure, sure.
So he gets onto another topic, or does he?
Here's video, ladies and gentlemen, out of Tennessee.
And this police officer, you know what, I'm going to come back from break, and I'm going
to get to this because I've got to find my article.
There's so many damn articles here and so much happening.
This is just crazy though to watch this unfold.
Before I go to break, ladies and gentlemen, we have some very exciting news, and I mean
extremely exciting.
One of our best selling products is turmeric.
We have the 95% secret humanoid.
He forgot the story.
He completely forgot the story.
Not sure what I'm supposed to talk about, just in case you were wondering, turmeric.
Yeah.
Okay, bye.
I forgot the story, so I'm going to do a plug.
Oh boy.
Yep.
So we get a little visit here at the end of the 26th from an old friend who declared it
over for humanity.
Sure.
A year ago.
There's only going to be lone survivors.
And that has been borne out.
And now he has a new story to tell.
Sure.
And then also he's got a new story out that's at naturalnews.com.
It's also on infowars.com.
Health Ranger posts new microscope photos of COVID slobs, COVID masks, mysterious red
and blue fibers.
And others have scanned them and found similar weird things that appear to be, well not appear,
they are moving.
And then there's also German researchers have tested what's in the Pfizer shot and it appears
to have things moving around in it.
And so we're going to get ahold of some samples and work with some labs like Mike Adams to
test this themselves.
But clearly this is getting weirder and weirder and stranger and stranger.
So I don't know what this has to do with vaccines.
This is just Mike took some pictures of masks and swabs and stuff.
And in reference to like the moving stuff and that in the swabs.
That's not from studies.
That was from a TikTok video that came out in January.
It's been pretty debunked by scientists, but the underlying claim of that video is that
people were being intentionally given more Jelen's disease with the COVID swabs.
The conspiracy was so dumb and evidence was so laughable that this one didn't really stick,
but it did get a lot of viral attention.
So it kind of makes sense for someone like Alex or Mike to try and, you know, wander
it a little bit, see if you can whitewash it a tiny bit, put a respectable face on,
see if you can make some money off this fake TikTok video.
It's hard.
Look, I'm not trying to get all delusions of grandeur a la Alex.
However, it does seem like these guys wake up every morning and they're like, what could
I do today that makes Jordan fantasize about owning a flamethrower?
What could I do today?
How do we bring Jordan and Elon Musk closer?
Let's see what it really is going to take for Jordan to buy a flamethrower.
So if you go and look at the natural news article that this is about, you can tell that
Mike is even a little self-conscious about this.
In a caption for the microscope image supposedly of a fiber in some mask he was looking at,
he adds, quote, we do not know why these fibers are there and we are not claiming them to
be more Jelen's fibers.
Okay.
All right.
I applaud that attempt to be taken seriously, although I think it's difficult when the,
you know, one of the other captions for an image of a mask says, quote, some areas of
the carbon fiber strands appear to surround exact looking objects, but they might simply
be bump textures in the white fiber layer.
Oh man.
Oh, might they?
That's like saying this, okay, we don't know what this screenshot is from.
We think it is absolutely an alien spacecraft.
However, it could be from a video game.
That's also possible.
Are you talking about Eddie Page?
Yes, I am talking about Eddie Page.
So over the weekend, Mike released a series of completely meaningless microscope images
of things that he's speculating are suspicious.
One of them was that picture of fiber strands in a mask, which may be an egg sac or may
be bumps in texture.
Sure.
By Monday, he published a blog post on his website about these images, and the exact
same image now has this text along with it, quote, what is this egg sac-like structure
in this first photo of a carbon fiber mask?
Gone is the very sensible suggestion that it might just be bump textures.
And now the goal is to push this egg sac idea as being the primary in the listeners and
readers minds.
This is the same shit though.
Like I don't understand how it is that you can have Eddie Page be a fucking moron and
everybody's like, nah, nah, nah.
Look at that idiot.
He's talking about space.
But then you let Mike Adams talk about microbes.
Fuck my, it's just, it's a difference of big versus small, it's the macro versus the micro.
It's stupid.
Fine.
It's the same shit.
You're not wrong.
This is essentially what I would call self-driven narrative escalation that Mike is engaging
in.
In the first instance, you implant the idea that something might be really suspicious
or there might be a totally normal explanation for it.
When you touch back on the idea, the normal explanation is gone and the speculation entirely
revolves around the suspicious possibility where the burden of the conversation becomes
disproving that this is an egg sac instead of the responsibility of being on Mike to
prove that it's not a bump.
That's basically the propagandist magic trick that they're playing, where the burden of
proof is ignored and made your problem instead of theirs.
Yeah.
Without using this rhetorical trick and ones like it, people like Alex and Mike's game
would collapse immediately because they can't defend anything that they say to any kind
of reasonable standard of proof.
The pope was arrested a year ago, it's a fake pope.
Prove me wrong.
Sure.
Now, you'll recall that it was over for humanity and there would only be lone survivors.
I do recall that.
I feel like we are some of the few people who recall that and many people just ignore
it.
You might also recall that Mike Adams was absent from Infowars for months because he
and Alex disagreed on whether or not COVID was real.
It does.
It did seem that there was a disagreement there.
And also I think he was advocating that people take veterinary products.
Well, there's an issue.
But anyway, here's Mike's new thing.
Fish penicillin's regular penicillin, man.
Here's Mike's new bullshit.
I want to say something really important here.
If they had done nothing, no vaccines, no masks, no lockdowns, no social distancing,
this thing would have already been over because natural innate immunity would have already
conquered this.
Okay.
All right.
Great.
6.30, about to start my day.
What could I say to Alex Jones that would make Jordan want to buy a flamethrower?
I'll write something out.
Maybe I'll just improv it.
Maybe I'll just come off the top, right off the dome.
Guess what?
Here's what it is.
Everything I've ever said is a lie, and I believe the opposite now.
So it was over for humanity.
There would only be lone survivors.
And he knew that.
But now if we'd done nothing, then everything would be fine now.
Yep.
Cool.
That really is something that should-
That's frustrating.
That really is something that should get you...
That should be more against the law than yelling fire in a movie theater.
You can't do that.
You just can't.
I just think everybody should boo Mike Adams everywhere.
He should be booed all the time.
But that's why he lives on a ranch, so we can't boo him.
There is a reason that rich people avoid poor people, yes.
Too much booing.
Yeah.
So I think that Mike, his progression from the initial article where he posted these
pictures to the Monday blog post that overhyped and escalated things, I thought that was pretty
irresponsible.
Sure.
And now if you listen to this, his appearance on Alex's show is going to be taking things
even a step further.
It's mind-blowing, Alex.
There are little hooks, there are little gripper fibers, red and blue fibers in these masks
and in the nasal swabs.
I did ultraviolet photography, I did iodine staining on some of them to show the contrast.
It is mind-blowing what's in these masks, and this is all getting inhaled into your
lungs and the little hooks are grabbing onto your lung tissue.
These things are designed to cause harm, not to help, and they do not block virus transmission.
So that's kind of the summary of where we are, Alex, right now.
So in the original post with the pictures, the game was asking questions.
It even ends with a declaration that, quote, we don't know all the answers.
It's all about making you worried about microscopic images and speculating about what they could
be while hiding behind a very clear statement that we don't know what these things are.
Then, by Monday, Mike's tone had changed.
Gone was the declaration that the answers are still unclear, and in its place was this
declaration, quote, it's clear that the masks and swabs are transferring materials to the
body, not merely sampling materials or filtering materials.
In other words, masks and swabs are themselves medical interventions with unknown health
consequences.
It seems like, with no new information and no real explanation at all, Mike had gone
from questioning to definitively stating things.
And now, here he is on Alex's show escalating these definitive statements that he can't
back up at all.
This is how the game is played for these people.
They're liars, and their lies escalate, because that's how you continue to profit off them.
It's a well-established game that they've played many, many times, and we've watched.
Oh boy.
I...
Flammethrower?
I just want to find them in a restaurant and scream at them.
Like I really don't know how loud I could honestly...
That's why it's a priority for right-wing propagandists to learn how to cook.
It's one of those things, Dan, where everybody knows I'm very loud.
But because I'm very loud, I have no idea what the ceiling is.
You know what I'm saying?
I really don't know.
You don't know your fastball.
Yeah.
If I could really let loose, I would like to know how loud I could be.
And if I saw one of these people in a restaurant, I think we might discover it.
It's like in Mortal Kombat, being pushed to your limit to find your superpower.
Exactly.
Yeah, I have to find my superpower.
I have to grow mechanical arms.
You'll turn into Banshee.
That's what I gotta do.
So, you know, we got people getting vaccinated.
Mike says, don't do it.
Don't do it.
Don't.
Sure.
Because apparently there's going to be a dying off of vaccinated people in the fall
or something.
Fine.
It's over for humanity who got vaccinated.
There will only be non-vaccinated people.
Fine.
Yep.
That's kind of it now.
Yeah.
Alex, you're going to see the hospitals in the fall or the winter probably filled with
people who are dying from this antibody dependent enhancement side effect of the vaccine.
And they're going to say it's a new COVID variant and not even point out that it's not
vaccinated.
You nailed it.
They're going to blame the unvaccinated for that wave.
But if you check, it's only going to be people who have been vaccinated that are in the hospitals
at that time.
And they're going to be dying in waves.
It's not a good situation.
This is part of the depopulation agenda.
This is going to play out over the next two to three years.
And people who have already been vaccinated, there is no undo, sadly.
There's no undo.
Listeners, let me just tell you this.
My spirit, my instinct, my intellect says, get to the country.
Get dug in now.
I've waited too long.
I've been so busy on air.
I haven't done it.
Go away some in the next few months because I have to get ready.
I mean, it's a miracle if it doesn't go to the next stage.
Bill Gates and the UN have set things in motion now that I don't think they can turn off,
Mike.
Yeah.
You can't turn this back.
Okay.
I guess when you're wrong, this'll be over for humanity.
I just get, I get so frustrated with this bunker and whether or not it's set up because
it keeps changing.
It's either set up or I haven't finished it yet.
I've been prepared for five years or yeah, it's full of survival food for me and my family
are going to be great.
We'll be fine now.
Also, sometimes things are just so bad that I've got to take off the work to build a bunker.
Of course.
I think he's fucking with people.
It's insane.
Also, if he's taking off time in the near future, I would suspect that it's not because
of bunker preparation.
It's lawyers.
I would think maybe that's more likely.
It's fun how it's almost like a glitch in humanity where we never really think about
how much we rely on shame just to like live in a society to the point where if you have
no shame, it's almost like a glitch in the matrix.
Like you can just get away with anything because people just assume that a human being, if
they said it's over for humanity, there will only be lone survivors and then was so wrong,
they didn't get to go back on the show for a while for them to come back and make a similar
claim in the opposite direction.
A human being would feel shame over this.
You would think that somebody would be able to regulate themselves to the point of like,
I should just stop.
Listen, I've been too wrong.
It's just too much.
Yeah, because I think that if you were that wrong, the correct response would be to reflect
on it and to be like, why was I that wrong?
What is it about my method of finding information and discerning truth?
What is it about that that was so wrong?
Is it that I don't have a process?
Yeah.
Oh no.
That's a problem.
Yeah.
You know what happens when you're making one of those papers for a school, or let's go
with earlier, the Stanford situation, they felt shame having their name attached to it.
They were like, we can't be a part of this and we can't let it happen.
Right.
Because they weren't.
Yeah.
So for no reason, Mike gets pretty shitty here.
Sure.
Well, right.
I believe the rapper DMX did die from the COVID vaccine that was then diagnosed as a
heart attack, right?
This would be an appropriate time for you to bark.
Yeah.
Go fuck yourself, man.
Get his name out of your mouth.
Yeah.
This is something that went around on social media, but there's no evidence that DMX got
the COVID vaccine.
And even if he did, which they don't even know, there's no way you could prove that
it contributed or caused his death.
This is just disgraceful.
Anyway, we have one last clip of Mike and he can fuck himself and I hope he's gone for
long times.
Just to kind of wrap up my appearance on your show today, this is an extermination agenda.
They will come for you sooner or later if they haven't already.
You need to get out of the blue cities, get out of the blue states, get to someplace where
you can have some self-reliance.
You need to get real assets because an economic collapse is coming.
They're going to confiscate all the dollars in bank accounts.
Oh, that was my next point.
Get scared of everything.
Get out of the cities.
Get all the money is gone.
Go fuck yourself.
Wow.
So this episode started with Alex saying that he was going to switch it up.
Sure, sure.
Did not.
No.
Didn't take any calls.
Nope.
Talked to a dumb idiot named Mike Adams.
Yep.
Complained very racistly about the Oscars.
You got it.
And lied about human tragedy in a foreign country for his own profit.
Yeah, that's the way to do it.
That's a real, that's a real, what would you call that?
Triple crown?
I would say, would you say he hit for the cycle on that one?
No.
So we get to the 27th and Alex starts up and a totally different man, totally different
vibe.
This is going to be an incredibly jam-packed historic transmission.
I know how to defeat the globalist.
I've done deep research and I've had major epiphanies in the last 24 hours.
I'm going to do my best to lay it all out today.
Major epiphanies in the last 24 hours.
You know, you can't go from opening your show with Unabomber to then being like, the next
day, I've had some major epiphanies.
Because that makes me feel like you've just escalated your Unabomber plan and you're feeling
better about it.
Well, it makes me wonder if like, what's the epiphany?
Because he keeps doing this.
Blow up universities and airports?
He keeps doing this.
It's nonsense.
So many shows begin with, I had a vision last night and then it never comes.
Spoiler alert, there is no epiphany.
You know, something that really should be more annoying is that how often he says that
he's transcended things and that he's above it or all of that stuff.
It's like, you realize that by any definition of transcending, you would not be doing your
show.
Right.
You would have stopped.
Because you're above it.
Yes.
That's the point.
That's how it works.
You're like so bothered by petty little things.
So bothered by Regina King at the Oscars giving a speech.
I've transcended everything except for white identity fear and victimhood.
Like Gautama wasn't sitting underneath a goddamn tree being like, oh man, Derek at the office
is a real fucking dick.
That's where you're wrong.
He was.
Okay, well that's fair.
Nevermind.
So anyway, we have big news, man.
That's why this is such a big show.
Sure.
So here we are.
I'm going to be very calm here because this is so important and so huge and so illegal
and so over the top that if we just put this information out there, it'll become normalized.
We must soak the sin.
We must cogitate on it.
We must mold around psychologically, spiritually.
We should pray about this because this is all now revealing itself.
It's coming out in the open.
I want to beat up whoever taught him the word cogitate.
It's really annoying.
Yeah.
So anyway, we got big news and when I was listening to this, I was like, all right,
hit me.
I'm ready.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Totally.
Come at me.
Just in one stack, one stack of one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine,
11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, one inch tall stack of 24 stacks.
This is just today's news is so mind blowing, so key, so important that I shutter at even
trying to properly document it.
So I, I will just direct you in this segment to what the big stories are in my view, and
then I will humbly try to cover it as best I can.
And then we got big guests coming up as well.
Oh boy.
That's really become his like tonight show.
We've got a great show for you tonight.
We're the big shoe.
They all can't be great, man.
They all can't be great.
Okay.
It's fine.
We've got a good show for you tonight.
That's fine.
You're a night show.
I've noticed that I have this little tick where I say that things are interesting and
a part of that is because I do think a lot of this stuff is interesting, but I do realize
that at a certain point I'm saying everything is interesting and maybe, well, that's fair.
Maybe that's not, but for Alex, it's, it's, I have news that will shake the foundations
of reality.
I mean, it seems almost easy to point this out, but if you weren't interested in it,
it wouldn't be in the show.
That's true.
But it is still a little bit redundant.
That's fair.
So here's the first story that Alex gets to, because I was just like, all right, let's,
let's do this, man.
You have 24 stacks of news, come on, rapid fire, baby.
We go out and tell them, Hey, the mask are never coming off until you say no, that gives
you bacterial pneumonia.
It psychologically screws up children and it doesn't protect you.
And Carlson is now saying that you need to go out and just like you see somebody beating
their kid at Walmart need to say, Hey, you need to stop that by frankly, you're their
parent.
The kid's out of control.
Maybe they need a good spat.
Maybe he's being too liberal there.
The point is this is child abuse more like you see somebody breaking the skin at Walmart.
Okay.
Alex trying to equivocate about, uh, beating the kids at Walmart.
All right.
It is so easy to see how quickly the party of personal responsibility turns into the
party of fascist Lee attack children because their parents can't take care of them.
They're wearing a mask.
Yeah.
Stop them from wearing masks.
Go into other people's lives.
The party of personnel responsibility.
Sure.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
So the first story is the Tucker is anti mask.
Great.
Okay.
Here's the second story.
Sure.
Here's the big super Supreme enchilada.
Is that two enchiladas medical doctors all over the world from Germany to Canada that
are being arrested by the police that's coming up German police ransacked the house of doctor
after he provides evidence in court, the children are endangered in their mental, physical and
spiritual wellbeing by the obligation to wear a face mask.
This headline appears on a page on the website, daily general news.com whatever the fuck that
is.
All right.
I know that I need to go to the general to get some insurance or something.
But also one of the problems is that this webpage is no longer there.
It's a four Oh four page doesn't exist.
That's a problem.
There's no snapshot of it in the way back machine.
And I find all of this quite suspicious.
Interestingly, I found an article on gateway pundit.
That's clearly about the same story, but with a slightly different headline, quote German
police ransack the home of judge after he agrees with evidence in court that children
are endangered in their mental, physical and spiritual wellbeing by the obligation to wear
face masks.
Yeah.
You notice the difference now longer physician.
Now it's judge.
Yeah.
That's no, I think police should raid.
Police should raid that.
Yeah.
There are news sources on this that I actually find credible about the story, but the narrative
is presented on gateway pundit type outlets is that this judge named Christian Detmer
had his house rated as retaliation for ruling the COVID-19 related cautionary measures like
masks could not be enforced in schools.
It is only related to two schools in this area.
It does seem like this ruling did happen.
I think I, I can be comfortable with some of the books that I've seen on that.
Although the impact and the scope of its applicability, or if it would stand up to a hearing in a
higher court, that remains an open question.
Sure.
I can't find any information about a possible raid that I feel comfortable believing someone
to suspend judgment on this until there's more details.
That said, Alex is telling the wrong version of this story.
He said it's a doctor who provided evidence when the story is that it's a judge who handed
down the opinion in the case, who ignored evidence.
I suspect one of Alex's interns found the story on a site like daily general news before
it was spun correctly.
So he's reporting the wrong version of the story here.
That's that's kind of what I think.
So that's the big supermassive enchilada.
Great.
Isn't that such like a small emblem of his worldview of just like, this is happening
all around the world from Canada to Germany.
Yeah.
And you're like, okay.
I cannot think of third country.
All right, buddy.
So, uh, here's the, what's another great, uh, this is the chilaquiles right here.
Joe Biden announced yesterday, he's going to send aid to India.
It's not vitamin C.
It's not vitamin D.
It's not an end of the lockdown.
It's not zinc.
It's not even oxygen bottles.
When any medical doctor in the Indians aren't stupid, they are you talking about space balls
because the population is so huge that you can do inhaled steroid and a hundred percent
of the time helps you knocks it out.
They're not telling them any of that.
They're shipping them tens of millions of doses of AstraZeneca.
That's even banned in the U S is not authorized in the U S Biden's going to dump Europe's
banned vaccine on the Indian total war crime.
First things first, the Oxford AstraZeneca vaccine was actually developed by the serum
Institute of India and is produced there under the name COVID shield.
That vaccine has always been approved for use in India and India.
Wasn't one of the countries that suspended it.
The reason we're sending a bunch to India is because in order to make sure the vaccines
could get made countries like the United States agreed to purchase a ton of them in advance
along the way, various countries got to decide which they would approve for use in their
country and it resulted in the situation we're in now where we have a ton of doses of the
AstraZeneca vaccine, but it's not approved for use in the United States.
It is effective and India can use it and they've chosen it's one of their approved vaccine.
So it makes sense to send it to them as opposed to letting it go to waste.
This could do that fake laughing nonsense all he wants, but this is not the story.
It's not what he's making it, but we have one more.
Also it's just to be clear, it is not like they're putting them all in boxes right now
and they're like getting all these little vials and millions of vials and all these
big boxes they're going to put up on a ship that's yeah, these, it expires.
They don't even exist yet, you know, like, okay, all right, man, come on.
So if that was the chilaquiles, then what do we got a chile relleno another dish schools
around the world are banning people working there who've taken the experimental MRNA gene
therapy because it can cause the spread of real viruses.
That's even your precious wall street journal and NPR reporting that.
So it's a big, big, big deal, ladies and gentlemen.
This isn't true.
There was one school in Miami called the Centner Academy that's banned vaccinated teachers
from interacting with students.
It's a private school that was opened in 2019 that appears to be run by nuts.
So I'm not too surprised here, but it's pretty funny that Alex is exaggerating this
into a phenomenon where all over the world schools are banning vaccinated teachers.
Ridiculous.
Wow.
Yeah, man, you can just be a dumb dumb anywhere and Alex will find you.
So we had, uh, our boy, the health ranger on the last episode and now we got another,
how are we going to up the game?
Oh, we got a ding dong.
Okay.
Well, ladies and gentlemen, he has been banned off of the internet as we know it, except
for his own site, which is still very popular.
It makes them mad.
So he's not banned off the internet as we know it.
Uh, yeah.
I mean, he still has a verified account on Twitter.
It seems like he's very not banned on the internet as we know it if his own page is
up.
Yeah.
So I checked that and it's still up there verified.
Sure.
And while I was confirming that I checked out his pin tweet, which was captioned video
proof that I'm on a no fly list.
Uh, my experience of this is a little bit different.
Okay.
Here's a little clip that made me like, I don't know.
And there's no way I could get on this plane.
No, you cannot allow, they're not letting you fly with Southwest.
With Southwest.
But maybe Delta, maybe.
I'm not sure.
Okay.
I know that was a TSA number.
I'm not sure if you're blocking off just the no flight list.
Did they give you a reason?
No.
It's a no fly list you said?
I'm not sure.
Oh, okay.
So that's from Nick's video.
Proof!
Here's Alex's coverage.
Okay.
So the truth gets out when you speak out and you take action.
Here's the article from info awards.com breaking America first founder, Nick Fuentes put on
no fly list.
And they told him why.
You were at the Capitol, not even in the Capitol.
See now they've arrested 500 that went in now.
So the video that Nick Fuentes posted of himself at the airport doesn't show them saying why
or even that he is on a no fly list.
Was that?
Weird.
It's weird.
The proof that is being presented doesn't seem to, it seems like it's bullshit.
Wait.
So the time that I saw all that trending nonsense about Fuentes is on a no fly list for sure.
Is that what that's all based off of?
What?
That, that, that he's on a no fly list.
His own video?
Um, yeah.
And I guess he, we'll, we'll talk about it a little bit more.
Okay.
He was trying to go down to a DeSantis rally in Florida and he wasn't allowed to fly.
And there are some better theories as to why.
Yeah, that makes sense.
And we'll get to that once Nick's on the show.
Okay.
But Alex has to spread some other bullshit first.
They're intimidating going to witnesses in the Chauvin trial and throwing pig blood on
what they thinks their house at pig heads and going to the jurors houses.
We now learned somebody had leaked it.
That's why they voted and went along with the mob, intimidating him, whether you think
show almost guilty or not.
He's got to go free.
I don't care if he's black or white because of that.
Alex has this story completely wrong.
I've still seen no evidence of any jury intimidation in the Chauvin case, but Alex is specifically
lying about one comment that was reported where someone referred to as a Chauvin juror
said, quote, I did not want to go through all the rioting and destruction again.
I was concerned about people coming to my house.
If they were not happy with the verdict, liars like Jack Pessobek started passing it along
on social media.
And the story spread pretty far that way.
And it's almost certainly what Alex is covering as real news here.
The problem is that this person wasn't a jury and the juror in the trial, she was an alternate
juror who played absolutely no role in the deciding of the case.
And the comment was taken out of context.
The full context of that quote is her response to a question posed by a local Minneapolis
news outlet about whether or not she wanted to be a juror, quote, I had mixed feelings.
There was a question on the questionnaire about that, and I didn't know because the
reason at that time was obviously I didn't know what the outcome was going to be.
So I felt like either way, the outcome was you're going to disappoint one group or the
other.
So I didn't want to go through this whole rioting and destruction again.
And, you know, a little concerned about people outside my house if they weren't happy with
the verdict.
Sure.
She was just discussing the idea of whether or not she wanted to be a juror at the time.
And totally reasonable fears, too.
Yeah, and this has been twisted by liars like Jack Pessobic and being misreported by Alex
in order to try and argue for getting Chauvin freed.
Of course.
Because of course.
Yeah, naturally.
So we get to Nick Fuentes, and I just do that because Alex likes to pronounce his name with
that hard U in there.
Fuentes.
And he's going to tell a story of what happened to him at the airport.
And I will say that, I don't know, I don't know if this did happen.
It's certainly not in the video labeled proof that I'm on a no fly list.
If this is his proof, you'd think it would be in the video.
Well, his story, it sounds like the story that someone like him would tell, but it certainly
doesn't match that video.
Wow.
Because she said, you know, is there anything that might be causing this?
Is it a mask thing?
Did you have an incident on American before?
I said, no, nothing like that.
Never any issues like that on American Airlines.
And you know, I've been flying pretty recently.
She said, OK, well, I'll give them another call.
And they relayed the same message.
I'm not able to fly.
And I said, well, you know, honestly, it's political.
I said, I'm a political guy.
I said, I think it's political.
And she goes, she goes, I'm not supposed to say this, but I think this woke stuff is out
of control.
I don't think it's fired, but they're pushing this on the corporations.
So, you know, she was even sympathetic.
Yeah, sure.
These people are psycho.
These are absolute psychos.
This is that Jacob Wall at the coffee shop kind of nonsense.
Absolute lunatics.
Yeah.
So this is not in the video, but this is the story.
He goes, he talks to these people and they say, no, you cannot fly.
So he goes, he goes to United.
And guess what?
This isn't in the video either, because he was talking to someone from Southwest.
Yeah, it does seem like he was talking to somebody from Southwest.
I went over to United.
I went all the way over to the other terminal.
I booked the same flight, you know, 1040 a.m. to Palm Beach from O'Hare.
I went up to the counter and she told me the exact same thing.
She was on the phone with the TSA for a half hour, said, nope, I'm sorry.
And she goes, and you know what?
I just Googled you.
And I think I know why that is.
That's what she said.
He goes, and I'm so sorry, but but there's nothing I could do.
I said, OK, is there anyone I could talk to?
Can I go to the TSA?
She goes, nope, nobody could talk to.
That's it.
So I'm on the no fly list.
And and it has to do with the Capitol on January 6th.
OK.
I don't see any indication that any of this is real.
This is all just being suggested.
Nope.
A bunch of nonsense.
No, but I should get a text alert if I know he's in Chicago.
He lives in Chicago.
I know.
But like where I can find him, you know, like in public, you know what I'm saying?
Like I only because Amazon Prime is sending me something right now and you know what I'm
saying?
I'm not going to say what it is.
Amazon Prime.
I only agree with this.
If the only use of that information is avoiding wherever exactly, I would absolutely avoid
it with the thing that I am going to like this kind of talk, man.
Oh, come on.
So Alex recaps Nick's story.
And I will say there are two giant assumptions in here.
Recap.
You've been put on a no fly list.
They admitted it's because you weren't simply covering the Capitol.
So no fly list and because you were covering the Capitol.
Right.
Those are the assumptions.
There's no reason to suspect that Nick is on a no fly list because of the events of
January 6th.
A lot of folks might have forgotten by now, but in December 2020, Nick made a big deal
online about getting kicked off a plane for not wearing his mask correctly and told the
guy on the plane, fuck you and eat shit.
That might have something to do with it.
Yeah.
You remember in that first clip that Nick was talking, he's like, is this something
to do with masks?
Yeah.
It's obviously because you got kicked off a plane six months ago.
Obviously.
I don't know if he's on a no fly list.
I would assume he's not, since the simpler explanation is that he's a public figure who
made a big deal out of an altercation he initiated on a plane like six months ago.
As a stunt?
Yeah.
So I would say that maybe airlines are like, nah.
Hey, fuck you.
Yeah.
How about that?
Even if it wasn't on my airline, I would maybe not let him on based on that sort of public
incident.
I don't want to deal with that.
I don't know.
You have the right to refuse service to an asshole.
So why would you want that?
Even the possibility of that happening again, especially if you know that he's a provocateur.
Yeah.
And him trying to pretend that that didn't happen is really funny.
Him trying to be like, oh, is there a mask thing?
No.
It must be the January capital six.
It must be that right.
Yeah.
So anyway, fuck him.
Fuck him.
In this next clip, Alex channels Reagan in a very inspirational way.
Sure.
Ronald Reagan back in 1989, right as he was leaving office, said, Mr. Gorbachev, tear
down that wall.
Well, I say, like he said in 88 was the year, not Mr. Gorbachev, tear down that wall.
I say, puppet Biden, tear off that mask off your dirty bandit face.
Don't think that's going to resonate through time.
No, just as inspiring, just as inspiring that is going to be one of those, you know, in
those montages where they do like, oh, the greatest generation kind of shit.
And they go through all of that and they go through the big moments of history that is
going 50 years from now, 50 years from now, that will be in the real show me your dirty
bandit face.
I could see it.
Things go wrong.
Yeah.
So Alex at this point talks to a Canadian preacher who's had the police show up a couple
times because he's not following COVID restrictions.
It's not the same Canadian church that we talked about before.
It's another one.
I'm going to skip this because it's, it's, who cares?
It's another, if you're a preacher that goes on Infowars, you're a piece of shit.
It's a bad sign.
Yeah.
You're a piece of shit.
So, uh, we, we have, uh, also Alex just getting into this weird thing where he's complaining
about the left and they're all, they're all demons now.
I'll just go ahead and play it.
Why not?
When I see the trendies with their mask and I see them with their hatred and their pedophilia
and I mean, cause they've converted a lot of the low level left into evil.
Now, I mean, there used to be kind of high level of super evil than kind of mid level.
Now the average leftist is for all intents and purposes, a devil worshiping ghoul.
I don't, I don't know what's happened to them, but they're gone folks.
They're programmed by big tech, they're programmed by media and they're a small minority of people,
but they infest all the main cities.
They command black lives matter, uh, and they command the Antifa and they're just gone.
Yeah.
So, you know, even the low level, this is just trickling down.
It used to just be like the top level was, no, now we're all demons.
Every single one of us.
We're gone.
There's nothing that can be done for us.
There's nothing that can be done for us, Dan.
I don't know if you know what kind of language that might, you know.
Boy, it doesn't, it's not reminiscent.
Nope.
So, uh, at the beginning of this episode though, like Alex had such promise.
He had an epiphany.
He had 24 stacks of paper.
Yeah.
I haven't gotten through one stack today of all I've got here.
Shame.
I mean, it's that much news.
Who's hosting the fourth hour?
I may have to take it over.
Oh, Paul Joseph Watson, I'll let him host.
I mean, ladies and gentlemen, this is genocide going on in front of everybody.
By the way, if we don't fund ourselves, we won't be here.
So it's a win, win, win.
Please support us at m4.com.
We've got a lot of new, great t-shirts.
Wonder why you didn't get through those 24 stacks.
You know, at a certain point, I think you would recognize that like, all right, I'd
never get through the first stack.
Only two stacks is the maximum.
Why do you have the other 22?
I mean, you know, everybody needs a little set deck.
You're delusional if you think you're ever going to...
Let's go back to late night.
Why do so many of them have that mic on the desk?
You know they're wearing lapel mics.
It's just set deck.
But it's like, okay, so you prepare a meal for yourself, right?
And every night you make 10 servings and you get through like three quarters of one and
then you're full and you throw away all that food.
And then the next day you're like, oh, I got all this food here.
This is going to be great.
I got all this food.
You get through maybe half of a serving this time because maybe you're not as hungry that
night.
Dan, there is a paper mill in Oregon that relies on Alex exclusively.
That brings me to my next point.
He better be fucking recycling.
I doubt he is.
Yeah, probably not.
So we have another guest here and it's another champion weirdo.
This guy, God damn, what a weirdo.
I am Alex Jones, your host and the great Steve Quayle, best selling author, filmmaker, one
of the first big survivalists, one of the top survivalists.
Top survivalists.
And I would read his books 25 years ago, 20 years ago and say quite entertaining.
And I knew a lot of it was true, but I thought some of the, some of the conclusions he came
to were a little extreme.
Well now it looks like he's been dead on.
Oh, what are those extreme conclusions?
Alex?
You want to talk about them?
Maybe they're giants.
You know what?
Here's my new pitch.
Here's my new pitch, Dan.
All right.
Before these assholes get to say a God damn word about being a survivalist, you have to
go on Naked and Afraid and win.
You have to.
That is it.
If you call yourself a top survivalist and you have not been on Naked and Afraid, fuck
off.
Get out of here.
I don't think Steve would make it.
No, of course not.
So I love that Steve was on because I had been wanting to play this clip for you.
Sure.
So Steve Quayle was recently on the Jim Bakker show and for just this clip, I was going to
make an episode out of it.
You were going to do the whole thing?
Because it, but it's so boring.
I couldn't do that.
So thankfully, I listened to the whole episode and I didn't want to go back and find it.
But thankfully Right Wing Watch had cut out this particular clip where, dude, get ready.
Thank you Steve Quayle for giving us an excuse.
Mike down to have your mind blown by Jim Bakker and Steve Quayle.
Zombies that are on the earth are a disease like any other disease that affects people
and they become like zombies.
Is that right?
Forgive me, but that's only part of the story.
Zombies, zombies also have the evil spiritual entity known as demon possession, okay?
Because there is no rationale with a zombie.
The best way to explain zombies' bloodlust is this, the appetite of demons expressed
through humans.
It should be astonishing to people that the richest people in the world, not all of them,
but some of them, are into occult ceremonies where they have to drink, you know, blood
that's extracted from a tortured child.
Now that's sick, but that's the appetite of demons expressed through humans.
The ancient world dealt with monsters, mythological and real, and this is something that is really
important to get through.
The disease will basically destroy the human defenses.
God gave us defenses as humans to resist the devil and he will flee.
But when you're inviting, or what's the word I want, embracing abject demon possession,
giving yourself over to be inhabitant, to be inhabited by the demons who then become
your inhabitants, it's a twofold.
What I'm saying, Jim, is they can induce zombieism, at least the appetite for human flesh.
But at the end of the thing, it's both hands, right hand and left hand.
And the left hand simply is the evil spiritual possession of that zombie.
So yeah, Steve Coyle just this month was on Jim Bakker's show talking about zombies.
Wow.
Yeah.
I do appreciate how much of Christianity does seem to get their idea of the world from like
the Hellblazer comics.
Like John Constantine is also a factor in Jim Bakker's reality.
I would love that conversation taking place outside of a televangelist's studio.
Yeah, that'd be fun.
Discussing, what does make a zombie a zombie?
Like me and my friends could maybe have that conversation.
That would be, I mean, yeah, you'd have to argue.
What are the essential elements of a zombie?
I don't want Jim Bakker and Steve Coyle having that conversation.
It'd be like a game of Scattergories, you'd have to argue your position on that, yeah.
God, what a fucking weirdo.
But you're going to come, ugh.
Zombies are among us, man.
You're going to really come out and say, see, but you, shouldn't Christians all uniformly
be like, we can't be associated with this because if we really do allow zombies, people
are going to put that together with the rest of the bullshit we believe and they're going
to be like, maybe Christianity's stupid.
Or that classical meme that Jesus is a zombie.
Yeah, exactly.
It's like, okay, if you start adding too many mythical elements into it, especially ones
that are referenced in Night of the Living Fucking Dead.
I would say that what your best order of business is, if you're a religion, don't incorporate
any universal monsters.
Uh-uh, no, no, no, no.
No mummies.
At no point in time should Jesus say, we're coming to get you, Barbara.
No Dracula.
That's not going to happen.
Yeah.
So anyway, I don't respect Steve Coyle at all.
No.
Um, and so we just have a series of him saying things and talking to Alex that I have no
interest in treating as real.
No, no even consideration.
You think zombies are real.
The end.
So anyway, the vaccine is part of a depopulation agenda.
This is what's really important.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is all about one thing.
It's about the depopulation of the world from 7.9 billion to 500 million and that's where
we're at right now.
That's a reference to the Georgia Guidestones, which apparently, uh, Steve Coyle believes
are real and the globalists are, yep.
I do love how the globalists love a round number that's easy for ridiculous idiots to
understand.
It's so convenient how ridiculous idiots are always given nice round numbers, you know?
It's great.
So, uh, you know, Alex Jones likes to talk about interviews that he did years in the
past that no one can ever find.
Of course.
And certainly prove a lot of stuff.
Yep.
Steve does too.
And actually I got the sense from listening to this that Alex's whole story about him
seeing fish people with sad human eyes is a story he cribbed from Steve Coyle.
You think he's stealing that story?
Oh no.
Alex, I interviewed one of the Intel world's most famous assassins.
He died 15 years ago and he said, Steve, I've been in a laboratory, some of the most secret
places in the deep underwater, uh, in the jungles, uh, in, uh, Borneo, uh, the Island
of dr.
Morello.
And he said, I've seen, I've seen things in cages, half human, half lion, by the way,
the lion men of Moab is literally in the old Testament.
But he said, these creatures were calling out to me in a human voice, help me, help
me.
I'm human.
And he started to weep.
This is a CIA guy.
He says, Steve, they weren't human, but there was a human component that was begging me
to help.
And there was no help for them.
That stuff makes a stick in my spirit.
Okay.
So your story that you're telling me one of the best assassins, one of the best assassins
for the CIA, someone who's the best at killing people.
Yes.
And especially for the CIA.
So, you know, there's no morality within this person that cannot be, I wouldn't assume.
So if the other details of the story are correct.
But his breaking point, or I don't, their breaking point was half man, half man, half
lion.
And by the way, no reason, no reason whatsoever, none to add in the lion men of Moab, because
these are genetically created now, not the lion men of Moab.
They didn't like reconstitute the goddamn lion men from the Old Testament.
That might be part of his argument.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
So they discovered old lion man blood.
I think that Steve's argument is that in biblical times before the flood, they were making human
animal hybrids.
See, that's kind of what I was thinking.
Yep.
And that history is repeating itself now.
Right.
Yep.
That's where we're at.
Yeah.
Yep.
So anyway.
You got to cop to this.
If you're a Christian, you got to cop to the lion men.
You believe that lion men are real.
The end.
Cop to it.
Okay.
So look, there's some similarities between zombies and lion men already in Steve Quayles.
And giants.
Those are always in the background.
Well, giants were always in play.
So there are some similarities between what Steve believes and let's say ancient aliens.
Sure.
Could be.
He thinks that there's a few differences.
The difference between, let's say my position, the ancient aliens position is my position
is the fallen angels, a third of them basically had sex with earth women.
This is before Noah's flood and corrupt the entire gene pool on the planet.
Now we are seeing in the book of Enoch that people used to say, was it true?
And then they try to suppress the Dead Sea Scrolls, but it got leaked out.
I've talked to some of the folks that are involved and it's all in there.
So they got 2000 year old scrolls saying that, wait, you talk to some people who are involved
in the leaking of the Dead Sea Scrolls.
What?
Oh boy.
Okay.
Yeah.
So anyway, yes.
Where Steve breaks off from ancient aliens.
I do love the combination of defensiveness and confidence in his position while saying
something so abjectly ridiculous.
If you are trying to be taken seriously and you need to clarify your position against
the ancient aliens position, you're underwater, man.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You're screwed.
Look, these ancient aliens people are crazy.
They believe that before the flood, aliens came down and built the pyramids.
That's stupid.
See, what happened is before the flood, interdimensional angels came down and built the pyramids.
It's completely different.
I'm obviously right.
Sure.
Okay.
So this fiddling around with human and animal hybrids and what have you, creating supermen
and sad human eyes, even assassins.
So that was going on in olden times.
And it's going on again.
I'll just let this play.
Okay.
Let's hear it.
Let's hear them out.
The Human Genome Project was to identify the DNA of the fallen angels.
When they had sex with earth women, they produced a hybrid.
Those hybrid became the mighty men of renown, the gods the ancient worlds worship.
And obviously now we're coming to that point where we're messing with genetics.
So I see you scribbling notes.
I just wanted to make sure that forever throughout all of history, written down in this notebook
is the Human Genome Project was about angels.
That's just what I wanted to be very clear and find the Nephilim DNA or whatever.
I'm going to underline it.
I'm going to make sure that no matter what happens, that's what it was all about, man.
The Human Genome Project was trying to find Thor, it was trying to find Zeus, it's trying
to find Heracles.
It makes sense.
I really, really, like honestly, and I mean this with all none respect, this is sad even
for Alex to listen to.
Yeah.
This is bad.
It really is.
Yeah.
Because it goes against his interdimensional theories.
I think that all of it's so nonspecific that you'd have a really hard time.
You can fit it in somewhere.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I get you.
I understand why you think it doesn't fit.
I think that's a good, I think you should keep that in your back pocket.
I understand that because you work from sort of a grounded place of reality where things
mean things.
Or at least narrative consistency.
Yeah.
I think that they could make this work just because nothing matters.
That's fair.
When you have no shame, it's like a glitch in humanity.
You can figure it out.
Yep.
So Steve is this guy who like, I really think that, I mean we've listened to him a little
bit in the past and he has a worse version of thinking he's a prophet than Alex.
Yeah.
Like he legitimately is just like, I know all God.
His whole story is that God gave him a vision of everything, but told him that he would
lock these things up until he needed to know them.
Yeah.
And this just is like, this clip I think is just a guy doing an impression of a prophet.
Wow.
The day will come, mark my words, when even vitamins will be made illegal.
Possession of vitamins, capital offense.
Possession of a Bible, capital offense.
Speaking the name of Jesus, capital offense.
You know, everything is going to be a capital offense.
I'd be fucked.
Here's what it boils down to, Alex.
Anybody but them are scheduled to be terminated.
Terninated.
Terninated!
I would like to mark his words about possession of vitamins becoming a capital offense.
B12!
Get it out of here!
Kill him!
Summary execution.
If you have riboflavin.
What about vitamins and just food?
No, you can't have it.
No.
Are you talking about regulations for the supplement industry?
I think that's what you're talking about, and I think that's something that terrifies
you more than anything in the world.
It's a little bit different.
Yeah.
So anyway, this was a nonsensical interview with a lunatic who has a bunch of really stupid
ideas about dumb shit.
The Human Genome Project, Dan, was about angels.
Great.
Also, zombies.
A group of scientists got together and they were like, listen, we can't not know about
these angels who fucked women in the past to create Thor.
We just can't not know.
So these zombies are also in play.
Sure, of course.
And all this is great.
Yeah.
But I think there might be ulterior motives to this interview.
Oh yeah?
When I heard this clip, mic down for this, because when I heard this, I took off my headphones
and walked out of the room.
I was just like, go fuck yourself.
So Steve Quayle, I know you want to talk about the Infowars phone here briefly.
I just want to thank you.
You knew that we were having trouble funding ourselves.
You said, listen, this is one of the best deals that the sponsors have had for many
years.
You tried to get me to give them as a sponsor years ago.
We did it.
The listeners love it.
I didn't realize it's one of the best deals out there.
Just let me tell people about it briefly.
It's not why you're here.
I just mentioned a new function that you were excited about.
Oh sure, sure.
Sure, that's not why you're here?
You got me a satellite phone sponsor, that's not why you're here, talking about your
dumbass ideas about the genome project.
Wow.
Wow, Alex, you're really willing to let him go that long just so he can sell a satellite
phone for you.
Yep.
Ooh, that's not good.
I don't know what the deal is here with this phone exactly, but there's the website
infowarsphone.com and it redirects to a website satellite phone store.
I don't know if they have an Infowars promotion going on, but if they do, they're keeping
Infowars and Alex's name the fuck off it.
Yeah, that would make sense.
Yeah, yeah.
I would do that too.
Yeah.
I don't know what's going on.
I guess Steve Quayle got him a sponsor and now, yeah.
That must have been a really rough marketing meeting for that company whenever they're
getting together, having like, okay.
I have, I got Alex on the hook for about 5K.
Alex Jones from Infowars.
Are we there yet?
Are we that far down?
Revenue is negative 10 billion.
Yes.
We'll take anything.
Yeah.
That's the only explanation.
Yeah, it's outrageous.
Although, I do think that there's a certain delicious humor of the trajectory of that
interview.
That's true.
Just saying these stupidest shit, the one where even you are feeling bad for Alex sitting
through this.
That is really sad.
And then the payoff, of course, is you got me a sponsor.
Oh, I really, really feel bad.
Yep.
I wonder if you got Jim Bakery that satellite phone sponsor.
That would make sense.
Man.
That would explain his recent air time.
He's a middle man.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
Hey, I get you this.
You get me some air time.
You let me talk shit.
Yep.
Anyway, Jordan, this has been our exploration of the beginning of the week on Alex's show.
I'm excited to see the response to the Giuliani raid, and I apologize that we don't have that
on this episode, but it was just too much with this bulk of bullshit that Alex was doing.
No, we're either going to have to focus a lot on the Giuliani raid, or it's going to
be one of those things where he mentions it, says that it's unfair, and then does not speak
of it anymore.
He might say that it's the end of the world, and he might not talk about it at all.
Entirely.
The range is infinite.
Who knows?
Yeah.
But we will find out soon enough.
Until then, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledge underscore fight.
Now go to bed, Jordan.
Yes.
We will also be on Facebook.
We are.
We will also are on Facebook, and if you would like, please, iTunes, et cetera, find a local
charity or bail fund in your area.
We will be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I was dishonorably discharged when I served under Major Kattelman.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
Thank you.