N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Damn, Ed, Jordan, I am SWEATING
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledgefight
knowledgefight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
you guys saying we are the bad guys, knowledgefight
Dan and Jordan, knowledgefight
Rattle her, rattle her, rattle her
I need, I need money
Andy and Kansas, Andy and, Andy and
Stop it, Andy and Kan, Andy and Kansas
Andy and, Andy, it's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding us
Hello Alex, I'm a victim, calling in with your Japan
I love your world
knowledgefight
knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're a couple dudes, I can sit around and drink novelty beverages
and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are, Dan
Jordan
Oh wait, sorry, we worship at the cult of the altar of Selene
Yes, that's what we do, we worship at the altar
Yeah, there we go
Dan
Yes
Jordan
Quick question
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot, why don't you go first?
Why don't I go first?
I might need to kick it around a little bit
Okay
Because I was about to say granola again
Oh, you can't say granola twice
Deep into granola
You can't say granola twice
Yeah, I know
My bright spot, Dan, is around this time of year
Every year my cousin and I get together and we go to a ball game
I don't know if you know this or not, Dan, but
I know you love the stick
I appreciate the game of baseballs
True, you love the steals
And we didn't get to do that last year and this year we just got the tickets and we're going to a game
Oh, that's great
It feels so amazing, it feels so amazing
I'm like shivering with excitement, I can't wait to go
That's great
It'll be amazing
Who are they playing? Who are the Cobes playing?
Who cares?
Oh, wow, okay
Also, it's the Pirates, so who cares?
But again, the Cubs are terrible this year, so again, who cares?
Alright
They're probably going to lose
Alright, let's see, what do I got?
I guess, I don't know, it's tough, this is sort of a hypothetical bright spot
Alright, I'm listening
I think I feel comfortable enough to maybe try to check out a gym again
Ooh
You know, like, we're vaccinated
That's good, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that is a bright spot
I think even wearing a mask, I think we're at a point where I could feel comfortable
Whereas, you know, like before, certainly there was no ability to exist in that kind of space
Oh, for sure
Well, I mean, your last visit to the gym was
Pretty bad
Nightmare-ish, hellish, yeah
It was a little, scary to see that level of
It was passive manslaughter, is that one way of putting it?
I think it might have worked out better than passive manslaughter
Sure
But it certainly was not for lack of trying
No, no
There was a lot of irresponsibility going on
Yeah
Did not care for it
But I feel like it's about time
That's great
I feel pretty good about that
Yeah
I always enjoy going to the gym
Spring
Yep
Time to go out, hit the beach of Lake Shore
Sure
Take your shirt off and really just, ugh
You know
I was down by the lake the other day
What were you doing?
On rocks
What were you doing wandering around on rocks?
Considering jumping in
Were you?
No
Were you doing
Just enjoying the lake, it was a nice day
Were you doing an Abilify commercial?
I was
Was that what was happening right there?
Staring off into the middle distance?
It was a nice day
So, Jordan, today we have an interesting episode to go over
We're going to be talking about April 30th, 2021
Blackpink!
I was going to say I'm banned
I didn't even
You almost said I'm dead
Shit
2021, I'm glad I'm dead
This is Unforced Error on my part
Yeah, well, I said Black Deck?
I think so
I don't think either of us succeeded
Yeah, this is a terrible idea
So, yeah, I said on our last episode that we were going to be covering the end of the
week
Yes
You know, because Rudy Giuliani's
Of course
Got raided and what have you
Yeah, we gotta figure out what's going on there
I couldn't waste time with that because on Thursday, news broke about Roger Stone's involvement
in the Matt Gaetz affair
I don't recall anything beyond somebody thinking, here's what I'm going to do
I'm going to give Roger Stone
Mm-hmm
Roger, I have a tattoo of Richard Nixon on my back stone
Yes
Incriminating evidence
I'm going to write a confession letter and give it to sneaky Roger Stone
I am going to give this crucial piece of evidence to the single worst person to ever
And I will keep snapshots of offers of bribes to get a pardon
Yeah, there was a Daily Beast article that was pretty bad looking
Pretty damning
I mean, look, anything could be fake
No, no, here's why it's so believable
Uh-huh
Because
The players involved act like themselves
Exactly, and everybody's so stupid
Nobody's doing anything like, even a half-assed attempt at Googling how to not get arrested
for these specific crimes would be like, don't give it to Roger Stone
Well, and the part of it that makes it even more believable on a personal level for me
is that they had their texting app set to delete the messages
Yes
And Roger followed through with that
Of course
Whereas Joel Greenberg did not
Ah, now that's where we're in
That strikes me as genuine
That's good stuff
Yeah
So that came out, I was like, well, the 30th is gonna be fucked up
Friday's gotta be fucked up
Of course
His buddy is like on the hook here in this Daily Beast article
talking with this guy who's admitting to having sex with a 17-year-old for money
There's a problem
Trying to get Roger, Alex's buddy
To get him a pardon
To get a pardon from Trump, and it appears through the texts
Sounds damning
That Roger is like, that's a thing that's done
250K, yeah, no big deal
Wow
So big news day for Alex
I am gonna put $250,000 worth of Bitcoin on Roger Stone not calling in on Friday
He does not show up
That is not a surprise
I will spoil that
I will take my 250,000 please
I didn't agree to that, but Roger is, he is not to be found
Not to be seen
My lawyers have told me to pray more
We do get a lawyer show up
Oh yeah, that's not surprising
Yup, so Jordan, we'll get into this and see what Alex's response is
But before we do, I gotta take a little moment and say thank you
And welcome in some wonks
So first
That's a great idea
Someone tried to catfish my mom with a picture of Alex Jones
And now I'm here
Thank you so much, you're now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
I assume the path that everyone took to our show
Sure
Next, actual biblical Satan
Thank you so much, you're now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Aww, thanks buddy, hail Satan
Next, human cat Rymera
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Oh, thank you very much, human cat Rymera
Thank you
Next, Fruitsie Collins
Thank you so much, you're now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, Fruitsie Collins
Thank you
And, Bianca Donk
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, Bianca Donk
Every time I read their name I cannot think
Honky-tonk
Bianca Donk
Remember that song, Honky-Tonk but Donkey-Donk?
I do, remember Honky-Tonk but Donkey-Donk
It's man. What a great time in culture. You know what's weird every time you remember something I get sadder. I
Don't know why I need to retain the memory
No, there's so many things you know that song is one of the main reasons I hate the doors
All right end the episode we have to end after that that was perfect you won you won you won you won
Podcast well, I'd like to take that win and transition it over into wishing happy birthday to Ying out there
I don't know when Ying's birthday is but it's in May from what I understand. Somewhere around yes
And I also don't know the name of the person who wished them a happy birthday
Why would you? That's not important. The screen name is Dan didn't say my joke name. See there you go
Sometime in May
Looks like you've been had. Sometime in May there is a person out there named Ying
Who has a birthday and also an anniversary with a person whose screen name is Dan didn't say my joke name
So it's vague. Here's here's what I love about us what?
Shows wouldn't do this what we're doing right now sure but two shows that did do this would do follow-up stuff
But that's why you come to us you come to us for us to
Vaguely know a little bit enough to be like you're great like to suggest
Yeah, yeah, so Jordan, let's get into it April 30th. All right Friday. Let's do it
Alex's show started with some troubling news
That comes was it that Matt Gates? No, no, it's troubling news that comes in the form of the voiceover
Coming to you live from the infowars.com
studios in the recaptured state of Texas I'm glad you responded that way because I couldn't tell if we've talked about that before
What did they recapture it from oh, I don't know it was occupied text. Yes, very entire career
It's been occupied but then we deliver it it was FEMA region sick, but then he was liberated for a while wasn't it?
I don't think so. I think what there was a time was it was like a state currently turning blue
Yeah, I guess it's been recaptured
Yeah, maybe that's meant to be like recaptured by democratic
I don't know. I mean the more
Latinx people are allowed to vote in Texas the more it is being recaptured from from the colonialists. So that's nice
Yeah, I thought I was strange and I think I might have heard that before in the past
But it struck me as very new and I don't know what it's in reference to. It struck me
Yeah struck me. Um, so I recaptured who got it Alex. Oh, okay and and Joe Rogan good for them
Yeah, good for them. So Alex starts the show off with some Lana Del Rey and it is also rude
No, it's it's it's more aggressive. Okay, some of the more
more
Symphonic moody or Lana Del Rey songs, but it's too loud and they did not mix this. Well, I am your host Alex Jones
I'm extremely honored
And blessed to be here
I want to lay out a great truth to you
the car up front
And then I'm gonna give you more evidences of it. You're a very small planet
Hurdling through space orbiting a standard yellow star two-thirds of the way out of the spiral arm of the Milky Way galaxy
Get up, there are seven and a half plus million people on this planet
The globalists see themselves as guardians of the earth guardians of the galaxy what and that they are doing almost our disease stunning
Poisoning dumbing down and then culling of the human population
Sure
And when you see their approach to animals you see their same approach to us
The EU has laws have been placed for more than a decade now that you don't take a sheep into a slaughterhouse
And hit it in the head with a hammer
That's too crude. You know, it kills it pretty much right away or knocks it out
Everybody was selling parties for money. What do you got to finish and then you butcher it?
And so that's what they're doing is poisoning us dumbing us down with drugs and electro magnetic radiation
in all systems
And psychologically confusing is taking God away from us separating us from God sure
So we don't have any North Star sure and then we'll be so stunned
so diseased
So much in a mesmerized sleep state, right, but they'll be able to then go ahead and gut us
Chop us up nicely and in the species as we know it. So these super predators can play God, right?
We're not I think I just heard that Matt Gates was going to jail
I don't know what you heard. All I heard is just stuff you can just say no
No, I don't know what humane practices at slaughterhouses have to do with those. That's
Cuz you got it in the slaughterhouse no country for old men. That was a book and a movie
I just I just hear Alex saying things that I just just reject. Yeah
No, that's that's a that's one of those things where somebody's still in time. Yeah, and after a while you just go
Screw you don't care or exactly what you were doing is like isn't there something you should be talking?
Yeah, yeah, it's good. Hey, aren't there crimes? Didn't you go? Didn't y'all?
Seems like you would be talking about all of them crimes. Yeah, Alex gets you know, we just just just talking through it
Just got to get through it. They need to bankrupt us and put us in to a
Position of total control and that's what all of this is about
But here are the really huge
gigantic
issues
everybody needs to be made aware of
and that is
Many of us
Into a post
Human world. Oh man, a special report just starts playing somebody
Somebody in there is I'm telling you dad. Somebody won. The music was too loud. Yeah, we've seen too many
Appropriate song choices. I think it's real
Also, I don't know if I have a clip of it, but Alex played Tarzan boy on this
Which he hasn't played in a really long time. I'm telling you there's a secret patriot inside the Infowars studio
Here's the sending messages. Here's the problem
It's that like the line between fucking with Alex and incompetence is indiscernible. Oh, no, it's impossible to know
There's nothing better than that noise. He made I know
It's just that moment of real resignation, yeah, just like this is how it is
He's too tired to even get mad. This is how it's going to be
This is how it was. This is how it's gonna be for the future. I love it
So Alex has a special report that he wants to play and it might have been that one that started
Accidentally, I'm not entirely sure here. He sets that up
But let me get these part of a report Gregory strongly puts out three to five minute reports. They're all excellent. I
Called him up at six o'clock last night
and I said Greg will you stay late tonight and tomorrow morning and get out a report on this because
Joe Rogan had the courage to have this guest on who's a big investigative journalist the Washington Post
And that was two days ago last night three days ago today, and it didn't get any coverage because they know it's true
They don't want to attack Joe Rogan for oh, yeah
The Washington Post reporter on about Fauci being on lab and the leak and covering it up
Which is true and which is huge but to have this come out and Joe Rogan cover it is massive
If we can force this story out
This this this could really
Devastate the New World Order their whole operation. So recently Rogan had an episode where he talked to a guy named Josh Rogan
Rogin sure not really. No. No, I understand this Joe and Josh Rogan
I got this guy's a reporter who worked for the Washington Post
I watched the relevant part of the interview and I don't find it to be super convincing
That said Josh was explaining to Rogan why the theory that the virus
Started in that Wuhan lab is not necessarily completely crazy
He doesn't prove or even claim definitively that he has information that Fauci or the lab is responsible for the outbreak
He's just reiterating information that's been widely publicly discussed over the entire last year
There's some circumstantial evidence that makes people think that it got loose from a lab
There's some circumstantial evidence that makes it look like the virus was naturally occurring
That's not even a new or controversial thing to say. Yeah, it's just that
Generally experts who have looked at it feel that the natural explanation is far more likely. Yeah
No, there was like it two weeks ago
There was another story where it's like DoD can't rule out a possibility and you're like, well, yeah, of course not
They're a bunch of yeah proving a negative is really really hard and unless it's a binary possibility
Right and you prove the affirmative right like it's very difficult. And so obviously
Obviously people who are talking about this seriously deal with it
Only unserious people would be like there is no possible way I declare upon
Yeah, yeah, like and people like Alex will create that of their opposition
They will create that straw man of their opposition cuz that's easier to argue again
Yeah
so Josh kind of seems like a little bit of a dick only because I don't believe that he's unaware of what he's doing like
He's not some guy on his first press appearance. He's a guy with a career in media
He knows that what he's doing is lending the credibility of his mainstream media credentials to be used exactly how Alex is using this clip
on his show now
Unless Josh had some actual evidence of anything the behavior he displayed in that interview is at best irresponsible
This next clip from Alex's show which is complete bullshit is the direct result of that kind of irresponsibility
Bombshell Friday live Washington Post investigation says Fauci behind Wuhan leaks and he's the main suspect
So now it's turned into a Washington Post
Investigation that Fauci is the main suspect in getting rid of the getting that COVID out there. Well, so yeah
I mean all you've done is
Create like because what what's proven by the conversation that he has with Rogan nothing
What what what what extra do they bring to the table other than sort of name Washington Post reporter?
That's what they bring to it. They bring legitimacy. Yeah from the Washington Post and it's Rogan gets to call it a win
Yeah, it's not introducing a new idea that like
There's a slight possibility that there was there's a lab origin. It's not that that's not new
It's normalizing the conclusion right that it was
From a lab. No, it's just irresponsible
And I just don't believe that somebody who could have the level of career that he does
Would be able to go on Rogan and not recognize that your behavior would be interpreted by listeners that way, right?
Well, I mean in that situation
there's two things going on one if you have any
Credibility that you've built up through being a reporter of any kind of quality or something and you go on info wars or Rogan or whatever
They're there to steal your credibility
They don't give a fuck about you your credibility is what they're stealing so they can do that and you're there
to get
Attention, right? That's the deal. Maybe sell something you're selling exactly
So if you're so like when you're a reporter for the Washington Post
If you don't know that you're there to sell something and they're there to steal your credibility
You're stupid like that's beyond the pale. Yeah, because that's the only reason you would go
Not because Joe's fun no, no because Joe's such a good Jamie is a cool, dude
I don't actually know anything about him never heard. I heard he googles. Yeah
Yeah, so Alex has a little friend from across the pond who pays a visit on this episode
Paul Joseph Watson sure boy. This is really just all about anti-muslim agitation. There we go
I was wondering oh boy
People say oh well the French they capitulated Hitler. So so what the French are people folks
they've just been controlled by tyrants like we are and
And we're all French tomorrow. London is London Stan. Look at our borders are wide open. Okay, so
France is the gateway to the UK and to the rest of Europe and the world
So we need to stand with the French people. They're good people. So the whole thing is essentially that this is a
extreme instance of anti-muslim
Yeah, programming. It's pretty it's pretty ridiculous. Yeah, just geographically. Mm-hmm. How could France be the gateway the channel?
Isn't the channel from France? No, I understand that the channel is for France to England
But I mean, you know gateway like for Europe like France is like if you're looking at a map of Europe
Right, right and you got the whole Europe thing. There are some friends being here
Yeah, then all this other stuff being in the way. Mm-hmm for the gate part. Yeah
I mean you make an interesting geographical that's fair. That's what does it feel?
That's true. It doesn't feel as real and does that argument scare you?
Because if not throw it away, there's 15 countries between them and the gateway to London and channel
So yeah, what's going on here is that there was an open letter that got published in France that was about
the fear of Muslims
We'll talk about it here in a little bit. Here's Paul discussing it
Well, this is an open letter sent to the government of France Alex
And we've heard noises from these military personnel before both active duty and retired by the way many of them retired generals
Warning about the situation on the edges of the suburbs of major cities in France and this mirrors across
Many major European capitals as well as other French cities such as Lyon
That you have this parallel society
whereby it's completely undermined the French government and their monopoly of power
Which is essentially what government is
First of all Alex's entire libertarian identity is based on the rejection of the state having monopoly on power
the entire reason that the Second Amendment so important is that if the populace can be armed and the state can't attain a
Complete monopoly of force. It's so weird to hear Paul be concerned about threats to the monopoly of power of the French government. Yeah
Wonder why that is. That's so strange
Yeah
Anyway, this open letter that Paul is talking about was an insane letter that was published in a far-right magazine called Valor's actual
in France last week
Interestingly it was published on the exact 60th anniversary of a failed coup attempt against Charles de Gaulle
Back in 1961 the idea of allowing Algeria to enjoy self-determination was put to a vote and Algerian independence won the day
overwhelmingly
naturally many former generals
Particularly those in Algeria didn't like this and they decided to form a junta and tried to take over major cities in Algeria
I was running things and then democracy boo
Oh, yeah, ultimately this didn't work out for these generals
But it did lead to many of them forming a group known as the organization army secret
Which was a terrorist group aimed at destabilizing the situation out Algeria in order to maintain French colonial rule
Because what needs to so you want the government of Algeria to not have a monopoly on power
Yeah, makes sense. It makes sense. Yeah, so it seems like this may be more than a coincidence that this letter warning of an insurrection
Was published on the anniversary of a failed insurrection aimed at maintaining an archaic and offensive status quo
Particularly when you read that one of their stated complaints about various anti-racism groups is that they want to tear down statues of famous French
colonialists
It's just it's a little bit. It's a little bit agro
Mmm, yeah that that does sound a little bit like
Memorializing the day Mishma tried to overthrow Japan like with a nice little letter like Emperor Hirohito was pretty great
I don't know if you guys remember that guy. He's pretty great
Naturally noted fascist Marine Le Pen has voiced support for the letter and its signers
Which is what very clearly a part of her push towards running again in next year's election against Macron so
Good. Hey, hey, you know
Yep, this is just anti-muslim agitation, okay
Well, we know is the UN admits a doubling ten years ago of Christian persecution now a tripling worldwide
So if you're a Christian anywhere in the world, the Muslims are killing you including Africa
We'll be right back with Paul Joseph Watson about what's coming next. Stay with us. There are very legitimate issues about
Christian persecution around the world and it would be wrong to not
recognize
that or to
To deny that or minimize it but the answer is not
Oppressing Muslims. No, it's not it's not
Turning it around
Okay, okay
Now I see what you're saying Dan and when you say that you think what we're gonna do is we're gonna break the cycle of violence
Mm-hmm. Now have you considered though that on the other side of that cycle? We're the ones committing violence
So like as long as we die before the cycle turns around again, I will we're golden
I will say that the depending on which side you're on it feels very different, but it's still bad does seem different. Yes
So one of the things that I think that is kind of becoming a thesis of mine
Over time as I see this behavior just repeated by over and over and over again by people
in the info war sphere is that I think one of the
characterizing
Elements of what makes these people in this world is an inability or an unwillingness to recognize the difference between fiction and reality
Right, right. I really think that it's just
something is
And I think it's more unwillingness. Yeah inability
Yeah
I I think that that's the or maybe maybe not unwillingness so much as all of the incentives
Push towards why deal with reality the incentives are towards believing in false reality
So why would you go back to real reality?
You'd have to get like a regular job and yeah, no Alex isn't gonna just like bag groceries, but it's not just Alex
I mean, it's Paul to sure Charlie
Michelle Welbeck famed French author and intellectual published the book so he'd already written
It was published on the day of the Charlie Hebdo massacre and he predicted that there would be so much
Discord and violence because of these Muslim communities that have not been integrated and that hate France
Allied with the left-wing protest movement, by the way
Isis literally puts out in their manifesto that they can make an alliance with the left wing
Because they also hate France and the West to bring it down
so he puts out a book on the day of Charlie Hebdo warning the
The contrived solution to all this would be in a Muslim government in a coalition with a left-wing government
That takes power and promises to get it all under control
So this book by Michelle hula back is not a prediction. It's not even a nonfiction book
It's a novel that presents a fictional future where there's socialists and a Muslim Brotherhood
Political party that banned together to resist the rising power from the extreme right-wing national front, right?
That's the plot one of the driving forces of the plot of this fiction novel. Sure. Sure in the fiction novel
There's a right-wing
Government oppressing everybody the type that somebody like Paul Joseph Watson would appreciate
Mmm, and then they banned together the Muslim Brotherhood and the leftists
And so Paul is taking that as an attack on the real world right-wing. Well, I don't look
I some people have found the book itself to be like fairly Islamophobic and it
Traffics in some troubling tropes, but I'm not really entirely sure because I haven't read it
I just read a description of the plot
I do know though unlike Paul Joseph Watson that this is a novel
Not a prediction of things to come like this dude looked into God's eye like Alex claims to okay has found this
This this vision of the future. No, no, no, I understand but that kind of it
So you're telling me that it's a novel right Paul says it's a prediction
Okay, but if you're right that means that all those Dragonlance novels I read when I was younger aren't gonna come true
Oh, no, Jordan
No
Jordan those happened in the past
That's not the future that's history, oh no, I flat times a flat circle. It'll be it'll come back around
Yeah, so Paul is just a real real piece of garbage
the French government literally came out before the first coronavirus lockdown the Ministry of the interior and said that it shouldn't be
enforced in these migrant ghetto areas so again
literally creating a separate law where the
Enforcement the lockdown the oppression imposed on us is not imposed on them because they're especially protected class
You can hear Paul's angle on this story
which is that poor migrant communities are being exempted from the draconian and
Fascistic rules that the white men of Europe are being subjected to because immigrants are a separate higher class of people to the globalists
Interestingly there's another side to this story and that is the one based in reality where the governments of Europe particularly in France
Didn't allocate funds to provide assistance to poor migrant communities
Non-governmental organizations were working to advocate for the establishment of mobile clinics near areas where migrants camped but their appeals generally went unheard
The accommodation of people experiencing homelessness was tragic at the beginning of the pandemic and there's still serious issues now
But you can see how Paul is rewriting governmental negligence towards a vulnerable population and to actually secretly being them getting favorable treatment
That sucks
Also, how do you how do you enforce a whole stay-at-home order to people who are experiencing homelessness?
Like what are you even talking about? I don't know if there's anything more right-wing than
Having white people ignore
immigrants and then blaming
Them. Mm-hmm. Yeah. Yep. That's the right wing. That's about all Paul's up to
Boy it's a bad appearance now Alex dropped something that I thought was really really interesting and confused me a lot
What is it a hot potato? It's now official. They're parroting from the BBC to CNN to ABC Australia
that
You will get your freedom when you have your vaccine the moment of freedom for you is when you get your vaccine
These are the quotes everywhere and it gets even crazier top scientist epidemiologist
You named her coming out saying Yale medical doctors that the majority people in the hospitals now are from the vaccine
And they're telling people that they have kovat
Wow
We predicted that here it is ladies and gentlemen
It's that thing about like your freedom comes when you get the vaccine
there was just somebody on a talking head show that was
Discussing how some people are not motivated by the idea that you can protect other people by getting vaccinated
So maybe appeal to people's selfishness
As a means of getting people to recognize the importance of getting a vaccine and I understand what this person saying
I also think it's a misguided
Perspective. Yeah, I don't think that taking the advice of one person on CNBC
as if it's the
Like the global position of enemy faction. I don't think that's a smart thing to do
But that seems to be what Alex is up to
No
I think a lot of people should take the things that I say and extrapolate them and put them upon every single person
Who disagrees with them? It's a great idea. It's a little it's a little silly and Alex plays this clip with this person over and over
Again, it's just it doesn't prove any point
Yeah
that's annoying but I have no idea or Alex was getting that statistic that a majority of people who are
Hospitalized now are there due to the vaccine not from kovat and because he's not providing a source
There's nothing I can do with that
I would I would argue that if that were true that would be the biggest news in the history of ever I can
Jordan tell you this though
newly published CDC study found that among people 65 and older the Pfizer and Moderna vaccines were
94 percent effective at preventing hospitalization, which is huge
Yeah, if Alex can produce this data, I'd be happy to look at it
But at this point all available information points the exact opposite direction
Yeah, especially considering how sensationalized it is whenever things don't work where it's like you just said
Oh, it's 94 percent effective at stopping hospitalizations
But how many times have we read an article that says that but all but instead of saying 94 percent effective
They're like six thousand people in the hospital now because of vaccines and then you're like out of how many Oh 100,000
You know, like it's oh
You guys suck at this if that were true
Imagine how the sensationalized news would report that shit. Mmm
everyone dying
People would sound like Alex but worse
So terrifying Alex is taking this news very well
So Alex has another guest on and it's that preacher from Calgary
I was on Arthur paulowski. Uh-huh. He's the guy who yelled at
I mentioned this he's the dick preacher. Yeah, we didn't talk about this
But we we mentioned it that he was on he's the other preacher. There's the girl. He's the other dick
There's the Grace Life Church, which is the one that where Alex was trying to get everyone to go, right?
Right, and this is another guy right who has a has a church and he wouldn't let people in to
Like he'd they'd gotten a bunch of complaints about them having services and not following kovat right guidelines
And so he just yell there's a video. I'm just yelling out out
And the people are like we just want to talk to you, but see now that's that's what you become a preacher for
It's freaking people out of a church. He's got to be a all-time good feeling
yeah, so he's on and I'm gonna go ahead and we'll talk about we'll talk about this a little bit this time, but I wanted to get
Arthur paulowski or art paulowski the great preacher that feeds over a thousand homeless people a week and who has his little church
It's been rated a bunch by the provincial police and others and now it was SWAT team to give us an update street church
Dot-ca was on Monday. Their services are coming up this weekend
They may try to lock the church up like they've done many others
He's saying he's gonna go to one of the places like Walmart or wherever. He's gonna announce it via email to his flock
And so they'll have it where they do allow it. So I thought that was kind of interesting
I'm not sure based on this interview if he's saying that he's gonna do this like go preach at a wall
Yeah, yeah, but on April 27th the last time he was on here's what Alex said you've got
to
Walmarts filled with people shoulder to shoulder, but I cannot have my parents for coffee in my house. That's against the law
I cannot have a church because that's against the law
But they can go with my church with my friends with my family members to IKEA and have a coffee over there
Why don't you guys go to Walmart say you're going go in and then hold a church service there
You'll be allowed to of course then they'll throw you out. That'd be a great time. That would be a great stunt
Oh, yeah, so I don't know if the reality is that this preacher has taken Alex's advice for a stunt
But that's clearly something that Alex came up with from the two of them. We're talking a couple days prior
Yeah, I remember my favorite parts of the Bible where we're when Jesus got ideas from the devil and the devil's like man
You should really try that out. That's a great stunt. Uh-huh. Give it a shot make all them low
I remember there was a couple chapters that really stuck out to me when I was a kid in Bible study
They were about God making dank memes totally totally
Absolutely. Absolutely. Yeah, so this preacher man, I
I don't I don't care for the way this guy thinks and the health inspectors receive a
Permission from a judge to use any force necessary and the judge's name
That's even more fascinating in this story is no David Gates out of seven billion names
They have found a judge that is a family of Bill Gates
I don't know David Gates the judge here in Calgary. What what?
Seven billion names. What are you talking about? Grow up grow up, sir
Grow up
There are not seven billion names Dan we have had to reuse a few
Six billion nine hundred ninety nine million nine hundred ninety eight thousand
Yeah, man, so the health department got a warrant to enter his church. Sure
And the person who signed it was Gates. What?
What are the odds? I man probably zero coincidence
I just you know
Like if I was in it at church and I heard him just go like and it's the same last name as Bill Gates
What does that tell you? I'd be like, oh no, I guess religion is fake shit. You
Personally are so stupid. I don't believe in God
You've shaken my faith. Yes. Yeah, you're too dumb. Oh, no
My whole life needs to be reevaluated. You're suggesting that all people named Gates are related
That's not good. Even if it's just for fun. That's still crazy
You're a dumb dumb. So Alex and this dude are talking and they they get to
Discussing how the left right the left. Oh, it's us. Mm-hmm
What they're doing is they're using the budget. Okay or something sure in order to get the police to attack Christians
That's what's going on. Interesting
Why are the police so happy in your area and in other areas?
With other churches to put fences up around them and to behave like something out of Soviet Russia
Because the mayor and the homosexual Muslim mayor night named she threatened to defund the police
He took 20 million dollars out of the police budget and then after a backlash. She gave them back to 20 million
Well, that's what it is exactly. The left everywhere is holding the police hostage by the purse strings
They don't get rid of the police. They want the police shutting down churches not stopping carjackers
That's exactly what is happening right now. Oh boy. If that is on the table
I will absolutely hold the police hostage if that is on the table. Somebody let me hold the police hostage
I will do it right fucking now. Yeah, this guy's worrying me a little bit. I did not know that was on the table
well, you know the you know, you got these this
This guy is worried about don't don't repeat what he said about that. I wasn't going to I was gonna say he's worried about the
Cops. Yeah. Yeah, we're all manipulated by the budgetary concerns. Don't worry to destroy churches
It's a that's my biggest fear and at a certain point you want to ask yourself a question and that is
When are you gonna rise up? Oh, I mean when is going to be enough when you know, where are you going to rise up?
Well, we noticed the master never going away. I told people they're they're never gonna end this until people say no
That's right. We will never say what we know about bullies that bullies
They will never stop bullying until you stop the bullying and that's what it needs to happen three words. No get out
No get out
Well, even the New York Times and Homeland Security saying it's a crisis that Christians won't take the vaccine
It's not it is a vaccine. You're all done a
Franken genetic re-engineering program see what I'm saying you prove that's exactly what it is and it's killing now more people
Than the so-called virus it. Oh boy
What are we gonna have to do? I don't know. What are we gonna have? I don't know. It's why it's a very interesting
Perspective to see like and what actually I think the only thing that I really find interesting about this is how how much it?
Makes sense like Alex started this sort of they're closing down all these churches. Yeah with the grace life Church
Yeah, they had that he had that reporter on from rebel news and she wouldn't go along with his like everyone needs to come
Right, right. All right, and I don't think that was fun for Alex. No, so now he's found Arthur
Pawlowski. Yeah, who is like everybody's got to rise up. Hey. Hey, look, I don't need any of your rebel media reporting bullshit
I want a stochastic terrorist. I think that this guy is exactly what Alex would have wanted out of the other
He would still be talking about the grace life church if he was willing to call for an uprising. Yes
Yeah, this guy is exactly what Alex wants. Oh, yeah, so
apparently Alex gets a lot of emails about big medical news that
It never never really makes it to the show. And actually I think that's good because they would just be anecdotal stories
That's true. It would be meaningless. It'd be chain emails
Our email is full of doctors and lawyers and teachers and nurses and we call them
They send us the evidence where they are giving people shots and people are dropping dead at the vaccination centers
And it's not just from the coven shot. Suddenly the flu shots are killing a bunch of people something's going on here
Yes. Yes. We knew that we knew the gates announced a few years ago that he wants to eliminate six and a half billion people
Now I got the judge gates that is issuing illegal orders against the Constitution the chapter rights of freedoms
We know something is going on and Christians have has always been in opposition to genocide and evil. So I think
Have you see I guess I mean like Alex if he's getting these emails
They're just be anecdotal stories, but they send all the proof. Yeah, just sort of never also buddy. Come on
Come on. Oh
Also that killing 6.5 billion people is the Georgia Guidestones. He's just referencing rocks in Georgia. Yeah, man
I really don't think that I would like my
Christian preacher adding a little Georgia Guidestone in there every now and again, you know
You know what people add in and making another reference to how the judges name is. Yeah, that's not good. No, it's not good
No, I got this judge name
So Polowski is the kind of guy though, who's not gonna be deterred by this the state cracking down on him sure
It doesn't seem like it. Well, what's the Bible verse pastor? I forget that the gates of hell shall not prevail against Christ Church
That's exactly that's why tomorrow. I'm opening the church tomorrow. I'm going to be preaching
Let the whole world see what is happening in the city of Calgary in this beautiful country of ours, Canada
And at least let there be thousands of people witness
Saturday Sabbath services tell us what time and where people can go to the website as well
Interestingly our tour did have his services the next day on this Saturday. How'd it go? Things didn't go well. Oh, what happened?
I'll just read to you here from an article in the Calgary Herald quote community members living on
living near Street Church say preacher Artur Polowski and his followers have threatened neighbors with violence after speaking out against the
Congregations disregard for public health measures and their hateful rhetoric Christians have always been against violence
Yeah, no, no, not their style from this article quote
Our neighbors here have been threatened for at least seven weeks by these anti-maskers who are violating health
Regulations and spreading messages of hate said Michelle Robinson who lives in the neighborhood
This is a very similar thing to what happened after the big uproar surrounding that Grace Life Church where Alex implored everyone to show up
people did show up there and you know, who knows if it was because of the rebel news reporting or just some blog or Alex who
knows exactly but
Elizabeth Simmons the deputy director of the Canadian anti hate Network told CTV this after quote monitoring the crowd
Quote it would be accurate to say that the event attracted far-right and right-wing conspiracy minded individuals for sure would be
This is important to understand
There's a reason why Alex is trying to ramp up and heighten the tension surrounding churches that refuse to cooperate with public health measures
This is an intentional strategy meant to create a standoff that will lead to a galvanizing moment for the extreme
Right, this is a super dangerous situation
And even if it doesn't escalate any further the neighbors of this church are having to deal with an incredibly unfair circumstance
Where this narcissist and preachers clothing is creating a powder keg in their front lawns like it's just inappropriate
and it we need to need to understand that this is an intentional thing whether or not Alex is sitting there with a whiteboard
Trying to draw out how to create a martyr. Yeah or to create a conflagration of some sort
No, he might as well put a billy. I'm putting a million dollar bounty on whoever can start a holy war
It's it's he's trying to ramp up the tensions that would lead in that direction and hoping for the worst
Yeah, well, I mean whiteness didn't work in America. So let's try religion in Canada
I think is what he's trying to do. It's it's it's pretty upsetting and I I hope for
You know all these these situations to be navigated
Delicately. Yeah, good luck
So Alex gets done with this dude and he gets back to the news and he's got a fucking bombshell
There's a huge report that's gonna be posted
In the next 20 minutes the band on video that we worked on for a while. There's so many examples of it
I only wanted a few minutes of it, but it's nine minutes of it and it's gonna be titled proof. Joe Biden has dementia
May 2021, but that's a good way to put her
Spring 2021, uh, just people know this is a new update
Or just breaking total proof Joe Biden has dementia and it's being completely handled
He has permission for everything. It's just it's just insane and he admits while he has to mention that he stole the election
It's it's just unbelievable. So I have so many guests. I'm not gonna have time to air this on the show today. Really?
You have proof
Tell me that you have a nine-minute video that proves Joe Biden both has dementia and stole the election
Uh-huh, but you don't have time today. Yeah, no time. Just I'm sorry
We have proof of Joe Biden confessing that he stole the election
We have perhaps the most important piece of proof of the 21st century. Yeah. Yeah
So the game that's being played here is he's trying to drive traffic to his website. Yeah. Yeah, that's definitely true
And you know that this is not worth his time on the actual show, you know
I I what one thing that people haven't really gotten me with yet is why I should care if Joe Biden has dementia
You know, like I I kind of don't care if they're weakened at burn easing him
Right, like so far. It's it's like I don't want a monarch. I
Don't want a president who's?
Doing all of that stuff. I'm fine if he's dead
I'm fine if he's dead and they've got him enough like a scarecrow stick figure thing behind him
They're just wheeling him out and deep faking his speeches. I'm fine with that
I feel like you speak for at least a segment of the population
I think we should get some polling on that. I think everybody would be fine
If you're just weekend at burn is it I don't know what the temperature of the country is
We would be fine with a weekend
All be fine with the dead president
Let's put it put it out on Twitter. All right, what happens? Yeah, so anyway back to statistics. Sorry. Sorry, but
Do you know about statistics?
bombshell 60% of new COVID patients are
Vaccinated dr. Harvey Reich
Very respected Yale medical doctor on new patients diagnosed with the corona virus more than half have been
Vaccinated and they're having autoimmune diseases
They're having allergic responses and the hospitals are being told call it COVID and of course
They test positive for it because the PCR test is set up just like Theranos did
So now that Alex has dropped a little bit of a specific piece of information
I can tell you what he's talking about
He almost certainly just saw this in a meme that was going around on social media
Alex has no idea who Harvey Reisch is or where that quote comes from
Yeah
It turns out that it was from an interview that Reich did on Steve Bannon's
Podcast where he said quote what clinicians are telling me is more than half of the new COVID cases
They're seeing to treat is people who've been vaccinated
They've estimated 60% of new patients. They've been treating have been people who have been vaccinated
So this is at best second-hand estimations based presumably on anecdotal information being thrown around on Steve
Bannon's podcast. Yeah, that sounds more trustworthy than data
According to the CDC as of April 20th, there were seven thousand one hundred fifty seven reported cases of people who were vaccinated
Who still contracted COVID that's out of 87 million people who have been vaccinated
So that is not really that surprising of a number
Everyone's dying. Yeah a CNN article from earlier in April had the figure at approximately
5,800 breakthrough cases of which only
396 of those required hospitalization, so it seems hard to believe that these numbers could be accurate
It's it's tough whenever you're working on numbers that are such a huge scale because what we should be saying is wait
396 only 396 needed hospitalization. We have miracles. We make miracles now
We create miracles and all this God bullshit. They keep talking about is insane because only
376 people had to be hospitalized from vaccine. We created it under a year. We need the ICP to make a song about this
So, yeah, like I said, the numbers do not match up and unless there's more than a second-hand story being told on Bannon's podcast
I'm just gonna ignore this
But it's important to recognize that this is the level of backing that a claim needs to have for Alex to take it as gospel
As long as it lines up with the narratives that he's currently profiting off of. Yeah
It's the only thing that really matters at all
I think what's fun about Steve Bannon's podcast is regardless of whether or not he
Previously was a very respected Yale medical doctor the moment you go on Steve Bannon's podcast
Very and respected are removed from my vab vocabulary. Yeah, Yale also published something a few number of months back
In August that was like critiquing and denouncing his yeah
Fervent support for hydroxychloroquine as a kovat cure. Yeah, Yale put out a look at this fucking asshole. Sorry. Whoops. He's got tenure
Yeah, what did we know? So Alex believes that vaccines are gonna be mandatory and man?
He says something that I think is really weird and it's going to be forced folks
Once they get a majority to do it there, they're gonna say oh things would open but you wouldn't do it
so there's still COVID-19 which they set a computer to clarify everybody has and
Then when you die the other viruses and things are actually releasing or people are dying from the vaccines
They're not just gonna die six months from now or two years from now like the ferrets died in a couple months
That's for humans a couple years out because ferrets don't live as long
So they do animal studies is they they'll die quicker, but it's usually the same
So, you know if a dog dies in a week humans will probably die in six months
If a ferret dies in a month humans will die in a year. That's math
Transitive property of ferrets. If a rat dies in a week a human dies in six months a year. I hate you
I hate you so much. They know what they're doing. I hate you so much. I hate you so much Dan for playing that clip. Dog ears man. Dog ears.
I hate you. I hate you
You yeah, Alex can say that you are supposed to keep me away from that shit
No, because it's important to recognize that he thinks dog ears are literal. I'm supposed to be protected from this
That's the kind of stuff that takes your breath away. Yeah, that's that's rough Wow
Yeah, if a dog dies in a way, so he thinks that when we talk about dog ears
We're not just talking about relative time that spans for life. He thinks that we literally mean that's the only way I can make that
Make sense. Yeah, he has to try to approach this from a number of different directions because I don't know if he knows this
But different animals have different biology. Nope. Nope, not true. Nope, everybody
Some things that are toxic to, some animals are not toxic to others. Nope, all things one. Some we are all God's creatures. Some responses that
All maybe God's image.
Okay, it's just timing based. Yep. I
Want to I I just I just can't. It's amazing. I just can't. It's real good. It's it is. It's good stuff
There's something admirable about a man who can so consistently say something that floors me
Yeah
And confidently and with it he repeated multiple examples of how animals have different lifespans
Multiple examples of the same wrong example that makes no sense whatsoever. It's good stuff. Damn
So just damn. So
Biden had given his his remarks before Congress
Mm-hmm, and he had mentioned something to the effect of white supremacy is terrorism and yeah, Alex is not happy about this
No, I wouldn't be surprised. This just went up on info wars calm. I told you this was coming yesterday
Nobody else was talking about it. I wish everybody was Tucker Carlson got it and covered it last night course
He said they're coming after you they told you being white inherently is bad
DOJ actively considering domestic terrorism law to target white supremacists
That's why they tell you Antifa doesn't exist. But white supremism is just an epidemic. That's why everybody's a white supremacist to be clear
I don't think I would support any new laws
for domestic terrorism
But I do think that the idea of taking white supremacy seriously as a terroristic threat
Yeah is something that is long overdue and it's also not surprising why Tucker and Alex are the people on the vanguard
Oh
Their entire, you know, their money is made by white victim hood. Yeah. Yeah
So yeah, your your best bet there for them is like it's a slippery slope argument
But even then you're arguing for white supremacy
Like the end that's what you guys are doing
You're not because at no point are they like well what we should do is focus on the extreme elements of white supremacy
Nope, none of that. So none of that just blanket you're talking about white people. I will kill you
It's really interesting that you say that because I think it even becomes more clear as Alex talks about some other political figures
Sure speaking on the issue
Hours earlier House Intelligence Committee representative Adam Schiff and the rest of the Chinese spies on his committee. Why as well the sinner
stage for the narrative by telling MSNBC's and no Wallace that the
The predominant part of the domestic threat is white
Nationalist. Ah, you know, we're not globalist
We can't ignore that because of a politically sensitivity that some of the folks are part of the Trump base
We have to stop there really quick because I think that Alex just tried to define white nationalist as just not global
Not globalist. Yep, that's not good. No, no
I don't believe that he doesn't know that that is a compound noun that has a specific meaning. It's a problem
I know that there are some people like coach Dave was one of them sure who I actually believe doesn't know what white nationalism means
He thinks he is a nationalist who happens to be white. Yeah, and that makes is like I am a white nurse
Yeah, I don't think he understands
Alex does yeah, I do not cuz he's I've heard him discuss some of the ideas
So him him couching that there is the opposite of globalist. Yeah, that's a problem
Yeah, yeah, that is interesting because Dave is astonishingly stupid. Yes, but Alex is stupid
Astonishingly, yeah, you know, yeah, let's finish this clip in there
And they go on to say the FBI the CIA the intelligence agencies are gonna disrupt us
That's when you send the Green Berets in to kill people. What that's what that means is it so it's all here
It's all being announced. It's all being done. It is the twilight of our Republic. It is a dictatorship
So no, that's not that's not necessarily what that means
But to be clear what's going on is that Alex is defending white supremacy and white nationalism because he knows that it's a part of
His power block. Yeah, he doesn't like that
People are discussing how these things are a problem and he's unwilling to separate himself from white nationalism because it's his bread and butter
People keep saying that I'm a white nationalist and that's way wrong now
I would just like my supporters to continue sending me Nazi coin
And that's the new official branded bit of cryptocurrency of it for worse. I only accept
I just want people to call me apartheid Dan. Yeah, I also think that Alex actually thinks that Swalwell's name is swallows. Well
That was something that was the name that Roger gave to him when a couple years back when Roger was mad at Adam Schiff
Yeah, yeah there they had that blow up and yeah, Roger would call him that
I think that Alex just doesn't realize that that's not his real name
He doesn't say it like as a joke. Can we live in a dictatorship?
when the man who is telling me we are living in a dictatorship just told me that he has proof that the dictator of said
dictatorship is
has dementia and
Admitted that yeah stole the election. Yeah, that wouldn't really be a dictatorship now would it be a weird one?
It would be a strange one. So speaking of weird ones
We shouldn't be seduced into thinking that because we're white we ain't right and you don't win an argument by
Manipulating definitions. Do you agree norm that you're a racist? Well, no
Well, that's because you're a racist. So Norm Pattis is back to be a really sensitive white dude Wow
Yeah, so that was a great joke though, I guess
Just to remind people in case look I'm not noted stand-up comedian
I'm not saying that norm is racist because he says he's not racist. I say he's racist because he
Nom, this was two weeks ago. I tried my debut at stand-up comedy the other night at a small club in Connecticut
And I ended my riff with the following
Hey, you know, I tried to buy woke insurance the other day that the crowd looked at me. What's woke insurance?
well
Woke insurance is what you need if you're a white man because I'm reading the paper and everything that's wrong with this country is my
Fault, how am I gonna pay for all of this?
I need well insurance and we're at a point where you know that sort of humor
It isn't necessarily farcical any longer it is I think that you know in comedy
There's some things that are evergreen like I could probably hear some Mitch Hedberg one-liners, right?
They've heard a hundred times. Well, it's still my insurance bit
This guy tried to give me my insurance for a donut I said, I don't need insurance for a donut
I used to be racist still am but I used to do
Boy racist Mitch Hedberg is a new character norm
Norm Hedberg
Don't let him tell you
All right, I'm gonna die so
Norm is a is a real sensitive gentleman love a racist escalator
Okay, I'm sorry, I'm gonna get lost to that for a while
Yeah, we can't do that too long if you if something if you get inspired, please feel free. I would know
Racist Mitch Hedberg is gonna live in my brain forever
So Alex wants to pair up Francis Boyle, yeah the guy who
Directed 28 days later
Danny Boyle, okay
Francis Boyle is the guy who Alex has on to talk about the Wuhan lab
All right, all these people are Nazi scientists and what-have-you. He wants to get Francis Boyle and norm together to
Have a lawsuit against me or sure do it. Yeah, let's get it done
So that's pretty funny
But then Mike down for this because Alex explains to Norm that the vaccines are dangerous and Norm's response is
Hilarious, okay
I've got to get him with norm pass these other lawyers so that we can go with this
It is great to file and say religious exemption First Amendment Trump's your BS totally reasonable
I believe that Norm's right to sue on that but we need other suits because this is new what's happening of them
shoehorning a genetic engineering totally different system in
I mean if I injected with cyanide and called it a vaccine would I get liability protection if I injected you with one?
This is a mutinogenic system. So I didn't get you on to preach at you norm. I'm just really pissed about this
You're taking action. You're a man of action. We salute you. I gotta get you a doctor
Boyle who's on with us tomorrow. We're gonna tape to air and layer at four o'clock tomorrow. I'm gonna send it to you
I'm gonna get you his number because I think you guys teaming up is gonna be huge. I'm gonna stop ranting
But give me your take on what I just said. I
Don't know enough about it to have an intelligent take what what you're telling me is that
significant portions of what has been sold in the name of public health is actually a pretext for something else and has
Implicit dangers that we're not being warned about if that is in fact true. That's an outrageous violation of trust
Look, well, we have laws in the United States that says a person is free to refuse medical treatment unless and and and and
In order to accept it. They must give informed consent. Now. I took the vaccine. I got double shots of Pfizer
Nobody warned me about any gene therapy or anything like that
So as far as I knew I was taking a vaccine that was tested under exigent circumstances
To meet an emergency. I've you know, I think I'm alright, you know, I'm like, maybe I'll be here tomorrow
Maybe I won't but what you're telling me is is that is basically pay better attention to what's going on
And I'm ashamed to say I haven't you know, let's be clear. You're a marathon runner. I saw you in the salad during the
Fuck I saw you eating a salad
I saw you eating a salad. I love the
Saw you eating a salad
I love the idea that Alex is sitting there and he's telling him like all this scary stuff and Norm's like I
Got the vaccine. Oh, no
It's funny when people take Alex seriously and try to restate the things back to him that he said
And try and act like they give a shit about kidding. Oh, I took the vaccine and now I'm worried. Oh
I was so scared
I had no idea that the guy who show I have been on a
Consistently for the past several years
Said that vaccines had something inside them that could kill you. This is breaking information to me the guy who I
Weirdly am on his show a whole bunch. Mm-hmm has been for a year saying don't get this vaccine
I got both of them. I got him immediately. I'm not as soon as I could now. I'm scared
I'm so worried that I'm gonna be oh, oh Alex. I could drop dead at any moment couldn't I?
I will say that he has the acting chops of most comedians that I've met. That's fair
You might fit in sensitive way, too
Right in there. Oh, yeah, so Alex has another guest after after Norm bails
Because he's so worried. He's got to get this vaccine out of him. He's got he's going out there. No
I'll give ball if I donate enough blood. I won't have any more vaccine in me
I imagine that's what he figured that does sound right. So he has Alex now has another person on and woohoo Nelly
So doctor, thank you. Dr. Carrie my day for joining us
I'm not gonna go over your whole bio
But here is a shot of it for TV viewers all the different places you've worked universities and hospitals and clinics
So Carrie my day is not a prestigious doctor
Who's been right about all this vaccine stuff the way Alex is gonna try to present her
She's a QAnon lunatic who's committed a series of public
Embarrassments that the audience that people like her and Alex have cultivated they're trained to ignore
Right an article in Vice pointed out a particularly sad instance of Carrie just believing whatever bullshit
She saw online quote this past summer
She was convinced that a long debunked website advertising the cannibal club restaurant in Los Angeles
Was in fact a real eatery serving human flesh. We taste like pork. She tweeted dear God
Help us change the world for the better. Oh boy. Carrie is an osteopath which on its own isn't necessarily a bad sign
However being an osteopath on Alex's show who also believes QAnon shit means to me that this is just a person pretending to be
A doctor. Yeah. Yeah
I was really I was really fascinated when she was like see what happens is if you eat a ferret
But then go to the cannibal club. It takes a year to digest the ferret true
But if you eat a person it only takes a week see it's reverse dog years situations at the animal club
It makes perfect sense
And also, I don't know if you remember this person because she has popped up on the show before but her big decline
Her big claim to fame wasn't saying that like kovat vaccines are gonna kill people
Her initial rise to prominence was based around a very not true claim that mr
Na would alter people's DNA. This in turn would change their DNA into something that would be patented in advance
So now your DNA was someone else's intellectual property
Bad
Conspiracy. Yeah, it's real dumb. But that's what she that's what she wrote. That's the wave she wrote in on
I it really bums me out. It really bums me out that these people don't understand
There are way cheaper ways
for corporations to steal money from all of us and they do it cheaply
This is so absurdly complex go if they're stealing your money at a regular low
Boring level. Yeah, they don't need conspiracies. No, as long as things like check cashing places
Or at least exist unregulated
That kind of stuff like why would anyone ever need to create oh
My yeah. Oh Jesus so stupid. Yeah, I mean you're you're evil Bill Gates
Who's the most evil man in the world who hates everybody who's creating this vaccine to kill?
Everybody is against fucking making a generic version of the vaccine that can be sent out around the world
He's actually doing the things that they say he's doing by not doing the thing that they say he's doing. Yeah, it's complicated
Yeah, sorry
Carrie is on and she has some bad news about periods
In one day I asked my members I said does anyone have any problems with their menstrual cycle infertility, etc
since
Being around someone who's been vaccinated and I had over 700
Responses within six to twelve hours. It's unbelievable
This is anecdotal and I do not trust the reporting of weirdo Carrie Maday followers online
Hmm, this is just one of the new trendy things that anti-vaxxers anti-vaxxers are pushing
It's the idea that people who've been vaccinated or shedding diseases that are affecting people around them
Yeah
This is why Mike Adams insists people stay away from vaccinated people and why that dumb school in Florida banned teachers who had been
Vaccinated a recent article in the New York Times deals with this in no uncertain terms quote
Vaccinated people can't shed anything because there's nothing to be shedding said. Dr
Celine Gounder a infectious disease specialist at Bellevue Hospital Center and a member of President Biden's transitionary
Advisory team on the corona virus quote to the people who shed virus are people who have COVID
So if you want to prevent yourself or others from shedding virus
The best way to do that is to get vaccinated so you don't get COVID very interesting
Very interesting take from her if Carrie wants to make this conspiracy stick. She's basically gonna need to create a new theory of medicine
Yes, which would be interesting
Uh, Dan, I've got a new theory of medicine for you. Uh-huh. The Lord's will
Okay. So what about what does God think about nanotech loves it?
Another top five things for God is a very interesting possibility is because we're using nanotechnology
Because they have the ability to be like antennas or uses biosensors
What if they actually are emitting some kind of frequency out there? This is I know it sounds sci-fi
But it's a possibility not just sounds dumb
Um, what if what if these shots are putting nanotech into us? What is Dan? Yep. What if
What if Dan? Mm-hmm? What if all right now hear me out on this none of our left feet are real
Whoa, none of them shit all of this
Everybody has one foot right foot only the left foot all nanobots
Created by the devil. What if Dan?
How does this what does this have to do with the Human Genome Project being made to get Nephilim DNA?
Well, that's where they got the Nephilim DNA. They removed all of our feet
Hurting me with your bullshit. Yeah, I mean like we just had Steve quail on the other day. Yeah, like what are we doing?
I'm struggling with all of the bullshit. You guys are expecting me to handle. Yeah, it's a lot
It's a lot but these are really serious concerns and it does turn out
I was kind of surprised to learn the carry is still worried about people having patented DNA
Sure
And everybody needs to know this that if any of these synthetic genes which the spike protein has
Synthetic genes in them if the synthetic gene gets integrated into our genome
Which can happen because we have enzymes in our body that can do that
If that happens then you can be owned by
Whoever owns that patent overnight
The Supreme Court Justice has ruled that a human being can be owned if they have a synthetic gene or genome
Inside of them. What's that court decision interesting interesting decision for Justice John Roberts to wait
Are you mmm-hmm? What's that court decision? I would like to know
Like that one. I fucking don't know the Supreme Court. So
Um, look, I don't find this person all that interesting. Oh, no
I think that she's a QAnon weirdo who has a bunch of really dumb ideas that aren't based on anything
But
This interview devolves
Okay
And it turns into a story of her getting inducted into the globalist cult or something
unclear
All right. Now you're selling me. Here we go. Okay describe that meeting where this whole scientific dictatorship tried to recruit you
Yes, this was actually a business owners meeting and we had to be bust into the
Location our cell phones were jammed. This is around 2014 and
We were locked in the building until the meeting was done. And this was a lot of big tech people CNN, etc, etc
I was a small fish and in there they talked about how they were going to change and modify
the behavior of the people of Georgia
with using their smart device a health app on there and with somehow getting they didn't tell us how a
Substance inside of their body that would be used as biosensors
The idea is they felt people here are too racist and they're not amenable to different cultures
so they took it upon themselves to change people and
They talked this is how I know about all these substances inside these injections because this is how I learned about them
they said these
Substances would analyze your data your thoughts your emotions. They knew if you're lying by a voice inflection app
Also, they knew if you're lying by a polygraph test with your sweat glands
They can do that also your blood sugar level your electrolytes test your breathing also
You know if you're having sex say you're interested in that if you're drinking alcohol if you're taking drugs
They know everything about you literally they said they could do it
So there's going to analyze this data and then they had an algorithm that a computer would
be in charge of and every time you lied even a little white lie about where you were the
This smartphone would know it immediately by these parameters and give you an instant repercussion
and then also over let's say one to three months all the lies would be added up and then you would be
Considered either a good human or a bad human
Computer would allow you the social credit system or cryptocurrency
You said this on my show this meeting happened man. Oh
boy, yeah, we
We are bringing together this meeting of the miracle on 34th Street friends to determine whether everyone has been good or bad
I wonder like I if I were in the position that she is in
One of the ways that I might make myself seem a little bit more credible. How's that provide details you think what's the name?
Is organization who else was there? It's CNN. What why was CNN there? You see?
No, see, you know
Okay, it was there. Okay. Wait, so the goal is to make people less racist. Yeah, that's why they have CNN
So that's why they have truth
What is it what do you raise we can't go to MSNBC
Shouldn't the story be that every time you're racist you lose points for your credit score. Isn't that only when you lie?
What the fuck is going on? So if you're lying about being racist, you will be shocked
Well, no, no, you're racist because you're sweet
You won't be right. I
Love I love the confidence and the worry with which she tells a story of people
Really just
Figuring out how magic works and using it in any and every possible way because all of that she just said is magic
Yeah, I would assume that what she went to was like some kind of a get-rich-quick
Motivational seminar or something like that. It's just completely changed
Like one time I went to a Cutco meeting. Ooh accidentally you'll learn a life
One way or another you'll learn how to cut a penny
And that was the same kind of thing I was like you can't leave
Maybe that's I don't know this this all just she probably bought a timeshare because that's basically when you're getting a timeshare presentation
Eventually, you're going to think they're trying to kill everyone. Yeah. Oh
No, they're gonna try and make and I bet that she was saying something racist
Trying to make people less racist
Okay, all right
So anyway, Alex is super into this story because of course, of course, he was his dad was they tried to get a dentist
Yeah, and when he was the smartest boy in Texas, they tried to get
Into the globalist depopulation Texas, so Alex reveals something else here that I was unaware of
Go back to how they recruited you to this because they do this to a lot of groups
They go you'll be part of a special thinker group. These are over the best people, but this is proprietary information
We can't let this out because this company only wants to give you this secret
Did they have you sign a form agreeing to non disclose or what was it like to get put obviously not?
And be taken there because they did this on 9-eleven at an Air Force Base
They asked all these CEOs to come the day before said it was a national security emergency
They put them all at 6 a.m. In there. They had jumbotron TVs the towers being blown up
We don't they told him this day. They followed orders, but but that's and that even came out
They did that by the way, you know that something secret happened on 9-eleven inside that that that hanger
Wait, wait, wait, wait, was this the day before or was it on 9-eleven? What were they shown?
And well, they got talking they got brought there the day before right and they had a nice evening
They had I like a little mixer sure right and then the next morning they get up
They're all in line for the continental breakfast and they bring them and they're like, hey, hold on one second 9-elevens happening now
Let's talk follow orders. Yeah, it seems like that's that's the story that I heard boy
I know I don't know this is even like I've seen loose change
Strange how many different things happened in the intervening time period between when they did and did not happen very weird
Mm-hmm. So she talks a little bit more about this this meeting
This is so stupid
Well, I didn't really know what I was getting into. I thought this is just you know more for political reasons
This is a good idea to join. I did it for a year. I had three different people and courage me and finally I went to
The first meeting which I just described which I was completely taken aback. No one prepared me for that
I tried to leave the building and they laughed at me and they said go ahead when they unlock the doors
My cell phone still didn't work and I I didn't know where my car was obvious
It was best in so I was stuck there and there was a non-disclosure in general that was signed but not for that particular meeting
but
It's a group so for a year they vetted you attested you watched you and then decided to try to bring in real first-level Wow
Yes, and yeah, I don't care if I had a non-disclosure in the general sense because these are crimes against humanity
Yeah, no shit. That's why there wouldn't be one. Yeah, that was just a regular old pyramids game. Yeah, that was a pyramids
Yeah, that was a pyramid scheme. Non-disclosure agreements do not cover criminal activity. Everyone fucking knows that
Yeah, how would you ever if you were running a secret taken over the world trying to control people with an anti-racism?
App that will monitor their sweat and dock their pay if they do I was I I was going to turn the person in
But then before I could testify against him, he married me. So it was against the law for me to testify against him
We've all seen movies. Yeah. Yeah, it's like okay. I was gonna blow the whistle on Hitler, but I'd signed an NDA
Yeah, you know you win some you lose. I went to the court and I told him all
And they said you're not allowed to look this is an NDA. Yeah. Sorry ironclad
Yeah, that that's the part of these supervillain fuck stories that are just so so much contract law. Yeah so much
Inviolable contract law. Yeah, despite dealing with the literal devil himself known for deception
somehow contract law
inviolable I'm
Almost certain. This was a pyramid scheme. Yeah, no, that's absolutely a pyramid. Yes
No, I've heard that story way too many times to not know that's a pyramid scheme. This is the Nigerian JT
Absolutely, yeah, so here's what we do everything makes sense like there's a year yeah of like people being like
Hey, you should come to this Tupperware party
Yeah, yeah boy is really cool not look. Okay. It's not you're not selling anything. What you're doing is you just get a
Discount whenever you purchase something and then if other people use your numbers, they'll get a discount too
But you'll get a little bead of that. It's it's the globalists are coming to kill you
And they're like busing in to like a convention center or whatever. Yeah. Oh god
and the laughing if you want to leave makes sense too because I want to bully people to
Or make it seem like they're giving up something. They're foolish to leave right?
Everything is just a bucket
That is exactly how it works
God what a fun but but I love how Alex gets so excited about it as opposed to dealing with this critically like
There's no fucking way
This happened. Like you said it. No, absolutely not
Um, see anyway, that's the only thing I think is really fun about her
now we come to the end of this and
That gates was not mentioned once that does not surprise me Dan that does not surprise me
How important it was to defend back gates initially and so important that you had to insert your own
Personal story and Roger came on and Roger
Was there to defend him? It seems like now in his hour of need dad in the most crucial juncture
I've seen 48 hours 48 hours after the crime now Joel Greenberg has done him dirty done him dirty
They gave him they knew I know he's lying they took I took a polygraph test with his sweat I know he's lying
Oh, yeah, shocking shocking. That story was not cover so strange. So weird. So weird. It seems like that would be fair
There was a lot to cover like Alex and Paul Joseph Watson's anger at Muslims. Yes in norm Pat by the way
Sensitivity about whiteness or well, they know what you went on doctor. Yeah
there's people with DNA getting IP and now everybody's gonna die because of
of globalists and yeah, they steal blood
It's just one of the things too that I've started to recognize and notice about these older episodes that I've listened to like these
2003 ones one of the real changes in
That I've seen is like there are so fewer guests back then and I think it's because Alex doesn't have to do shit
like he can eat a sandwich or he can let these
dumb dumbs talk and like it's just so easy for him to have five guests on a show as opposed to
Like covering anything. Yeah, his heart's not in the game. No
This is a guy with senioritis. Yeah, I mean in his defense
Yeah, it sucks. Your show sucks the people you work with suck and you suck. Of course, it sucks
Yeah, you should be having a bad time
Anyway, Jordan, you've come to the end of this and man just embarrassing
What
What about this episode was embarrassing
It's just like anybody who was looking at this from the outside would be aware that news had broken that's super relevant
You would force yeah, and it's news in a story that they have dealt with
Already vis-a-vis saying that Matt Gaetz just likes to party. Yeah, he loves to party
It seems like the kind of thing might want to follow up on especially considering
one of your
on again off again employees
Is in the mix well, and here's the here's the funniest part and not the funniest part. It's not funny
It's a really fucked up situation sure
But what's funny about Alex and them being so insistent on hey
This is a guy who just likes to party is the the more details you find out the more you're like
He didn't know she was 17 at the time. Mm-hmm. He didn't find out till later
Oh, you know where that kind of shit happens if you're a guy that likes to party all the time
Maybe you don't ask questions first
Mmm, it sure seems to be a reasonable situation instead of one where you're making it so ridiculous that this guy could be
Guilty of this crime sure, you know
like you built the story that it fits it and to the extent that like
sex workers shouldn't be
Stigmatized absolutely as long as they're of age and everybody's consenting and everything. That's that's not like anything. I would
Shame anybody about absolutely now, I'm more interested in the selling of pardons
See now here's the fun thing about that one
I almost and like I saw that and I was like, oh that's totally a crime and
No one's going to follow up on that part
They're gonna be like gates get him get him not the everyone knew that Trump was selling pardons for money. So
everybody knew that so clearly
You could text about it or you didn't have to go into like a parking lot somewhere or people in Trump's orbit
We're selling influence. Yeah to persuade pardons, which yeah
You know do one or the other is it appears to be what a lot of that conversation was about. Yeah, it's fucked up man
Yeah, that's one of those things where Trump would be like
Yeah, if you weren't trying to sell stuff off of my abilities, I would be disappointed in you
You're not doing the job on you. I am I'm stealing. Yeah, you should be stealing too. I
You know what? I'm confident Alex is gonna cover this on Monday. You think so
You are way too confident. You are way too confident. I'm not gonna talk about a
Tell Roger maybe gets arrested again
And then he insists he's innocent. He's being framed. Who's Roger texting for? Hey, I got 250 K Bitcoin
I could use a pardon right about now. Let me rephrase that who's Roger
Never met the guy never heard of him. Yeah, we'll be back Jordan, but tell them we have a website
We do have a website. It's knowledge right calm. We're also on Twitter
We are on Twitter and Facebook is that I'll just refer you I'm gonna be sure to do this
iTunes and if you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area. Mm-hmm. We'll be back until then
I'm neo. I'm Leo. I'm DZX Clark. I'm Daryl run this and now here comes the sex robots
Andy in Kansas you're on the air. Thanks for holding
Oh Alex, I'm a first-time caller. I'm a huge fan. I love your work. I love you