N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying we are the bad guys.
Dan and Jordan.
Knowledgefight.
Riddle her.
I need money.
Andy and Kansas.
Stop it.
It's time to pray.
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding us.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first-time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
Knowledgefight.
N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey, everybody.
Welcome back to Knowledgefight, a little show where my friend and I like to get together,
drink novelty beverages, worship at the altar of Selene.
Yes.
We're still getting the smooth intro.
That one's gonna take a little while to kind of integrate in.
We worship at the altar of Selene and talk about Alex Jones.
Yes.
How are you?
Jordan.
Dan.
Nice to meet you.
It's a pleasure.
It's wonderful to meet you, Dan.
Ah, boy.
Now, since we've officially introduced ourselves, I have a quick question.
What's your bright spot today, Dan?
Why don't you go first?
Because I have a hunch what yours might be.
Oh, well, mine is obviously the release of my super-secret project.
Policy Wonk John sent us a-
You believe it's John.
Wait, well, I know it's John, probably.
The handwriting might be an issue.
The handwriting leads us to believe it's John.
I think it'll be easier just to say, if you are someone with bad handwriting who sent
us Pathfinder rule books, this one goes out to you, buddy.
Pathfinder rule books and all sorts of other figurine things.
So cool.
Not like a Warhammer figurine, but like a book of standee things you can play with.
Yeah, yeah.
Pre-written campaigns, all this really cool stuff.
And Space Finder, too.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
The outer space version.
We'll have to figure that one out eventually.
Yeah.
But when that package came in, just to give a little behind the scenes intel, I got overwhelmed
by the number of books and I said, Jordan, this is on you.
This is, yes.
I believe you-
You need to read these.
Your words were somewhere along the lines of, you need to finally do some work.
Yes.
This is your job now.
Figure out what to do with this.
Yes.
Get a job.
Essentially.
Yeah.
I couldn't handle the idea of even cracking one of those books and then getting lost in
it.
Yeah.
No one needs that.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I read them.
It was very hard to do.
So we decided to do as close to a Pathfinder campaign as possible.
As inspired by this.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So we've got you, Dan.
We've got our brilliant friends, Marty and Sarah from Marty and Sarah Love Wrestling.
Yeah.
And then we have the lovely and talented Liz Anderson, who is absolutely fantastic.
And we are all playing a campaign that I wrote.
Yeah.
And we're all just...
I mean, we're not really playing the goon so much with the...
We're playing your game.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, and the first episode of it is on our Patreon right now.
Yes.
Yeah.
But it's not like behind a paywall or anything.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's just posted there.
Just a reminder, everything on our Patreon is not behind a paywall.
And if you enjoy that, you should check out Marty and Sarah and Liz Anderson's projects
and support them.
Yes, absolutely.
Yep.
But I don't know how to embed things places.
I don't know.
Yeah, if you...
So it's there.
If you know, embed it, we won't bother you.
So actually, this kind of dovetails into my bright spot.
Yes!
First of all, I mean, semi-bright spot.
I really did enjoy doing that.
I know.
It's great.
It's certainly outside of the realm of what I normally am comfortable with in terms of,
I don't know, playing characters or whatever.
But everyone's character is so fun and silly.
It's great to get together a bunch of middle-aged people who have never played any kind of role-playing
game before, and we're all stand-ups and improvisers and podcasters, so it's basically just a
free-for-all.
Yeah.
And I'm excited to see where it goes.
But also, in relation to these Pathfinder books and everything that came in, I realized
that we need to catch up a little bit on Z...
Ooh, the mailbag!
...some of the mailbag.
Yeah.
Because we were going to do some more bonus episodes we haven't really been able to, and
then now this secret project has been unveiled.
And then it begins.
That's kind of...
Yeah.
We have the D&D kind of thing where we also zip the mailbag.
Yeah, that's not gonna happen!
That's weird.
We're not gonna make a...
My character is running away from a bar at the same time.
Oh, what's this?
We're not gonna make Thomas the devilish Catholic come after anybody.
So Jordan, one thing, we missed this one a little ways back, but I wanted to say thank
you to Matt, who sent in that little poster of Chicago venues that we have.
Oh yeah!
Yeah, that's so cool.
Yeah, that was a really awesome little art piece, and we've missed that when we were
at ZFN in the past.
Oh man, that's super cool.
Yeah, and so thank you to Matt.
Another person here, Sarah M., very excited about this thing that came in a little while
back.
It was some honeys that they were...
They're like...
Metal honey is the name of the company.
Yes!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's spicy honey and like a really...
Like a flowery elixir one.
They were fantastic.
And so I wanted to say thank you to Sarah for those, and also the hot sauce of the month
has continued to roll in.
Absolutely delightful, or have we had a kind of dud yet?
I don't think we've had a dud.
Some have not been as good as others, but I gotta say, this one, the Marie Sharps, the
habanero one from Belize that came in, that has been pretty...
Those ones are pretty in my wheelhouse in terms of like an everyday sauce.
Those have been pretty heavy in the rotation.
I feel like there was actually one in the hot sauce of the month that was kind of disappointing,
but I don't remember what it was.
There was one called Illuminati, like naughty, like bad.
Naughty, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't think I liked that one much.
Maybe it was just bitter about the pun though.
That does sound like...
I mean, unless you were in the Illuminati, unless you were like Jay-Z or Beyonce, I
don't think it should be that offensive to you.
No, but I also should say this came with some Mexican candies, the honeys, which is a cool
thing that apparently is a signature of the Metal Honey brand.
Nice.
Send some candies along.
I like it.
Which, of course, I certainly need more candies.
Repeat customers, that's what they're going for.
Yeah, so I appreciate that, and also I'm way overdue checking the mailbox, so there will
probably be some more coming up in the near future.
So Jordan, today we got an episode.
Do we?
Yeah, we do.
I think it was difficult to decide what to do, and I want to walk you through my thinking.
So the first thing I thought of was, I don't care about Alex's take on Bill Gates getting
a divorce.
I don't care about anything to do with Bill Gates getting a divorce.
I think it might be interesting to see him try and weave that into somehow it's part
of the globalist's plan.
I don't know, I don't care.
I think it's also a little bit like, I don't know, no matter what, it'll be disappointing.
I don't care for it much.
And I also started to realize that our show right now is becoming too much just Alex being
a goddamn anti-vaxxer.
It's so one note to a certain extent that I just, I get just burdened by it.
At the same time, we've been looking at 2003, and I had a realization.
You know where we are in 2003?
May?
Yeah, May 7th, which is the day this episode comes out.
This is a rare opportunity.
If we go back to 2003 today, we can cover something 18 years ago to the day.
Okay.
Well, now we have to.
I felt like I had to.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's nothing we can do but that.
Yeah.
So today we're going over May 7th, 2003.
I'm Dan.
This is 2003.
Welcome to the wonderful world of 2003.
The music was revolutionary.
Shit was happening.
People were having meaningful conversations on the street.
2003, just a heavy time in America.
Was 2003 Stankonia or The Love Below?
I want to say that was around then.
But I could be wrong.
Yeah.
I measured time by OutKast albums, in case you were wondering.
I think it might have been A Quemini.
No.
Okay.
When was Bombs Over Baghdad?
What album was that on?
That was, or that was...
What album was that?
I'm going to sleep.
Oh no.
No.
Bombs Over Baghdad, that was Stankonia.
Okay.
Well then that was probably around 2003.
Yeah.
It was around 2003.
I would assume.
I'm more of a...
The time in my life that I would consider the salad days are the Southern Playlist of
Cadillac music days.
That's really where I live.
Yeah.
Fair enough.
And Italians.
Yeah.
Anyway.
Yes.
Jordan, let's list some more OutKast albums.
Okay.
Before we get down to business on our trip to the past, let's take a little moment, Jordan,
to say what up to some new wonks.
Ooh.
So first, Rick and Hannah, this is for you.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, Rick and Hannah.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Next, The Goddamn Pac-Man.
Also included in this is a shout out to you, Jordan, because of baseball season, and The
Goddamn Pac-Man wanted me to let you know, go Padres.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Goddamn Pac-Man.
Do you have any animosity towards the Padres?
No.
The Padres are fantastic.
Fernando Tatis is one of the most exciting, probably maybe the best player, and they stole
you Darv- Well, when I say stole you Darvish from the Cubs, what I mean more is the Ricketts
family threw you Darvish into the ocean and was like, San Diego, you can have him for
peanuts, Dan.
Peanuts!
All right.
Sorry.
Next, I'm Laura Taylor, and I'm definitely a witch.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Laura.
Next, Mike The Parrot Head.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, Mike.
I did this shout out mostly because Mike has a secret agenda, and that is to see what kind
of overlap there is between our podcast fans and Jimmy Buffett fans, and I'd rather not
know.
We'll never know.
I hope not to.
Nope.
Next, Danny in Mexico.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Danny.
Thank you.
Next, let's get some technocrats.
Okay.
All right.
First, we got William P. Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
Also, The Baby Blaze, let's spell B-L-A-I-S-E.
Okay.
The Baby Blaze.
Who is a punk.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate.
That's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right.
We got to go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you, William, and thank you to The Baby Blaze.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
I don't know why I've lost my mind.
I just had to double check it.
Yeah.
Of course it's not on Stankonia.
It's on Bob.
It's on Bob's Over Bed.
That's the name of the album?
Yes.
Of course it is.
What am I?
Stupid?
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
Yep.
Okay.
Clearly.
Yeah.
So, Jordan, we start here at the beginning of the day, the show, as Alex does.
He starts at the beginning.
Of course.
And I have got this thesis that I'm working on that continues to seem more and more accurate,
and that is that Joe Rogan stole the word powerful from Alex.
Another powerful broadcast lined up for you.
It is the 7th of May, 2003.
I'm Alex Jones.
If you were born on the day that this episode was recorded, you can vote.
Yes, of course you can.
Of course you can.
That's powerful.
That is powerful.
I've never done a, what's 18th anniversary?
What would that be?
An eel?
Oh, I don't know.
You speak Greek.
What do you mean?
Well, I mean, if it's a millennium is a thousand, that's kind of Greek.
I don't know if there's a word for an 18 eel.
Why not?
Wow, these Greek.
These Greek people without their 18s.
I thought you meant like, you know how like it's a paper anniversary or like a gold?
Oh, sure, sure.
What's the 18th?
Well, what's that one?
Ink?
I don't know.
Papyrus, actually.
There's some weird ones in that list.
Papyrus spatula year.
I mean, I could look, I could check.
I don't care.
I don't think it's important.
No, we don't have the time to waste.
More importantly, Alex has undoubtedly got a claim.
He could take Joe Rogan to small claims court for stealing the intro of his show being,
this is a powerful transmission.
You know, I think they've gotten a lot from each other out of this situation.
I don't think Alex can be mad at Joe for what he's contributed in response for getting powerful.
But what I would like to say is that this furthers Alex's argument that I hate to say
I kind of agree with, that Joe is a sneaky snake.
Joe is a sneaky snake.
That's true.
Yeah.
Powerful sneaky snake.
Maybe that's what Alex said.
Maybe that's what it's always been.
That's why Joe can't get rid of Alex.
Alex has powerful over him.
Could be.
He's got too many skeletons in the closet.
This might be-
We've blown the whole thing open.
This was not what I was looking to discover, but I think we might've figured it out.
We got it.
Yeah.
We did it.
The corruption is-
The corruption.
It's the word powerful.
It's blackmail.
This is why there's an intellectual dark web.
The whole thing goes back to Joe stealing the word powerful.
I knew it would happen.
Oh, well.
Now that we've solved that, let's get into something a little more meaty.
Okay.
I now admit that the Private Lynch thing really wasn't a rescue.
It was totally staged.
The Iraqis had been gone for two days.
The doctors had walked down the road and told them days before to come get her.
The special forces hours before the raid had been across the street.
They knew the area was deserted.
Turns out it was theater, Hollywood.
So for the last few days here in 2003, Alex has been touching on this story of the alleged
rescue of Private Lynch, and I've been waiting for him to dig into it with some real depth
so I can get a better sense of his exact position, but it doesn't seem like there's much here
past what he said in that clip.
His position is that the rescue is all just Hollywood theatrics and nothing more.
The story of Private Lynch is actually a fantastic example of the precise problem with what Alex
Jones does for a living and how easy it is to get seduced into his way of thinking.
For some background, on March 23, 2003, Lynch's convoy was ambushed outside Nasirah in Iraq
and she was taken hostage.
Eleven of the other members of her group were killed in the ambush and Lynch was taken to
nearby Saddam Hospital.
There she was treated and on the evening of April 1st, she was rescued by US forces.
From this point forward, the story is one of complete malpractice by the media where
sensationalism led coverage of the story.
Unnamed sources claimed that she'd been shot or stabbed, but conflicting reports came out
from her doctors who said that she had no such wounds.
Even as media outlets ran with a sensationalized version of the story, other outlets were digging
in to sort out what was and was not the truth.
By April 15th, outlets like the Washington Post were beginning to critically examine
their own initial coverage and question whether their account was accurate.
Washington Post headline, whoops, really should have done a better job on that one, our bad.
More or less, yeah, it's interesting.
And gradually, things fell apart and the truth of the matter came forward.
When Lynch was taken to Saddam Hospital, she was given appropriate medical treatment and
when US forces arrived to rescue her, there weren't any Iraqi forces there and much of
the characterization of her as a Rambo-type was based on overdramatization and misstatements.
Now, it's absolutely true that much of the media completely fucked this story up and
they may have had forces that were pretty excited that they were fucking it up.
The war in Iraq at that point was not full of good news like the Bush administration
would have wanted it to be and the idea that they would try to take this story and use
it for their purposes definitely seems like what they did.
If you read the House report that investigated the flow of information about the rescue titled
House Report 110-858, you can definitely see instances of members of the Department of
Defense giving inaccurate information about the rescue, which fed into the heroic drama
that was being sold by the media.
Are you telling me that war-mongering politicians and their, oh, okay, you're doing this wild.
I'm not telling you that entirely.
I'm not saying that definitively.
Sure.
And I think that's important.
Yes.
Well, there's one instance.
On April 2nd, Brigadier General Vincent Brooks, a spokesperson for CENTCOM, told a press briefing,
quote, there was not a firefight outside the building, I will tell you, but there were
firefights outside of the building getting in and getting out.
That was not true, unless you take a very broad view of what getting in and getting
out means.
Well, we started the war a couple of months ago, so there were firefights for us to get
there, and then whenever she left, the war was still going on, so there were firefights
when we were leaving.
See?
On April 3rd, Navy Captain Frank Thorpe was quoted in the Military Times as saying that
Lynch, quote, waged quite a battle prior to her capture.
We do have very strong indications that Jessica Lynch was not captured very easily.
Reports are that she fired her M-16 rifle until she had no more ammunition.
None of that information is accurate, but it feeds into the creation of a story out
of the movies for the public to enjoy.
Yeah, like what they did with Lynch.
Pat Tillman?
Yeah.
Tillman, that's right.
Yeah, that was another thing that was in that House investigation, the flow of misinformation
surrounding that circumstance.
Now, the thing is, those people and their statements, the Brigadier General Brooks and
Navy Captain Thorpe, are not necessarily the people who gave the statements unnamed to
the Washington Post.
Sure, true.
It's not like these people's statements, as inaccurate as they may be, are what fueled
directly the media sensationalism.
And it would be impossible to prove this definitively, but you'd also have to be kind of naive to
think that it's impossible that someone within the Department of Defense wouldn't have seen
the potential to spin this story for some much needed good press for the war.
You could have that suspicion, and you could point fingers at the media for bungling the
story, but if you do that, you have to be careful about where you're pointing.
If you damn the media for their mishandling this story, you also have to credit the media
for doubling back and questioning their own coverage when new information came to light.
This doesn't necessarily excuse the sensationalism that characterized the initial coverage, but
without actual journalists continuing to pursue the story, even if it meant embarrassing themselves,
this thread would have been much harder to untangle.
Second, if you believe that the DoD was definitely trying to pull propaganda games here and pushing
a false story, you have to ask how good they are at that.
This was a relatively easy propaganda story to pull off, and it fell apart in a matter
of weeks.
If you believe that this was all government spin, then I would suggest that this story
serves as a terrible argument that the government's always lying to us, and in fact it kind of
more firmly sports the idea that when the government tries to lie on a scale like this,
it doesn't work.
I mean, you know, at the time they had just lied their way into a war, so I bet they weren't
really caring too much about whether or not everybody caught them lying.
I mean, and then as far as the competence with which they do things go, they had just
incompetently lied their way into a war that they were fighting incompetently that were
still fighting incompetently, so it would make sense to me that the government, as it was
at the time, would very much try and push the story so incompetently that it would backfire
on them.
Interesting.
Yeah.
So I think the most important thing about this, and the most important aspect to really
delve into, is where one thinks the conspiracy exists.
I don't fault people for thinking that the Bush administration would have a vested interest
in the sensational version of the story being reported, and that possibly unnamed US officials
fed the flames of the story to the media, so you can suspect, you know, that they maybe
wanted the media to get this wrong in this way.
That's a different thing than the narrative that Alex is selling.
The story that Alex is telling is that the entire rescue operation itself was a contrived
theatrical affair, which is completely unsupported by the facts.
The DOD Office of the Inspector General conducted an investigation due to the insistence of
Rahm Emanuel, of all people, into the allegations that the rescue was, quote, premeditated fabrication.
From the report, quote, based on the results of the preliminary inquiry conducted by the
Inspector General, United States Central Command, we concluded that the allegations were not
substantiated and that no further investigation was warranted.
During the inquiry, the Inspector General, US CENTCOM, reviewed numerous classified operational
documents that were not available to the media, and interviewed over 30 witnesses, many of
whom had firsthand knowledge of the events at issue.
In addition to this, Vernon Loeb, one of the writers of the first Washington Post story,
the actual first one that shed off the sensationalized coverage, he was interviewed on NPR's Fresh
Air in December 2003.
In that interview, he clarifies that the information he was getting that the story was based on
was wrong, but it ultimately traced back to bad intelligence from the field.
Inaccurate information was conveyed, collected from intercepts and misrepresented and misinterpreted
details, and then that story was reported.
Which kind of puts a little bit of a hole in the theory that is all an elaborate hoax.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's more mishandling, and if you want to get a conspiracy about like, hey, it works
in certain people's best interests that there was this mishandling.
That's not crazy.
Yeah, no, I mean, it seems almost impossible to think of it as anything other than opportunistic
idiots bungling a martyr story, you know, or a war hero story.
And I think if you want to keep it in that sort of territory, you're on more, like, not
totally unreasonable ground.
Yeah, that seems reasonable.
I'm doing it the way Alex is doing it, and this idea that it's like, ah, they had premeditated
intentions of creating this fake rescue in order to trick people into supporting the
war or whatever.
That is where it's like, okay, this is a conclusion that is unearned, unsubstantiated, you can't
back this up, and it's nonsense.
And this is the point that I'm trying to make.
When you have this suspicion and this like, I don't know, I don't trust these people pushing
a fucking war, and this story, it was mishandled on some level.
Inaccurate statements were made, whether it was because of bad information being conveyed
to the people making the statements or some kind of a, eh, mishandling, who knows.
That suspicion is not that bizarre.
It's not unnatural to have that healthy distrust, but that healthy distrust gets transmuted
by someone like Alex into confident assertions of a conclusion that isn't based in reality.
And that's where the danger is, even with this 2003 Alex that's a far different Alex
than the present in terms of some of his methodologies.
That is true.
I mean, but it's just so easy, it's just so easy, especially at the time, because they
literally lied us into a war that's never going to end.
Like that's a conspiracy on the level of something that is so huge.
I mean, an actual war, an invasion of another country, and it was a conspiracy, and it was
a lie that it's hard to imagine anything's beyond those people, you know?
Like why would, do you really think it's beyond the people who lied us into a forever war
to fabricate one small thing?
You know, like that seems like a reasonable overreaction at the time.
If that makes sense.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Right.
But what you're describing is essentially Alex Jones's sort of indoctrination process.
Exactly.
Yeah.
I mean, yes, it is compelling and it certainly could be persuasive to say, they did X, why
wouldn't they do something else?
And that's fine.
But then, all right, any argument is gone.
Why wouldn't they do, you could just use that to justify 100 conspiracies that you want
to believe in.
Oh, totally.
Totally.
And it's just, it doesn't work.
Yeah.
No, I don't think there's any way-
If you prove that someone is morally capable of an act, it doesn't prove that they did
it.
Right.
Right, right, right, right.
No, totally.
I absolutely agree.
But that hijack is what Alex uses.
Right.
If they are morally capable of this, then they must have done it.
Right, right, right.
And that's just not reality.
Yeah.
It's hard not to think that history is going to look at the Bush administration as infinitely
worse than anything Trump ever did.
It's hard to think that history won't look at Bush as one of the single worst genociders
there's ever been.
Feels like Trump has some time left, though.
That's true.
He can still catch up.
So Alex has some interesting predictions that he makes in this episode that seem very
reminiscent of the present day.
The New World Order is here.
It's in our face.
It's with us right now.
And they're preparing a national draft.
Even if you don't serve overseas, you'll serve here in- Yes, we've looked at the programs.
Paddle tail squads, anti-gun programs, environmental cult groups locally, literally what they are.
Under George W. Bush, who's the testular head of things right now, they put a Republican
in for this final destruction of America so conservatives would hesitate just long enough
so they could get the job done.
So we've been in the New World Order for 20 years now.
Yeah, yeah.
No, it just occurred to me that when he says all of these things and then they don't happen
and he's like, see, we stopped it, like, yeah, but now you've been foiling the same plot
for 20 years.
Yeah.
This is like, we're reading Batman serialized comics.
Bush was going to put in the draft and that was going to have tattle tail squads and then
Obama was going to have a draft and it was going to have the Obama youth or whatever.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then, you know, and he puts the Joker back in Arkham Asylum and then a week later
Joker breaks out with the same plan again and he foils it again.
And there's a whole lot of immediacy every time.
Every single time.
The only difference I would say is that within the world of DC Comics, the Batman and Joker
do exist.
Yeah, that is true.
That is true.
It would be like if Batman was making up Joker schemes in order to foil them over and over
again.
Oh shit.
And did not possess the creativity to come up with new plans.
I think you have got a new take on the Batman character.
It's a rich psychopath who is inventing super villains in order to play out this massive
fantasy that he has of being a superhero.
Oh my god, that sounds real!
I know a guy who could write that for you.
Yeah.
So at this point in 2003 there were some beginnings of democratic processes being attempted within
Iraq.
Mm-hmm.
And Alex has some interesting takes on that.
They've been on the news and they're saying to everyone that, oh look, this will make
the detractors shut up.
They said it might be five years before there were elections in Iraq.
And look, already in Mosul, an election.
Well I went and actually read our own government's release of what they've done in Mosul.
They have, our government has chosen 200 people, former assets, still current assets, CIA,
current leaders, communists, others.
And just like they chose Saddam to be the dictator of Iraq back in the 70s, been their
hit man since 58.
Well now they're just choosing 200 strongmen and they quote, will elect, they will appoint
the governor of that northern district and the gubernatorial seat will be Mosul.
So I was able to find articles and outlets like the New York Times and LA Times about
the Mosul election from early May 2003 and the tone that they have is a lot more restrained
than Alex is presenting it.
The New York Times article starts like this, quote, Iraq took its first faltering step
toward democracy today when a large ethnically diverse group of local leaders held an election
to choose an interim government in this northern city, Iraq's third largest.
The reporting recognizes that this is a first step in a process, not necessarily the end
result itself, whereas I feel like Alex is trying to pretend that the media is saying
that this is a job that's finished.
The election that was held wasn't just agents selected by the CIA or whatever the fuck Alex
is saying, it was a group of 240 tribal leaders and local residents from nine ethnic groups
that make up the population of the area.
These 240 selected a group of 24 council members who then went on to choose a mayor.
I'm not going to pretend that I know whether or not this was the best way to handle a preliminary
election for an interim government, but my point is that from everything I can tell,
Alex is misrepresenting what's going on.
It's great to be opposed to the war because you should be, but your opposition should
be based in reality and I don't feel like there's a lot of dealing with the war as it
exists on his part.
Yeah, yeah.
It seems like if you don't deal with such a massive thing going on and instead create
toxic conspiracy theories about it that push people towards the far right, I bet that's
going to have repercussions later on.
Yeah, I don't think it was the right way to express opposition.
Yeah, I think later on we're really going to find out that the results of those things
combining are really going to be bad for us.
I think my parents' friends who were hippies might have had a better handle on things.
Yeah.
So, you know, on our last episode about 2003, I think, maybe it was two back, Alex discussed
how he was going to go to Missouri to do a radio event.
Sure, sure, yes.
Car dealership opening.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
And this is so foreign from Alex's present-day mentality because I kind of believe he's telling
the truth here.
Okay.
So the whole proceeds, 15 bucks, go to KCXL, they wanted to give me some of the money,
but I said, you know, I'm not like the Patriots for profit, I'll come up and sell my videos,
that's fine, but you just keep the money.
You've had us on for three years telling the truth, so I'll come and speak at your event
and this will certainly help you guys expand your operation and increase your power and
everything else.
So they're great folks.
I hope a lot of you come.
I hear thousands are planning.
I kind of believe that he probably would turn down money to do a radio event back then.
Yeah.
It doesn't feel insincere.
I don't like it.
I don't like it, Dan, but I do buy it.
I think I believe him here.
I don't know, though, I don't know the tone of his lies in 2003, Dan.
I also think that there's a possibility that he has a reason to believe that he could make
more money selling DVDs than he could for whatever his appearance rate would be.
Yeah, I imagine they didn't give him.
It's still a calculation, maybe.
Maybe the appearance fee was lowball enough that your pride would be better off denying
it than taking it.
That could be.
But yeah, apparently he was willing to go for free to a radio event in Missouri back
in 2003.
Yeah!
Yeah, that's intense.
So at this point, Alex not only going to radio events for free, he is also doing the work.
He's doing a lot of work.
Another side note, I am running on three hour sleep and I've done this about four days straight.
I do this a couple times a year.
Well more than that.
Maybe that's why I look more like Jabba the Hutt instead of James Bond like he used to
look.
But the point is, the point is, I have completed a new film.
It is done.
It is being mass produced as we speak.
So on the website we say that it ships in one week and that's accurate if you want your
order sent out first, you'll definitely want to go to Infowars.com or Infowars.net or PrisonPlanet.com
and click on the shopping cart to order Police State 3 Total Enslavement.
So I have decided that it's been too long since we've done a documentary and as we're
back in 2003, Alex just released this documentary.
I feel like it's perfect timing.
We've got to cover Police State 3.
We're going to cover Police State 3?
I think we might.
Oh shit.
Yeah.
Oh boy.
I got this, you know, this energy.
Was that the one whenever Bobcat, his star was really starting to wane down after three?
Was that the one?
That was Mission to Moscow.
Okay, that was five.
Was he still at five?
I don't know.
Oh, Bobcat.
Matt Bobcat.
Nicest guy in the world.
I'm sure.
Love him.
Yeah.
So Alex has got this new film.
Very exciting.
Yeah.
Good for you.
Police State 3.
Can't wait to watch that bullshit.
Oh boy.
So that may be coming soon.
Also, Jordan.
I don't know.
I don't know what's so egregious to me.
The idea of going online and putting a dramatic documentary title such as Police State 3 into
your order cart and you're just staring at Police State 3 clicking buy.
You got to feel like shit if you're not buying Police State 2 and 1 also.
There might be important information on those.
Yeah.
Is it serialized?
Are we going to miss out?
I don't know, but if we do cover it, I'm not doing the other ones.
No, you're going to have to watch them for background.
I don't know if I'm going to.
So at this point, Jordan, we know in the future, present day.
Who are Alex's enemies?
Oh boy.
The list is ongoing, but mainly S.T.E.L.T.E.R.
No, not individuals.
How would you describe them?
Oh, literal demons.
Minions of the devil.
Yes.
Interestingly, here is who the new world order is in 2003.
Okay.
I have poured my life's blood into these films.
My burning the candle at both ends in the defense of the Republic.
If this was the Alamo, they're coming over the wall in the defense of the Republic.
And we're defending against the new world order, the European bankers that own our government,
and we must educate people if we're ever going to have liberty.
So it's European bankers is the new world order.
It's not so much the devil, the literal Christian devil.
Yeah.
I mean, it's nice that we haven't seen the enemy at our gates yet, so to speak.
I think it's interesting how there's this fast and looseness.
Yeah.
What do you actually think?
I don't know.
I don't either.
That's what's so interesting about this, because we know in the future he will be fighting
the devil.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And there's some slight indications that we've seen from 2003 that he seems to think there's
something going on.
Right, right, right, right.
But then, when he's talking about the new world order, he talks about it in terms of
international European bankers, which is exactly the sort of presentation that he wants people
to have at this point.
This is about the Federal Reserve.
This is about fiat currency.
I don't know.
I want to know if he actually thinks it's the devil back then.
I kind of think that... Here's what I think it is, all right?
Here's what I'm going to go with.
I'm going to go with its necessary escalation is what happened.
Like Iron Man came out around 2003.
It's just one dude fighting against his director, or whatever it is he's doing.
Real low stakes.
By the end of it, we've got to restart the universe.
He starts out.
He's like, oh, European bankers are out.
And then 20 years later, we're fighting the literal devil.
It makes sense.
Yeah, but look, dude, Iron Man-
If he's doing Batman, he's essentially doing the entire Marvel universe as we go along.
In Iron Man, Robert Downey Jr. wasn't pretending that he wasn't fighting Thanos, right?
He didn't know he was fighting Thanos.
But Alex seems to have some awareness of the devil.
Well, there is that.
There is that.
But Thanos didn't hatch his plan for another 10 years, or whatever.
It's a line of awareness that I'm interested in.
I can't quite get my finger on it yet.
So Alex goes to calls, and he takes a caller who wants to talk about Dennis Miller.
Sure, great.
Mark in Minnesota, you're on the air.
Go ahead.
Hey, Alex.
How you doing, sir?
Oh, pretty good.
I seldom watch TV, but I just happened to be watching The Tonight Show last night.
And Dennis Miller was on there.
And I always seem to-
Yeah, so-called, ultra-socialist, anti-gun.
Real quick, ultra-socialist Dennis Miller.
But one fun thing to point out is this is 2003, because Dennis Miller was on The Tonight
Show.
Now, worshipping Bush, pro-war, anti-freedom.
Of course, this is a liberal sneak attack.
I mean, he's like just- I mean, nothing but praise and accolades for Bush.
I mean, Sig Hill, George Bush.
Let me tell you something, I have him on tape literally engaging in a 10-minute worship
session.
Yes, you saw that then.
Well, no, I saw him months ago.
It's wall to wall, sir.
Fair enough.
Yeah, I mean, hey, yeah, good.
Dennis Miller sucks.
Was this back when he was on Monday Night Football?
Oh, man.
Jesus.
No, I think that might have been a few years earlier.
Oh, okay.
But like this, yeah, this is- sure, yeah, Dennis Miller sucks.
And he was a guy who promoted the Iraq war in a shameless way.
Yeah, he went crazy.
But I think time has shown us that he stayed on that pretty conservative path and was pretty
in favor of Trump.
Yeah, he's a real piece of shit.
He followed a lot of the similar path that Alex walked out.
Yeah, yeah.
And instead, Alex is saying this is a secret socialist ultra-left person trying to pretend
to be conservative in order to Trojan horse George Bush on us.
That explanation, it doesn't make sense in hindsight.
Just a fucking dick who lost his mind.
Yeah, yeah.
Real dick.
It's nice to know that no matter what era we live in, right-wing commentators will still
have very strong opinions about comics who don't matter.
Yeah.
Great.
And it's pretty universal in no one likes Dennis Miller.
Yeah.
Fuck them.
Except Bill O'Reilly.
Fuck them too.
So in this next clip, Alex talks about an interaction that did not happen.
It's not globalists in a hot tub.
It seems to be a Nazi at a gas station, maybe.
Is that a classic joke?
I don't think this happened.
About two weeks ago, I was taking the family out and I was, my wife, my parents were in
the car, we're going out to eat and I run into the store, pay for the gas and I'm standing
there and a guy with iron cross tattoos, everything else is in there, Mr. Trendy, who's not trendy
at all, establishment brainwashed carbon copy cookie cutter creature, and he's buying this
proud to be an American decal at the front counter and he goes, man, I'll tell you, I
love it.
All this oil we're getting.
And I go, oh, oil.
And he's, yeah, it's great.
And I'm like, well, you don't think you're going to get that oil, do you?
I don't care.
We're tough.
And the guy behind the counter started, you know, laughing at him and he goes, Hey, how
you doing Alex?
The guy behind the counter knew who I was.
And I said, look, don't you know, they're killing people over there and you know, this
is a fraud.
They told us it wasn't about oil.
Now they admitted, ah, so what we needed, I said, sir, you're not part of the establishment.
They can't, they're like a poor North Korean who just loves Kim Jong Il, but you can't
help these people.
From at least 2010 onward, all the way to his running for president, Donald Trump was
completely preoccupied with the idea of taking oil from countries where we've been at war.
An editor's note in an article from the Brookings Institute called it quote, the most dangerous
and irresponsible of all the Republican nominees' policy proposals.
And Alex justified it when Trump had the exact same perspective he's shooting down as dumb
back here in 2003.
Yep.
Also, I think it's weird, um, that Alex is saying that being a Nazi is trendy in 2003.
I don't know what kind of company he's swinging with back then, but, um, honestly, for Alex,
that guy was ahead of the times.
Really.
He was, he was out at the forefront of, of pop culture.
He was an early adopter.
Absolutely.
Of the right-wing eventual.
That guy's, that guy's basically the Jack Kerouac of the, of the Beat movement.
You know, he was there early.
That's tough.
Yeah.
I just don't like the idea of like looking at somebody with an Iron Cross tattoo and
be like, fucking trendy.
It's like my, like how I look at my friends who were too into Tiger King, and I'm like,
that's how Alex looks at a guy with a Nazi tattoo.
Absolutely.
Fuck.
Either that or he's just like, oh, look at you.
So many goddamn Nazis with their Iron Cross tattoos everywhere these days.
Johnny come lately.
There used to be bell bottoms and now there's Iron Cross tattoos.
Right.
What's the next fad?
So I think that one of the things that I keep getting a sense of in these 2003 episodes
is a lot of Alex's opposition to George Bush comes down to a complete feeling that Bush
is going to take all of his guns.
And I want to keep mentioning that not only is Bush going to reinstate the Clinton gun
ban and a magazine ban with pleasure, by the way, they are also going to bring forward
our Lady of Peace Act that registers all gun owners, shuts down gun shows.
Well, it's all the stuff in S-22.
Our Lady of Peace is one bill in S-22 and there's the shut down the gun show section,
national ballistics database, I mean, stuff that makes what Bill Clinton did look conservative.
Folks, mayday, we're losing everything here.
S-22, also known as the Justice Enhancement and Domestic Security Act of 2003 was introduced
by Tom Daschle on January 7th, 2003 and he promptly died before even receiving a vote.
Yeah, I was going to say.
Clinton signed the federal assault weapons ban in 1994 and it was set to have a sunset
clause after 10 years.
So it was a ban that only existed until 2004 when it would be reexamined and it expired
in 2004 and Bush did not renew it.
Yeah.
None of the stuff that Alex wants to make these listeners scared of happened, which
is kind of the case always.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Well, it distracts from the stuff that is happening and that's, you know, you don't
want to get in the way of real things.
True.
You could get hurt.
That's why you don't make Shadowgate, Dan.
You don't get in the way of the real stuff.
Oh, yeah.
You stay away from that.
You stay away.
Stay away from the gate of gates.
Alex doesn't get into that deep spy stuff.
And whatever you do, don't talk about Roger.
Oh, yeah, you're gone.
So Alex takes another call and this guy has a perspective of like, you know, we're over
there and we're trying to bring democracy into the Middle East countries and what have
you and I don't see anything happening here.
I don't see anything happening in my life, whatever.
Alex says something really fucked up after that.
He said before, but the fact that he keeps saying it troubles me.
You know, it's funny that you mentioned the thing about people sharing in the power.
I was thinking about that same issue three days ago.
It popped into my head and I said to myself, wait a minute.
How is it benefiting the general population of this country?
In other words, how are we sharing in any of the benefits of what's going on?
I stopped and I looked around.
Gas prices are still about as high as they ever were.
Nothing has changed, at least as it relates to John Q.
Publick.
And we're losing our liberty and freedom.
I mean, if we had some war emperor who was totally reaffirming all our rights, leaving
us alone, really taking out the we're not being really giving up freedom, really trying
to train with them, I'd say, well, this is this is a radical departure from what George
Washington said.
But it's not that bad.
It's not that bad.
He has a very conditional idea about colonialism.
Yeah.
Does not seem to have a principled idea against regime change.
No.
Against nation building.
Yeah.
Which is what he wants people to think he has.
And it's not it's conditional.
It's about whether or not the people who are going and taking over other countries leave
him alone or not.
Right.
No, no.
You'd be totally fine with like King Leopold if he just didn't take away his gun.
One hundred percent.
It's fucked up.
Yeah.
No, he's against regime change, except for in the right conditions.
Just like he's against the Capital Six riot because it wasn't the right time.
It wasn't the right preparation.
Yeah.
That to me is really a real glaring hole.
And like, I can't I can't I mean, I guess a lot of the times people who would be listening
to this maybe back in 2003 or just listening to it on the radio wouldn't be listening to
it as critically necessarily as I'm listening to it now.
But that seems like something that should be a real problem for him and his listeners.
The idea that he would be OK with a war emperor who goes around as long as they reaffirm our
rights the same way that George Washington would have now obviously abolishing the Constitution.
There would be a discussion.
There's like all of his intros are like, you want to end tyranny?
Well, so does he.
It's like this.
You understand that this is exactly the way that, you know, people rationalized a lot
of it.
So you want to end dictatorships?
How about a benevolent one?
Right.
Interesting.
Yeah.
And then now in the present day, I guess recent past when Trump was in power, he wanted to
colonize space.
Yeah.
Take over Greenland.
I don't know.
Man, I heard that shit so much.
Do those people who call in and they're like, what do we get out of this war?
Do they not understand how psychopathic that sounds like?
Hey, what do I look?
I'm sure it's fine if we go, you know, slaughter a bunch of civilians, my bottom line, what
my gas prices are going to stay the same.
Yeah.
Fuck you.
How about that?
Gross.
You fucking psycho.
Also, I was just sitting here thinking about it and it's like, let's imagine like a president
that we were supportive of.
Sure.
Just coming out being like, I think I'm going to buy Greenland.
Just imagine, even if you agree with all of the other policies, imagine going along like,
you know what?
This is a good idea.
I'm telling you.
I can't imagine it.
Here's what should have happened.
Here's what we would have gotten Carter a second term, all right?
The gas crisis is going on and he's like, hey, you know where there's gas?
Me neither, but let's buy Greenland.
I'm going to take big swings, baby.
It's ours.
Yeah.
So Alex has a guest, which is sort of a rarity.
I think this is only the second guest I've seen so far in 2003 and here he comes.
We're joined by an expert on the New World Order.
I've read several of his books and for some reason we haven't hooked up over all these
years, but it's good to have him on.
Dennis Lawrence Cuddy, historian and political analyst, took a PhD from the University of
North Carolina at Chapel Hill, major in American history, minor in political science.
Dr. Cuddy has taught university level.
He's been a political and economic risk analyst for international consulting firm.
There's a few things that really concerned me about this intro that Alex is reading for
Dennis Cuddy.
This is the exact wording that you'll find for him on pretty much all other websites,
but it just doesn't sound right.
When someone has been employed as an actual professor, their bio probably wouldn't say
that they've, quote, taught at the university level.
It would almost always specify the school where they were a professor.
Professor of blank at the University of blank.
Honestly, I've given a few lectures at colleges, so I guess I could technically claim that
I've taught at the university level, but it doesn't mean anything.
Oh shit, Dan.
You can get on Info Wars.
The second issue that I have with his bio is that he specifies a major and a minor in
terms of his PhD, which is a little bit bizarre.
Typically that's the language that people use to discuss their undergraduate education.
Whereas if you reach the graduate level in a doctoral program, you'd be unlikely to have
a minor.
You'd probably discuss your area of emphasis as a way of discussing, you know, your credentials.
This just seems really, really weird.
It sounds like what you would describe if you didn't get a PhD.
Well, I was worried about that because it does seem like that.
Yeah, or if you purchased one from somewhere outside of the United States, perhaps.
Well, I was concerned, but I was able to find his dissertation, which was published in a
1978 issue of the Journal of American History titled, quote, American Immigration to Australia
1945 to the Present.
So it does appear that he did complete a PhD program, but I'm not sure what this area of
study has to do with qualifying him to be an expert in the New World Order.
If you check out his bibliography, it's shockingly all weird books about the New World Order
and not so many books about Australian immigration.
That sounds about right.
Anyway, Dennis Cuddy is still active as a conspiracy weirdo to this day, and it appears
that he's been pretty pro-Trump, which raises an interesting question about why he's not
still a figure on Alex's show.
I thought maybe they didn't hit it off, but they get along pretty well.
Interesting.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know what happened, but he's not a name that I recognize from any of the present
day sections that we've covered.
Maybe he just got out of the game.
No, he's still in the game.
Maybe he got out of Alex's game.
Maybe he got out of the heat, yeah.
Maybe he's just like, Alex is an asshole.
That's probably the case.
Anyway, this guy's got an interesting strategy to convince people.
I know you can't discriminate.
If you're a university Ph.D. program, you can't discriminate based on religious beliefs
or ideology, but could you be sneakily like, hey, what if you wanted to go on Infowars?
Would you go on Infowars?
And if the answer is yes, they're like, ha, caught you, no Ph.D.
To be fair, it was 76 when he got his Ph.D. and Infowars did not exist at that point.
Alex was two years old.
Look, you can't litigate ex post facto.
I've heard that from somewhere.
So look, we want to give you this degree, but there's a two-year-old over in Dallas
and he's going to do something real weird.
Look, if the devil has been aware of Alex Jones from the beginning.
So I don't know.
Anyway, Dennis has got this interesting trick that he uses because he wants to cut through
the bullshit.
Oh boy.
Like, if people don't agree with him, here's how he cuts through the bullshit.
This is sneaky.
Let's hear it.
How do we stop the New World Order?
How do we educate the left and the right that they're really just part of a phony system?
Well, the first thing, you have to crack through their predisposition to think you're a nut
if you talk about conspiracy theories.
And the best way to do that is, the way I do it is I set them up by saying, suppose
I told you there was a power somewhere so complete, so pervasive, so interlocked, so
watchful, you better not speak above your breath if you speak in condemnation of it.
After they get finished laughing in my face for a while, I say, well, I didn't say that
one of your heroes, Woodrow Wilson, said that.
Now you've got the retention.
First of all, I can't imagine how little I'd care about having a Woodrow Wilson quote
snuck up on me.
Oh no, my hero, Woodrow Wilson.
Yeah, I think I would be like, boo!
So secondly, and more importantly, what this guy's doing is misusing a quote from Wilson's
Platform 1913.
The full quote he's going from is, quote, since I entered politics, I've chiefly had
men's views confided to me privately.
Some of the biggest men in the United States, in the field of commerce and manufacture,
are afraid of somebody, are afraid of something.
They know that there's a power somewhere so organized, so subtle, so watchful, so interlocked,
so complete, so pervasive, that they had better not speak above their breath when they speak
in condemnation of it.
If you continue reading, it's super clear that what Wilson's talking about isn't a spooky
cabal of globalists, but the completely unregulated nature of industry and how people who have
already amassed a certain amount of power can use that to stomp out people who are just
getting started.
From a little later in the text, quote, and this is the country which has lifted to the
admiration of the world its ideals of absolutely free opportunity, where no man is supposed
to be under any limitation except the limitations of his character and his mind, where there's
supposed to be no distinction of class, no distinction of blood, no distinction of social
status, but where men win or lose by their merits.
I lay it very close to my own conscience as a public man, whether we can any longer stand
at our doors and welcome any newcomers upon these terms.
American industry is not free, as once it was free.
American enterprise is not free.
The man with only a little capital is finding it harder to get into the field, more and
more impossible to compete with the big fellow.
Why?
Because the laws of this country did not prevent the strong from crushing the weak.
Antitrust issues were a really big topic of politics in the 1910s, and that's why it was
a plank in Wilson's agenda.
He was clearly in favor of taking power away from monopolies and giving a better chance
to smaller, up-and-coming businesses, and that's what this passage from his platform
is all about.
If you just take a look at the section that Cuddy is reading out of context, it could
sound like they were saying there was a group of villains running the world or whatever,
but if you take it within its proper context, you read something very different.
He's just in favor of regulation.
I...
Oh, boy.
You know, a guy who says that, who also made the black servants in the White House hide
it whenever he walked by because he didn't want to see them.
Not cool.
Maybe if you say that and do that, like, you gotta go back in time and kill this guy.
Look, I'm not here to litigate Woodrow Wilson's career.
I'm taking the text.
No, no, no, totally.
I just can't hear it in my head and know that at the same time without losing my mind.
I understand it.
That's why you're here, because that reaction is difficult to have.
Yeah, it's very difficult.
But the reason I'm here is to explain why this person is misusing a quote.
I understand.
We're a great team.
Yes.
And I don't know if I can accept that he doesn't understand that context.
I find that difficult to believe.
The Cuddy.
Yes.
Yeah.
I find it difficult to believe that he would be able to read that quote, read further in
the text, and not understand what this is about.
Now, it's possible, and it's also possible that the depth of his research doesn't include
the other paragraphs after this.
Sure.
I've seen this in some other text, in the same way that everybody in the right wing
has not read Tragedy and Hope, they've only read stuff from like Skousen talking about
Tragedy and Hope.
Right, right, right, right.
So it's possible that he has this second hand, this quote, and it sounds really good, and
it's a way to freak normies out.
Hey, check this out.
But I don't know, I find it to be a problem for me to take him seriously.
Anyway, they're talking, Alex and Cuddy, and one of the things I like is he's Dr. Cuddy,
and that's Lisa Edelstein's character on House.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
All right.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
She's great.
All right.
Okay.
So they're talking, and they get to a conversation about Bohemian Grove, and Alex has some more
details about how unheroic his breaking in was.
Okay.
Let me bring this forward.
Are you aware that I snuck into Bohemian Grove?
Yes, sir, I've seen the video, very good.
Well, I mean, I frankly couldn't believe it.
I saw the news articles, the British media got me a map in, some of the code words from
the spies inside, and I frankly believe I was actually allowed to sneak in there now
that I look at it as part of a larger throw-it-in-our-face move.
Oh.
Okay.
That certainly fits with, you know, like Ronson saying you were just allowed to walk in.
Yeah.
Huh.
The story seems a little more dashing when he tells it now.
Yeah.
It's a little more humble back at this point.
Interesting.
Yep.
Let me bring this mic down for this clip, because this pissed me off.
So Alex is talking about Bohemian Grove, and he wants to bring up the satanic element of
this.
Sure.
Right?
You want to talk about their Satanists, and I'm like, hey, this is one of the big things
I'm interested in 2003.
Are you fighting the devil?
Of course.
We got to know.
This pissed me off.
How does the satanic element behind all this operate, you know, talk about the Illuminati,
the history of this.
Who are we really dealing with?
Well, first, did you see any people running around naked there?
It goes on for 15 days.
I was there at the kickoff.
David Gergen in the Washington Times said that they do indeed do that.
Yeah.
Spy Magazine admits that they ship in the male prostitutes.
I didn't see that.
I saw some weird behavior.
I didn't show any, you know, I'm not going to go up and show old men and bank chairman
with their.
Well, I'm not going to.
I saw some things.
I saw mainly a strange urination ritual where two men walk up, pull their pants partially
down and and then start urinating in front of each other.
I didn't put that in the video.
I'm guessing they were just drunk and they like peed on a bush.
Yeah, that sounds more weird urination ritual.
Ah, interesting.
You know, I've come out of many a Cubs game before and thought, I got to get this weird
urination ritual done real quick.
Yeah, I've been to bonfire parties.
They were just full of weird urination rituals.
Hey guys, real quick, I'm going to take a walk over here and do my urination ritual
real quick.
Yeah, that's weird.
But the thing that, the reason I'm pissed off by this is they don't get back to the
initial question.
Hey, they just get sidetracked by talking about peeing.
It's like, God damn it.
I wanted to know about the satanic element.
That's why I'm, that's why I'm listening.
It doesn't seem like it's that big of a deal if you're just going to get distracted with
urination rituals.
It's certainly not important enough to come back to immediately.
So, um, this guy, Cuddy, um, prediction, uh, guy, he's a guy who knows things, he's read
these documents and uh, boy, this, this, this, uh, take did not age well.
The uh, the current situation with Iraq, what I tried to do there was say, uh, okay, if
this power lead is in control of things and if there is a war, uh, military conflict in
Iraq, what will happen?
And I said, there's two possibilities.
I said, if it's a staged war, it'll be over relatively soon, uh, with relatively few casualties,
even from chemical or biological weapons.
And that's basically what happened.
So it's a staged war because it's over quick.
You know, that's really comforting to know because I was worried that it was going to
blow up into a thing that destabilizes the entire world.
Yeah.
This is bad thinking.
So his other possibility is thinking is what it is.
His other possibility is that it's a real war and, but everything that's happened would
have happened differently if it was a real, it's like, this is just terrible.
Wow.
Yeah.
So that didn't like, it doesn't age well.
Those who learn the past about Australian immigration are doomed to repeat the extra
other past.
Yup.
Yeah.
So, uh, one of Alex's big, uh, reasons to believe that 9-11 was an inside job, uh, is
that they were running a drill.
Sure.
Yeah.
Drills are very important to inside jobs.
Yes.
Man.
This, this made me laugh really hard because Cuddy accidentally punctures a giant hole
on that theory by trying to help Alex out.
No one's asked any of these questions, have they?
No one's asked why the AP reported that the CIA was doing a drill that morning of flying
jets in the buildings in New York and DC quote their cover for why NORAD stood down.
Uh, yeah, and that, uh, the same outfit, uh, had a similar drill the year before and nobody
picked up on that either, but they had the drill that morning at that very time.
That pause, that pause is great.
That pause is staring daggers.
That is a man who just got sliced to shreds with a glance.
It's so important for the, uh, the theories surrounding the drills that they're not B
drills regularly or similar drills that have happened in the past.
And they do it every year and nobody picked up on it, Dan.
Ugh.
Oh, so bright and cheery, he's like, I'm so helpful.
I love moments like that because I do think that as much as, you know, there's still a
bunch of dumdums back then, there are people who are less on the same identical script.
Like when you listen to these present day episodes, it'll be like Alex interviewing
his fucking lawyers who are doing yes and games with him.
It's basically just not only that, but Alex, everyone kind of knows to not like puncture
anything or not to say anything that could be like, well, that's a reason why this doesn't
make sense.
And in this moment, that guy has just thought, thought that added to the conspiracy and in
fact it actually blows it two shreds.
Makes it look bad.
He was like a retriever bringing you the paper after stepping in a pile of shit, walking
through your door.
And he's like, I'm so good.
See, I brought you the paper and you're like, you, oh shit.
So earlier Jordan, we learned that Dennis Miller is a big time socialist, huge socialist.
But now it is time to play the game show that is taking the country by storm.
Who is an ultra commie?
Every episode.
I mean, at this point it's almost like Dennis Hastert.
I don't know.
It could be anybody.
Every episode so far in 2003, I think we've had Alex out somebody.
There's a new ultra commie.
That's true.
So who's it going to be this time?
They're dropping like flies.
You think it's Hastert?
No, I'm going to go with Condoleezza Rice.
Interesting.
Uh, you were starting out a little earlier with a, uh, development, a discussion on,
um, Mr. Crystal.
I don't know if you quite got to it.
I'd like to hear the rest of what you were going to tell us about Mr. Crystal.
Ultra commie.
Don't tell me.
It's Billy Crystal.
Ultra commie.
All right.
So yeah, we've got, uh, Michael Savage, Bill Crystal.
That is what happens.
That is what happens when you don't find Curly's gold.
All right.
You become an ultra commie because it's clear that the ruling class has taken the gold before
you got there.
Wrong.
That's the rule.
So earlier, um, we got distracted by, uh, urination rituals when Alex was about to talk
about the satanic element.
Sure.
This is like a prank on me.
I swear to God.
If they can be industrialized as snow factories, people are going to accept being prison guards
as their job.
They're going to accept being tattletale squads.
They're going to accept this.
They say America is going to be a police state enslavement grid that produces propaganda
for the world.
They said that's what America will be.
The armpit of Satan literally, uh, am I on, Oh my God.
Okay.
Uh, Alex's mic went off in the middle of him saying Satan literally.
I know it is, it is a little bit of a tease.
It's like, this isn't admissible.
He could have said anything.
He could have said anything, but you're like, he was going to say literally, literally.
And you know what that means.
I can't make this up.
I'm going back into the past.
I've been intrigued to see if he thinks that Satan is literal back then.
His mic goes off in the middle of saying the word literal.
Oh dude, you're a witch.
It is.
You're a witch.
It's becoming troubling to me.
The level of these coincidences.
It is dangerous.
Yeah.
But it is also pretty funny that his mic just went off and his guest is like, what?
What's going on?
The only word that we needed to hear is the one word.
And I needed him to expound on it more.
You know?
And then Mike's off.
There we go.
Anyway, this is a catastrophic problem that he's having.
And economics and your job, and you're willing to have lower wages becomes more important
to you than the old fashioned patriotism.
Thank you for joining us.
Thanks for joining us, Dr. Cutty.
We'll be right back, folks.
Thank you.
Stay with us.
Who boy.
Oh man.
Something's bad.
Yeah, that's not good.
Yeah.
It is.
I mean, this does screw up my conspiracy theory to know that this kind of thing happens every
year.
That does, it does bother.
It makes me worry.
I don't know.
I can't imagine.
I just have to assume that it's like, well, it's 2003, he had bad tech back then.
Yeah.
But he kind of understands that he has bad tech back then.
He doesn't expect anything else.
Sure.
So like one of the things that I think is pretty cool about 2003 is like, that's a big
problem.
Yeah.
You're on the radio, your mics just go completely out, your guest is left to try and tread water
on his own, and then you got to go out to break.
Yeah.
And Alex deals with it gracefully.
I'm down here in Austin, Texas, and we're hooked up with the folks at Genesis, and rarely
does my little stereo line cut out to them right there at the end.
It was cutting basically bring us out of break and I barely got back on in time to take us
out of that little segment there, but good job getting me hooked back up.
A lot of weird electronic stuff on my end.
We got a lot of callers and I want to go to your calls.
There's no like the globalists are trying to take us off air because we're too dangerous.
There's no freaking out and leaving.
He's laughing.
You know, it's like, I got a tech problem.
Yeah.
I'm not a normal person responding to difficulties that would be expected.
That's true.
That is true.
Now, admittedly, I will say that there is, that would give me certain justification for
a larger reaction if, uh, say I'm having the same problems after spending $60 billion on
a studio.
You know, like if you're still having those problems, you should be angrier than if you
have shitty tech.
Yeah.
No, I mean, it does make sense because then you really can't blame it at all on the tech.
No, but it is on you.
It is definitely on you because you have not solved the problem for sure.
That outbursts that we see in the present day.
It still is.
It should be directed inwards as opposed to screaming at the staff and the, uh, the, uh,
the audience.
Yes, definitely.
I just like, I just prefer to see this like, cause it's, it's not like a child lashing
out, uh, uh, constantly.
It's like, you have a huge problem that happens on your show and you're able to laugh and
come back from break.
Sure.
Like, ah, good on him being able to take us out to break and handle it, you know, Hey,
you know, sometimes Genesis feed goes down.
What are you going to do?
Sure.
Let's go to the call.
Yeah.
I mean, everybody likes the VH1 part of behind the music where there are the, they're on
their meteoric rise, but they're just beginning and they're playing their show at the dumb
bar down the street and little did everybody know what he was going to do.
So, uh, yeah, this is fun to see.
So Alex gets to talk in a more about, uh, the democratization in Iraq and the government
that is coming in.
It's going to be a good one.
Well, we know from history that, uh, again, very shortly after this episode, uh, de-bathification
happened.
It was a good idea.
Iraq, US reconstructing bath units, the most vicious bath CIA torturers, those trained
in the U S all of Saddam's top henchmen, except for a few titular head, uh, go sacrificial
lambs, uh, are going to be put back in control.
So wrong.
He's wrong.
Wrong about that.
Oh boy.
Quite wrong.
Yeah.
So, um, it's, it's just interesting that he's, he's consistently going down this road and
it does set up an like a weird, I don't know what's going to happen as you know, like May
comes to an end.
May continues.
Like, how's he going to navigate that territory?
It is ironic even that it is almost his exact opinion of the bath that was echoed in American
policy while he's criticizing them in the idea that they would do the opposite of what
they believe.
Yeah.
It is strange because the way he's presenting things, he doesn't really have a good leg
to stand on to be opposed to de-bathification.
Right.
Once it comes along.
Exactly.
And I don't think he'll be willing to be strongly in favor.
Certainly as things go along, I don't think he'll, he'll own the consequences.
It didn't, it didn't go well.
No.
Yeah.
So, uh, I would say that listening to this episode, there is very little, um, in terms
of news stories.
Sure.
There is a little bit of like a couple of headlines thrown out here and there.
He talks a lot about Richard Pearl, who he calls the Prince of Darkness.
Sure.
I think there's, he's obsessed with that dude because I've heard him talk about that dude
in the present day.
Really?
Yes.
Constantly.
20 years.
When he gets drunk on like a Rogan's show and stuff, he'll talk about Richard Pearl,
the Prince of Darkness.
He would go around, he'd go around at parties and tell women that like he kills people because
he thinks it's hot.
He thinks that that'll get him aroused and stuff.
Okay.
He won't be like, he brings up this dude a lot.
All right.
Anyway, it's, there's not a whole lot.
I do like a lifelong grudge.
That's admirable.
Yeah.
There's something almost noble about that.
Do you think 15 years from now he's not going to be yelling about Stelter?
Yeah.
That's true.
So, uh, Alex gets to the end of the show and he realizes, man, I didn't, I missed some
stuff.
Oh, there was so much news we didn't get to.
More and more cities are passing pro bill of rights resolutions.
A lot of conservative cities are doing it.
I've got one on info wars.com.
You ought to get to your city council or county commissioners and the man they pass it.
So important to reaffirm the bill of rights.
They can claim.
We don't have any rights.
They're still God given.
We still have them in the Anton LaVey, Christian conservative, Neo con, the commie cons will
be resisted, will be exposed with their little liberal buddies, totally staged.
The people are waking up, millions of beginning to fight.
You cannot stop us all.
So have no fear.
We shall prevail.
Good God that was uninspired.
Oh boy.
That was boring.
We shall prevail.
Let's go on guys.
This is before he started doing his Churchill impression.
Hey, now we shall fight them on the sheet.
We're going to, okay guys, we got to get up.
Yeah.
So Alex, Alex comes to the end of the show and realizes that he didn't cover most of
the news as opposed to it happening an hour before the show ends.
And then still no more news is covered.
Um, but yeah, he has, he's got a minute and what he wants to really hit on is there are
people reaffirming the bill of rights, which is very meaningful and important.
It's not, this is just the same thing as in 2009, all the 10th amendment resolutions and
stuff.
It's like, yes.
Okay.
We have to have the state houses pass these things that say the same thing as the constitution.
Like, I don't know, man, it's, it's.
What, to what extent do they describe God given rights?
You know, like, give me a biblical explanation of what rights God specifically gives us.
Because I don't recall him writing the goddamn bill of rights.
I don't know if it's derived directly from anything in the Bible, but this is, this is
a pretty standard element of anti-communism.
No, of course.
They have this idea that communism seeks to outlaw religion and get rid of religion and
in doing so you get rid of God and if you get rid of God, then there's no more justification
for why people have rights because they're endowed by the creator.
So therefore now you have no rights.
Sure.
Communism gets rid of God, which gets rid of rights, which makes you all slaves.
That's where the important hinge is for the God given rights aspect.
Right.
No, no, I understand.
I just, I just feel like if you want to win in the marketplace of ideas, you should kind
of write down what rights you're peddling.
Well, they did.
And we'll compare them to the other thing.
They did.
It's in the Declaration of Independence, Constitution.
It's those rights.
Those aren't rights that are given by the Constitution, those are God given rights that
are protected by the Constitution.
Oh, oh, so it's even dumber than I thought it was.
Sort of.
Right.
It's the same kind of, I don't know, it's an argument that you can run into a lot.
It's the notion of like, does all morality stem from religion?
Sure.
Is ethics possible outside?
Naturally.
And I would argue that it is.
Well, yeah, obviously.
We have several thousand years.
But there are those who think that no, morality and ethics are impossible outside of a religious
framework.
Right.
And I don't know, I don't buy into that, but that seems to be kind of a kernel at the base
of their idea, like Alex and a lot of his associates' conception of rights.
No, I just didn't, I didn't quite understand what they were talking about.
Because generally speaking, whenever people start talking about God, I appreciate it if
they have some sort of biblical basis for it.
It's just guns.
Yeah, it does sound like it's just guns.
Man, people love their guns.
It was the 11th commandment.
It's just, there's just, man, guns aren't, oh.
The 11th commandment was, guns, baby!
Guns, guns, guns, baby!
Yep.
And Jesus said to, at the last, one of you will betray me before the cock, with a fucking
shotgun!
So, we come to the end of this exploration of back in 18 years ago today.
18 years ago today.
What an interesting glimpse.
This very night, 18 years ago.
Such wrong ideas about what was gonna happen.
Such misguided nonsense.
Not good.
A weirdo presented as an expert.
That's pretty normal.
Yeah, that's fair.
And more evidence that Alex should sue Joe Rogan for using the word powerful.
I think it's trademarked.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, I think you could get a, it'd be tough, though, to win a lawsuit whenever you've got
that, oh, Alex just said, we're gonna play that clip of Alex saying he's gonna gut him
like a pig, you know, like, how are you gonna win that kind of lawsuit?
Free speech, man.
Ah, that's fair.
I'm infuriated by the, going to urination talk and the mic's cutting out right around
when Satan was coming up.
It's gonna be the armpit of Satan.
I take that personally, a little bit.
It's very funny.
But I'm excited to see if the next couple episodes have anything that'll help clarify
positions.
It'd be more funny if somebody actually cut off the mic whenever he was about to say,
literally like, we can't have that out there, boom, red button.
Fred Anderson dives on that.
Red button, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
He's up in Minnesota listening to The Feed's comic.
I've never seen anybody move that fast.
Yeah.
We'll find out more in the future, but until next time, Jordan, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yes, we are also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledgefight.com.
I go to bed.
Jordan.
We're also on Facebook.
We are Facebook.
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work.
Yep, we'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo, I'm Leo, I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
And now, here comes the sex robots.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first-time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.