N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys. Knowledgefight.
Dan and Jordan, Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air. Thanks for holding.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledgefight. I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes. Let's sit around, drink novelty, worship Celine.
Yep, oh boy.
We're going to struggle with this for a while.
Talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
We should have added this earlier on, maybe in our 300th episode, and then we'd be practiced by now.
I just need to also be more mindful of it.
True, true.
When I'm starting the episode, just remember, novelty beverage is out, worship Celine in.
Right. I mean, when you're starting any religion, you want to be more mindful.
Sure.
I think that's the point.
There needs to be some intention to it, which we're failing.
Sure, sure. Yeah.
Well, that would be our religion.
Yeah.
Eh, came back to life, who gives a shit? Whatever.
Live your own way.
Yeah. So Jordan, how are you doing?
I'm doing well, Dan. I have a quick question for you.
Sure.
What is your bright spot today?
My bright spot today is actually, I think, okay, so you know how like in school you'd be like,
when am I ever going to need to use this?
Sure.
You talk about like math or anything.
Sure, sure.
I sometimes feel that way about this podcast.
Like I learn stuff and I'm like, when am I ever going to need to do this?
Fair, fair.
I spend a lot of time learning things that will never, ever come up in anyone's daily life.
No, no, no. I think you're going to have a lot of natural sounding conversations that just end up in this information.
I had a moment where it actually came into play.
Oh shit.
And it felt really good.
Okay, what happened?
So I was taking a Lyft ride from coming home and the guy, it was a very nice conversation.
Nothing against this guy.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
But we were talking about some of the like difficulties of the COVID year and all this.
And the conversation veered into talking about like public debt.
Sure, sure.
And the deficit.
Sure.
And so this guy was saying that-
The Fed was started by three senators.
No, no, no, no.
Nothing that hyper specific.
Not there.
No.
Okay.
Just that like China owns half our debt.
Oh yeah.
And without even missing a beat, I was like, that's not true.
And he's like, yeah, they own a lot.
I'm like, they own a bit, but not nearly that much.
I've looked into this.
It's mostly stuff we owe ourselves.
Listen, sir, sir, I am one of the few people who, when you hear I've looked into this,
you fucking listen.
China owns a lot of debt.
Nope.
Lyft ride over.
And you jumped out the window.
Guy was very nice and I didn't like want to shame him or be a dick about it or anything.
No, of course not.
But it was a rare occasion where it was like, ha ha ha.
Not going to back down on this one.
This is the hill I die on.
Yeah.
So how about you?
What's your bright spot?
I've been to my first Cubs game in two years, Dan.
Why was that?
Why was what, Dan?
Don't make me do this.
Happy birthday, Jordan.
Thanks, Dan.
Fine.
It was your birthday this weekend.
It was my birthday this weekend.
Happy birthday.
Yeah.
I went to the game.
It was fantastic.
I have a very fun story that is going to sound self-aggrandizing at first, but it is very
much not about that.
Frank Rizzo said you had the best arm in the game.
If only.
If only, Dan.
Is that his first name?
Anthony Rizzo.
Who's Frank Rizzo?
Frank Rizzo is a guy.
Who is Frank Rizzo?
Character or something?
Yeah, I think so.
Anyway, keep going.
Yeah.
Anyways, everybody was socially distanced in the park.
It was good stuff, and row behind us about 10 seats away, there was this dude who showed
up wearing a goddamn t-shirt.
It was a nice day, but at Wrigley, whatever it is outside, it is 20 degrees lower than
that.
Sure.
On the thing.
This guy is absolutely freezing, and then the sun goes behind the clouds, and everybody
is freezing.
Everybody is curled up, and I keep turning and looking back at this fucking guy with
his bare sleeves.
I'm losing my arm.
I'm losing my mind, right?
I have to go.
I can't do this anymore.
So I go and I buy him a fucking blanket.
I have to.
This is not me being generous.
This is me like, I can't watch this fucking game unless you do something.
So it's either you get a blanket, or I ask them to make you leave.
Those are your options.
Blanket it is.
It's not a self-aggrandizing story at all.
You got to buy him a Snuggie.
That's basically what it was.
So it turns out Frank Rizzo was the racist mayor of Philadelphia.
He was a notorious-
That's why I remember the name!
Yeah, he's a piece of shit!
I'm looking at his Wikipedia page here, and as mayor, Rizzo was a strong opponent of desegregation
in Philadelphia schools, and prevented the construction of public housing in majority
white neighborhoods.
While running for a third term, Rizzo urged supporters to quote, vote white.
You know, I think that says a lot about us, that the first Rizzos that come to mind are
in your situation, anti-communist nightmares!
And in mine.
Well, also Ratso Rizzo, wasn't he a Muppet?
Ratso was great.
Anyway, Jordan, today we have a prison day episode to go over, we're going to be talking
about- our last episode was May 7th, 2003.
Correct.
Now today we're going to be talking about May 6th and 7th, 2021.
Blackjack.
I think we both stopped for a second to see if the other would do it first!
What is wrong with us?
Why can't we do our own bits?
Well that's like, you know, when you get to the door at the same time with somebody who's
holding the door for who.
It was like I was letting you go, excuse me sir, after you.
This is interesting, it's a fun stretch of time and I'm excited to get into it.
But before we do, Jordan, we've got a wonk and a technocrat to give a shout out to.
First, a wonk, thank you so much, Marnix!
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk!
Thank you Marnix!
And technocrat, Dirk Gently's cat, thank you so much, you are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey mate, that's fantastic, have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
Alright, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, alright?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Dirk Gently's cat would also like to say happy birthday to Will S.
Ooh, happy birthday Will S.
So Dirk, you might notice there's a few, only a few policy wonks.
It's a bit shorter.
Yeah, and that's because in honor of your birthday, we have some birthday shout outs.
Okay, okay, alright, we're doing May all at once.
Not all of May, but it turns out there's a cluster right around here that I think it's
because of you.
Naturally.
So, Steven, happy birthday from Keith, that was over the weekend on the 9th, the 9th.
Happy birthday.
Day after your birthday.
Sunday.
Oh, come on, don't give people...
Don't give people detailed information.
My passwords aren't that strong.
Oh no.
You might want to rethink those.
So also, Corinna, happy birthday, that's coming up on the 11th, so coming up in the middle
of this week.
Happy birthday, Corinna.
And Tom, from his brother, Megaron.
He's just ten rons put together into one giant ron, naturally.
Is that how it works with the Queen's measurements?
I know, do you mean like he's ten stone?
Metric?
Couldn't come up with the word metric?
I was going to go with Power Rangers, he's a megazord.
Okay.
And that is also on the 11th, happy birthday, Tom from Megaron.
Also, we have something that I missed in the mailbag last time we got together, so this
was something that I actually had on the list that I was going to bring up last time, but
I had forgotten the note in the other room, and this note is too good not to share with
the world.
Dear Dan and Jordan, the Society for the Preservation of Raptor Royalty have determined that I am
no longer fit to be regent for this raptor princess, as I have been traveling and moving
too much to keep her safe.
Dan, I hope she doesn't eat your chocolate.
Jordan, I hope Dan doesn't eat your chocolate.
Thank you so much for your wonderful podcast and for the cool community on Facebook.
You guys help me stay sane, happy euphoria chocolating, I think, euphoric chocolating.
From Karen C, so this ceramic raptor princess is just the coolest thing.
I have to assume that Karen found this at like a thrift store or something, but it is
just amazing.
It's so cool.
I'm going to post a picture of this on...
It's really kind of, it looks like it was made with, somebody made it and they were
like, this is going to come in handy 20 or 30 years from now.
20 or 30?
This looks like it's from the 20s.
It does kind of look, wow, that is old.
Yeah, it's gorgeous.
Thank you so much.
Also, this was the package that came with all the candy that was marked Dan stop opening
Jordan's candy.
That was the best.
Yeah.
There was some candy and I was like, Dan, you can't eat this candy.
No.
It was the package that had a bunch of points.
You opened it.
So why don't you describe it?
That was the best part of this.
The first message, it was wrapped really, really heavily.
And the first message was like, Dan, this is Jordan's candy.
Don't eat it.
And you just gave it to me from there.
So I took it home and I started trying to unwrap it.
The record should show that I did follow the instructions.
Yes, that's important because there were further instructions as you opened it up.
Down on the paper was written like, Dan, if you've made it this far, you need to stop.
And then still further was like, Dan, you've stolen Jordan's candy at this point.
It was just guilt.
It was fantastic.
I can't imagine how ashamed I would be if I saw those notes.
If you saw the second note, that was the best part.
The best part was I was like, God damn it.
If Dan had seen the second note, it would have been just, he would have spent two days
thinking about how he's the person who made it to the second note.
I feel like it's a test I didn't know I had passed.
Yes, you passed it.
So that's great.
Thank you so much, Karen.
That was a fun insult, I guess.
No, I think it was a test and you passed it and you're now King Arthur?
And the raptor princess will be well taken care of on our shelf of curiosities.
So Jordan, May 6th and 7th, I should say that this is a little fun for me.
There's actually, I mean, granted, it is like I brought up, like we're just anti-vax bullshit.
Right, right, right.
Whatever.
But there's a specific in this episode that allowed me to dig in a little bit and I enjoyed
that.
Excellent.
So here's an out of context drop from today's show.
All right.
Shut up, Jones.
Okay.
Might be able to use that quite a bit in the future.
I would stick with that one.
So here we go.
Alex is starting out this May 6th show and there's, see if you can think of a children's
story that comes to mind when you hear this.
Okay.
The information I got before the broadcast started, dovetailed with all the major research,
scores of top scientists in other major studies.
But when I read the study from an extremely prestigious viral research institute at the
University of Texas, Galveston, where they do level four bio weapons research, I was
completely blown away.
And quite frankly, had trouble even being on air at this point.
This audience is millions of people.
You're incredible.
You're amazing.
But I've learned how the paradox works.
But I said, I have total proof that they knew that the COVID-19 vaccines, both mRNA and
virus vector delivery systems.
So both the Moderna, the Pfizer mRNA, and then the AstraZeneca and J and J shots, the
two different classes in the main literature warns that it causes massive auto-immune response
in the brain, the heart, and in the cardiovascular system, and that they recommend it not be
done because it caused massive death in the lab animals.
If I had that info, which I do, and I cover it here on air, it just gets lost in the background
noise.
But if I built it up and said, oh, this Saturday, I'm going to do a special show for three hours,
commercial free, everybody tune in, we would have millions and millions of people that
tuned in specifically for that information.
They would take it very seriously, like they were at a restaurant waiting for a big, nice
plate of food to come out, devour it, and then share it with others mentally.
And that's basically where we are.
Also, this audience is incredibly influential.
A lot of important people listen, but this is at this point, I should probably just go
off air and, or have Owen Schroyer come in and do a great job hosting, and just go show
this document.
That's definitely fiction.
Yeah.
So I just keep hearing the boy who cried wolf here.
This is a guy who's like, I have said that I have solved every problem too many times,
and now it's just background dressing.
Can't really pull this off.
People don't get excited anymore.
Not really doing it.
And now the only way for me to escalate things is to do a show on my day off, because that
makes it look like I'm serious.
I guess.
And, oh God, Diminishing Returns, oh no.
It's almost as if there was some sort of law that somebody wrote about Diminishing Returns.
Also, I don't remember if I pulled a clip of this, but later in the show, so Alex is
saying that he's going to have to come back on Saturday to cover this thing, this mega
bombshell because it's the only way he can get attention.
Can't not.
He does realize, ah shit, I'm supposed to take my daughter fishing on Saturday.
So he gets a pail of God and he's like, maybe I'll do it on Sunday, I don't know.
This, this man is truly the tip of the spear.
Yes.
Tireless.
The study that Alex is referring to is from 2012, and honestly, he's messing up some details,
but he's more right than he usually is here.
Interesting.
Granted, this is a study about SARS, not SARS-CoV-2, but in terms of the level I'm used to him
making things up, I was surprised to open the study and see this in the conclusion section.
Quote, these SARS-CoV vaccines all induced antibody and protection against infection
with SARS-CoV.
However, challenge of mice given any of the vaccines led to occurrences of TH2 type immunopathology
suggesting hypersensitivity to SARS-CoV compounds was induced.
Caution in proceeding to application of SARS-CoV vaccine in humans is indicated.
That's pretty interesting.
And on its own, it sounds pretty scary.
Like the idea of making a coronavirus vaccine for humans is something that shouldn't be
done.
But it's pretty important to recognize that this is a part of medical literature history,
and that's not a static thing.
This probably doesn't need to be said, but changes have been made since 2012.
Additionally, the circumstances were different with a worldwide outbreak happening now creating
necessity, which of course is the mother of invention.
You can find some discussion of this very study Alex is referencing in more detailed
write-ups about the path that research has taken in terms of developing a coronavirus
vaccine going through SARS, MERS, and now SARS-CoV-2.
If Alex is just looking for flashy ways to smear science, he could find all sorts of
studies from the past that have shown difficulties with vaccine development, but that game relies
on pretending that people don't learn from these studies and then adjust their approaches.
One important thing to recognize is that the study that Alex is referring to, which you
can find by googling the title, Immunization with SARS Coronavirus Vaccines Leads to Pulmonary
Immunopathology on Challenge with the SARS Virus.
That's the title of it.
If you look for it, it's about completely different vaccines than the ones that have
been developed in response to COVID.
If you just read the first few pages of the study, you see that the vaccines that were
tested in this were two varieties.
They were inactivated whole virus vaccines or virus-like particle vaccines.
The Pfizer and Moderna vaccines are mRNA-based vaccines which work entirely differently than
either of the types in this study, so there's no direct relevance between the shots and
this study at all.
The Johnson & Johnson vaccine is a viral vector vaccine, which is fairly similar to the virus-like
particle approach, but with a very important distinction.
The virus-like particle vaccines in the study use the structural elements of SARS devoid
of any viral genomes to trigger an immune response in people, whereas the J&J vaccine
uses a non-infectious virus to create the spike protein of COVID, which then teaches
our body to recognize that specific spike protein and fight it.
The point here is that this study Alex is covering is not a bombshell.
It does not require coming in on Saturday, but it does have a couple of good buzzwords
that jump off the page, and if you don't pay too much attention, it can kind of look like
it supports its narratives, Alex's narratives, but it's all bullshit.
This is going to be one of the things that he talks about almost exclusively, and it's
amazing to see how much he just makes up.
He's just making shit up.
It's amazing.
And look, okay, you can tell me the challenges and the things that were wrong in 2012, right?
But if you tell me that they're the same now, how many iPhones was that a go?
Was that, wait, what was that?
Was that the iPhone 4 years?
We're better than that now.
People were still talking about the Mayan calendar.
Exactly.
Yeah, we're fine, okay?
Don't tell me that in 2012, oh, in 2012, they had trouble making a vaccine.
So we should stop.
Well, there's a lot of variables that go into it and actually color the progression of the
vaccine's development.
Totally.
And some of that we'll discuss a little bit later, but look, dude, Alex found out about
this and he is fucking mad.
This could save hundreds of millions, if not billions of people.
I thought it was over for humanity, again.
I'm unable to continue the broadcast at this point.
This is not a drama.
I just can't do it.
I was already doing too much this morning on other big subjects and then I got blindsided
by this and I'm in a controlled rage right now and I've got to take some time off, so
that's just the way it is.
I don't even know if I'm coming back anymore.
Maybe they need to kill everybody because the public doesn't care.
Maybe you deserve to die.
Okay.
It was at this point that I suspected Alex was in a bad mood about something.
Maybe something in his personal life was not exactly to his liking.
Why are so many people willing to follow somebody that publicly pouts like a whiny baby?
What are you talking about?
Jordan.
Maybe you all should just die.
Great.
Yes.
We want you to lead the fucking resistance.
Jordan, this isn't a drama.
Jordan brought this study to his attention when he had already done so much work and
now everyone's got to die.
I just don't remember fucking Che Guevara in the middle of the revolution just being
like, you know what guys?
Fine.
I just don't even, no, no, no.
I just don't even care anymore.
I don't even want to lead this revolution.
I'm sick of this.
Yeah.
To quote Castro, wah.
Jesus.
Yep.
I mean, folks wants to protest about this study, man.
He wants to get out there and bullhorn like his roots.
Like he wants to get back to who he was in waking life.
That image of a guy driving around red in the face.
Hero.
There's no doubt about this as a mass kill operation.
No doubt.
Maybe we should all go protest at Dell Children's Hospital or maybe go protest at the FBI in
North Austin.
I mean, I don't know what you do.
I mean, to draw attention and bullhorn here is the university of Texas prestigious bio
weapons research lab saying any vaccines for the coronavirus family cause massive auto
immune responses, strokes and heart attacks and blood clots.
Look at this.
They studied it on a whole bunch of animals and it killed mass numbers of them.
And we've already known this.
So there are some very basic lies Alex is telling about the study just in that little
rant.
And if you pay attention to the specific things he's lying about, you can see his motives
really clearly.
The first thing to be very clear about is that this study only had to do with reactions
to a vaccine in mice.
At the end of the study, they even say, quote, limitations of the present studies include
their performance in mice only and uncertainty of the relevance of rodent models to SARS
coronavirus vaccines in humans.
Max is skimming the study, so he's only looking at the first page and abstract, basically.
And if you only look at that and you don't actually read it, you might think that there
are more animals involved.
In the design section of the abstract, it says, quote, four candidate vaccines for humans
with or without alum adjuvant were evaluated on a mouse model of SARS and a VLP vaccine,
the vaccine given to ferrets and non-human primates, another whole virus vaccine and
an RDNA produced S protein.
Ferrets and non-human primates are referenced, but not as participants in the study.
The context of that is that VLP vaccines are typically the type that are given to those
animals.
If you weren't paying attention to the study at all and you just wanted to use the appearance
of it as a prop to scare people, it'd be really easy to see multiple animal names in the first
page and just kind of run with it.
Yeah.
Which is what Alex is doing.
Yeah, he's painting that like 12 monkeys picture where there's all these animals in cages in
like a dark lit room somewhere.
Yeah.
So Alex is making up that the study showed that mass numbers of animals were killed because
of the vaccine.
There weren't massive numbers of mice involved to begin with, and if you read the study,
you would know how the study was designed.
They vaccinated the mice with the different vaccines and 56 days later, actually that's
not entirely true, 56 days into the study, five mice from each group were killed to assess
how well the vaccines had worked and to gauge lung issues that existed.
The remaining mice in each group were challenged with live SARS and then killed two days later
so their lungs could be studied.
There's no indication that lung issues or vaccine concerns killed even a single mouse
in this study.
Alex is making that up to make this story seem more interesting to his audience.
Third, Alex is making up the effects that this study found in vaccinated mice who were
faced with a SARS challenge.
He's including autoimmune conditions in the list because that's been a big talking point
on Infowars for a long time, so it's meant to give him the appearance of being right.
Strokes, heart attacks, and blood clots are included because these are the things that
people have been discussing as possibly related to various vaccines for COVID-19.
Naturally.
There's not evidence of a causal link, but a public conversation about concerns surrounding
those issues has been going on, and Alex is trying to exacerbate those concerns and scare
his audience.
And in the study, as we know, the only real result was all of the mice had increased flatulence.
That was not in the study.
Oh, are you sure?
It should have been.
The actual study doesn't involve any of the conditions that Alex was listing.
The effects studied were entirely surrounding damage to lung tissue.
One of the following must be true, and I cannot stress this enough.
Alex has either not read this study at all and is just making all this stuff up, or he
has read the study and he knows that he's lying to his audience about what it says to
scare them.
There isn't a middle ground, but I will say that in that first possibility, that first
category is skimmed it and read a few words.
Yeah, that is definitely more likely.
Yeah, but it's still just making up what you think those words are.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's bullshit.
Yeah.
And I love it.
I love it.
I imagine when he looks at a article, it probably looks like, when you and I look at something
to read, we like see all the words, right?
I imagine every time he looks at one of these, it's like a redacted document in his brain.
Like his brain just cuts out all the words that aren't like usable.
But instead of the black bars, it's like demon faces.
Yeah, it's just squiggly lines that burst off the page.
Or clowns walking, like doing John Cleese.
It's the pink elephants and he's got the brown bag and he looks at it and he's like, oh shit,
I got to quit drinking.
Instead of words, it's John Cleese, so he walks, but it's a weird clown.
That's my theory.
Sure, sure.
So Alex is going to leave.
Uh-huh.
He's got to go.
Maybe he doesn't.
Okay.
You know what?
I'm not going to go off here.
I'm just going to read the whole damn study on air, how's that sound?
That sounds good.
And again, usually these studies mince words and this spells it right out in the summary
on the front page, University of Texas, level four bioweapons lab in Galveston, Texas.
There's no way he's reading this study on air.
This whole overly dramatic breakdown of having to go off air and then deciding to stay on
air and read the whole study, it would come off a lot more genuine if he hadn't followed
the whole part of the beginning there where Alex was complaining that no one pays attention
to him unless he makes a big deal out of things.
There is that.
It almost feels like this kind of like fake struggling that he's going through.
It's like a piece of the necessary performance that he has to carry out to make anyone believe
that this piece of supposed evidence actually means anything.
Yeah.
It's all just, it's just an act.
Yeah, you know, it reminds me of when James Brown used to, somebody would put the blanket
over his shoulders and he'd be like, ah, I'm too tired.
I can't go on anymore.
And he'd start walking off stage, but then the music would bring him right back, Dan.
I mean, it gets you into the performance, I guess.
Yeah, but you know, he's coming back.
Especially if you're on tour with him and you've seen it over and over.
I'm basically on tour with Alex.
You're the grateful dad.
Yeah.
And I do not like the hits.
The hits are boring.
Also, small point here.
It's like you've been following around Fish for 10 years, but you hate them.
But also don't, like, I think that's the worst example, right?
Fish do a lot of improvising.
That's true.
Yeah.
A lot of those like long jams are, they put out all of their shows and people listen to
them.
Like that's the exact wrong example.
That's a good point.
Look, I don't like Fish or anything.
Look, there are no doors.
But I think that that's a bad example.
Anyway, small point here, Jordan.
The lab at the University of Texas, Galveston is a level three biosafety lab, not a level
four.
I would feel like a stickler for pointing that out when Alex said it was level four,
but there's a big difference between those two.
And also that information is literally on page two of the study.
So if he made it that far, he would know what level it was.
I think he should read the whole study on air.
I think it would be a smart move in his situation.
Ain't gonna do it.
I kind of doubt it.
That makes sense.
But he is going to yell a lot.
That sounds like it.
Some of the rats died today.
Some died in six weeks, but they died and they bled out, folks.
They what?
Where their brain meets the sinus, they bled out their lungs, they bled out their thighs,
they bled out their stomachs, they bled out, they bled out, they bled out, they bled out,
they bled out.
Just like you shoot somebody with a 12-gauge shotgun with a double-aught buck, they bleed
out in about a minute.
This way you bleed out over the next few years.
My God.
Wow.
I want to read.
I would give anything to read an accurate scientific study that was just like, there
was blood everywhere.
Oh, the rodent manatee.
Oh, it's a nightmare.
It was a bad lung.
Oh, everywhere we went, blood on the walls.
It hit me in the nose.
God have mercy.
I mean, I don't want to minimize the grossness of even just reading this, all these mice
are euthanized.
There's something about it that makes me kind of uncomfortable.
There's a certain amount of it that's fucked up.
But it's completely different than what Alex is describing.
It is not people injecting mice with a vaccine and then them suddenly exploding in a blood
field.
Watching them bleed out.
It's not a samurai movie from the 70s, man.
So Alex is lying about one line that I think someone must have highlighted for him in the
study.
Quote, mice were anesthetized with isoflurane and then bled from the retroorbital sinus
plexus.
He's taking the second half of that sentence about bleeding and then pretending that it
didn't follow the first half where the mice were all put down in accordance with the methodology
of the study.
This doesn't mean that the mice died bleeding from their noses, but that's the image that
Alex wants to use these words to paint and it's a complete fabricator.
It's complete nonsense.
It's childish.
Just going up on JSTOR, reading the introduction, the very end of it is, Oh God, what have we
done?
Science has asked too long whether or not we could.
Make mice bleed out?
Yes.
Yeah.
So anyway, Alex makes up some more shit.
Yep.
Imagine a 2012 highly respected peer reviewed university of Texas longterm study on all
sorts of different animals, finding massive blood clots, brain damage, heart attacks,
organ failure, you name it, and cautioning against vaccines for the coronavirus family.
So that clip is 23 seconds long.
And here's a list of, I bet there are more, but I caught eight here.
Maybe.
I got six big ones.
Six big ones.
Okay.
Errors.
That is one.
It was not a longterm study.
Right.
Two.
It wasn't on all sorts of animals.
It was just mice.
Right.
Three.
It didn't find massive blood clots.
Nope.
Four.
It didn't find brain damage.
Nope.
Five.
It didn't find heart attacks.
True.
Six.
It did advise caution with proceeding with the application of SARS coronavirus vaccine
in humans.
That's all good and well, but it doesn't match the, what Alex is saying.
Like don't overdo, don't open Pandora's box.
Yeah.
Totally.
There's a few others in there, but, uh, I, I felt like some might be splitting hairs,
but those are the major issues of the actual study.
Those were bonus ones that I just gave him just on account of being Alex.
I just assume you, whatever you think it is, add to, just to be safe.
You're a gambler.
I'm a gambler.
I like it.
And I think that's a safe bet.
Yeah.
Alex's brief summary of the study gets so much completely wrong that even if you didn't
suspect as I do that he's a willful liar, you should be really worried about his ability
to convey accurate information from primary sources.
Even if you think he has a heart of gold and he means well, and you know, he's a good guy,
this is a staggering display of inability to do the job he's tried to give himself.
This is like, sometimes I'll, I'll check in and I'll listen to these like, and I'll find
the primary source and it'd be like, Oh, this is bad.
This is bad work.
This is funny.
Yeah.
It's so embarrassingly bad.
The bleeding out the noses.
This is, Oh God.
This is like, he's like a kid.
He should, he should begin this segment with that a carnival music, but in a minor key.
So you know, we're entering into a real fucked up world.
You know, nothing, this is topsy-turvy world.
Nothing's going to be real and it's all going to be terrifying.
Just coming into, yeah, it'll be great.
Yeah.
I agree.
And man, I can't even begin to tell you there is a punchline that it floored me.
Okay.
All right.
You, but you must think of the mice holy mackerel.
You ought to read here.
Overhead shot, please.
What happened to the mice bleeding out their sinus, bleeding out their brains, bleeding
out their hearts, young mice, middle-aged mice, old mice, all the mice, young mice,
middle-aged mice, old mice, you have mice that were just getting ready to go off to
college with their whole lives ahead of them.
Mice that were two days away from retirement.
Totally planning a life after their career at the software development firm.
Going to move to Florida.
There's some traveling.
Yeah, absolutely.
It was finally time.
Maybe going to get into the puzzles, you know, with your old, your spouse, my mouse, your
spouse mouse.
Spouse mouse.
Oh, God damn it.
Then you got to think about the adolescent mice who just made the cut for the varsity
football team.
Short, short.
Yeah, of course.
Cut down in their prime.
Yeah.
Could have been Heisman contenders.
Bo Jackson mouse.
He was almost going to make it in three professional sports.
Yeah.
Tragic.
It's her middle-aged mouse.
He's really, really painting a picture.
For a man who's killed that many dogs, how dare he try to make me care about mice?
What an asshole.
Again, just to be totally clear, I have reservations about the way animals are used.
No, absolutely.
Animal testing is fucked up.
Yeah.
I agree.
I don't want to unpack that right now while I'm busy laughing at middle-aged mice.
What a dick.
Young mice, middle-aged mice, old mice, they come for us all, man.
So Alex continues to make stuff up.
Neutralizing antibody assays.
What happened to the animals?
Death.
University of Texas.
This is prestigious.
This is the university did a long-term study on a bunch of vaccines they already had on
the shelf and they all do the same thing.
MRNA or virus vector.
Alex is just skimming the paper now and he saw the headline neutralizing antibody assays.
And that's just the section about how post euthanasia, the samples are taken from the
animals and how they're processed in such a way as to preserve the evidence that antibodies
that might be detected were from the vaccine that was given as opposed to another source.
Alex has no idea what the words he's saying even mean.
He just knows they kind of sound scary.
Also, this study has literally nothing to do with MRNA vaccines.
None of the four vaccines studied were that type and Alex is just throwing that in to
make the audience scared of current day COVID-19 vaccination.
Of course.
Because he has an agenda.
Yeah.
Boy.
And again, it's, it's a, it's a lab that they're, they're, they're put, they're put down.
It's not like Alex is making it sound like everybody is like, okay, we injected them
with the stuff and then they've got a giant meat cleaver and they just chop the mouse
off and they're like, we'll move on.
No, no, no.
Maybe there is a little bit of that, but I think the image he wants people to have is
that he, they injected them and then just watched them slowly.
Yeah.
Wow.
That's probably like they were counting the time.
Right.
Yeah.
That's cool.
Why'd they never have a vaccine for the Corona family?
That's the most common, one of the most common families because it's a fricking protein that
your body's made up out of.
What else has your body made up?
It's incredible.
And I've got some, I was so ready to cover all this other news.
I just spent last night and this morning reading 50 something pages of a Pentagon DARPA document
just, I mean, I hope you're excited to have Alex not talk about that supposed DARPA document.
I'm looking forward to a 50 page DARPA document.
Bad news.
Also, the reason there wasn't a coronavirus vaccine prior to now is primarily because
it's a challenging thing to do and money wasn't there for the research.
Most Corona viruses are not generally very severe and the two previous times there were
serious outbreaks with SARS and MERS, both were handled relatively well with containment
measures and proper protocols, so they never got to the point where money was flowing in
as an urgent solution was needed.
Like now.
Right.
COVID changed that factor in the equation.
And thankfully we also had some preliminary work done in forms of studies that were done
in the wake of SARS and MERS that helped inform current efforts that were going on.
Of course.
A coronavirus vaccine probably could have been made in the past.
It just would have been a question of marshaling efforts and resources into the right places.
And that wasn't something that was seen as a good investment until recently.
Right.
Hopefully that lesson's been learned.
Yeah.
You know, I would like it if more people realized that science, when it succeeds, is the culmination
of failures and not like a simple moment of single, a brilliant inspiration that appears
out of nowhere.
It's the culmination of years upon years upon years of work.
Yeah.
And realistically, like a hundred things could go wrong and then that could lead to
something that's really huge.
Totally.
Whereas, you know, you're not going to make the playoffs if you have an 0 in a hundred
record.
Right.
We're trained to have this win-loss kind of like success-failure way we look at stuff.
And it, yeah, it's a different paradigm.
Yeah.
It's a completely different paradigm.
Failure is the goal.
Because if you fail all the time, then when you succeed, you're like, holy shit, this
is real.
Yeah.
So Alex has a bit of white identity based fears floating around.
Oh yeah, about white.
We have Carol Baker, CDC spokeswoman, telling a giant amphitheater full of scientists and
doctors and nurses that white people are inherently bad and must be gotten rid of because they
don't submit to the government.
So that's where this is coming from.
And I guess we do have kind of an Irish, Scottish, English background of a thousand years of
war between those groups and kings trying to get freedom.
And that's where the Magna Carta and then juries and basic rights come from.
Yes.
What white people basically invented really, really anchors the other white people that
want to run things.
Wow.
I don't even know where to begin with all of the things wrapped up in just that.
Just saying that means you extrapolate what it means if this is real.
But I've heard Alex say things like that in the past, like the idea that sort of white
people created freedom.
No, totally.
But I have often thought that was kind of just a stray thought.
Maybe he was in too deep on a sentence.
Sure, sure.
No, it's fundamental to his worldview.
It's fundamental to his worldview that no other culture has ever created any system
of freedom.
Of freedom.
Yeah.
Freedom is essentially a white creation.
He cannot possibly believe that anything else happened.
It's outrageous.
Yeah, he can't.
Imagine him reading about a matriarchal society.
Matriarchal societies that have existed in our past so many times and how much better
they are.
I can't even... Well, better is relative, but there are systems that work and are better
for... It depends on where you're living and the circumstances.
No, totally.
Totally.
I'm sorry.
My anthropology hat slipped on.
I understand.
I respect that.
I'm very troubled by that.
That's really fucked up.
Yeah.
But also that clip that he's talking about, about Dr. Carol Baker.
It's a clip that's been posted all over right-wing media.
It's about a minute and a half long, and it's a clip where Dr. Baker is saying that the
solution to getting rid of vaccine denial is getting rid of white people.
This is not at all being suggested as a serious solution.
It's clearly meant as a shock statement that furthers a different argument, which is conveniently
edited out of the clip that gets posted all over the media.
Most of the places you find this clip where they post it, it's super vague about where
the video comes from, sometimes just a year, and it's often the wrong year.
I suspect this is an intentional strategy to make it harder for the audience to confirm
the claims that are being made about it.
I tracked down the full video, and it's from a panel discussion being held by the National
Meningitis Association titled, quote, Achieving Childhood Vaccine Success in the United States.
It's not a giant amphitheater, but that visual does a lot more work for Alex, and he knows
the audience is just going to accept it over dumb shit, he says.
The larger context of the comment was in terms of a conversation about strategies to increase
vaccination rates.
Another panelist had suggested media training for doctors, and there was some disagreement
about whether or not the media training would be impactful.
Dr. Baker was expressing the position that the discussion to get children vaccinated
is an individual event that happens over and over all over the country every day, and media
training might not necessarily be the most helpful thing.
The conversation had also touched on multicultural issues, like communities that claim exemptions
from school vaccine mandates.
The comment Baker made appears to exist in the intersection of these two ideas, but it's
kind of a freewheeling panel discussion, so they kind of go off on some tangents, and
makes it a little bit difficult to know exactly where she was going.
But having watched the discussion, I'm absolutely certain that it has nothing to do with appealing
to white genocide.
I don't know.
It just sounds like the CDC's...
I feel like maybe the CDC is overreacting a little bit to the Trump years, but calling
for white genocide does seem...
She wasn't with the CDC at the time, I believe.
I think she was...
Right.
Of course not.
Yeah.
Because who fucking cares?
Previously.
Yeah.
Let's just lie about everything.
But Alex, boy, what a mess.
Yeah, that's not good.
White people invented freedom.
Oh, man.
He's in a mood.
Man.
Yeah.
I mean, the English, Irish, and Scotch thing, they invented freedom?
Like there was no...
Well, it's because they were fighting about kings or something.
I mean, couldn't he say...
I mean, if you want it to be a super...
Don't white nationalists claim Rome too?
Or was...
I think they love Vikings.
Or was that too swarthy at the time?
They love Vikings.
They like...
Well, yeah.
They're like the Norse runes.
Yes, yes.
The people who we most associate with freedom.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Great.
So Alex is in a mood.
And I think I might be able to tell you why.
Why?
Mic down for this.
Okay.
I have been called away to a little court hearing today, the wonders of family court.
So that's why I taped something this morning, because I've got to go at one o'clock today.
But I'll be back after that this afternoon.
There is so much to cover and so much to get to.
I wonder if that has to do anything with his mood.
Might be a bad mood.
Might be why he's fine with everybody dying.
Could be fine.
Could be something to do with it.
When I said that, I was like, oh, the mystery becomes clear.
Yeah.
This is like the scene in a Poirot thing where it's like the great six f1 down.
Yeah, the dramatic reveal.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, this is the dinner party.
Yeah.
I will slowly reveal the perpetrator of the court.
I have to go to family court.
Yes.
Caught him.
It was him.
Okay, yeah.
He was guilty.
Oh, this is why this is a bombshell.
No one pays attention to you.
Yeah, yeah.
And everyone's got to die.
Great.
Yep.
Okay.
Thanks, Alex.
Even though he has to leave early, it doesn't stop him from continuing to be wrong about
everything about this study.
Sounds right.
Overhead shot, please.
Well, this just got brought to my attention.
I went and checked it on the University of Texas website.
This is the University of Texas Biological Research Center, level four, one of the most
prestigious in the world.
Immunization with SARS coronavirus vaccines leads to pulmonary autoimmune response.
Immunopathology is what that means.
And it says this autoimmune response is in the mice.
We test on mice that are very similar to us with the way they react.
And then they have to show the photos and all of it.
And they have the control group, the non-control group, the control group, you know, those
that were a challenge got really sick.
Those that weren't given it didn't get sick.
They did a bunch of studies and it's got all the photos of the holes even in their lungs,
their brains.
And their hearts.
What?
Wait, what?
They did three different vaccines.
They did three different vaccines, three different types.
Show me those fucking photos.
They all killed the animals.
So that's the University of Texas.
So the lab isn't level four.
Immunopathology does not mean autoimmune.
The article has nothing to do with autoimmune conditions.
Correct.
Alex is making up how he imagines this test was run.
The only mice in the study were not challenged with live SARS were the five from each group
that were killed two days early so they could have their lungs examined.
The entire story of the vaccinated group getting sick after the challenge and non-vaccinated
group being fine, that just comes from Alex's imagination.
There were no photos in the study of hearts or brains because it's only about the lungs.
That's the word Alex keeps tripping over in the study's title, pulmonary.
Alex is making up that the other photos are in there or maybe he hallucinated them.
I'm not sure.
Also, they tested four vaccines in the study.
Alex just thinks there were three because he was skimming and he saw the line, quote,
three different experiments performed for comparing different vaccines are reported
here.
On page two, that's where that quote comes from, at the beginning of the study design
section.
In reality, there were four vaccines.
Two of them were the same type of vaccine, whole virus vaccines, but they were prepared
differently and used different adjuvants.
So they were experimentally distinct.
Sure.
Also, none of the vaccines killed any animals.
Right.
This is all nonsense.
Alex cannot fucking handle doing a...
Again, I mean, I just want to read that study where they're like, fuck it, man.
There are brains with holes in them, dude.
Put it in the study.
Sure.
Great.
Awesome.
Anyway, he continues lying.
Of course.
Well, I'll give Bill Gates and the UN and the globalists this.
They've got huevos the size of the Grand Canyon or the size of the Grand Tetons, size of the
planet.
The National Bioweapons Lab, level four, found that all coronavirus vaccines cause bleeding
in the lungs, the brain, the heart, and blood clots on a massive scale.
In some cases, the majority of lab rats died.
And that's the headline.
Immunization with SARS coronavirus vaccines leads to pulmonary immunopathology with all
the challenged subjects, all the lab animals.
That is from 2012.
And there's a bunch of other reports coming out.
They knew this.
They did it.
That way, they could plausibly deny when your loved one has a heart attack or a stroke or
a blood clot and you see what's coming out with all the vaccines.
Please don't forget, we're Lister supported, turbo force, 10 hours clean energy, back of
stock, 40% off.
Hey.
Holy shit.
Oh, boy.
That was a 90 degree turn.
God damn.
Jarring.
That hurt.
Yeah.
I feel like I was in a 30 mile an hour car crash right there.
That sounds like a guy who's got to go to family court, plugging like a guy who's got
to go to court with his ex-wife.
Yeah.
That'll do it.
So Alex has Nick Fuentes on for a little bit.
And I didn't point this out on our last episode, but when the two of them were talking, Alex
said that Nick Fuentes was going to get a channel on band.video on Alex's site.
And I just took that to be stray talk because he said that to almost everybody who's seen
the old man house phone.
He said that to almost everybody who's nuts and a problem.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
But they have followed through and now Nick has an America First channel on Alex's website.
Or, actually, that's better.
Keep it there.
Sure.
Keep it all there.
Get rid of everything else.
So he's also got another iron in the fire that he's going to explain here.
So I was on your show last week to talk about my placement on the no fly list, which we
suspect was for political reasons, and you brought on the great lawyer, Norm Pattis,
and we got a chance to talk a little bit.
Really?
And I actually gave him a call after your show, and I've now retained him to represent
me in a case against the TSA, and we should be filing, I believe, next week.
So we're going to take it to the courts against the TSA and the federal government.
I guess stand up didn't work out.
Wow.
Man.
Norm is running a good game.
I don't know about that.
There's something about some idiot just suddenly calling you because of Alex Jones and being
like, fuck it, yeah, I'll run your dumb lawsuit that's not going to go anywhere, you idiot.
Yeah.
Pay me.
I guess there does appear to be a space for, like, I mean, this is a scam.
Yeah, absolutely.
It's not a real lawsuit.
No.
It's at best a fundraising opportunity for Nick Fuentes.
Agreed.
Norm's going to skim some of that off in billable hours or whatever.
Yeah, why not?
I guess that is a career path you could go down as a lawyer.
Like Larry Klaiman did that for years, filing frivolous nonsense lawsuits.
You're just a scammer.
Yeah.
That's fine.
And if he wants to do that, great.
I don't know anything about, I don't know a lot about his career.
I know it seems like he's taking a turn for the racist lately.
And I guess, you know, getting in bed with, I guess just being associated with Alex Jones
too deeply.
Yeah.
This is just what happens.
It is.
It gets you.
Like Barnes ends up, like, doing interviews with Stefan Molyneux, and Norm's doing racist
stand up and hanging out with Nick Fuentes.
Yeah, you just can't, you can't do it.
You can't, you can't, you can't go on to do something else.
You can't exist in the modern GOP without being a white nationalist anyway, so.
Seems tough.
Yeah.
So Alex goes off to family court, and I stopped listening.
I don't care.
I know.
He's off to family court.
Yeah.
So he comes back in May 7th.
Right.
Uh.
Does he come back in that day?
I mean, not when his show's on.
Oh, okay.
He might have shown up, like, for the war room or something.
Gotcha.
I would assume he came back and had a little bit of a business meeting with a model.
Sure.
I would assume.
There's very little doubt of that.
Yeah.
There's a lot of work to get done around the office.
Like, that chair needed to be thrown over there.
I'm redecorating.
Yeah.
And that wall was, it was there, and there were zero holes in it.
And so I fixed that.
It is, like, an unforgivable problem.
So Alex comes back on the 7th, and he gets on air, and I was floored by how boring the
first, like, half hour of his show was.
Oh, yeah?
He says nothing.
Aw.
It's treading water.
It's just like, here I am.
He does a half hour of, I'm about to get to something.
Kind of.
He doesn't really feel like he was about to get there.
It felt like other people might be getting to something.
Right.
He is not.
But here's a little clip.
The government's outlaw, the government's criminal, the government's oppressing you,
the government's not legitimate, it's Chai-Com Globalist run, so following its directives
is now a crime against your family and humanity.
Any of this unconstitutional crap, any of the contact tracers, any intimidation to have
guards, anybody telling you you gotta wear a mask, anybody giving you this crap is part
of the enemy army, literally, that engineered this whole damn thing out of Wuhan.
I listen to stuff like that, and I just, I can't understand how anybody could listen
to Alex, take him seriously, and not recognize that terrorism is the directing.
That's what, terrorism against the state is basically the only logical outcome of the
things that he's saying.
If you believe the things that he's saying, there is no solution.
No.
You're fighting the fucking devil.
Yeah.
The devil doesn't care about courts, the devil doesn't care about elections.
No.
There's no making peace with the devil, he's the devil.
Right.
You have to eradicate him.
Yes.
And then the people who follow him, and surprise, all that's left is white people who you're
friends with.
I guess I'm not being totally fair, because the other conclusion I guess could be complete
isolation.
Like, you could have communes in the woods or something like that.
Or complete splinter society.
Trying to topple the state.
Those are the only two legitimate outcomes, because political organization is meaningless.
Right.
And like, okay, now the government is, it's outlaw, it's whatever, so any kind of rules
that come from the government are not to be followed, it's a crime against humanity to
wear a mask.
Why would you run for office?
You couldn't do shit.
What would you, yeah.
You'd get absorbed by the devil.
Totally.
I just, I was thinking about that because I was so bored by the beginning of this episode.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it just, it strikes me that anybody who takes this seriously, they just can't.
Or else they would be doing something horrible.
I'll pitch them on this, okay, they've already tried to topple the government and it didn't
go well.
True.
So try isolation.
Everybody in the right wing just needs to go away.
Well, I would recommend isolation with another individual for about an hour a week, chatting
about.
What do you think?
Life.
Just talking about your problems.
Yeah.
Yeah, get some.
Bounce it off another person.
Just.
See how it feels to say some things out loud.
Let it out.
Yeah.
I recommend that for everybody, actually.
Not a terrible idea.
Not just people on the right wing.
So, Alex, you know, the day before, he was mostly just lying about this study, and I'm
not going to lie, he does more of that.
But today, he seems to be in a different mood.
I would describe his mood as being very similar to a guy who went to family court the day
before.
Steel prices have tripled, corn has exploded, every commodity is exploding.
And that's why I said, get into a basket of commodities.
That's my advice to myself, if I was an investor.
And get invested in a place in the country, doesn't need to be fancy, but away from people
and know your neighbors, and have friends and family that are aware, and having your
own gang, your own people to watch each other's back, is the most valuable thing in this universe,
other than a relationship with Jesus Christ, the son of God.
And so you better get ready now.
I mean, look, I told you this a year ago, buy ammo, buy guns, they're going to steal
the election from Trump.
Then they're going to really clamp down.
They're going to start a race war as the cover for the economic collapse.
This is all a battle plan.
We know what they're going to do.
We should have been able to stop it.
Enough folks didn't listen.
Now people are listening, and I don't say that to act tough.
I don't say that to be impressive.
It's just, everybody needs to know what you've done keeping us on the air.
We have all the big so-called government intelligence agencies listening.
They're now just like the schedule, webs on a Labrador Retriever's feet, or it's like
a, like people that grow a sixth toe or something.
They don't have any power.
They're just puppets.
So corporations, the private groups, the big tech, it's got their own hit teams, their
own labs making deadly synthetic drugs.
I mean, just their own pedophile operations is giant industrial level evil.
Just chewing up humanity like a combine cuts wheat or bales grass into bales of hay.
As soon as we realize how much trouble we're in, we'll be able to turn this around.
But I told everybody this, so I'll do a plug right now because I sell and stay on air with
what I do myself.
And when I got the best storeable food company, we sell it directly from infowarsdoor.com.
They're full catalog.
You get 10% off, the lowest price already out there, but I can only run that until next
week, next Wednesday.
All right.
Sure.
Yeah.
Easter sale.
You got to head to the country.
Got to run away.
Absolutely.
And just incidentally.
By the way, I'll plug this now while we're here.
Look, it's a favor that I'm really, really, what do you think about it?
Honestly.
What do you think about it?
I am gifting you this plug.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's a blessing.
And so in order for you to repay that, you need to buy lots of food.
Wow.
You can get 2020 food prices now at preparewithalex.com or just find the subsection, storeablefood.com.
And I would buy a lot of food.
I'm buying more storeable food.
I'm buying more ammunition.
You said you have none.
I am selling my house in Austin.
Good.
Just had the realtor photographer over to get that done.
And I am telling you right now, ladies and gentlemen, that there's a 90% chance we're
going to go road warrior in this country for probably five, 10 years.
Sure.
And when this is all over, I would be surprised if 50 million, a hundred million people aren't
dead.
And you know, I've never talked like that in my 27 years on air.
I only think that a 90% chance it's all over.
Okay.
Yeah.
I've never talked like that.
I've never said anything like that.
Except for every time I was at court the day before.
I have never said anything like that roughly 7 billion people will be exterminated so that
only 500 million are left.
I've never said anything like that.
You know me.
I've never talked like that except for almost all the time.
I'm not really a doomsayer, you know, I'm not, that's not my thing.
I'm not the kind of guy who likes to scare you.
I like to play it close to the best.
Also boo.
Now you should be terrified of all the people coming to kill you.
Yes.
And sure they look nice and they say nice things and they're exactly like you and they're
just normal people, but they're actually working for the devil and you should murder them.
And road warrior.
For five to 10 years.
Road warrior in five to 10 years.
No, four or five to 10 years.
Oh yeah.
Oh that's right.
Yeah.
Yeah but you know, 50 to 100 million, that seems pretty good for a road warrior situation.
I mean road, that's a pretty severe situation.
Sure, but I feel like everybody was dead in road warrior, you're going through the wastes.
No, I'm kind of agreeing with you, that's kind of a bright side kind of thought.
Yeah, that's not bad.
I would, if that was the worst road warrior was going to get it, I feel like it could
be worse.
Fair enough.
So you know, it's the glass half empty, glass half full, Alex half empty, you half full.
I'm an optimist, everybody knows that.
So Alex sent this study that he found, that he was lying about all day yesterday, to a
guy who works at UT.
Who knows who this guy is?
Okay, just a guy.
And I just thought this was really silly.
I sent this to an individual I know that is high up in the board, let's just say, well
I gave way too much, didn't I, let's say heads up a department at the University of Texas
last night.
And when I, I know this person for a long time, and when I send them text messages,
they usually don't respond for like a week, but he responded back in about 20 minutes.
And I said, Hey, UT put out this big study under a federal government grant nine years
ago that, and I said, tell me what you think of it.
I didn't even say, they said it was bad, don't take COVID based vaccines.
This is 2012.
I just said, Hey, UT put out this interesting report on COVID type viruses nine years ago.
What do you think?
Hell, I'll show you the text, I won't show you the name.
Stop texting me.
He messaged me back like Timothy Slater, and he said, well, it's very technical, but obviously
I'm not taking the vaccine and this is a warning.
This is a warning.
This study was a warning.
How, what?
What?
Well, with global stuff to do all their dirty work out in public.
You know, I understand that, but I really, really don't give a shit about what anybody
on any board thinks.
I have a hard time with boards.
While also the guy saying that he's not going to get the vaccine, I'm not entirely sure
what all of his medical issues are, but Alex says that he's like, it's obviously someone
on the board at UT is probably not a younger person.
And also they had COVID already.
So their doctor had told them, this is what he reads from the text message.
Their doctor had told them that they already had a lot of antibodies naturally occurring
from having had COVID.
So the doctor had advised them not to get a shot, which is, I don't know.
I'm not a doctor.
So I don't know, but that's slightly different than don't get the shot, it'll kill you.
It's going to kill you.
You will, there are going to be pictures of holes in your brain.
It seems like there's a slightly different pieces of advice.
Could be a different angle.
Also the idea that this is a warning is just so dumb.
I love it.
So dumb.
It's a warning.
Oh, I'd like to warn Alex.
Um, no, you, you should know what you're talking about or else you sound really stupid.
That was a good warning.
That's titled immunization SARS coronavirus vaccine leads to pulmonary immunopathology
of challenge with the SARS virus.
Emu path.
The challenge is the group of rats that were given the vaccine versus those that aren't.
And they have autoimmune responses and their hearts and lungs roll up and they got bloody
holes in them.
Then they died of blood clots, which I'm sure you're hearing about in the news.
I feel like I'm flogging a dead horse or possibly a dead mouse here, but I am constantly hitting
this drum of Alex, not knowing anything about this study that he's reporting on, but he
just keeps being wrong in new ways.
He's wrong about the details of this study, but I think it's more disturbing that he doesn't
understand basic terminology that's used, which makes me think that he doesn't even
have a handle on the most elementary conversation that's going on in terms of this study as
well as any others that he might be trying to discuss.
Yeah, that sounds right.
Alex says that the term challenge refers to the group of mice that were vaccinated as
opposed to the ones that were not.
And that's not what that term means.
In the case of this study, there were groups of mice that were given various non-experimental
injections to serve as control groups.
For instance, one control group got actual live SARS, another just got the adjuvant.
The term challenge refers to taking all of the mice in the experimental and control groups
and challenging their immunity by exposing them to live SARS.
That's what this experiment did.
And it's critical to understand that concept, to understand this study at all, to any degree.
There are times when Alex is being really dumb and it's funny, but this instance is
almost getting embarrassing.
Like this is disqualifying, childish.
I think so far his descriptions just of like, here's what a study is, give me great concern.
It's like, and this is true with just about everybody who's like, I know science, just
describe how you do a study after, and this is supposed to be after he's read how they
did the study.
He poured over it, man.
Yeah.
So just tell me how a study works.
This is day two of his coverage.
Just give me a simple, like here's the beginning of the study and explain to me what you think
science does.
Well, it turns out, I mean, I don't, I didn't see this, but it turns out that this study
is actually evidence that giving the vaccine around, it's going to kill kids.
Sure.
These people are sick and now they're going to target the little children and mess them
up for life.
Oh man.
Wow.
I'm like, oh, suddenly all these kids have heart problems and have brain problems.
Well, there's some conspiracy theorists say it's connected to the vaccine.
No, the university of Texas says, don't do it.
It'll happen.
But you don't care that young rats and old rats got sick and died.
Because you're liberal.
You're saving the earth for yourselves.
Sure.
I don't not care because I'm liberal.
I don't care because I read the source.
Wow.
That would help.
Don't you remember the part where the source was like, oh my God, there are all these mice
bleeding out.
We got holes in their brains and then rats broke in and they ate the mice and now they're
exploding.
They're going to give it to children next.
How old are the rats?
There are no middle aged rats.
There are young rats and old rats in this circumstance.
That's a relief.
It is a relief.
We're all middle aged here.
It makes us more comfortable.
Yep.
So, at the end of last week, the world was reeling from the news that Bill and Melinda
Gates were getting a divorce and I didn't care.
Shoot them both into the sun.
I didn't care for Alex's thoughts on it or at least I thought I didn't and then it turns
out there's a massive conspiracy here.
Why would I have guessed otherwise?
Right.
Robert Barnes has shown up and Alex is now explaining to Barnes how this is all...
See, I feel like Alex should know how Family Court works pretty well.
Well...
I mean, why was Gates and them crazy enough to do this?
I think it's because he got busted with Epstein and they panicked as a diversion and they
had this plan, Operation Lockstep on the Shelf.
In fact, I know that's what happened.
His wife's now confirmed she's pissed that he was having sex with kids probably.
Okay.
A lot of words in there.
That was a lot.
She's basically confirmed probably.
So yeah, his theory...
How many adverbs are too many adverbs?
That many.
That many adverbs.
His theory is essentially that Bill Gates got caught up with Epstein and it was all
gonna come out and he's gonna take the fall for it now.
And so his wife got a divorce to protect the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation and she's
confirmed it probably, basically.
Basically.
Probably pretty much.
There was a story I saw in the Wall Street Journal that was about how Melinda Gates was
mad about Bill Gates having an association with Epstein.
Why?
And...
That was good acting.
You appeared actually surprised.
Thank you very much.
And some people have made comments about that, but I think that the bridge that Alex is crossing
is a little bit shaky.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, well, here's the bigger issues there.
She knows he was hanging out with Epstein and he went to the island.
It would be insane if she was not at least a little bit concerned about that.
So that's not really a story to me.
We all know that he spent time on Epstein's island.
We all think Bill Gates is an evil bastard.
Like it's fine.
You know?
I don't care why they're being divorced.
I just want them shot on a rocket into the sun, Dan.
Sure.
But you have to understand that the divorce is a critical part of COVID existing.
Ooh, no.
I was definitely not understanding that.
Because the divorce is protecting the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation now that Bill
Gates is about to go down.
But COVID was released because the Epstein connections were coming out in like 2019.
Sure.
And they fucking panicked.
They hit the button that said COVID.
Right.
The COVID button.
And then there was a worldwide plague in order for Bill Gates's...
Why is this the first I'm hearing of this particular aspect of the conspiracy considering,
as Alex has told us so many times, he knows exactly how this is all going to play out?
Well, I would suggest it's probably because this is improvisational storytelling and not
actual news or research.
Also possible.
Yeah.
It seems like a fun wrinkle for Bill Gates's character.
Yeah, why not?
Put it in there.
A good way to contextualize the divorce.
Right.
Right, right.
And that's kind of just the way Alex was feeling.
Yeah.
This is character development.
Gotcha.
So anyway, Barnes is in.
And also Alex calls him Barnes and I feel like don't fucking call your lawyer by their
last name.
That's just not cool.
No, no, no.
I want to give my lawyer a nickname.
I want to call my lawyer Dickie.
Hey, come on, Dickie.
Let's go.
We got lawsuits.
Come on, Dickie.
You are fucked if you are that familiar with your lawyer.
I want to call my lawyer Mr. Misses Something.
I want a deep professional distance between us.
I don't want to be like, what do you think of Barnes?
I do not want to text my lawyer with a question about something.
No, no, no.
I don't want to text my lawyer when I'm drunk.
Hey, Dickie, come out tonight.
Come on, buddy.
We're going drinking.
So Barnes has got some news.
Okay.
Robert Barnes is about to give you exclusive breaking information.
Here is the exclusive breaking information as humanity fights back.
Robert Barnes.
Yes, we're going to be filing suit over the next two weeks across the country against
three groups, governments, employers, and educational institutions that are attempting
to force or coerce people to have the vaccine.
So Barnes is going to go spread a bunch of attention grabbing lawsuits around, which
seems to be his specialty.
Yeah.
I just, I find it impossible to believe that you could listen to this entire show, hear
Alex say that the government is an outlaw, and then listen to Barnes say he's going to
file some lawsuits and be like, you get them.
Yeah, this is going to solve things.
This is an exclusive that I wanted to hear about.
And I can't wait to throw some money at Barnes to support these lawsuits.
We have to.
What if we're able to get an injunction against the devil?
Ooh, then we'll put his plan off for at least four more years.
Such comical nonsense, what he's asking the audience to accept and believe.
Yeah, yeah.
It's wild.
I don't, I don't think much of Barnes to go to the forest.
You have to go away, get ammo, get food, hide, prepare for the road warrior.
Now we've got an exclusive, sell some of that ammo and give you that money to Barnes.
We've got a couple of lawsuits going around.
Yeah.
Jesus, man.
I don't think much of Barnes and I wasn't like really all that worried about this lawsuit
going anywhere.
And then I heard this, I'm like, this is not going anywhere.
So working with Bobby Kennedy and others on all of the legal issues related to these cases
and the constitutional issues, we will have the suits filed within the next two weeks.
He's working with Robert Kennedy, the anti-vax kingpin.
Yeah, yeah.
This is not going to work out.
If you're Robert Kennedy Jr. and you don't get to call yourself Bobby.
No, I feel like Barnes was doing that to sort of cover up the stink of the name Robert Kennedy.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, absolutely.
He was not like, it's Robert Kennedy Jr.
He's like, Bobby Kennedy.
His ears perk up, they're like, did Sirhan Sirhan actually hide his, or what?
Yeah.
Another person I don't want to be on familiar terms with.
Robert Kennedy Jr.
Oh no, Robert Kennedy Jr., okay.
So I'm going to just skip ahead real quick because I want Barnes to explain his lawsuit.
We're suing under the ADA, the discrimination act that prohibits discrimination against
anyone who is perceived as disabled.
We're going to be doing the same thing actually in the context of the vaccines because my
view is that requiring someone to have a vaccine is a perception that they're disabled and
then treating them differently based on that perception is discriminating against them
based on your perception of their disability.
And that too is prohibited by the ADA and state analogous laws that are also similar.
So the fact that Barnes is working with Robert Kennedy and the idea that this is the keystone
of his argument combined to tell me this is not a case he expects to win.
I would very much like to be in court the day he says those exact words to a judge.
Just on its face, I suspect this would get thrown out, but there's a huge element of
disability law that Barnes seems to be pretending doesn't exist.
According to the government's page on disability discrimination, they do make a very important
caveat.
Quote, the law requires an employer to provide reasonable accommodation to an employee or
job applicant with a disability unless doing so would cause significant difficulty or expense
for the employer an undue hardship.
Even if somehow Barnes were able to convince a court that not wanting to get a vaccine
was legally analogous to having a disability, he would still have a really hard time overcoming
the argument that having people potentially spreading COVID around a workplace or school
doesn't represent an undue hardship on an employer or educational institution.
You run the risk of your workforce or teaching staff falling ill, and that's not even considering
the potential of having to shut down a factory or a possible bad press that could come from
being the site of a new outbreak.
Much like Nick Fuentes trying to sue the TSA, this is not a serious case.
This is a grift and a PR stunt disguised as a legitimate lawsuit.
It's all just grandstanding and attention seeking behavior, and it's wasting everyone's
fucking time.
Yeah.
Yep.
But I do also want to be in the courtroom.
Right.
Yeah, no, totally.
I do think it would be pretty funny.
I get-
Let's go to a courtroom.
No, absolutely not.
Like, I do get that lawyering is a profession and lawyers like to protect each other, and
you know, judges don't often hold lawyers in contempt of court for, say, I don't know,
going on Info Wars and saying that the stated reason that you're doing this lawsuit is based
on magical nonsense thinking that you don't understand whatsoever that you may- what are
you fucking talking about?
Yeah.
You know what I think the issue with Barnes is?
I think that he's less a lawyer and more a guy who has a page on Dave Rubin's Patreon
clone called Locals.
That sounds like it.
And I think he's promoting his Locals page with the looming idea of these lawsuits.
Great.
And I think that he's just trying to sucker people into supporting him on fake Patreon.
Wow.
And yeah.
How did that lawyer collective of constitutional lawyers work out?
Remember that one from a few years ago when he was going to start that group of people?
Oh, they changed the world.
Oh.
Well, that's good.
Yeah, I don't know if that happened.
Boy, it seems like-
It was a bad idea, so I'm actually kind of glad that it doesn't seem like it happened.
Yeah, but it seems like they tried to get a lot of money for it.
I wonder what happened to all that money.
Oh, well.
Would you like to know how the Chinese people made COVID?
You would?
That sounds more exciting.
They gotta change the subject over to- this clip is nonsense.
Okay.
So that's how this- there's a lot of ways to do it, I've read about it.
But one way the Chinese were doing it at Wuhan was, again, use a bunch of gene guns, firing
a bunch of viruses together until you finally go through an electron microscope and find
one that got the viruses together like you wanted, all meshed together.
Then you replicate that in the pig.
The pig dies of the virus, so you know it's deadly.
You grind it up raw, feed it to piglets.
Those that die again, you do it, then you extract the blood, then you take out the viruses
you want.
You have a growth of viruses, and you keep growing them, and then you release it into
the human population where it starts replicating, and then you have the answer to the disease
you created.
The idea that this just accidentally, at the time it came out, when Trump was defeating
China, and the world was waking up, and nationalism and free market was exploding, and we were
going back to who we were, like 1955 on steroids, but for everybody, they had to counter it,
and this is the globalist counter-offensive, and they admit they had plans like this on
the shelf before.
So my god, it's so obvious.
What?
It's so obvious.
What did he just say?
Look, Occam's razor tells me that's exactly what happened.
Did he just say it's so obvious?
It's so obvious.
Alright.
So obvious.
Should sci-fi come with a warning label, like, you know, warning, advisory, for people who
cannot tell the difference between reality and fantasy, this is really going to fuck
you up.
Yeah.
This is really going to screw you up, you're going to think shit like what Alex just said.
Do we need to have tests before you can read science fiction?
Maybe.
Do we need to have some sort of comprehension test where it's like, listen, it's like a
family video, you know?
Like they've got the room in the back with all the porn, you've got to be 18 to go into
that room.
Libraries should have that, but for sci-fi.
Well, I think that science fiction expands people's minds in such a way that, you know,
as a young boy reading like Ray Bradbury or something, you know, it hugely influenced
a lot of creativity that, you know, maybe would have laid dormant in me as a young boy.
And I think that that's the case for a lot of people.
And I think that the good outweighs the bad because I think the case of Alex is so extreme.
I'm not saying 18, I'm saying there should be a test, like whenever you can pass the
test.
I don't want to limit the excess of sci-fi to the young kids out there who could use
it.
Might be overkill.
As far as I know, there is only one person who has a relationship with sci-fi like Alex
Jones, and it's Alex.
I know, but we've got to stop him!
Granted, the consequences are severe.
They are very bad.
They're very severe.
They're very bad.
And he's created a false reality for a lot of people to live in, and it's very profitable.
But I don't think that, I don't think we need to regulate sci-fi.
Might be an overreaction.
Might be an overreaction, I understand that.
Look, spitballing.
It's blue sky thinking.
I'm just trying.
I'm trying to come up with reasons for this man who says that they're going to feed a
pig to another pig to get the first...
Yeah.
I do like the idea, though, that Alex explains all that, and he's like, it's so obvious.
And Barnes' reaction is, exactly.
Exactly!
What are you people in your brains?
This is what I'm talking about when you go back to 2003, and you have these guests that
are a little bit, at least like, on their own turf, or whatever.
They're not these boot-lickin'...
sycophantic nonsense people.
Not only that, Alex, but yes.
Of course!
It is too obvious!
You are totally right!
No, naturally!
So we gotta learn about a false flag.
Oh, sure, of course.
I think Barnes might be wrong.
You dig in deep, you find out the Klan was not an organic, authentic group.
The Klan would rise and fall depending on what the politicians in power supported them
or not.
They were weaponized tools of the establishment infrastructure local to the community.
They were not some organic group.
That's why, you know, people said the Klan made up of poor white people.
Totally false.
If it was poor white people, there would have been some rich white people hanging from trees.
There weren't.
Oh boy.
I don't even want Barnes to speak.
And now that he has, I regret it.
The Klan was a false flag, my friend.
That is, that is...
Yeah, it's a bummer.
Oh boy.
So also, he thinks not only that the Klan is a false flag, but that Antifa is, uh, they're
hypocrites.
If people want to look at Antifa, if Antifa was legitimately an anarchistic group, a group
that was opposed to capitalism, why have they never attacked the Federal Reserve?
But um...
There are, you know, first of all, it's not an actual group, but also like there are people
who associate with anti-fascism who are capitalist.
There are people who are anti-fascist leaning who are anarchist or believe that there is
a place for the state.
You know, like it's not, it's anti-fascism.
Here's not, I feel like he's missing that crucial aspect because I think it's, I think
it's intentional.
No, obviously it's intentional.
He's a lawyer.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, you can't be like, if Antifa wants to be an anarchist group without immediately
stopping and being like, does Antifa want to be an anarchist?
Did they name themselves...
Anarchy.
Anarchist group or anti-capitalists, Antica.
Like sure, we can do all of those things, but if you're describing it, it's called Antifa
for fascism.
You can be for capitalism and still against fascism, although one might argue that the
eventual road will always lead to fascism, but that's a conversation for a different
day.
And I feel like prior to becoming an out-and-out white nationalist as he is now, Stefan Molyneux,
the guy who Barnes is fine hanging out with, he was an anarcho-capitalist.
He did say that.
So.
Yeah.
Anyway.
Hey, how about this, how many Wall Streets have you fucking occupied, you dumb shit?
Why haven't they ever gone after the Fed?
Who do you think occupied goddamn Wall Street?
Well.
Sure.
But that was a false flag.
Oh, that's true.
Anyway.
My bad.
Barnes skedaddles out because he's got to prep that lawsuit.
Yeah, no, no.
He's working.
It's totally gonna work.
Overnight.
Yeah.
So Alex goes to calls and this caller, this little 10-second clip is perfect.
They're announcing the new booster shots are going to be patches with micro glass that
goes into your skin so they can track you.
Did you know that?
No, but I mean, I believe anything now and I just, I just.
Yes, you will.
Oh, oh no.
No, no, no.
Ma'am.
No.
Somebody save her.
That was a perfect moment.
Yeah.
Alex says something and she's like, I didn't know that, but I'll believe anything.
You will.
You will believe anything.
So you're listening to this bullshit.
Yeah.
Man, you could probably run and win office as a Republican if your slogan was just, you'll
believe any old shit I say.
I bet, oh God, I bet if you did something that would be like universally decried as
offensive and horrible.
Yeah.
Like just, I'm going to run for office, but I'm never going to wear a shirt.
You know, it's just like, yeah, I feel like we, most people wear shirts.
I'm not a shirt guy.
I just don't do shirts.
Come on.
I say it like it is shirtless.
If you're really confident about it, I bet you could win on a GOP ticket.
Probably.
Yeah.
Cause they just don't fucking care.
They don't, they just hate the left.
That's it.
I stick it to the libs, but I insist on every public appearance that I have.
I'm wearing a snake on my neck.
Listen, listen, here's what we got.
You want to stick it to the libs.
You go with me.
Shirt or no.
You want to not stick it to the libs, you vote for one of those other assholes over
there.
They're not going to stick it to the libs.
No, probably wearing a suit.
Look, look, no shirt, no shoes, no service.
No libs is what it is.
No shirt, no shoes, no libs.
Snake around my neck.
Vote for me.
So Alex, Alex has been having a good time on this, uh, this episode, but he kind of
fucked up.
He meant to play a bunch of videos of Antifa pretending to be cops.
Sure.
That sounds right.
Um, but wait, I'm sorry.
Antifa pretending to be cops.
He just hasn't gotten to it though.
And I really wanted to spend a half hour today on the Antifa videos of them acting like police
and attacking everybody and going crazy and I'll try to play a few of the clips, but I'll
just have to, I'll have to do it on the Sunday show.
But I said four hours of your calls with your stories and I've been doing a pretty good
job lately to get to these calls because they don't want this heard, they want this shutdown.
But again, they're, they're, they're collapsing the economy and they're going to use a race
war as the cover for the collapse and then blame that on the race war and the American
people.
So the banks don't get blamed.
That's the big one ties together with the COVID that's a drill for martial law.
But your calls actually are paramount above that.
If I have the energy, I'm actually pretty exhausted right now before our, if you take
about an hour off to do some, you know, research, I call that off, not talking for, I go back
on air, but maybe I'll pop in there in the warm today.
Wow.
So, I mean, I, you know, that's difficult to follow just as ideas, but I guess the only
thing I really take issue with is the idea that, well, there's a, you know, obviously
there's going to be a global collapse and there's a race war coming naturally in order
to make sure the bankers don't get blamed for that global class, but your calls are
more important naturally.
Absolutely.
I don't know if I were a caller, I would take issue with that.
I just don't even, I don't even know how to hear him.
He's just saying words.
Yeah.
That's exactly what I'm hearing.
I'm just hearing him say words like when he's, when you're following along with what he thinks
is supposed to happen, what he's certain is supposed to happen, everything he's doing
is insane.
It is an insane person.
Like that's what I'm saying.
Is this real or fake?
It doesn't matter if he believes this stuff, he's crazy.
And if he doesn't believe this stuff, he's maybe more insane.
Yeah.
Cause this is...
Ahhh!
Yeah.
So Alex does end up playing some videos of Antifa acting like cops.
I think.
I'm not sure.
I didn't watch the video.
I was just listening to the audio and this is a surreal thing if you are just listening
to the audio because you can't see what's on the video and he doesn't say like, he doesn't
narrate the video at all.
Instead he just kind of mumbles about violence and it's very upsetting.
They're like pretending and larping, they're like a SWAT team stopping a bank robber, but
they're not.
They're just beating people up and attacking people.
I mean, I just, I couldn't be a cop and be around these people.
I mean, it's just, it's just incredible.
And then they go, don't attack us while they attack you.
The left is just trash.
And I'm sorry, man.
I love that with the metal baton, they start attacking them.
We're going to slit your throat, all this stuff.
Huh?
I mean, it's just who they are, man.
They love it.
I see.
I can't get around that.
I'd go, I'd go King Kong on those people.
I mean, I'm telling you it'd be bad, man.
Are you sure you don't want to fight a lawsuit?
I got a real problem.
You want to punch my buttons, be five or six people standing there and kick my ass.
That punches the buttons, man.
That the bunch of overwhelming group of people.
That's when the big can of crazy man gets released and that's when people start getting
hurt really bad.
I mean, I even looking at it, I just, oh my God, I mean, those people would have their
noses torn off, their heads bashed in, and then, uh, you know, some hat, somebody by
one of them stabbed me from behind.
I don't even care because I just destroy each person and one at a time only takes about
five seconds.
You actually get ahold of anybody can do this.
Anybody can kill really what people have governors.
I don't have one.
Whoa.
Okay.
Oh, this has gone in a direction.
Yeah.
That's not good.
Hey Alex, did you go to family court yesterday?
Uh, well I do need to reestablish my male dominance, otherwise I won't have any self
esteem whatsoever.
And the only way I know how to express that is through fantasies of violence, which makes
me a healthy person as everybody else.
And assuring my audience that it's easy to kill people.
Yeah, that's what it is.
That's cause I'm a man, you know, I don't have a governor.
God, I would, I would not like to see this kind of conversation on any program, like
any program that's trying to be political or talk about issues, mumbling about murdering
people is just, oof.
Well, whoever, I mean, what lawyer was it that made it so that they couldn't show clips
of his show?
Barnes.
Yeah.
Was it Barnes?
No, no, no.
Cause, cause whoever did that, man, imagine just going to family court and just being
like, Hey, after we went to family court last time, I'm going to play this clip of Alex
on his show.
It's very easy to kill.
I do not have a governor.
Yes.
Most people think it's hard to kill.
That's just cause they won't let themselves.
I on the other hand, have an ease with murder.
Your honor, could we please keep this man as far away from us as possible?
Yes, of course.
So Alex says something about murder that I actually kind of think is, I mean, it's not
news.
By the way, anybody can do this.
Anybody can kill really easy.
People have governors.
I don't have one.
And five, six people sort of follow me, even though I'm 47, I just young.
I just want to, I want to tear them to pieces.
And I know a lot of you have that in you too.
And the left doesn't get that that whole veneer is starting to peel away, ladies and gentlemen.
So I don't have a governor.
No, I think we know that.
And we have known that for a long time.
We're very well aware of it.
Yes.
That's kind of been the whole thing about you and your types, Alex, is that you very
clearly want to kill us.
Yeah.
And we won't stop talking about it.
In just, just amazing how in a very short period of time, you can say the left is just
trash.
They're just evil.
They're just like this.
Now, obviously I could kill and I want to, and I have no governor.
And I know you do too.
And you could kill.
And it's much easier than you think.
But that's the problem.
That's the problem, Dan.
The left is trash.
Yeah.
Now, obviously I have no governor or a moral system and I'm willing to kill.
Despite being a Christian, I am ready and willing to kill with no governor.
I have no governor.
And the left thinks that they're all safe, but the veneer of our politeness and non-murdering
is starting to slip.
Hey buddy, it slipped a while ago.
Yeah.
You remember when you stormed the god damn Capitol?
Or the Unite the Right rally or any of the...
All the murders you guys do?
Oh yeah, there were those too.
There's all the fucking murders.
The time Stuart Rhodes talks.
Yeah.
That fucking psycho.
Jesus.
Anyway, we have one last clip here because Alex takes a call and I just want to play
this because I think it's unhinged.
One, I was going to see if you could hold a call-in prayer session show, like a segment
hour for on Sunday or Sunday night or something like that.
I think that's really smart.
Or beyond that, people tell their testimony and talk about God and talk about how we need
God.
In fact, I don't think that's just an hour of a show.
I'll do the next Sunday or a special show next week dedicated to God.
You're right.
All right.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Because on October 12th, 2016, you prayed for Trump to win and I prayed right along
with you.
And I think that granted the prayer, but...
Yeah.
I think our prayers got Trump elected and look, this is just like, this is great.
If I were Alex, I would be so pumped about something like this because it's like, okay,
the audience is starting to suggest that I become a televangelist.
Yeah.
If I can make this transition work...
All I gotta do is just push a little bit through.
Yes.
If I can have a proof of concept where I start doing shows that are entirely pure religious
nonsense and I can make that profitable, I can stop this whole bullshit.
I can stop doing things that are going to get me sued all the time.
I just want to scream at these people.
I don't...
Why...
I wish I didn't have any...
Governor?
No.
Biblical education.
Oh.
I just...
It drives me insane.
It was hammered into me so much, so fucking much, now that the idea of these people saying,
oh, we're so fucking Christian and the left is evil and immoral and shit.
Read your goddamn Bible.
Do you imagine?
It's in there.
Can you imagine how Jesus would feel?
If you made money off of praying to him.
No.
He's going to...
He's going to do an hour long show just about prayer for you, and then he's going to plug
in the goddamn middle of it.
In the middle of your prayer.
And you're going to tell me.
You're going to tell me you're Christian.
You fucking pieces of shit.
Please smite the global.
God damn it.
I hate these fucking people.
Please smite my enemies.
Amen.
Also, God, I should tell you it's 25% off.
I know.
On bodies.
It's unreal.
Unreal.
It is just, it is just sitting there.
And I see...
Yeah.
I think, I think it would introduce a difficulty for me in terms of like, if his show went
full televangelist, I think I'd have to keep...
Having me here?
No.
I think I'd have to keep doing it.
Right?
I have to keep following the show.
Sure.
But at the same time...
I mean, it's a new, it's a new frontier for us.
Yeah.
And to be clear, I don't think that necessarily that's where he's going.
Although I do think it would be a smart decision.
Probably.
Which is why whenever there's sort of indications of an instinct to go that way, it's like,
well, you should take that offer, Ant-Man.
Probably smart.
Yep.
If you can survive these cases that you're in the middle of now and get to televangelism,
you're golden.
God, yeah.
Jim Bakker's been scamming for decades.
Decades!
He went to fucking prison.
He's not even trying.
No.
He stopped trying after he went to prison and just smoothly walked back into it.
He has a compound.
In the Ozarks.
Everything you talk about.
And no one talks about it.
Everything you talk about, like I want to move into the middle of nowhere.
Just do it, Jim Bakker.
He sells survival food.
He owns people who live in his compound.
That's real.
He can tell them what to do whenever he wants.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
That's the hammock.
That's the retirement that all shitheads like Alex should dream of.
Yeah.
Anyway, I thought this was fun.
If only because this study was just a travesty of Alex just being unable to even deal with
any kind of source material.
No, that wasn't even redacted.
That was lit on fire before he even had the chance to read it.
Yeah.
It made me think very frequently.
All right, shut up, Jones.
Quite a few times.
Nicely done.
Thanks.
Well done.
Nice bookend.
We came full circle.
There was a narrative through line and you closed it out strong.
And I came up with Spouse Mouse.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah.
In a stroke of genius.
Oh, God.
It was a good day.
I am never going to top Spouse Mouse.
You'll top Spouse Mouse.
I'll try.
Dan, Spouse Mouse is not that good.
I might be tired.
Anyway, Jordan, we'll be back for another episode soon.
But until then, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yes.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's adagotabedjordan.com.
Knowledge underscore fight.
We are on Facebook.
If you could please find a local charity or a bail fund in your area.
Also check for a new episode of our role playing.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
Middle of the week.
Yes.
We will be putting that out middle of the week.
Should have another exciting installment of Dutch Wildfang and Friends.
Let's hope so.
That's what I'm calling it from now on.
Dutch Wildfang and Friends.
I thought God's Damn Wizard was a terrible title.
No, I know.
It's a play on God damn.
I assume there's a wizard we're going to run into eventually.
Yeah.
So enjoy that.
Look for that.
Indeed.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX.
Clark, I'm Daryl Rundis.
And now here comes the sex robots.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.