N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Damn, Ed, Jordan, I am SWEATING
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledgefight
knowledgefight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying we are the bad guys
Dan and Jordan
knowledgefight
I need, I need money
Andy and Kansas
Stop it
Andy and K-Andy and Kansas
It's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan
I love your work
knowledgefight
knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight
I'm Dan, I'm Jordan
We're a couple dudes, like to sit around, worship at the altar of Selene and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are Dan
This is the second time we've had to record the intro because something happened and it wasn't recording
And in that we riffed about how I'm not a one take guy, now this is the second take of our intro
So here we go, and it was better on the second go round
I'm not sure it was, I think it was a little smoother on the first take
You know, you were a little in your head on the second take because you were disappointed that the first take was so good
And you wrote down in your notebook, not a one take
Well, that's my fault, it was too good a joke
It was
It was too good
I had to cut you off at the pass
Yeah, well you know what my bright spot is
Uh, this?
You got it
Dan, quick question
What's up?
What's your bright spot, buddy?
My bright spot today, Jordan, is that I made a return visit to the much-legended
Ballyhooed
No, I don't know if anyone's Ballyhooed, but it is the stuff of legend the witch store here in Chicago
Agreed
Um, I went there, they have crystal balls and books and probably tarot cards and
For sure
Uh, sage that you can burn to like purify places and what have you
But they also have a large selection of bath salts
Uh huh
And I have gotten
Bath salts that grant wishes
That is true, that is true
Yes
Um, I have a bag that has, uh, it promises psychic powers and I have not used it yet
Because I'm afraid to
Does it describe them?
No
It doesn't, what?
No, no
I need more, I need specifics
If you're gonna give me psychic powers, that can backfire so easily
That's why I haven't used them yet
It's too risky
Too much power
Uh huh
No one man should have all that power
I've seen a number of these movies about telepathy that end up because it's such a,
Such a nuisance hearing everyone's thoughts
Yeah, totally, you think it's a good idea
It's one of those classic monkey's paw type situations, you know
Be careful what you wish for and I will never wish for psychic powers
Yeah, so that's, that's on, uh, on my, near my bathtub
As a, in case of emergency, break glass
Right, right, right
Get some psychic powers
But yeah, for now
They're at the gates, get the psychic bath salts, quick, get Dan in the bathtub now
For now it's just tranquility and peace
I like that, that's a good spell
So how about you?
Uh, for me, Dan, uh, the French Open
Coming, coming up soon, coming up soon
Rafa in a bunch of, uh, he's at the, uh, playing on clay right now
Getting, uh, uh, uh, ready to go for his, uh, inevitable next French Open win
And today he fought a really tough, uh, match with, uh, Shapovalov
Who is also one of my favorite players
Okay
He's a Canadian kid, gangles, uh, in the present tense
Like he's gangling at you
Okay
Uh, incredible tennis player, though
Fantastic match, won it in the tie break
Rafa, it's just great, it was a great morning
Very exciting
It was a great morning
That was at three this morning, I bet?
That was at, that was at six this morning, thank you very much
Well, I'm glad you, glad you got to enjoy that
Yes, I did
So, Jordan, today we have, uh, well, I was gonna say it's interesting
But we have an episode to go off on
See, now that's what I want
Yeah
That's what I want from late night shows
I've been, I've been broken
Ladies and gentlemen, tonight we've still got to do a show
It's Thursday, I don't know what to tell you
It's in the contract
No, that's not fair
It's, there's some fun stuff in here
But there's, there's another thing that I'm just becoming endlessly, um,
What's, what, ground down by
Ah, yes
I will say
Yes
So this is May 11th, 2021, Blackjack
Blackjack, oh, I wasn't even close on that one
No
No, that was brutal
So, the thing that I'm getting ground down by is that, um, thing that we've already talked
about, that sort of dynamic, this show is incredibly one-note
It's all anti-vax nonsense
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Um, and when Alex comes through with something exciting like one of these primary source
documents that's, like, actually, oh, this is kind of an interesting thing to look into
There's things we can learn here
Sure
Middle-aged mice come up
Fantastic
Spouse mouse
What fun we can have there
Totally
Other times, Alex just, he's got nothing
Sure
And sometimes that nothing comes in the form of a bombshell
And I'm sick and fucking tired of non-existent bombshells
Have we heard anything about Polygon yet?
No
I'm sick of the, like, the biggest news in the world being nothing and just, like, that,
it burns out something in your brain
Yeah
You know, where you're just, like, hearing somebody be so fake excited about something
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Something, I don't know, I'm gonna be in the past for the next episode
You're being gaslit
You're being gaslit in a way that is exhausting
You can only be gaslit so long before it starts to break your psyche
At the same time, I have no expectation that I should be believing Alex
Sure
So that helps a little bit
It does
It makes it less painful, but the process is still there and it's frustrating
You're not completely inculcated from that kind of result
Yeah, and so today's bombshell was just, like, I'm out, I'm gonna be out for a while, so
Today's bombshell
Yeah
Okay
I'm selling this episode real well
So, Jordan, before we get into this, though, let's take a little moment and say hello
to some wonks
Ooh, that's a great idea
So, first, I can't wait to see LeVar Burton host Jeopardy in July
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, I agree with you on all fronts
I bet LeVar Burton's a policy wonk, too
That'd be nice
Honkinatrix, practitioner of clown-like bondage, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Thank you
Next, The Foxiest Chicken, Emily, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, The Foxiest Chicken, Emily
Thank you
Next, Frank Rizzo, Jerky, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, Frank Rizzo, Jerky
And, uh, I don't want to say this, oh well
Don't whisper it into my ear and I'll say it
I'm not going to do that
Okay, fair enough
I'll just bite the bullet on this
The Return of Poop Feast 420, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, I'm looking forward to the third installment, that's going to be my favorite
Revenge of Poop Feast 420
Yes, absolutely
And then I'd like to say thank you to technocrat out there, David S.
Thank you so much, you are now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
Crikey, mate, that's fantastic, have yourself a brew
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business
We ain't making that money off that heroin
Why you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large
I declare info war on you
Thank you, David
Yes, thank you very much, David
Also, I don't know how to do this exactly sometimes, you know, like
Yeah
Well wishes for birthdays
Sure, sure, sure
Sometimes it's kind of difficult for me because
You do it at the bottom of a well, naturally
That's where I throw my pennies
For everyone's birthday, I should say, everybody who we wish a happy birthday to,
I do throw a penny into a well
That's really nice of you
That's nice of you
I should do that, I just, you know, I don't walk by enough wells
Yeah, there's so many in my neighborhood
I know, it's true
I'm not always sure whenever someone's birthday is on the weekend
Whether we should do this on the Friday show or on the Monday show, what do you do?
That's fair
Do you do it after the fact or do you wish them a happy birthday a couple days early?
It's like Saint Patrick's Day, when do you celebrate it?
When is it observed?
When is it, yeah
I never quite know, but I'm gonna go ahead and go ahead of the game on this one
On the 16th, this weekend coming up, Cameron's got a 30th birthday
And Nicole would like to wish him a happy birthday
Well congratulations, Cameron
Yep, happy birthday, hope you have a great one
And hope doing this in advance was better than like if you'd heard this on Monday
I've been like, wow, that would have made my birthday a lot better if I'd fucking heard it earlier
Yeah, but what if this is so important to him that now
the rest of his actual birthday is just gonna be a huge letdown
Everybody's gonna be like, happy birthday
And he's gonna be like, my birthday was when the Knowledge Fight guys said happy birthday for way too long
This is the risk we take
So Jordan, there's one bit of news that's been going around that I want to address
Doesn't come up on this episode, but it is something that happened
at the beginning of this week, and that is that Alex is back in the gold game, my man
InfoWarsGold.com
Alright, it's about time
Yeah, I've been seeing indications that he was getting ready to start this back up again
But I wasn't sure if he was ever gonna take the plunge
And then a large portion of the show on Monday was an interview with his new gold sponsor
A guy named Drew Mason from St. Joseph Partners
A precious metals outfit out of Pauley, Pennsylvania
I didn't know too much about this guy or his business
outside of the fact that he decided to get into business with Alex Jones in 2021
So I can't say much about what's going on with him, but I know he's not cool
I cannot give this gold away
I'm gonna have to partner with Alex Jones
So I did find it interesting
I was looking into it a little bit
And there's no physical address for St. Joseph's Partner available on their website
That struck me as a little bit curious
It's just an asshole with a chest buried in his backyard
Well, the contact information is literally just an email address
Yeah, exactly
It's an asshole with a chest buried in his backyard
But here's where things get weird
Okay
So if you click on their contact us page
An image of a Google map pops up
With a marker at the address 8 The Green Dover, Delaware 19901
However
That's a tax shelter
Delaware is a tax shelter state
If you Google St. Joseph Partners, you get a different address
1776 Lancaster Avenue, Powley, Pennsylvania
This is the address for Powley Plaza, which is a strip mall of shops
It doesn't look like there's a real, like, brick and mortar location for this gold out there
Sure, sure, sure
There is a Reed as Italian ice
I think they specifically may have chosen 1776 as a...
No, I don't think so
I think it's a coincidence
Oh, okay
Powley is a city with a population of, like, just over 3,500
So why would they have a shop there?
It's ridiculous
Right
It's a UPS drop box
That's what it is
Yeah, of course it is
Yeah
So as you astutely already realized, Delaware is a tax haven type of state
Yeah, yeah, yeah
And 8 The Green
Thanks, Biden
8 The Green in Dover is a pretty notorious address
It's the location that's used by a company known as a registered agent incorporated
which allows people to incorporate their business in Delaware
Right
Which a lot of folks do to avoid
Avoid taxes
But it's actually not that...
It's not all about taxes
So LegalZoom has a breakdown of the advantages and disadvantages of incorporating in Delaware
And one of the perks is when you file in Delaware, you don't need to disclose your
directors' and officers' names to the state, which allows you anonymity
Oh, that's way better than not paying taxes
I bet people would pay extra taxes for that option
This became an issue a few years back, as was covered in the Delaware News Journal when
the SEC was trying to investigate whether a number of Delaware-based LLCs had engaged in fraud
235 companies were at issue, 24 of them were based in Colorado, while the rest were in Delaware
And most of the businesses in Delaware were run through a registered agent incorporated
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Anyway, none of this proves anything that's explicit wrongdoing, but it's a bit sketchy
I would say that the only way Alex could come up with a gold dealer I'd be less inclined
to do business with than Ted Anderson is if it was a guy who had no apparent physical
address whose site appears to be explicitly saying that he got a phony incorporation in Delaware
Yeah
I would steer clear of this, and if anybody out there is actually interested in investing
in precious metals, I have to assume that there is a safer and better option
So many other options that aren't just a weird dude with a UPS dropbox
Yeah, it's...
There's at least three other options
There's renting a boat and going under the water for sunken treasure
That's a way better option
Yeah
Then of course there is globetrotting and stealing ancient artifacts from Egypt and the like
Sure
That's always a good option
And then I guess the securities market?
Alchemy
Oh, alchemy
You forgot alchemy
Shit, I forgot four
Yeah
Yep
You're right
There's always four ways to learn
You got it
So yeah, I don't know, I'm not too excited about this endeavor
I think it looks really sketchy as hell
And it's just another instance of Alex having like landing pages with other people's shit
Right
Because it's like, okay, so yeah, infowarsgold.com
But that just takes you to St. Joseph Partners slash Infowars
It's just taking a cut
It's just an affiliate tracking league
Yeah, basically
Yeah
So we get to May 11th here, starting it off, Tuesday's show
Okay
Alex has big news
Does he?
Ladies and gentlemen, it is Tuesday, May 11th, the year is 2021
And this is undoubtedly the most important news we've ever broken today
I stayed up here late last night but got too exhausted to finish the report
It'll be done in a few hours and I was so pleasantly surprised
when I got home and turned on Tucker Carlson to have dinner with my family
that he stumped us
Gross
Yeah, I know, that was an upsetting image
Gross, gross
But even past that, I love the idea that it's like, I have the biggest news of my career
and I got sleepy last night
I was just too tired
Honestly, you know, around 11 o'clock the Xanax kicks in and I'm just out
I'm in a life and death battle with the devil
Sure, sure
And I have the silver bullet that will defeat the devil
Right
Yeah, I mean, I think that's one of the devil's big advantages
He never seems to get tired
He casts sleepy spells on people
Well, that's nice, that's nice
So I was curious about this big news
and actually I decided that this would be the day that I've covered
because he's got the biggest news ever
Of course
We already had the biggest news ever like twice this week
Right
And so I was like, wow, I mean, this has got to be big
Here's the headline, Tucker Carlson, Anthony Fauci let the coronavirus pandemic happen
Well, they did it on purpose
Why isn't there a criminal investigation?
Well, we have the smoking gun where the director for Bill Gates and for Fauci
admitted to creating the five in one super virus on video
So the video that Alex is referring to is an episode of a podcast called This Week in Virology
produced by the American Society for Microbiology
Sure
The guest is Peter Daszak, the president of EcoHealth Alliance
Alex claims that he's a director for Bill Gates
but this clip that's from the actual interview seems a little bit at odds with that
Do you have support from say Gates Foundation?
No, we don't, we never got Gates money
I think that Gates, Gates have a strategy of specifically targeting things
that they consider neglected, diseases that were neglected
We're working on what they consider not neglected diseases
So I guess he got no funding from Gates
Yeah, that would make sense
Anyway, big mess up there on the giant news of the day right out of the gate
Yeah, that's not a good start
So this is a really interesting interview that Peter Daszak had
but it's being completely misused by Alex
to paint the picture of a guy confessing to created SARS-CoV-2
In reality, the EcoHealth Alliance is a nonprofit that works on global health issues
from the perspective of what Peter calls One Health
This is a philosophy that every condition has a human component,
an animal component, and an environmental component
Trying to approach any condition without considering the intersection of these three
is not going to be as full of a strategy as taking the full picture into mind
Right
The EcoHealth Alliance grew out of a conservation organization
and part of their ethos is a belief that you can make pragmatic
and economically sound arguments for ecological conservation
For instance, in the interview, Peter brings up the unexamined health costs of deforestation
that massively outweigh the profits that are made from the practice
Right
If it can be made clear to everyone, the decision makers,
that not only is destruction of nature bad,
but it's also not even in the best interests of profit,
these people believe that they can make headway towards conservation action
Right
I watched the whole 35-minute interview and essentially what it comes down to
is that Peter discusses working with labs in many countries, including China,
where they do surveillance of animal populations
to try to identify any diseases that could become a problem for humans
Sure
One of the concerns he brings up is coronaviruses
and he discusses how you can manipulate coronaviruses in a lab pretty easily
Alex is taking that statement to be a confession
that Peter combined a bunch of viruses together
and then unleashed them as SARS coronavirus 2
But the reality is really different
It's really just about crafting lab tests that assess
whether or not newly discovered viruses can even infect humans
Yeah
If I were Peter Daschik, I would immediately sue Alex Jones
Totally
There's a video with a picture of him with the title, quote,
Smoking gun video Fauci project manager confesses to creating COVID-19
That's a definitive claim
That is definitive
That Alex is reporting
Defamatory
It's outrageous
And I can't imagine, like, how unsafe this is to do to somebody
Yeah, no, no
And I don't know, like, exactly what the line is for, like, public figure
But I'm not sure that I would put the president of eco-health non-profit
as a public figure in the same way that, like, a celebrity or someone
At the same time, I guess an argument could be made
that he's become somebody who goes around on some news programs
talking about COVID
Because of assholes like Alex
Alex forced him into becoming a public figure by giving him the attention
that he should never have had in the first place
if anybody responsibly treated this fucking pandemic
No, I think even without some of that, he would have been seen as somebody
who would be gone to for interviews on, like, in the early days of the outbreak
Sure
I think he still would have made some media rounds
But again, what I'm saying is I'm not sure exactly where that line is
Yeah
I'm not sure what side he's on, but I would be, I would be
Let's find out, I would like to find out
I would like to fuck around and find out, quite literally
I think it would be worth discovering
because you can't just do this to people
It's outrageous
No, I saw a little bit of that Tucker thing and I just began spitting
Like, the idea of him doing that after being the cause of us all being locked down
for a fucking year
That's grounds for immediate slapping
If you see him, you get to slap Tucker Carlson in the face
The Tucker piece was largely based on that article that Nicholas Wade wrote
And even that doesn't claim to have a conclusion
The second or third paragraph of it is, I have no direct evidence for either theory
Yeah
Whether it's a lab origin or natural origin
And it's being used by people like Tucker to push the, it must have been made in a lab
Yeah
Now, Alex's version is far more irresponsible than what Tucker's doing
Oh, totally, totally
Which is, which is normal, but
Anyway, Alex got scooped by Tucker
Now, I told you at the end of the war yesterday
that the biggest news yet was coming out, but I would break it today
Tucker Carlson broke it last night and he gave you about 80% of it
But the clip he didn't play, and we're going to get to that after we play the Tucker Carlson
Report, a part of it, is that the director of the program under Fauci and Gates
On record funded by them, four million bucks for just six programs
They funded some others as well at the Wuhan lab
Gave an interview and admitted they were splicing five viruses together
As a bio weapon to then produce a, quote, vaccine for it
And that they got emergency authorization to do it
This is game over for these people, ladies and gentlemen
If the public ever grasped this
It's game over
Yep
Sure
A lot of stuff being made up in that clip
Yikes
So Alex plays Tucker clips for most, like a lot of the first hour
That's, that's a good job
And I don't make a big enough deal out of this, but like he plays a lot of the first hour
A lot of Tucker Carlson clips
That's great
It's a lot of, like in place of special reports sometimes
You'll just have a Tucker segment
That's awesome
I love it
I love not having to do my job, and that is a perfect encapsulation of
I will just let a famous person fill in time
That's great
And it'll deeply associate myself with him
Totally
Yeah, it's
Brilliant, brilliant marketing strategy
Anyway, I found this to be a little funny
Here's Tucker Carlson and we'll come back with the rest of the story
You're never taking off the mask
Get ready for a lifetime of filthy wet cotton covering your mouth
Reduced oxygen flow to your brain
And a world where every stranger looks the same because no one has a face
When Kamala Harris and her husband kissed the other day while wearing masks
They were giving you a preview of your daughter's wedding
In a masked world, human beings never really touch each other
You whiny fucking babies, you whiny babies
I don't watch Tucker Carlson that much, so I don't know if this is like indicative of his style
That is, whoa, holy shit
He's got some very dramatic writers employed on that staff
That is your daughter's wedding
You're gonna watch your daughter and her husband kiss with masks on
Okay, instead of sign language, there should just be a picture-in-picture of a guy making the jerk-off motion
Just like, listen to this fucking asshole
What a dick
Ugh
And I mean like, what was it, just like the next day the CDC released guidance that if you're vaccinated you don't have to wear masks
No, that's, it should be criminal
It should be criminal to be Tucker Carlson
It should be criminal
You can slap, if you see him in the streets, you slap him in the face
This is a dangerous precedent to set
You're right, you're right
Gotta walk that back
Okay, there's only, then we will only set this precedent for one person
I'm not sure I can sign off on that, but the point is, you're never gonna be taking the mask off
Smashcock, two hours later
The next day, Jesus Christ
Great, cool
Anyway, Alex has the biggest news ever
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm Alex Jones, your host
We're breaking the biggest news we have ever brought out on air
It is incredible what's happening
The lab manager for the COVID-19 gain-of-function research being done at Chapel Hill
had it moved with the scientists at Wuhan and then admits on video to merging five viruses together
to be able to then deploy them
See, I was listening to this and it didn't match with the interview that I had watched
Yeah
It didn't seem at all accurate
He's on video saying five different viruses were combined
Play that clip
What a bombshell, he confesses to it
So I was really confused
Like I said, it didn't seem like it was what I had watched
So I went and I watched Alex's special report about this
I was trying to figure out what was going on
Right, right, right
And that helped make it a little clear
Daschick was talking about how some of the coronaviruses they discovered didn't have
known treatments, and the interviewer, the person giving the interview, asks a follow-up
question about that
Daschick then discusses how if you're going to create a vaccine for something like SARS
because so much of it involves the spike protein, you probably want to create a vaccine that
was effective against multiple coronaviruses
Sure
He was just discussing it in terms of like that is that seems like something people would
do if they were going to go that route
Have you ever
That is not at all as him saying, I've used viruses
I've fused viruses together
Alex might as well just scream like, we kill one bird, one stone, no more!
He's like, Alex is pretending this guy's like, I stitched together viruses with a needle and thread
Exactly, yeah, yeah, yeah
He's got some magical sci-fi technology where it's spinning around with, yeah, it's stupid
Now, it should be incredibly clear and very strongly pointed to that Alex is talking about
this with the premeditated intention of hurting people, with the idea of shutting down the
economy, the idea of killing people in the developing world, and he's saying that this
guy is admitting to doing that by way of creating the virus SARS-CoV-2
Yes
And I think he should be sued for that
Yeah, he did just call the man responsible for what would essentially be mass scale murder
So I would hope that that would be in some way defamatory
It feels like it's real playing with fire
Especially considering everything we know about Alex's audience
Yeah
Anyway, I was like, wow, okay, this is not a bombshell
But it feels like Alex is going to talk about this quite a bit
A lot
Uh, then he said this and I was like, what?
Now, I have Alfie Oakes on about the pipeline shutdown, the food shortages
He's one of the biggest producers of food in Florida, if not the biggest
He doesn't just own grocery stores
His real business is growing food
And I wanted to get his expert take on the inflation we're seeing and where that's going
So Alfie Oakes is the guy who owns that grocery store that Alex went to in Florida for a week
a while back
Is he a former oil pipeline expert?
I don't care
No, he's not, but I don't care what he has to say either
However, it should be noted that he's only relevant in any way because he's made a big
deal out of how no one has to wear masks in his grocery store
In a completely unrelated story, I would like to inform you that Ted Nugent tested positive
for COVID just one week after doing an in-store appearance at Oakes grocery store seed to table
Prior to this, Oakes had appeared on Ted Nugent's YouTube show called The Spirit Campfire
and said, quote, no one is getting infected here, no one's dying
I want to get the truth out, it's a fraud, it's a sham
And people have to wake up
Anyway, fuck these people
Oh my god
God, I'm starting to think that believing that witches are responsible for your problems
is a recipe for getting COVID
So Alex has this idea that no one else is posting this Tucker Carlson segment
and so he's going to put it up on his website, but just because no one else is posting it
not because he's trying to poach content or anything
We're going to have the whole thing posted to the Band.video
so in case they try to take it down
and the full Tucker Carlson 14-minute dialogue has also been posted
because Fox isn't posting that on YouTube
They always post this full show, they always post clips, they're not doing it
So in the interest of public interest, I'm posting it to Band.video
for commentary and analysis and historic reference
Historic reference
That's a free copyright
I'm not canceling Alfie Oakes, I already did it yesterday
and I'm not canceling Ted Nugent, they're here and it all ties together
but after they're gone in an hour and five minutes from now
I am going to, you see this stack right here?
This is all the documents he's talking about and the videos of total open and shut case
There isn't a grand jury in America
If I had a day to show them this and the clips would not indict Fauci
and indict Peter Daszak and all these people
That'd be really funny to see Alex trying to prosecute a grand jury
Yeah, you know this, Alex doesn't have his heart in this
It doesn't feel like it
I think he didn't actually read the story
because I get a sense at a lot of points that he doesn't really have a handle on the details
of things and he can't really weaponize the story correctly
He's treading water a whole lot
and that's one of the things that I find incredibly frustrating
Like this video, this podcast interview was months old
It's maybe a year old
Of course
I think it was from March 2020, I believe
and if you go and look at it on YouTube months back
people are commenting on it like, oh my God, the smoking gun
of, you know, so it's something that's been in that space for a while
Alex has no rush to report this
It's just that Tucker brought it up the night before
So Alex needs to make a bombshell out of it without actually knowing the story at all
And so he just kind of rushes to air and it's stupid
I just, I find myself just incredibly uninspired
And at the same time, I think it's incredibly funny that Ted Nugent probably got COVID
by going to this guy's grocery store
and they're both guests on the show today
Yeah
That's weird
Yeah, that's, I don't even know how to deal with that
Honestly, in like a real universe where you believe in reality
like where you accept reality as a thing
I can't be in the headspace of somebody who thinks any of what happened is okay
It's funny, but it's not great
No, no
It's not the kind of funny I'm looking for
No
And this is why I'm going to be in the past for a little bit
No, it's, I'm going to scream, I told you so funny
Yeah
So anyway, Fauci, that guy, Tony Fauci
who Alex actually looked into like at the beginning of the pandemic
and he's an all-star, he's a legend
and Dr. Steve Pacanik said that he's one of the best who's ever existed
One of the best there's ever been
But then all that went away really fast
Hey, wow, that's because he's evil
Anyway, he's got to be executed
Well, I'm going to tell you Fauci and Gates and all of them
are going to be lucky if they just spend all that rest of their lives in prison
after we have Nuremberg trials
A lot of them
If justice is done through the courts
I'm not calling for outside the courts of vigilante stuff
but I believe they should be tried for treason and biological warfare
under the Nuremberg code
And I believe just like Nazi scientists, they should be executed
Oh, I thought you meant hired to work for us
I stand for justice against these criminals
And we'll see who wins in the end of this
But I know this, I'm with God
And that's what really matters
God watches over our battlefields, over our lives, over our children
and over our destiny
And I put my hands into Jesus Christ's hands
I put my soul into Christ's orbit
And I commit myself to God
All right, I got to go to break
We got Alfie Oakes coming on
One of the biggest food producers on the East Coast
to tell you what's really going on
with the giant food price increases that are already here and coming
Don't forget, you have until tomorrow night at midnight
that it's got to end to get last year's prices on high quality, affordable food
ready to ship to you within days
They ship it out the next day
That's convenient
It's May
Yeah
You're going to have another chance to get last year's prices today
I think so, yeah
December, you'll have a chance to get last year's prices
You're going to be all right
It's not going to be it
The Easter sale is going to be going in December
Yeah
So yeah, I just, I found that to be like, just, right?
This is how it goes
Yeah
Intense, violent fantasies towards his enemies
Blah, blah, blah, I love God
Food guy's coming on to scare you, I sell food
Yeah
It's cookie cutter, cut and paste
That is really, really lazy
It's just really lazy
It is
And we all have our bad days, but for Infowars, this is just unacceptable
And it's such a stark contrast between the bad day that surrounded the middle-aged mice
Because at least that's funny as hell
Yeah
That's lazy, that's bad, but there's a funniness to it
There's an energy to it
This is a 35-minute podcast interview with a guy from a year ago
Yeah
That is interesting, but Alex doesn't have a handle on it and can't really do much with it
It's just, I don't know
And your guests are a grocery store guy and a
A perv
A perv, a former, yeah
Fuck both of these guys
So there's other news in the world though
Sure
Of course, that pipeline
Naturally
Yes
Mm-hmm
Yeah
I heard this clip and my response to it was, okay, Alex, fine
Then you've got the Keystone XL Pipeline that was opening a few months ago
It got closed to bring in all the oil from Canada and around the Midwest down to Houston
To be refined and then sent up the Colonial Pipeline to the East Coast
So Biden shut that down
They say some shadowy hacker group did it
They say they want to post-industrial America
He said he would kill fossil fuels
I believe the main suspect is Biden now blaming Russia
That's just where the historical evidence is
And, you know, if he already shut down our main other pipeline
Well, why wouldn't he shut down the other?
I have made up that Biden is the prime suspect in the Colonial Pipeline
And now I'm reporting it as the most likely possibility
Interesting
Yeah
Interesting if true
Historical analysis
If true, that would be
That's a way bigger bombshell than anything else
Bombshell President Hacks' Own Pipeline
That's a bombshell
That'd be crazy
Right there
Yeah, and also I can't help but, like, now that I know that Alex, you know, back in the past
Would say that his prediction of 9-11 was based on historical analysis
Sure, sure
And research
And then it turns out it was just a dream
Bill Cooper said that
But he also just had a dream
Well, it was a good dream
I can't help but hear him say stuff is based on, like, research and analysis
And be like, you're probably lying and you probably had a dream
Yeah, you watched the net the night before and then transposed Biden's face onto Sandra Bullock
Which is a nightmare, I agree
You fell asleep watching Tucker and now you had a little bit of the Nyquil and you're fucked up
Man, I still can't get my head around the idea that the whole family, like,
gathers around a dinner table and they have Tucker Carlson on
I bet they don't
Of course they don't
That would be a, that's the worst thing I can think of
Yeah, I bet they don't do that
I bet Alex sits alone and eats dinner watching Tucker Carlson
Yeah, I imagine Alex spends a lot of time alone watching Tucker Carlson
Gotta take notes
So Alfie Oakes is on and it's mostly just about fear, spreading fear about food and stuff
Sure
But you also should know that if you want to take that seriously
You should know what else Alfie believes
We know that Biden, the Biden White House agenda is lockstep with every single thing that these
globalists want to do to ruin our country, to have their takeover
We're the last beacon and I do feel, with all this doom that we see
I do feel very confident that we're going to get the country back this time
It's not going to be easy, it's not going to be as fast as everybody wants
But our American spirit is still there
I feel firmly that there was 80 million people that voted for Trump
And somewhere in the 61 million that voted for Biden
And the majority of Americans even in the national polls do not agree
70% of Republicans, 31% of Democrats in the numbers higher know it was a fraud
Stay there, let's talk about solutions
Yeah, so Trump actually won in 2020 and we're going to get the country back?
Huh
So does he seem like a really credible source, the kind of guy you want to hang out with?
What is it about white man and undeserved confidence?
Where does it come from, Dan?
He says looking into a mirror
I don't know if this confidence that Alfie's got is undeserved
Because I think he's a sleuth
That's possible?
I think he's a sleuth
And I base that on this next clip where he lays out a conspiracy that is almost certainly true
He can probably not come close to proving it
And he might also tip his hand a little bit too much at the end of this one
Will he give me a discount on eggs?
Maybe
Okay
These companies like Monsanto in particular owned by Bayer
Think about this and this scam has been going on for a long time
And it used to be maybe thought of as a conspiracy theory
But we're watching it play out
Used to be
We disrupted like putting real fertilizer in the ground
Like real organic fertilizer
They're putting this chemical MPK that Bayer will sell these farmers
Universities are telling them it's okay to use
Then because it's not nutrient rich
It grows an inferior product and most of it's GMO stuff
So then that product grows
We put it in our bodies
Our bodies are starving to death
We fill up our guts with stuff
But we're starving because the food that we're eating is not nutrient rich
And then guess what?
We get ill
And guess what company is selling you the pharmaceutical drugs
That supposedly make you better
It's Bayer
It's the same company
So it's a vicious cycle
And it's really
I don't know if they were that genius to create it
Or if they've just been
Let it go along the way
But this
Oh we actually have documents where they give us the illnesses to then give us the treatments
Exactly
It's 100% what's happening
And this is why
I'm not saying it because I have local farms and we grow the stuff the right way
But go out there and support your local farms
Oh it's good that you're not saying that because you run competing business interests
Well
Because I might have been worried that
There's that
Look I'm no fan of Monsanto
No I think we've all
I think that's the only thing that unites all Americans except for the ones who work high up in
Monsanto is that I think everybody's gotten high and yelled about Monsanto to each other at one point or another
Yeah I think that some of the practices that they have are disreputable and I'm not a fan
But I don't think it's sensible to speculate that they are making everyone sick
So Bayer can sell prescriptions
Or whatever
And then for Alex to say we have the documents that they get us in order to sell us cures
But I mean you don't need
That's so not specific
You don't need any conspiracy theories because a business trying to monopolize food is bad
Yeah
Before you go any their entire existence is now based around trying to control food
And everybody needs food
Yeah the idea I think ever of making terminal seeds you know that don't
That that's just so fucking evil I'm like real downright
I'm not
God damn
I'm not sure what you do to legislate it but any company that would be interested in doing that
I find to be abhorrent
Yeah
And I understand why the profit motivation would lead you to that idea
Yeah no of course
But it's it's no good
Yeah no absolutely
So anyway I don't like Alfie much I think that conspiracy that he's got is really stupid
But he did contribute to one thing I can get behind and that is probably giving Ted Nugent COVID
That is good that is good
Uh so
Not all heroes wear capes dad
Well Ted Nugent's back and better than ever
Damn it
He's fine
Shit
But he still rambles a lot
Okay
So right now as I face you Alex I couldn't be healthier
I couldn't be more cocked locked and ready to rock the glock around the cock Mr. Spock
And I killed two black pup with my bow and arrow
I'm literally tooth picking my teeth right now in an in an immeasurable joyous celebration of medicine
It sounds like he always sounds like he's on coke but talks all the time about how sober he is
Yeah I know
It's really frustrating
That's so annoying
So anyway a lot of this
I hate him so much
A lot of this appearance on uh the show is about how excited Ted Nugent is that people celebrated
him getting COVID because because it validates him because all these bad people are against him
And I would say that it's just because he's been a dick for a really long time and no one likes him
Yeah
Yeah but some of my other musician friends from around the country got hit real hard
Now you never heard those stories
Yes you did
And no devils wrote journalistic hate hoping that my friends and other bands die
They weren't shitty
For the Chinese virus but they did that about me
Because you're shitty
I know you love me I feel the love I celebrate the love
But do you realize as as bad of a mofo as I think I am
I couldn't possibly be as wonderful of a human being to deserve the hate from the Satanists
That they've trended a global article celebrating my sickness and suffering
Is proof that they're scared to death of me and it makes me so happy and so strong
Oh man that's cute
No no one is scared to death of you we were all just kind of hoping you'd finally go away
I do think that there's something probably unhealthy about people being happy about or
laughing at or celebrating when some tragedy befalls someone who is an asshole
Sure sure
But I would be an idiot to not think that the reason is because Ted Nugent's a fucking idiot
Yeah
Alright he's a fucking asshole
It's not because anybody's afraid of him or his ideas
He's ready to rock around the clock like Spock or whatever the fuck cares
Yeah this is all your fault it's all his fault personally like that's that's the thing it's
it's not necessarily schadenfreude so much as it is when somebody spends so long telling you that
this thing isn't even fucking real and all of this shit everybody's celebrating because fucking now
do you get it do you get it now and they won't and they won't so that's why the only thing you
have left to do is be like well I guess I just hope he dies or goes away
You laugh you know you laugh at Ted Nugent getting COVID after going to a
COVID is a hoax grocery store and having a whole long period of time where you're yelling about
oh you know it's not that bad it's all wow in the same way that like you laugh when Ted Nugent
bans guns at his concert right you know it's the same yeah kind of like oh that's interesting
no it's a it's a physical real world example of the you know me reaping versus me sewing meme
you know like that kind of thing so now Ted Nugent has an interesting metaphor here that
I was very confused by I want to see if you can make sense of this okay well I consider myself a
Schindler and my list of Jews that I'm saving is growing so quickly and so voluminously and they're
all white brown shirts hate everything I stand for now that's some metaphor that I think the Alex
Jones viewers will understand but some people will completely miss my point is that I have
dedicated myself to being in the asset column to be productive so I I do think he's right that some
people will get that metaphor confused because even when he's trying to explain it he's just
he's explaining it that he's put himself in the asset column of life he's productive yeah that's
what he's talking about and the way he's explaining that is he's Oscar Schindler right saving Jews
who's on he what does he mean does he have a physical list of people that he's acting like
Schindler about or is it just that the brown shirts don't like him well I mean based on what
he's describing like being productive yeah in the asset column yeah the only way that that really
helps other people is by example I guess sure so I don't know I don't understand this no I don't
understand that metaphor I don't think it's offensive I don't see him actively saving anyone
and I see him stealing the valor of an actual hero in order to prop himself up and boost his
ego and confidence yep it was offensive yeah very offensive so uh there's a solution to the problems
in the world and of course it's guns but there's another solution uh that Ted Nugent has it's more
Alex's ah what do we do when the country's awake uh but they've stolen the election and are really
trying to start a civil war well Alex number one uh we need more Alex Jones that are willing to
put their literally their lives on the line spotlighting the cockroaches that have metastasized
into every orifice every every element of America the media our government uh Hollywood uh academia
it's literally at their best moment they're marxists more often than not they're literally
rock solid in this in the Satan column if you look what they're doing that the economy it's
all artificial we're selling pork bellies and orange futures that there are no groves of orange
to represent and the pigs won't have enough babies to produce the pork bellies that they're selling
I mean I'm just the entire player but I understand economics 101 but the most important thing is to
support the Alex Jones to watch Tucker Carlson and look at the evidence and share it with our
dumb friends and our dumb family members with all due respect I don't have any dumb family members
and I don't have any wrong friends but I see them wearing masks on their motorcycle so I know there's
some really dumb people out there that have turned into walking breathing mouth breathing zombies
so there's something that I that stuck out to me when I was hearing that and it's just he's angry
yeah he's really really really angry he's trying to come off with this laughing like I'm just a
guitar player but yeah but he's fucking so mad there is there is an effect of rage underneath
everything that he's saying that is really unsettling yeah yeah he's a he's a real psycho
yeah it's a real psychopath kind of thing to do it feels it it feels scary let's call John Ronson
and uh see what he has to say about the psychopath test for I just love I just love to go from one
clip where he describes himself as Schindler and then to the next clip where he describes his
political enemies the same way the Nazis described the Jews boy it's not glaring it sure seems like
a strange thing for someone like Schindler to do yeah awkward yeah weird awkward is not the word
I would use almost like all Nazis now want to describe themselves as the Jews despite the fact
that they are still trying to exterminate them weird great so um they have uh Alex and uh Ted
they have uh some commonalities uh some less complimentary than others um one of them that
is a little bit maybe neutral is an interest in the outdoors and hunting sure um and so Alex
believes that the most effective way to convert liberals over to their side is to go hunting and
then Ted Nugent says something that I find a problem getting back to hunting I found with
leftists and liberals I've taken a lot of Hollywood people out over the years my judge and I did a few
times in Texas they convert to shooting and hunting instantly and and don't know why they
were taught to hate it so I found the most successful way to convert leftists is if you
can get them hunting or fishing there's no question about I've had such a success with
that from the rock and roll world that I'm in where they've been brainwashed that somehow
animals have rights in between the barbecue the brain dead propaganda mushy goofness that exists
out there but to the man and the woman and mostly the Ted Nugent camp for kids children we baptized
tens of thousands of people who were animal rights inclined because of the propaganda
and then they realize you want grass-fed natural organic renewable ultimate healthy protein it's
called venison I don't know if he actually has a camp for kids but if he does I'm gonna guess
he's not all that hands on that should be illegal that should be illegal but I think that just from
from like a you know umbrellaing out from that clip sure he believes that animals don't have
rights yeah no he absolutely believes that anything that is an animal is subject to man's
domain over earth he's a dominionist I think that there's there's an interesting argument to be had
that animals have more rights than we ascribe to them right I think because they have less agency
I am not fully conversant on some of the arguments in favor of vegetarianism or veganism from
ethical perspective sure but I think that there are some interesting uh things that can be
discussed along those lines right and and I just look at it as like I live with a cat Selene is
like a friend to me yeah and I believe that she has many rights now if I were Ted Nugent
I should only be mad if you killed Selene because she was my property right the only thing there is
a property right that's been violated as opposed to something really fucked up you've taken the
like life of this this uh this companion animal what that also means though is that you have the
right to kill Ted Nugent if he attacks Selene in any way because property rights are sacrosanct
yeah it is it is strange too to imagine the way he would distinguish between humans and animals
in terms of where do rights begin yeah um I think that's really troubling I I think I think you
could go too far with it maybe I would say that if you think animals have no rights you are probably
of the opinion that uh many people are also animals who don't have rights or cockroaches
exactly so uh I would uh I would not enjoy anybody who's like no rights that's not good
and I think typically it's best to to err on the side of uh being more sensitive sensitive to uh
ascribing rights to to animals I mean they can't communicate but they're clearly having a like a
conscious experience absolutely there's no way that you can have not figured out that animals
have personalities by now it's it's pretty pretty messed up yeah Ted yeah Ted anyway again there
should be a restraining order keeping him away from any children if somebody writes his songs
that's an immediate restraining order away from children I'm choosing to believe that that was
a metaphorical flourish like rock around the clock with a sock on my head sure sure glock
bock bock yeah that's a chicken doesn't have rights that's true anyway uh Alex gets uh Ted
out of there and uh it's because he's got the biggest news in the world to break which I mean
he's had a bit of time to do that already decided to talk to Alfie Oakes and Ted Nugent oh my god
ladies and gentlemen I'm about to break the most important news in my 27 years on air
Reagan breaks union strike absolutely incredible and if this information does
not bring the criminals to justice if it does not reverse the operations that they've launched
then things are going to get a lot darker a lot quicker let me give you a summation before I go
through the evidence so when Alex says something like if this doesn't bring down the globalist
things are going to get dark fast it's essentially him saying I can't make up anything more
sensational or antagonizing than this like the next step from this is me telling you to kill
people yeah I can't make it more clear I already know this is impotent so you guys better
glean my actual meaning from this because I'm making it very obvious yeah so anyway you get
to the big news emergency alert Fauci project manager confesses to creating COVID-19
Tucker Carlson began to break this last night I told you on the war room we'd be breaking it today
he broke it that's great but he didn't get to the last part where he admits the project manager
because legally they couldn't get to that last five get the five viruses that they combined them
for a vaccine but to make the vaccine you got to make the pathogen of something that never existed
that no one would ever make yeah I think Tucker didn't cover that because it's not in the interview
yeah so this next clip I thought was really funny because he's talking about Tucker's segment about
this yeah and while he's talking Alex is kind of being a little wishy-washy about whether or not
Tucker segments being censored sure and I think it is this like all right I'm posting a 15-minute
long video that's clearly owned by another media organization yeah I better come up with a good
reason why that's okay something and now Tucker Carlson has come out the 14-minute report last
night that they're not posting the YouTube so we posted the Bandaw video and exposed this
so we posted the Bandaw video and exposed this the censored Tucker Carlson report Anthony Fauci
let the coronavirus pandemic happen why isn't there a criminal investigation that's the Fox
news headline and Fox has the report but it's not on YouTube there it is censored see the
Tucker Carlson Wuhan lab report Fox News won't let you see and that's the crew's great I didn't
give him a headline this I did say the headline this morning I actually said say see the censored
report see the censored Tucker Carlson Anthony Fauci so just change the headline please to
censored and then this headline overhead shot please this headline right here this headline
Tucker Carlson Anthony Fauci let the coronavirus pandemic happen why isn't there a criminal
investigation okay this is the censored report in the sub headline you explain that Fox isn't
posting this online they may have changed that since I went live oh well maybe okay maybe they
posted it okay okay all right all right get at it again jerk off motion in the picture in picture
a hundred percent Jesus so Alex ends up talking a little bit about this story about the
interview on the This Week in Virology it's just this is tragic so here it is
Peter Daska president of EcoHealth Alliance starting in 14 with project lead on six NIH
projects would focus on the emergence of novel zoonetic coronaviruses COVID with bad origins
some of the project's work was performed at the Wuhan Institute of Virology now we're going to
show you him saying that it's an hour-long interview oh Alex is just stumbling over
everything yeah it's not an hour-long interview it's a 35-minute interview it's not good just
everything is is just it's even by the rules of rounding up you're going to 40 it feels like a
guy trying to climb a rock but it's just covered in slime or something yeah it's just not working
no it is very much like he doesn't understand at all what he's talking about and so they're just
like we don't have much else on the show today clearly all we could get is fucking Alfie and a
disgusting Ted Nugent so fuck it let's air tucker stuff and I'll just kind of riff through it
yeah and like really oversell it yeah so he talks a little bit more about some details and it's
again not accurate the six project received a total funding of three million seven hundred
forty eight thousand seven hundred fifteen dollars from the National Institute of Allergy
and Infectious Disease that's what Fauci is the head of and we've got all the grants and all that
all the grants and all that right here so Alex is reading some information here but he doesn't
really understand any of it the amount that he's talking about that three million plus dollars
that's the amount of grant funding that EcoHealth Alliance has received since 2014 from the NIAID
for a project that was meant to assess the risk of bat coronaviruses spurred on by the SARS and
MERS outbreaks and the need to prepare right right right right one of the findings that this research
that was funded by this grant arrived at was they found a number of bat-borne SARS-like coronaviruses
and interestingly they also found quote serological evidence of human exposure among people living
nearby this is something that tends in the direction of the natural origin theory for SARS
coronavirus 2 people who are researching naturally occurring coronaviruses had found a number of them
and discovered evidence of previous spillover of viruses that had previously gone unnoticed if the
particular virus had been different in any of those cases or something had gone slightly
differently people had interacted differently any of those instances could have been the start
of an outbreak yeah Alex's main piece of evidence he's presenting here these these grants and this
study it actually makes me think the opposite of what his conclusion is I'm I'm blown away
like this is this goes back to that hospital this goes back to the COVID payments from Medicare
where it's like they get 16 grand like I'm blown away that you think you can make me worried about
a conspiracy theory where it's like it cost the globalists and the devil three million to kill
everyone on earth if that's how much it costs to kill us why do I have to deal with all these
fucking billionaires they don't need that money they could kill me with a few million yeah nothing
yeah yeah it's I don't know it it's that it's that part of your brain that just doesn't quite
you know three million dollars is a whole lot of money it seems like an insane amount of like I
would I will never see three million dollars but yeah that's nothing in terms of a research grant
that was over the course of 2014 to seven years yeah it's not that it's not that much in terms of
what research actually costs yeah absolutely I mean for a business if you want to say if you
want to say that a conspiracy theory about this is a huge deal over seven years a business would
probably be disappointed with revenues if they were only at that amount Alex would be disappointed
Alex would be furious with revenues if he didn't get a three million in five years in seven years
or whatever yeah so anyway I just found myself incredibly uninspired by this conspiracy but I
was inspired by this which we've heard before but I got to thinking about it a little more
I was talking to Dave Mustaine one time I'm not name dropping he said I want you to help me write
a new album with songs like Four Horsemen I wrote and I just looked at him right along my car here
in Austin I said dude this is a very surreal day we just had dinner with Willie Nelson
and I said I said I think that's up to you to write that album and he did write that album
so I what a great story that was that was a great story that was on par with I was walking down on
uh New York City Avenue and I saw Ben Affleck and I was like hey Ben and he was like hey
Dave Mustaine was really drunk around me one time exactly it's the same story that sucks yeah I
kind of disappointed because I it sounds kind of like Alex is trying to claim that Dave Mustaine
wanted him to help so so respects Alex as a songwriter but he wants him to help write
songs that would be on the album right that had Four Horsemen on it and that was Kill Em All
by Metallica which came out in 1983 when Alex was nine yeah I wish I wish that was what he
was actually claiming yeah but it's like no I want you to help me write songs that are like that
let's get a burrito yeah I can't imagine I can't imagine anybody turning and looking at Alex sober
and being like hey I want you in an enclosed space with me uh writing songs together Alex
Alex you're basically the Jim Steinman of your generation I need you to bring this song to life
come on get uh get Taylor Swift's producers out here get those Swedes get the Matrix yeah get
them going where's the dream would you need them for Alex's next album so I I think we've been
talking a little bit uh along the way through this episode that it just feels like Alex doesn't have
anything to grab on to no just it it feels really in terms of the conspiracy here's two and a half
minutes of Alex saying nothing okay basically just kind of dancing around but he doesn't know
anything to to latch on to terrible this is hands down the biggest crop of awakening the the the
biggest hall of truth the biggest wound to the globalists the biggest opportunity to deal a
death blow to these people politically to their agenda to kill their agenda and I mean the domino
starts falling you're gonna have Nuremberg trials I mean there's gonna be people getting hung sure
because that's what happens when you launch a bio attack is you get marched up there and they pull
a switch and a trap door opens up and you fall about you're a fan of Assad that's what happens
and your legs start kicking you take a dump down the side of your leg what I don't like death I
don't like killing people I don't like starting to fight with these murderers but they started
to fight with us and and I'm just telling you like I said in the first hour that we don't
want any violence against Fauci or Bill Gates or the New World Order from vigilantes you want to
take our governments and our countries back and we want to have them indicted with all the evidence
and we want to see them up on Nuremberg too and that's what last weekend I had the weekend before
last I had Dr. Francis Boyle on and he laid all that as well then the punishment for what they've
done is death and so I don't say that to be dramatic I don't say that to stick my head in
the mouth of a lion these guys are hyenas but still they can what stop it because I will not be
a coward coward and I want to thank God for your prayers listeners and I want to thank God for
God taking action this is devastating devastating devastating
there's no way to describe how much trouble they're in and I can tell you this they're
never going to get out of this now one way or another this is a political death blow to what
these guys did they're megalomaniacs though they were mad at Trump they were mad at Bolsonaro
they were mad at Boris Johnson who's a follower but thought he was winning Brexit and could do
what he wanted they launched this to bankrupt the small economy to bankrupt the hard-working people
to let the global banks and big box stores take over with big tech and they had it cooked up and
they had it ready and they did it in China so they could release it so they had plausible
deniability and so it was an attack on humanity none of that has anything to do with any of the
bombshell stories nothing just rambling and ranting about nothing yeah assuming the conclusion
has already been made it's it's it's time filler it's nothing yeah that's brutal yeah that's brutal
also if Alex says megalomaniac if he calls somebody a megalomaniac and doesn't say it takes
one to no one then it's disqualified it doesn't count if you do say it takes one to no one maybe
i'll listen to you because you are number absolutely one of them yeah but i think i think
what's going on generally speaking is that alex doesn't have a good handle on this story he knows
a few details he's already spent those um so you spend a bunch of time rambling about uh you know
like Fauci will hang and uh oh we've all proven it it's all this great sure because i think what's
really interesting to the audience isn't it really the nitty-gritty details or anything like that
it's an emotional experience yeah and alex is giving them an emotional experience and that is
the this is the end that we have details are bad whenever but we've won there's no way they're
going to get out of this one it doesn't sound like the duke boys they're in trouble i don't know the
duke boys tended to get out of them not the globalists oh that's fair this is a big deal
and i'm here to tell you that i have never felt so much fulfillment and i wouldn't call it
satisfaction this is a horrible thing we're in a global war the globalists are at war with
humanity this is a terrible thing happening but i've been around 47 years and i have never
never felt so much satisfaction in my life except maybe a few times where i was getting my ass
absolutely beat uh and i dug down deep and turned on the turned on the ben grim power and you know
broke that guy's jaw and saw his head at the ground and i wasn't happy i'd hurt him bad but
i was happy that i'd won the fight it was just a it's a feeling of just satisfaction that you just
you did it and you reached down and you turned it on ed risking my life you risking your life
everything we've done together man the satisfaction right now because i can tell
you they're not going to survive this and everything they've done to all these people
these millions they've killed all the people they starved to death with the lockdowns they're gonna
get retribution they're gonna be avenged so alex is basically like on this tip where he's like the
nuremberg trials will start in june yeah like you might as well be like planning them and getting
like a twitch stream ready for the nuremberg trials yeah this really does seem like uh
army building that's supposed to no it's not it's it's given the good news of the the victory
we have won yeah the globalists are done now that this video from a year ago has been talked about
that doesn't sound true to me no it doesn't no that's the emotional experience that alex is
wishing to create and convey because he's got nothing else yeah he's got nothing else and this
news doesn't really lend itself all that well to like uh be very scared yeah it is interesting the
oh the like there is a ratio between emotional manipulation and actual details for right-wing
people because they you can't just give them information that that that doesn't work you
have to have emotional manipulation and you can't let information get in the way of that emotional
manipulation but you also can't have nothing like this is nothing it's a lot of nothing yeah nothing
you know it's it's uh it was infuriating to listen to in the in the sense that it was
um kind of like i would describe it as being like eating a cinnamon twist from taco bell
but without any of the flavor i was about to say empty calories no taste yeah it was exactly
cinnamon sugar on it but it's that same you get you got the texture of what you were supposed to
eat but there's nothing to it it's just mush yeah yeah and and as somebody who you know really does
get excited when there's uh middle-aged mice studies to look into of course uh whenever there's
something like the spars document to look into totally i find this to be a little bit unsatisfying
and i take it personally yeah i i resent it yeah yeah i don't think that alex's quarterly uh
job evaluation is going to go well just just from my perspective having uh information about how
uh the boss feels uh which is springsteen of course q3 is gonna be rough it's gonna be terrible
he's gonna have to get his numbers up if you want a sense of how real a piece of news is to alex
i think one of the things you should take uh stock of is how much of the time of the
show is actually spent talking about that bombshell yeah yeah is this such a bombshell
that you don't go away and talk to alvie oaks and ted nugent forever yeah is this such a bombshell
that you don't uh i don't know spend the end of your show just talking about nothing and then
cover this for a little while i want to play a short clip from the war room not
owen schroyer three to six p.m but steve bannon's war room and i know steve bannon
and roger stone have had their fights uh i i don't want to be in a fight with anybody
i've had my issues with bannon but he's obviously a smart guy but he and his
host co-host made a statement about alex jones people used to think was crazy
but now he's improving right well that that's how it is when you're ahead of your time but
it's not about me being ahead of my time it's about people realizing that we don't make this
stuff up we really tirelessly research and we have a wide spectrum understanding of the world we're
not specialist generalist in that we really study how the globalists operate and we know how they
do things so we know how to counter them and and we know how to beat them everything should be
about the globalist because they're the ones in control of civilization taking us to a very bad
place and so that's what i'm getting at here but it is good to see it trend yesterday alex jones
trended on twitter again that alex jones was right and uh you can just type in my name or you can do
it all over many other places sure sure so so a little bit of alex jones uh media attention gets
some get some coverage here i i just feel like he's such an insecure dick yeah like it's it's
so sad like uh how many times has have we heard him talk about hating steve bannon he's a fucking
worm the worst he's the devil he's part he's gone to the globalist he's part of their team
he was so pissed off when steve bannon named his show war room it was an attack on info
force trying to take away all their hey but look he's a smart guy because he said something nice
about me and let's spend 10 minutes on my show talking about how someone said something about me
what an asshole not hard today alex isn't a bad guy well i wish i hadn't screamed that everybody
should kill him uh it turns out that you know he said i wasn't a bad guy so yeah he's a pretty
cool dude he gets it he gets it have you ever seen uh uh bill mar's basically secret tucker
have you ever have you ever seen like a a breaking news story uh or a bombshell report
and then all the news organizations who normally have like live blogs and there's constant media
coverage just kind of stop and they're like can we just ramble around a little bit we just got
to have a little fun you know this bombshell story is fine but you know i'm just gonna talk
a little shit with my buddy over here right wolf blitzer guy derails the show situation room
for a while because someone tweeted about it yeah so brian stelter is just all of a sudden like
hey guys you know uh i met willie nelson one time yeah yeah we went out for dinner one night
uh you know he's like hey you pretty good songwriter yeah brian stelter is like oh one
time i was hanging out with uh uh jumbo wumba and they wanted me to write an album
oh boy yeah and even just like let's let's think of it even closer analog imagine brian stelter
taking time to yell about alex jones's appearance totally totally so look at how big
look at how big fat alex's neck is isn't that great isn't this great content that everybody
tuned in to see yeah so uh i feel like the job has not been done and alex doubles down on not doing
his job all right folks um i meant to take calls today i did and paul watson's coming up i got a
lot to hit before the show's over in 22 minutes or before my part of the broadcast is over
but let me do this because it's so powerful i aired it during a little no man's land first five
of the second hour but this is really an important report he's playing a special report for the second
time in this show he's replaying a special report that that's how little he cares about the story
that he's covering this is this is kind of amazing yeah this is a complete abdication of any even
pretense of work yeah yeah yeah to me to me every indication is like i don't know enough to
competently even riff on this yeah yeah yeah uh but i do want to cover it because tucker
covered it last night and i'll be way behind if i wait until tomorrow this is the bullshit that you
get from a shitty boss where he's always any mistake you make like perhaps not being able
to figure out how the phone system works for 20 years he's always screaming at you but then
whenever he comes to work with this bullshit you don't get to yell back at him that he's wasting
everybody's fucking time somebody should drive like a button where they get to scream hey screw
you you suck at this job i think that's what our podcast is oh that's fair so we don't have a
button though alex uh spent some more time uh talking about the pipeline hack and uh i want
to remind you that he's always right his gut is very strong this is not gonna sound good this
ain't hard oh i'd give it about a 95 chance the globalist did the pipeline shutdown
five percent chance somebody got pissed they shut down keystone inside and it's doing that to show
everybody the dependence on pipelines 95 it's globalist five percent chance that i'm wrong
it was done by people pissed off uh with the keystone being shut down to show people how
dependent we are but see that's in a logical world you do that and then maybe we'll understand but
no there's no logic here yeah so wait what 95 chance globalist false flag five percent chance
false flag carried out by people trying to remind us that pipelines are important okay so it's an
educational false flag so if i understand correctly there's a zero percent chance it
was hackers the logical in a logical world yes naturally somebody on the inside would be furious
about people shutting down the keystone pipeline yeah so it only makes sense that they would then
shut down a different pipeline as an educational lesson yeah yeah yeah like hey be careful what you
wish for right that's exactly what's going on call that terrorism that would be technically
terrorism yes yes there might be attacking infrastructure to teach a lesson to let's say
spread fear yeah i think i think it's interesting to see the way that alex's brain kind of like
comes up with possibilities yeah he's just a terrorist you know anything has to be fake
everything has to be everything has to be fake what kind of fake is it yep it's very stupid what
a dick yep so alex is uh ranting because again just filling time the left want to be homeless
they want their children brain damage they want to be dead everybody i know the one got the vaccine
had strokes or heart attacks they love it they tell me oh their kids died they're in the news
oh my kid died it's a you know it's a wonderful thing it's a happy thing that's how all this crap
works ladies and gentlemen or goes on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on from there
hey guys i just hit my wireless headset and knocked my audio off and i forget how this works
i've got a lot of settings somebody come here and just take this little beauty for me and
punch it up where it works thank you so much somebody scream at him now uh it's right there
on the other table just i can bring it to you if you'd like just right over there thank you
now ladies and gentlemen we are here fighting the new world order as hard as we can and and we can't
do it without your support and i sell you things that i know that you really really really really
need and so we go i get the best horrible food company with the highest quality for the lowest
price we get it ready for everybody just bring it on to me thank you appreciate that uh and and
thank you sir and we we bring you those products so we can get money to stay on air and sell you
something you need it's called symbiotic relationship a 360 win a non-zero sum game
it's how i operate and so you got 2020 price parasitic would be better until tomorrow night
and then it's gonna go to its regular price it's still a great deal and they've told me in the next
two weeks or so they're gonna have to go up in price so you're not just gonna not get to sale
it's gonna have to go to price because the whole thing's shutting down and the supply chains are
breaking down and the pipelines are being turned off because we're under attack be afraid wow
you see you see the transition generally from like scary narrative into ad but then you saw
the reverse where it's the ad leads into terrorizing the audience of course that's uh
that's nice i have all this food for you and the price is good now but hey tomorrow price is gonna
go to regular and actually i know that in two weeks prices are going up even more and also
everything is going down because we're under attack get your food now or die listen all i'm
saying is that i am going to take you hostage with fear and then you will give me money yeah
and that's why you should be afraid yep very very afraid very afraid i'm getting more storeable food
for the office i'm getting more at my house i ordered more last week i i told my wife go get
all the little delectable canned goods and things that save and some of the gourmet storeable foods
as well just get ready and my parents have got a trailer out a little ranch i've got a solar and
all the stuff that's gone in and i gotta get a little shack or something for me too because
it's gonna be like road warrior if we don't turn this around and there's not much time left what's
the shack for so info war store.com it's a funky little shack um look i am sick and tired of
schrodinger's bug out location i know right i'm so sick of it i don't care for this nonsense of i
have a compound or maybe i should make one because the world's so dangerous and scary now yeah
ugh it's a will they won't they that uh is infuriating yeah let's get together with rachel
ross come on buddy also here's the thing that i want to bring attention to at the end of this
episode alex is talking about how we need to be really scared you gotta buy that food yeah got
a bug out location and all this course half an hour earlier he was laughing about how fulfilled
he feels because the globalists aren't done for right thanks to this bombshell that he can't quite
get himself to really cover it in any detail absolutely that is incongruent it's nonsense
and the reason is because the emotional experience of defeating the globalists is something that he
wants you to you know it's yeah it keeps people having fun yeah and then at the end you gotta
scare people because that's how the money comes in yeah no one makes money off defeating the
globalists yeah yeah it's terrorist edging yes so annoying yeah i would like some sort of
man you just get caught up in that you know it just rewires your your ability to process if
you're just so emotionally overstimulated all the time with no actual release it just drives you
insane like it's it's insane it's it's borderline solitary confinement you know yeah it's awful
yeah and i think i think that's the i don't know yeah i don't know what else to say but yeah it's
a mess it's kind of weird how you can sell stuff because of that isn't that a weird uh aspect of
our biology is that somehow all the way along the line evolution has led to people being like
be afraid and buy my shit well i mean i think that's the american dream snake oil salesman
and what have you there is a certain american aspect of the snake oil it's very americana
the way alex is uh it kind of manipulating people in order to sell them bullshit yeah it's hard to
it's hard not to think if we ever did eradicate these type of snake oil salesmen that we wouldn't
also have like writers and and different people making nostalgic stories about when you the snake
oil con man going from town to town you know just to be clear when you say eradicate you're talking
about like regulate out of existence yes yeah yeah no no no no no this is not a this is not
a cockroach system i mean like we don't have the snake oil salesman anymore it's some long
distant point in the future right people will feel nostalgic for them yeah of course yeah of
course because we're insane yep yep oh well yeah anyway um hey i look forward to going back to the
past because i find myself incredibly frustrated by this asshole yeah and i don't want to hear
about another goddamn bombshell that's disappointing i want to go back to the past
when news was measured and uh sometimes guests were combative sure and uh everything was what
it was yeah and uh not this overly dramatic nonsense uh every single day yeah it's just
the the candle is burning too bright no it's bad yeah anyway we'll be back but until then
we have a website we do have a website it's knowledgefight.com yep we're also on twitter
we are on twitter it's at knowledge we're fighting i go to bed jordan yep we're also on facebook we
are on facebook if you'd like and if you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your
area to help out people for sure uh we'll be back but until then i'm neo i'm leo i'm dzx clark i'm
darryl rundis and now here comes the sex robots andy and chanzas you're on the air thanks for
holding hello alex i'm a first time caller i'm a huge fan i love your work i love you