N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Damn, Ed, Jordan, I am SWEATING
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledgefight
knowledgefight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying we are the bad guys
Dan and Jordan
knowledgefight
Riddle her, riddle her, riddle her
I need, I need money
Andy and Kansas
Andy and, Andy, stop it
Andy and, Andy and Kansas
Andy and, Andy, it's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding me
Hello Alex, I'm a first-time caller, I'm a huge fan
I love your world
knowledgefight
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledgefight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're a couple dudes, I like to sit around, worship at the cult of Selene's altar and
talk about Alex Jeff
Indeed we are Dan
Not as smooth as the first time I got it right
I know, it was, but you're getting there, we're getting there
It's practice, it's work
You know what, a lot of people need to see the process of becoming good
instead of just seeing the finished product
No, definitely, and I consider this part of my 10,000 hours towards getting that introduction
Absolutely, absolutely
Also part of your 10,000 hours towards telling Malcolm Gladwell he's a moron
I consider that my community service
Good stuff
Hey Jordan
Hey Dan, I have a question for you
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today is actually, maybe you should go first
Maybe I should go first
Mine might be a little extended
Alright, okay, mine's just loud
Well, preemptively, neighbors
Neighbors, fair enough
My bright spot, Dan, is Shohei Ohtani
Today just hit his 12th home run to win
Congratulations
It's incredible, and he has a
Is he on the Cubs?
No, absolutely not, no, he's on the Angels
He hit his 12th home run, and he has an ERA around 2
And he has several, I mean this dude, here's why he's my bright spot
So he's a pitcher
He's everything, Dan
He is the only baseball player on this planet that has ever lived
Who can reliably throw a 100 mile an hour fastball and hit 450 foot dingers on the regular
And I have thought about that, and here's why it's my bright spot
Is because unlike so many other achievements, right now is the only time in history that
anyone has ever done what Shohei Ohtani is doing
And maybe he's the only person who has ever lived out of the 50 billion people estimated
He's the only one who can do this
That's really, really insane to me
For some of our international wonks in baseball
It's very rare for a pitcher to be able to hit well
No, no, no, no, that's not what it's rare
But you can hit well
It is rare for a pitcher to hit well
Yeah
It is not rare for a pitcher to hit what is he's on pace for over 40 home runs in a season
That is crazy
That's not rare
That's never happened
Anybody who wants to talk to me about Babe Ruth can shove it up their ass
Babe Ruth hit home runs off of people who threw slower than I do
Sure
Babe Ruth is shit
Babe Ruth is garbage
He was a garbage human being who played against garbage baseball players
Understood
For some context, one half of Major League Baseball as an organization doesn't make pitchers hit
That's how not good at hitting generally pitchers are
Yes
Part of the game was like, these guys are so bad at hitting, we have to change it
Yeah, let's not bog it down
I was going to make a joke about Jeff Supon
I believe famously hit a home run in the World Series for the Cardinals
He did
No, there was the Cubs reliever, I can't remember his name off the top of my head
But he was one of the last people to hit a home run in a playoff game as a relief pitcher
Hell yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Rare
Very rare
But the point is
You get to see him play
There's only one
Like, how insane is that?
There's only one person
But I also think about this, you're saying he's on pace for that
Sure
That to me, I just imagine being in that position, being in those shoes
Like, I don't know how you would handle that pressure
Yeah, no, totally
I don't know how he could, you know, I don't know
But he grew up in the Japanese Baseball Leagues, which if you've never
Like in the Japanese Baseball Leagues, if you're eight playing for your team
You have the same amount of pressure as a Major Leaguer in the United States
I don't know if you know anything about it
I don't, I have not looked into this at all
But they are fucking intense
Okay
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So Jordan, my bright spot is I made a little trip
Long overdue trip down to the box, the mailbox
Yes, indeed
And I have some stuff to take out of the bag
Yep
Excellent
One thing I realized, I didn't mention this when it was my birthday
Because it also included a gift for your birthday
And I forgot when your birthday came around
But our Black Dragon Queen Christie sent a very nice care package
Oh yes, of course
So thank you so much for that
Oh, absolutely
And then I went to the mailbag and there was some other stuff that was a bit birthday related
Bex sent in some young ginger ale, which I don't know what that is
Me neither
Young ginger, could be a wrap name
It could be Carl Jung's specific ginger line
Sure
Also, I believe Bex sent a pink ukulele
Which I'm a little confused by
But I'm excited to try to learn
I was trying to learn a couple chords last night while I was playing around with it
And my fingers are too fat
So I don't know if it's gonna work out
But what happened to those knowledge fight guys?
They turned into a weird ukulele band, I don't know
But we could do some cover songs
Yeah, why not?
Absolutely
Also
You Belong in the City is ripe for a ukulele parody
Also in this was the Sega Mega Drive Classics for the Switch
All right
And I've been used to seeing these kinds of collections of old games
Sure, sure, sure
And typically they end up not having the license to have like actually good games on it
But this is pretty solid
You got Dr. Robotnik's Mean Bean Machine
Sure
Classic
Gotta have that
Sonic, Sonic 2, Toejam and Earl, Vector Man
Are you reading them in chronological order?
Comic Zone
Oh shit, I do remember Comic Zone
Wow, the past is far away
The entire Streets of Rage trilogy
Okay, well that we haven't had in a long time
There's a whole lot of stuff on there and it's very nice
It's been a long time since I've moved from left to right and punched things
Yeah, there are a couple games that are entirely that
So then I got another thing here
And this was a little bit weird, Jordan
I feel like I'm gonna need your help because I think this might have actually been for you
Okay, okay
So here, this card came
And look at the front, look at the front
Alright, alright
Okay, there is a dog resting his, well there's a puppy resting his very cute, very lovable face
On top of a kitten who is staring cute and lovable
Now look at this, look at this on the inside
It says, yeah, we listen and we have feelings too, comma, Jordan
Right
Love, comma, nothing
Nothing
Okay
Now, this came inside a box
That had two mugs and this is one of them
Okay, alright, you shall know the truth and the truth shall make you free, alright
Central Intelligence Agency, sure, sure
Now, there is a sticker on the bottom that implies that this came from a gift shop
Yes indeed
So, either the CIA is trying to fuck with you and let you know, Jordan, that they're listening
And you have hurt their feelings
I don't understand
Either the CIA is very sensitive
Or it's somebody fucking with us, I'm not entirely sure
Alright, yeah, dot, dot, dot, yeah, we, but who's we?
CIA, man
It's the CIA, but I mean, why would they send me a cute little puppy?
It was from a nondescript address in Virginia
Oh, well, that would kind of make sense then, wouldn't it?
I don't know, it's entirely possible, but I mean,
Occam's Razor tells me that it's someone fucking with you
But I still appreciate a mug
Sure
I like a nice mug
Admit how ironic it would be for Alex to constantly claim that the CIA and all important heads
of state listen to him and yet we get very kind, almost downright cute cards from the CIA
Letting us know that they are listening
And that you are being too mean
I apologize to the CIA, I guess
Wow
Is that what I do? Is that all it takes? It takes a cute kitten and a cute puppy
Jordan has issued an apology to the CIA
See now, what they don't realize, it does take both
For all of our leftist listeners out there that really look at Jordan as this kind of like,
oh yeah, he gets it, he's on the edge, man
He just apologized to the CIA
I would be surprised
Centrist Jordan
Honestly, I would be surprised to know too many leftists who,
upon receiving a cute puppy or kitten card, wouldn't be like
I mean, it softens me a little bit just to know that cute puppies
Oh, damn it, they got me again
Oh man, I had the CIA all wrong
Oh, damn it
So Jordan, today we got an episode from the past
We are talking about May 8th and 9th, 2003
Ooh, fun
Continuing our march
One of the things I wanted to try to do was I wanted to try to keep pace
Sure
With 2003, I don't think we're going to be able to do that
That's going to be tough
With two episodes a week, it's a little tough
It's going to be a hard fight
But here we are, May 8th and 9th
Got some interesting stuff to go over
Some weird parallels with the present, as per usual
Naturally
Due to my witchcraft
You are a witch
But before we get into this, let's take a little moment to say hello to some wonks
Ooh, that's a good idea
So first, Andrew Buchholt, thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Andrew
Thank you
Next, ZZ Pop, thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, ZZ Pop
Thank you
Next, All Hail the Cult Leader, Selene
Thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Uh, thank you
Next, Good Good Muscle, Nate
Thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Good Good Muscle, Nate
Thank you
Next, Jordan's Banshee, Laugh Is My Bright Spot
Thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Thank you
Next, Gon AFK
Thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much, Gon AFK
Thank you
And we've got a technocrat
To give a little tip of the cap too
So Mr. Mac Mackington, thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate, that's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
We got to go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why are you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you, Mr. Mac Mackington.
Yes, thank you very much, Mr. Mac Mackington.
Also, before we get into this, this show business,
the sexual business of the show.
Not show business.
No.
Certainly not.
We've never been in show business.
We have mics we're holding in our hands.
We are not in show business.
No.
I got a message from a Jeff, character named Jeff.
And Jeff wanted to get a message out.
And that is, apparently, they have a friend named Alex,
who's opposed to the spider leadership.
And this is relevant, because you're
wearing the spider leadership t-shirt right now.
Perfect.
So this friend of Jeff's is opposed to you.
OK.
Also, apparently, Jeff's brother, Evan,
just got into the show.
So what up, Evan?
Hi, Evan.
Welcome to the Wonkaree.
What are we doing?
I have no idea.
This is just what we've become, I guess.
Welcoming new listeners individually?
Why?
Why are we doing this?
I don't know.
Don't you realize what can of worms you've opened up again?
Every time you add another thing, it never ends.
Oh, god.
Oh, boy.
So here are a couple out of context drops.
OK.
The first is a little, it's actually
a little game I want to play.
And that is, Alex or Bill Clinton?
OK.
I love this country.
Was that Alex, or was that Bill Clinton?
Do you need to hear that again?
Yes, one more time.
OK, here we go.
I love this country.
OK, we can't do, this is a stolen news radio bit
from four years prior to this show airing.
When Phil Hartman went on as Bill McNeil
and did long interviews with himself as Bill Clinton.
We can't say that it's that.
I will say that it's definitely not that.
It's definitely not that.
It is either Alex Jones sounding a lot like Bill Clinton.
Sure.
Or Bill Clinton with Alex's going
to break music playing in the background.
I'm going to go with Alex on this one.
You're right.
Oh, wait.
So here's Alex doing an impression
of a dude smoking pot.
Yeah, you ever seen the artwork in the Denver airport?
Yeah, man.
It's good to know that the Denver airport will never die.
No, and finally, third out of context drop,
unprecedented, Alex doing an impression of himself.
The valedictorian of the school today
doesn't hold a candle to my father.
OK.
Wait.
A little sad.
Your father today?
No, back in his dad's day.
That's when people were smart.
I really don't know if that's how anything works, especially
not education or knowledge.
Nope.
So we start here on the 8th.
And Alex actually begins the show
with a story that there's some mirror
parallels to the present day.
It's now coming out that what may have killed that NBC
reporter was his small pox injection.
So see, it's mainstream.
These vaccines are deadly.
You don't have to take them.
But the government's trying to set a precedent that you do
by saying, oh, you're crazy if you don't.
Well, I guess then 99-plus percent of doctors, police,
and firemen are crazy because 99-plus
have refused to take it.
But David Bloom didn't.
And he's bye-bye.
And many others that are taking it are bye-bye.
It looks like more than one out of 1,000 die that take it.
Those are now official numbers, by the way.
First things first, Alex, not the last stat
that he cited there, that's a little outlandish,
but he's not off on some of this stuff.
But the story that he's telling about this
is missing some points.
I was able to find a CBS News article from May 2003, which
discussed a proposed plan to vaccinate half a million
health care workers against smallpox, of which, quote,
only 35,000 of the targeted workers had been inoculated.
There's not good evidence that I can find that anyone was
refusing the vaccine, just that the program may have only
vaccinated about 7% of the stated goal population.
So Alex is saying 99% are refusing the vaccine.
So real decent chance they weren't refusing it,
but one in seven is closer than I'm used to him being.
Sure, sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
93% of the targeted population that they
meant to get a smallpox vaccination did not get it.
Sure.
Alex is making up that they all refused.
Right, we don't know how the not getting it went down.
It wasn't like we know for a fact.
No, instead, actually 7%.
There's a real decent chance that most of that
was just due to structural problems with how the rollout
of the campaign was.
Yeah, not enough people even knew about it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And part of it is most people do not
need to get vaccinated against smallpox nowadays.
The reason is because thanks to vaccination efforts made
by the people who came before us,
smallpox was declared eradicated in 1980.
After 9-11, there was a concern about a terrorist group
or a hostile government using smallpox as a weapon.
And as such, the US government stockpiled massive amounts
of smallpox vaccine in order to be prepared
for that kind of possibility.
But typically speaking, most people won't need that vaccine.
The people who do, according to the CDC,
are typically lab workers who might
be in contact with any viruses similar to smallpox.
The push to vaccinate in 2003 was
based on fears of this potential terrorist attack.
And what was ultimately decided was
that it wasn't worth the risk.
And vaccines could still be effective after someone
was exposed to the virus, so there wasn't
much of a need for this.
The program was ended early, and only a total of about 39,000
people were ultimately vaccinated.
A large part of the resistance to this program
was that people didn't buy that there was a real threat,
since Bush had been pretty clear that there
was no information of an imminent attack,
and hospitals were reluctant to participate.
In the end, however, through this program's failure,
public health preparedness was improved.
And even critics of the smallpox campaign
credited with helping us be more ready for the later
outbreak of SARS.
Sure, sure.
David Bloom was a 39-year-old combat reporter
working with NBC.
He passed away on April 6, 2003, while on assignment,
reporting from Iraq.
It's pretty well understood that the cause of death
was that Bloom had developed a blood clot in his leg
from spending days on end crammed into an armored vehicle
and having deep vein thrombosis.
This clot made its way to his lungs
and caused a pulmonary embolism, which resulted in his death.
In the days after he passed away,
a doctor named Brian Strom made a number
of comments to the media about the possibility
that Bloom's death was related to the smallpox vaccination
he'd gotten several weeks prior to his passing.
There's no direct evidence to support this conclusion,
and Alex is kind of just making stuff up,
riffing and jumping to conclusions here.
That said, no medication is fully without some risk,
and the smallpox vaccine is no exception.
Compared to the horror of having smallpox come back, though,
the risk is very minimal.
Isn't it so fucking, it's just so indicative
of how stupid people are that the government was like,
okay, now, despite not having any idea whether or not
they could have weaponized polio,
or smallpox would weaponize smallpox,
or even have some way of delivering it,
we're just going to go out of our way
and protect ourselves against the possibility
of a smallpox attack, despite the fact
that the overwhelming number of humans
have died of diseases that have occurred regularly,
and at no point in time have they been like,
let's put a lot of effort into preemptive, yeah.
I mean, they have.
I mean, they have, but not like, yeah.
You know what my point is.
It's not like the Bush administration
wasn't also getting tetanus shots.
Sure, sure.
I don't know what you're even saying.
Sure, but my, fine, fine, fine, whatever.
I feel like you're just looking for a way to attack.
I'm not looking for a way to, I don't need to look.
Sure.
I think when you look at this,
it's like, it's a terrifying prospect,
and I think that maybe there was some chatter of some sort.
I would believe possibly that like,
oh, this is something we should be concerned about.
Sure.
Somebody might have a sample
of some laboratory smallpox that could really fuck things up.
Totally.
And I think that maybe if you escalate in your head
what the possible threat is,
then the idea of a campaign
of vaccinating healthcare workers
who might be in the front lines or soldiers,
that makes a certain amount of sense.
Right.
Looking back, we obviously have the gift of hindsight
knowing that this didn't happen.
Right.
And it can look a lot more silly.
But, and even back then,
you could probably make a pretty decent argument
that it was excessive.
Right.
You kinda understand where the thought process comes from.
No, naturally, but it's just,
we've had too many examples of this type of paranoia
being the excuse for action
when it's paranoia that inherently devalues
the life of other people,
as opposed to paranoia that's like,
hey, diseases just come out of nowhere
from shit all the time.
That's infinitely more important.
Instead, it's like,
we've always gotta be preparing for a war
or an attack or someone to try and kill us.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, yeah.
I think I might've misunderstood your point.
Yeah.
And I think your point is fine.
And definitely, I think it was indicative
of a lot of the public mentality.
Especially in 2003, when everything is an attack.
Yeah.
But I also think that you can do both.
I think that,
and that might be where my head misunderstood
what you were saying.
No, no, no, totally.
If it were a one or the other choice,
then yeah, focus on.
No, no, no, totally, totally.
But I think everybody was kind of,
ideally, had their head on swivel, looking around.
No, my point isn't invalid,
but it's not necessarily the best way to go
about talking about stuff.
I don't think you broke new ground.
No, I didn't start a revolution, Dan.
Anyway, this clip, I thought,
was a really good instance to illustrate
why you can't take vaccine-related stories seriously
when they come from Alex.
No matter what the reality of the story is,
Alex is always going to take the story
about the possibility of danger,
and he's gonna report that as definitive,
and then he's gonna exaggerate it out,
and it's like, oh, it's been proven.
They've shown it, you know?
And it's the same thing that he does
with the COVID-19 vaccine stories in the present day.
This behavior is consistent,
because he is staunchly opposed to vaccines,
not based on the science of it.
Absolutely, and you can argue,
and the problem with it is that the argument of like,
look, 20 years ago, this asshole was saying the same lies
about different vaccines,
and you can see that those didn't come true,
so why would you believe him now?
And the argument will always be like,
yeah, yeah, yeah, but it's a Black Swan event, you know?
Sure, this one was a fake.
They wanna make you comfortable with their vaccines
until they do it, they wanna lull you into,
and you're like, fine, we'll never win.
No. That's it.
You can't really beat back that thinking.
No, no.
And I think that if you are able to get yourself
to a point where you recognize that like,
oh, he does do this over and over and over again,
regardless of the circumstances,
you have to start to ask yourself why,
and what is it exactly that is the opposition to vaccines?
What is that about?
Right.
And I think you could probably come up
with a couple of possibilities.
One is a sort of inclination towards divine science.
Sure, sure.
I guess the idea of medical intervention is against God.
Right.
And I'm not sure if I believe that Alex is there,
because he's gotten surgery.
Yeah.
You know?
Yeah, no, but it is that kind of like,
when it happens to someone else,
it's very much the will of God.
And when it happens to you,
the will of God is to save yourself.
You know, the Lord helps those who help themselves.
But when other people die, it's because it was their time.
It was their time to go, Dan.
You can't deny them that.
Sure.
I'm saying that's a slightly unsatisfying explanation
for Alex.
The other one that I come up with is the notion
and understanding that like vaccines
have drastically improved the lives of poor people
and people in developing countries around the world.
And I don't know, a whole lot of Alex's policy positions
seem to be about not doing that, cutting off foreign aid.
Those sorts of things are things that seem to be
kind of overlap of a lot of his beliefs.
Yeah.
I don't know if that's where the opposition comes from,
but it certainly makes more sense
than legitimate scientific concerns.
Yeah, yeah.
When you think about when typhoid spread
through wealthy neighborhoods,
there was far less like anti-medicine spread around
about that shit.
It was very much everybody needs to clean their hands.
Everybody needs to stay safe.
You know, that kind of thing.
Yeah.
So Alex gives a little bit of a spiel
at the beginning of this episode.
And he talks about like, you know, hey man,
sometimes the world doesn't make sense.
And that's when you need a little bit of Infowars.
That's true.
Again, I'm Alex Jones, your host.
The websites are infowars.com, infowars.net,
and prisonplanet.com.
If the world doesn't make sense to you,
if you wonder why you keep losing your liberties
and more and more factories are shutting down
and why the borders are still wide open,
as the government tells you to give up liberty for security,
you'll find the answers right here.
You wonder why our government creates Saddam Hussein's
and creates bin Laden's and arms North Korea's
and then engages the American people
in these costly and dangerous wars.
You'll find the answers right here.
You're wondering why police are running checkpoints
and why there's cameras everywhere
and why your children are being trained
how to turn you in for owning guns
when your guns aren't even illegal.
You'll find the answers right here on this show.
Is it the devil?
It's gotta be the devil.
Is it secretly the devil?
It's gotta be something like that.
I'm confused.
I mean, I understand.
No, I think we were all wondering that.
Those are correct wonders.
Sure.
There's some of them are more valid than others.
True.
Yeah, certainly there are.
Hey, it is confusing.
Militarization of police is confusing.
It's wrong.
What's going on here?
Why is this happening?
I don't get answers from Infowars.
No.
And knowing what he turns into
and that the devil is actually behind the globalists,
I wonder if he's just not telling the audience
at this point that this is secretly
just a big religious campaign.
Is this part of God's plan for him in fighting the devil
to lie to these people early on in his career
so he can kind of like slowly trick them
into being the holy warriors that God needs?
Right.
A saint isn't going to bring these sinners in.
Exactly.
That kind of idea.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That might've been a quote from Red Dead Redemption.
God was talking to Saul
when Saul was like nine or 10 in his dreams.
And he was like, listen,
you got to lie to everybody right up until the good time.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know.
It's really strange to me.
And like I've said in these 2003 episodes,
one of the things that I'm trying to keep my eye on
is this idea of how much of the devil
does he think he's fighting the devil in 2003?
Right, right, right.
And you know, if he does, then that clip is abusive.
And if he doesn't, then his worldview doesn't make sense.
I would appreciate it if that clue, yeah.
So Alex has got a headline that's not a headline.
Coming up in the next hour,
Eugene police illegally raid homes
with a tank prompts federal lawsuit.
Eugene police illegally raid homes with a tank
prompts federal lawsuit.
And wild stuff comes out of Oregon,
but it's happening all over the country.
This headline that Alex is reading
is not from a news story or any kind of journalistic source.
It's actually the title of a press release
that was put out by the office of Lauren Regan,
the lawyer representing the people
who were the subject of this raid.
Yeah.
I can understand how this is still a source of information
and it's entirely possible that a lawyer's press release
could have stuff worth conveying,
but it seems like something that shouldn't be treated
as the same as an article in an actual news outlet.
Incidentally, this case resulted in the city of Eugene
paying one couple $30,000 and another $92,000
to settle their cases,
which claimed unreasonable search and seizure,
excessive use of force, assault, and false imprisonment.
The police contended that it was an instance
of them having bad information
and believing that they were raiding a drug house,
whereas the couples believed
that the police got a warrant by lying.
Whatever the case, it's not good policing.
And even if the intel had all been good,
seems like their actions would have been excessive
for a drug raid.
Anyway, the point here is that in terms of the big picture,
that this kind of police action is wrong,
Alex and I are in complete agreement.
Not hard.
I still don't support how he pushes the message though,
however, given that he's presenting this biased information
from the lawyers of people involved in the story
as a neutral headline.
It's not necessarily the way you would wanna go
about framing your case,
even if your case is something that I agree with.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, it would be hard to be on the wrong side
of strangers destroy your home for no good reason
and face no punishment for it.
Sure, sure.
You know, like that seems obvious.
Yeah, and Alex spends a large portion of this episode
talking about this couple's houses that were searched
and they were, you know, held.
Right.
And it does
become hard to take seriously.
Yeah.
Knowing the present.
Like I do care for these people
who had this police intervention in their lives
unnecessarily and they were treated poorly.
I just don't consider Alex a legitimate person
to make those points.
Absolutely.
Anymore.
Yeah.
Anyway.
That is also a really good question about the,
I mean, as far as the fighting the devil
in the past and the present goes,
another like question that that raises is,
is this guy that guy or does he change into this guy?
And what does that mean?
You know, like, are there,
is it possible that Alex and I
could have had a conversation in 2003
that wouldn't have wound up with me
trying to throw something into his face?
Probably, I bet it is.
I bet you would.
You might not really enjoy it all that much.
Right.
But yeah.
And is that because he's lying to me
or is that because he was a different person?
Yeah.
And does that raise the possibility
that I could eventually change into this very monster?
That's actually why we're doing this.
Isn't this terrifying?
It's truly a nightmare.
That's really the thing
that this is all about is like-
But what do we turn into?
Yes.
Looking at this and being like,
what do we have to be afraid of?
What are the signs?
What's the, yeah, yeah.
Can we get, somebody get a whiteboard up
with a checklist. This is a cautionary thing.
Yes, absolutely.
So Alex starts to read this article
and it's interesting that you bring up this,
the differences between present
and like is this the same person?
Sure.
Because he starts to bring up this article
and you can see in this clip,
similarities and differences.
Like, okay, one of the big similarities,
he starts reading and everything he reads,
he editorializes on.
Sure, sure.
He adds a whole bunch of stuff
that's not in the article to the article.
But a big difference,
he says that this was written by a lawyer.
He doesn't clarify that it's the lawyer
of the people who were in the story.
Sure.
But he does give a clarification
that I didn't expect from him.
Let me just read part of this powerful article
and we're gonna talk to the lawyer
who wrote the story
and got some of the other mainstream articles about it.
Lauren Regan,
Eugene police illegally raid homes
with tank prompts federal lawsuit.
And in the pre-dawn of October 17, 2002,
approximately 50 police officers
that see this every day
from multiple police agencies
that are federalized
under multi-jurisdictional task force,
swarmed residential neighborhood,
we saw this in Austin.
You can hear the difference in his voice
when he's editorializing.
Yup, yup.
That's, it's,
it's almost courteous in a way.
You can feel him almost telling you
when he's not.
There is a slight bit of that,
but it's still like,
okay, I'm gonna set out to read this article
then I'm gonna interrupt myself constantly
with stuff that's not in the article.
No, there's definitely that.
It's a little bit dicey,
but yeah, it's slightly more responsible feeling
because if you are actively listening,
you can tell when it's like,
these are the words of Alex.
Right.
This is his reading voice.
And I don't know.
And you know why that's a more compelling show
than just reading the news
because this is very similar
to how some asshole might be reading an article
as he's reading it.
You know, like if I'm reading a dumb article,
sometimes I'll read a sentence
and be like, these motherfuckers are stupid.
And then I'll read the next sentence.
You know, this is an engaging way
of almost reading the news with your buddy.
I don't fully disagree.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So Alex gets to talking about other places
that have been raided.
Now it's raiding neighborhoods.
In a town in Missouri two years ago,
AP headline, town searched in drug raid.
Folks, this is as bad as it gets.
This was a case from early 2002
where a 27 month long investigation
into an international gun and drug smuggling operation
culminated in arrests in a town called Carthage in Missouri.
This is a real headline from an AP story,
but the use of the words town searched
isn't meant to be taken completely literally.
The multi-agency task force
that was working on this extended operation
set up some checkpoints to make sure
the subjects of their investigation couldn't flee,
and then they made their arrests.
Again, I'm not justifying this policing necessarily.
I'm just saying that the image that Alex wants to create
of cops kicking in every door in this town in Missouri,
looking for wrongdoing to jam someone up,
that's not accurate.
No, I mean admittedly- That's the image he wants to create
and it's not real.
Admittedly, when they marched those elephants
across the Rockies to get there,
I felt like that might've been a terrible idea,
but Carthage.
Right, I got it. Carthage, Dan.
I got it. Carthage, because of-
I was trying to think of a way
if there was a like a Fitzcarraldo joke I could make.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The elephants and the carrying a boat.
Sure, sure, that could've-
It wasn't worth it. I feel like my Hannibal reference
was better than you gave it credit for it.
It was, but I think I probably would've enjoyed it more
if I wasn't trying to make a Fitzcarraldo joke and failing.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We were working at cross purposes on that riff.
Yeah. So I can see that.
I apologize, I should be there for you more.
That was on me.
Anyway, the point of this though
is that Alex is completely just fudging this.
Yeah, yeah.
But it's a good headline for him, meh.
Anyway, he gets to talking to this lawyer
and I guess if you put the pieces together yourself,
you can kind of make sense of the fact
that this isn't a headline.
This is, the press release word is never used,
but you can put the pieces together
that this is a lawyer representing the people.
Sure, sure, sure.
A not unbiased actor in this circumstance, if you will.
Yeah, and I think that this lawyer
seems fairly straight up.
I think she's distracted and maybe a little bit bemused
by Alex's constant-
Right.
detractions.
That her name was Roberta Barnes gave me some pause,
but once I found out there was no relation,
I felt more comfortable.
So Alex knows how to arrest people.
You should know that.
Okay.
And how you arrest somebody is you park down the street
when the perp leaves in the morning,
you do a little work, you surveil them for a couple of days.
When they go to work, you pull them over,
you pull them out of the car,
you take them back to the house with a warrant,
you go in the house, nobody gets hurt.
But see, that's not fun to suit up at 3 a.m.
in black uniforms and feel all tough
and go rumbling down the road in your tank.
These are all wannabes who probably
washed out in the special forces.
Now they get to pick on women.
Right.
I mean, this show is a really abusive, psychotic nature
to drag a naked woman outside with a black hood on.
Go ahead.
So I don't, you can tell kind of there
that she's trying to respond to stuff.
She's trying to say anything edgewise, yes, yes.
That kind of is how I would characterize the interview.
It's not hostile by any stretch.
She has a point, I don't know if she necessarily
knows who Alex is.
And Alex certainly isn't as toxic an entity in 2003
as he is in the present.
Right, right, right.
You might not think twice about an invitation
to come and talk about this case
that you're passionate about
and you want to get attention for.
And you don't know going in that it is going to be
a life or death struggle to finish a sentence.
You didn't know that.
And you don't know that Alex is going to be constantly
trying to drive the image of a naked woman
being dragged out of her house to his audience
because that's visceral for them.
Correct, yeah.
Whereas you maybe want to talk about.
I have things to say.
You want to talk about rights.
You want to talk about infringement of citizen civil rights.
Totally.
Yep.
So anyway, the interview is not that great
or all that interesting, especially I think partially
because I mean, I agree with Alex.
I don't agree with his tactics.
Sure, sure.
I don't agree with him sensationalizing the story.
Right.
But in terms, like I looked at the story in normal outlets
and the conclusion of the police shouldn't have done this.
Yeah, it's not hard.
I agree.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I know because we're in the future
that the police and the city of Eugene
did pay out a settlement.
Yeah.
And that doesn't take away whatever these people experience
but it certainly is some sign.
No, no five figures is restitution for the cops
destroying your home, you know, and your sense of safety
forever.
Yeah, there's going to be psychological things
that remain.
Yeah, absolutely.
You know, there's a modicum of justice in a settlement.
Sure, sure.
And no one died.
So that's great.
No one died, yeah.
Anyway, the interview ends and Alex says this
and I just rolled my eyes.
All right, the third hour will be an absolute news overload
blitz.
I've got 50 articles I haven't gotten to.
I will get to them.
I will get to your calls.
1-800-259-9231.
He's the same guy.
Oh boy, oh boy.
He's setting himself up for failure.
Like if he plans to get to 50 stories plus calls in one hour,
that's just not possible.
If you factor in commercials, he's
giving himself like 20 seconds per story.
That's not even enough to get through the headlines.
He should be more realistic about what he can and can't
cover in the time he has and then focus
on what he has the time to cover.
Sure.
It would make for better content.
It wouldn't be so dumb.
It does make it, I don't know, what would I say?
It does make it far more reasonable to just ignore
that in the present, though.
You know, it's like a long running joke on a sitcom.
Like a Simpsons bit, it's been going on for 30 years.
What are you going to complain now?
If Alex says he's going to get to the stories
and you've listened in 2003, you know damn well
he's not going to get to the story.
So who gives a shit, you know?
Because for me, I'm looking at this like Dr. House.
Sure.
You know what I'm saying?
Sure, sure.
In the present day, Alex has this list of symptoms, right?
Right, right.
And we go back to 2003, and he's got the same symptom.
It's like, all right, that's not part of the condition.
That's not part of the disease, yes.
I got you.
I'm playing diagnostic games here.
Understood.
Cough is not part of it.
So Alex has trouble with quotes, and it extends
far beyond Thomas Jefferson.
The globalists' mind controllers say
that perception is reality.
I am mental.
They create the perception that the military and the police
on our streets is good, when if you investigate,
you'll find out it's bad.
So Alex saying that, you know, claiming
that the globalists use that quote,
perception is reality, that's interesting,
because that's a quote most famously attributed
to Republican strategist Lee Atwater.
Yeah.
A man notable for his intense use of racism
as a political tool.
Oh, yeah.
Name one big strategy that he helped institute.
It's on the compass.
Also, he's associated with the Willie Horton ad.
Sure, sure.
Also, he's pretty notable that in 1984,
he became a senior partner at Black Manafort Stone
and Kelly, the consulting firm run
by Alex's future good buddy Roger Stone.
Wow.
Perception is reality.
Woo.
Man, Jesus.
Yep.
1984, good old Roger Stone looking to his left,
seeing Lee Atwater thinking, I got
a bright future in front of me.
Paul, we're going to do great things.
You and I definitely aren't going
to get charged with crimes in 36 years.
Oh, boy, we're definitely not laying the groundwork
for all the crimes we're going to do.
Yep.
So this was interesting to me.
Sure.
I'm going to stop saying interesting.
But this was weird.
Fascinating.
Sure.
OK.
Alex has an intense news blitz he needs to get through.
Yes, we're in a full hour of news blitz.
I forgot about that.
Listen to this.
OK.
And I'm sad for our troops that are being
used for the new world order and are
being injected with deadly vaccines,
are being brought back here and turned
into militarized police.
We need to remember what America is about.
What makes America America is because it was a free country.
Now we're beginning to lose that.
We're seeing the shift rapidly.
And patriots everywhere need to be veterans
in the second American revolution,
or I should say, restoration.
For all the veterans that really gave all,
we've had requests for this song.
We'll air it.
Then I'll come back and talk to John in Indiana,
or John in Missouri, and others that are patiently holding.
And I'll launch into a bunch of geopolitical news
and information.
So again, stay with us.
I think this song says it all.
It's not sappy.
A lot of people die to defend liberty.
That's what that flag symbolizes, is our republic,
not a unit of a world empire.
And then Alex plays the entire song of Billy Ray Cyrus'
Sun Gable.
I was worried it was going to be what I heard it being.
And then it was that.
And now I'm unhappy.
I would give anything to go back to that moment in time
and tell Alex about Miley.
Heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh.
Oh my god, it's so weird.
It's so weird.
He plays a full song as like a shout out to the troops.
And he doesn't sing along with it or editorialize over it?
He just leaves.
Oh.
Yeah.
Well, you know, he couldn't eat a sandwich as easily back then.
That's probably true.
Yeah, that was bizarre.
The format is very strange.
Yeah, that's very weird.
That makes me feel deeply uncomfortable.
A lot of people have been wanting me to play Billy Cyrus.
No, no, no.
And I say to them, no, again.
From everything I understand about Alex's format,
song requests are not right.
You can request songs.
He doesn't play songs.
No, he's not a song player.
No.
What a weird, yeah, OK.
Very strange.
All right.
So the news blitz doesn't really happen.
But Alex does take some calls.
And one guy, this guy is interesting.
He seems to believe that spam messages.
Oh.
Right?
Yeah, not the food.
Spam messages need to be clearly delineated as something
with a commercial purpose.
Because he got accused of spamming somebody.
And he was just trying to harass them.
OK, two things if I can get to them.
One is the supremacy clause in the Constitution.
And the other is this law of attempted legislation to make
spam a felony on the internet.
I tried to.
Spam is commercial.
It's got to be defined as commercial gain
and that kind of stuff, not forcing
complicit media to see the pictures.
Well, sir, the White Paper Doctor Two was written.
If your email goes to somebody wrong,
you get live in prison in a labor camp, OK?
Right.
What?
I was accused of spamming people many times
right after 9-11, Iraqi war.
They leave their email addresses in the newspaper articles.
And one guy, he shifts his email address
so he doesn't have to receive these
because he knows that he would be guilty of mispresient
if he's alerted to the treason that's going on.
Yeah, so apparently this guy goes and finds
email addresses in newspapers and then harasses the people.
He's worried about a law against spam.
Yeah.
That's a fundamental misunderstanding
of all of the problems with what you're doing.
You bet.
But it's fun.
I can't believe you got the point that wrong.
Yeah.
It's a fun call, though, because you
can see the dynamics that are going on.
And like, I don't know, that sounds like an Alex Jones
listener to me.
They're trying to make a law making it illegal for me
to send chain emails to my family.
And that's going to really get in the way of me
kneecapping this reporter over here.
So we've got to stop this chain email law.
It is not spam when I email a journalist 100 times in a day
and tell him he's going to go to jail for treason.
It's not spam.
I'm not a bot.
I'm an asshole.
I sent every one of those messages by hand.
I clicked the button.
I'm proud of being an asshole.
So Alex has one more caller that we're
going to hear a little bit of.
This person's talking about, so you've
got the new money coming in, the new bills in the US.
And a lot of people have a lot of theories about that.
And this caller believes.
We'll never have Harriet Tubman on the $20 bill.
This caller believes that there's like metal strips
and stuff in the money.
Sure, sure.
If you hold on to the money for more than a month,
it'll be able to time that.
I like this.
This money will know when it's changed hands.
This is a good conspiracy.
I like this.
And if you hold on to it too long, it'll auto-tax.
Oh, no.
Real quick, what that man was talking about on the money,
this was on a program the other day.
One of the things with the money,
with the strip when you get it, if you don't pass it
on within a month, you'll be taxed on it.
Oh, it'll be valued, I reported that three years ago,
from the Federal Reserve Board of Virginia's website.
A real good person to have on would
be Donald McIlvaney, intelligence advisor.
If you could get him on and interview him.
He's very well versed on all of this.
I have no idea how the timer of a month
would start.
I love it.
If I were to buy something with a bill, this is ridiculous.
I like it.
Anyway, I don't know anything about this Donald McIlvaney
guy, but I did look into him a little bit.
And I did find that his main website is just
a portal to a gold sales outlet.
How's he doing?
I don't know.
Oh, so he's saying that maybe you shouldn't get paper money,
and instead you should get gold.
So then he, of course, sells gold.
That's very strange how that works.
It's so strange.
It's almost like these people with these completely nutty
conspiracy theories about paper money
always tend to sell gold.
It's super weird.
Super weird how people who hate the Fed and paper currency
love and also sell and profit off of gold.
They have a weird financial motivation.
Super strange.
So we go to the ninth.
OK.
And I didn't find that episode all that satisfying.
A lot of it was about talking to that lawyer
and just kind of spinning his wheels.
Sure.
Then I got in on the ninth, and I found myself very excited.
Is that the right word?
Interesting.
Coming up in about, I don't know, 16, 17 minutes,
we'll be joined by Jeff Singer and Dave Moore, who
are on a local country FM in Colorado Springs.
We're on, of course, on KWYD 1580 in Colorado Springs.
But we're going to have them on because, of course,
you heard last week they got suspended
for criticizing the Bixie Chicks.
And maybe you heard on the news that they got
suspended for playing them.
But we'll get to the bottom of it.
Alex just.
Oh, would you say they got canceled, if you will?
Alex just misspoke there, and he tried
to cover it by insinuating that the media had gotten
this story wrong by making you think that the two DJs got
in trouble for playing Dixie Chicks
when maybe they got in trouble for criticizing them.
Only Alex can get to the bottom of it when he misspeaks.
How could you know?
So these two guys worked for KKCS 102 FM in Colorado Springs.
Sure.
It's a station.
They had to put in place a boycott
on playing the Dixie Chicks songs
after Natalie Maines had some comments at a concert
that were seen as being anti-troop when she said
that she was ashamed that President Bush was
from the same state as her in Texas.
Good for the Dixie Chicks for being ahead of their time,
you know?
Now we're all ashamed of the United States,
but they really got there first.
Obviously, this was an instance of everyone losing the damn
mind and the right wing shitheads doing
a dog pile on the Dixie Chicks.
But some of the details of the story,
particularly about this DJ situation,
might not be what you remember.
OK, is this a clown sending a, what's it, poison again?
No, no, this isn't a ricin.
This isn't a ricin situation.
Dueling Elvis in person winners?
I was going to say, this isn't that?
Not quite.
Oh, OK.
So in terms of these actual two DJs,
the story that I remembered was that they dared
to play a couple songs from the Dixie Chicks,
and that was enough to get them in trouble.
Sure.
An article from the Times Herald Record has some other details.
Quote, KKCS had instituted a ban on the Dixie Chicks, who
at the time had two songs on the charts.
But two DJs at the station, Dave Moore and Jeff Singer,
decided that two months was punishment enough.
They broke the ban.
At 6.15 AM on Monday, May 5, 2003,
they locked themselves in the DJ booth.
They started with long time gone,
and they didn't stop playing Dixie Chicks tunes until noon.
Was Adam Sandler and Brendan Fazier there?
What in God's name happened?
Yeah, I didn't remember that was part of the story.
I don't remember airheads being real life.
Yeah, even though I agree with the point of what they're
doing, I totally understand that that's
a brazen act of insubordination.
Listen, you guys are heroes, but we can't just
not do anything about this.
Ultimately, what happened is that the station manager, Jerry
Grant, gave the two a choice to either continue playing
Dixie Chicks songs and get fired or stop, unlock the studio,
and be suspended for a few days.
And they chose to end the occupation of the station.
So courageous.
I have a huge problem with everything
surrounding this story, but I'm not
sure I disagree with these two DJs getting
a slap on the wrist for essentially, like you said,
living the movie airheads.
Yeah, yeah, I mean, come on.
You can't live the movie.
You can't live the movie airheads.
You just can't do it.
It's like what they did.
Even in the movie airheads, they couldn't
live the movie airheads.
What they did was for a good cause, sort of,
as we learn later.
And I support the statement of playing their music.
Censorship is dumb no matter what.
Absolutely.
And so I wouldn't want them to be punished too harshly,
but you can't lock yourself in a radio booth
and pirate the transmission and expect nothing to happen.
There is that.
If I were your boss.
But the protest is there's consequences.
I think that is actually a pretty restrained response
from the boss.
Couple days suspension, whatever.
Almost wise too.
Because if he'd overreacted, everybody
would have turned it into a cause.
But giving them a slap on the wrist
is almost insulting to them.
Like, your protest was worth nothing more
than take a day off.
And from some of the articles that I found,
it seems like Grant, the station manager guy, was like, yeah,
we were getting ready to start playing their music again
anyway, but we wanted to do it on our terms.
And this wasn't the way we wanted to do it.
Right, right, right.
You guys stole our thunder.
I could see how this would be like, eh, you know what?
It's ultimately the audience and the people.
It's been two months.
The audience is kind of over it.
The rage cycle has run its course.
We got it.
Freedom fries.
Let's move on.
It's stupid.
And so the station's getting ready to be like,
let's go back to normal.
Let's just pretend this is happening.
Landslide.
People like that song.
Yeah, everybody's fine.
Everybody's fine.
Yeah.
And these guys just jump the gun.
Yeah, which is also interesting, and maybe probably
for the best, I bet they got a shit ton of free press
out of that.
He even suspended them, and then they came back,
and everybody was like, yeah, you guys are back on that.
I don't know.
I don't know if you remember those dudes' names.
Oh, no.
They're titans of the industry now.
I just said their names.
You don't remember them.
Dave Grohl.
I mean, it's a story that you kind of remember in as much as
I do remember that there were some DJs who got in trouble
for playing Dixie Chicks.
Sure, sure.
I don't remember those details.
I don't remember their names.
No.
I don't think that they're Kevin and Bean.
Or have not gone on to live echoing throughout history.
That's true.
Yeah, so I don't know if the publicity stunt angle of it
worked out as well as you imagine.
But yeah.
Yeah, good for that.
Anyway, when I heard that they were going to be on,
I thought, OK, here we go.
Yeah.
This is nonsense.
This should be fun.
This is exactly the kind of thing
that I think is really fun about going back to 2003.
Totally.
These long-forgotten sort of, I don't want to call it trivial,
because what happened to the Dixie Chicks was so unfair.
And I'm not going to minimize that at all.
Of course.
But in terms of Alex's world, this
is trivial compared to we're all going to die.
Right, right, right.
We're fighting the literal devil.
Also, these two guys got suspended
for playing the Dixie Chicks.
So there's a little bit of a disconnect in stakes,
if you will.
And it's a time when these guys are probably
not super political.
But they don't know who Alex Jones is.
He has a nationally syndicated show.
Right, right, right, right.
Why not go on it?
So you get this weird intersection
of things that would never happen nowadays.
And I think it's amazing.
Yeah.
Anyway, just to check in on where Alex is at with the NRA.
How are they doing?
They would then deny that S-22 even existed,
the gun registration bill.
But now it's come out that it does.
And they weren't going to warn you about it.
So they're loyal opposition.
And it makes sense.
When the NRA gets more members, when
things are going badly for the Second Amendment,
they get more signups.
Yeah, so Alex doesn't like the NRA at all.
He hates them.
I don't like this.
I don't like going into the past as much as you do.
Because I find that his behavior is less egregious.
And thus makes me feel more like I'm saying stuff
where I'm like, I mean, yeah, that's a good point.
I don't like it.
Because his behavior is still egregious.
It's just under the surface.
No, no, no.
But also, here's the thing that we
need to really finally delineate.
It's like, yes, opposition to the NRA is great.
Opposition to Bush is great.
We can agree with those things as sentences
on a piece of paper.
Correct.
Now, the motivation for why Alex is against both of those things
is different than what we think.
Totally.
And so I actually think that you can be,
what you're experiencing is exactly
what lured a lot of people who wouldn't agree
with Alex's radical politics.
Exactly.
Into thinking he was more in the center than he actually is.
Totally.
You know, you think like, oh, this guy doesn't like the NRA.
Right.
Maybe he's one of these people who's kind of conservative
but kind of gets it.
No, he's more extreme than the NRA.
Totally.
I know.
That's so frustrating.
He's attacking from way far to the right.
I know.
It's so frustrating that he could get away
with it conceivably.
Yeah.
And he does.
He does.
And he does, as we're talking about him now.
So obviously got away with it.
And I think it worked really well for him at this era.
Yeah, he nailed it.
Yeah.
And I think one of the things that is really good for him,
too, is this branding.
And we're talking about this attacking the NRA
from the right, because he is a extreme right wing person.
Right, right, right.
And attacking Bush because he's extremely
far to the right of Bush, not because he's to the left
or he's in the center.
People could get that impression.
And Alex plays into that impression.
Totally.
And in this next clip, he's talking
about how people call him a commie
because he's against Bush.
Again, I will make the admission here.
I'm pro-gun 110%.
It's an absolute right.
I'm pro-sovereignty.
I'm pro-family.
I'm for low taxes.
I'm for abolishing the Federal Reserve.
That means in today's dialectic that I am a ultra communist.
Now, if you're a neocon who's an admitted Trotskyite,
if you're a beatnik who has a national talk show
and who's an admitted communist, you are now a conservative.
And I'm not being sarcastic.
I am now a communist because I'm pro-America.
They, the communists, learned how to flap American flags
in our face and talk about how conservative they are.
They are now the conservatives.
See, Alex has this superficial defining himself
by opposition to things that actually
does fool a lot of people.
I'm opposed to Bush.
And now everyone calls me a commie.
When I was against Clinton, they called
me a hard-right extremist.
You were, and you still are.
Right.
Yeah.
I don't know if I ever had anybody who I heard say,
like, Alex is a communist because he's against Bush.
No.
I just think that people thought he was more sensible
than you might think on first blush.
Right.
And if you are an enemy of any part of the right wing,
you will be called a communist, regardless
of anything you may or may not have ever said or believed.
Possibly by other people in the right wing.
Yeah.
No, definitely.
Like Alex is calling Michael Savage a communist.
Exactly.
No, definitely that.
That's what I'm saying.
This is just bickering.
Yeah.
It's just whining.
So I think that there is a pretty key problem there, too.
And I do think that it's something
that I notice about Alex.
And that is the defining self by opposition
or by others' response.
Yeah.
When he talks all the time about knowing that he's right
because people are attacking him and stuff,
it's like, that's not a reliable metric of, you know,
oh, I'm right because everybody hates me.
It's like, wow.
Yeah.
Does that mean that ISIS is right?
No.
If he goes to therapy one time, the first question
is just going to be like, how do you define yourself?
And he's going to talk about everybody but himself.
And he's going to be like, no, but like from the inside.
And it's going to be six years of constant talking
to just even figure out where he starts.
Yeah.
So these DJs come on.
And I got to say, there's a little bit
of a different style for Alex.
He opens the interview by asking a tough question.
OK.
Let me just get this out of the way up front.
Was this a stunt you guys pulled with management?
Absolutely not.
No.
Nope.
All right.
Well, we did it.
Good journalism, everybody.
Let's go.
Let's wrap it up and go home.
That's certainly better journalism
than he normally does.
It is.
It is very much better than a leading question like, so,
how long has your management been evil
and in the pocket of the devil and the globalists
that have been trying to oppress you?
I think Alex's bedside manner leaves a little bit
to be desired there in terms of like, was this a stunt?
No.
Shit.
No follow-up questions.
I was going to say, that does have the feel of like,
maybe if I just surprise them aggressively,
they'll be tricked into answering honestly.
So one of the things that I think Alex had been presenting,
and I think it's what a lot of people felt,
was that this was a principled stand
that these DJs were making.
That it was, they were opposed to the band,
and they played this music as a way of being like, no.
We believe in free speech.
Pirate radio.
Vietnam War.
We're doing it all over again.
If you listen to them, it's very clear
that that's not the case.
OK.
They did not agree with what Natalie said.
They agreed with the band.
They just thought it had run its course.
Due to a majority of, not all of our listeners,
a couple of months ago saying they did not
want to hear the Dixie Chicks on our radio station because
of what Natalie Main said about our president over in London.
So it was starting to turn the other way,
like can you start playing the Chicks?
Yeah, we had requests for them and everything.
But we decided we are, for our troops, 100%,
we're for the president 100%, but we're also
for the First Amendment 100%.
Should Natalie Main, the Dixie Chicks, say what she said?
Absolutely not.
Well, America, I mean, in America,
you've got the First Amendment.
That's what the military is for, is
to defend our constitutional republic.
And just this whole blacklisting, this whole demonization
of the Dixie Chicks over this has sent shockwaves
across the country, a giant chilling effect,
and America's going in the wrong direction here.
Well, but they were fine with this for two months.
Yeah.
They were fine.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Until the tide started to turn and people were like,
eh, we want to listen to the Dixie Chicks.
Ed, didn't you read the First Amendment?
It has an expiration date of two months.
I don't know.
I mean, I don't know how I feel about this
from a station management perspective.
Do they have the right to just say,
I don't want to play this person's songs?
If they don't have a contract that they have to play,
maybe it's shitty if you're not playing someone's music because
of a political reason.
But if you're a metal station, you're
not required to play reggae, right?
Unless, I don't know, Wyclef says something anti-Bush,
then you have to play it.
And so it is a protest to not play it.
What if this is, like, we're talking mid, late 90s,
you've got an alternative station,
but you hate Peanut, just personally.
Just personally.
Do you have to play 311?
I assume not.
If you're a station manager and you just
have a personal problem with Nick Hexum,
do you have to play 311?
I don't think so.
I don't know.
It's weird.
And certainly, I'm opposed to politically just saying,
no, your politics are such that I'm not
going to play your songs.
But I mean, if I was going to be impressed by these DJs having
any interest in the First Amendment,
then their actions would have probably come earlier.
No, it is a little bit like a.
This is just, I've decided that it is no longer popular for me
to suppress this speech.
Yeah, I mean, it's like if Barnes and Noble was like,
eh, we're not going to carry Jane Austen.
We're just not doing it.
I remember her comments about Bush.
And so we don't carry it anymore.
And then two months later, they're like, eh,
we'll put Jane Austen back in there.
No big deal.
Yeah, this new Jane Austen novel is pretty hot.
People like it.
So yeah, this is pretty much exactly what they say.
They're just like, oh, the listeners
wanted them to come back.
We listened to our listeners.
And the listeners said they didn't want to play it,
so we listened.
Well, that's good, but I do want you guys
to go back and get on the radio and go,
you can tune into Alex Jones at 1580.
Will you do that for me?
No, seriously, guys.
Was that a joke?
No.
He said no.
Seriously, guys.
I think that was not a joke.
That was very much not a joke.
Guys, please give me a plug, please.
That wasn't even like one of those jokes where you laugh,
but you're hoping they'll be like, no, no, no.
We're totally going to do that.
You'll be like, no, that wasn't what I was trying to do.
I was just making a joke.
It wasn't that.
It was like, hey, plug me on your show.
No, seriously.
Hey, guys, you made a lot of news with that suspension,
and you might have more listeners right now.
And could you please plug me?
Yeah, it is nice to know that clout chasing, still
strong back in 2003.
Oh, yeah, he was an early adopter.
So Alex has, it's fucking clear.
He doesn't really spell it out, but it's really clear
that he thinks that there's a conspiracy afoot.
So here's the conspiracy.
Clear channel on a bunch of radio stations.
I already believe it.
Right?
Yeah.
So Clear Channel own a bunch of radio stations
and also a bunch of concert venues.
True.
So what they have done.
And billboards?
They have manufactured a whole crisis
where the Dixie Chicks get kicked off these stations that
are owned by Clear Channel.
And then they go on tour, and they sell out all their shows
at these venues that are owned by Clear Channel.
Now, I would suggest that the Dixie Chicks don't
need to sell more tickets.
No, they were doing all right.
They were huge.
They were about at the peak of their power.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They were huge.
One of the reasons that it was so nuts
that they were almost piling on them in the right way
was because they were in the top three, top four country music
acts in the world.
They were killing it.
Yeah, yeah.
That's why they had to be taken down,
because they had too large of a platform to criticize Bush
with.
Yes.
So Alex tries to lay out this conspiracy to the DJs.
Now, for this conspiracy to make sense,
there's two things that need to be true.
One, this needs to be a Clear Channel station.
True.
Two, the venue where the Dixie Chicks are playing
needs to be owned by Clear Channel.
Both of those must be true for this conspiracy
to have any effect on them.
Now, I have read that is your station Clear Channel?
No.
OK.
I mean, I have some on there.
They said that simultaneously?
I actually read this piece of history.
They've been asked that a lot.
Clear Channel, a big part of their business
isn't just playing music.
It's putting on concerts.
Is it true, from what you know, that Clear Channel was actually
involved in promoting Dixie Chicks concerts?
I don't know if they are the promoter behind the Dixie
Chicks concerts or not.
I know they have several venues across the country,
including a couple in Colorado.
And they have Clear Channel Entertainment,
which promotes concerts.
But I'm not sure if they're one of the promoters for the Chicks
or not.
Have the Dixie Chicks played at their venues?
They, not at their, well, their venue in Colorado
is fairly small.
The Dixie Chicks will be playing at the Pepsi Center, which
is a large venue.
That's where the Nuggets and the Avalanche play.
Yeah, well, I have read that they've been involved.
So could it be a larger publicity stunt?
Boy, they get all this attention.
I guess we won't know.
But you know, on radio, people do pull stunts.
And we're trying to find that out.
People do pull stunts.
True.
But this has fallen apart.
Usually, it's more like payola or something like that.
Sure.
Not necessarily this.
I think that this interview has fascinatingly fallen apart.
Because these DJs are not free speech crusaders in the way
that Alex maybe would have liked them to be.
It would have been great.
And now, they have refuted twice in the span of about a minute
pillars of his conspiracy that Clear Channel is trying
to boost their live ticket sales for one of the most popular
acts in the world by pulling a stunt where they get
kicked off radio stations.
Yeah, yeah.
If you were Alex, and you had a top three of things
that you hoped were true, at least one of those
should have been true.
Man.
None of those.
No.
Oh, that's not good.
Nope.
At the very least, you're not a data point
for the Clear Channel conspiracy.
So I think Alex is recognizing some of the similar things
that I am, and that is that this has fallen apart.
Sure.
And so he decides to retreat to attacking these guys.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
We support Natalie Maine's right to say whatever she wants.
So since you said it, we don't agree with what you said
by any means.
Let me ask you a question.
You guys supported, then, the takeover of Iraq.
Well, you know, we support our troops.
And it's hard to say whether we're there,
because I don't know personally whether or not
there are weapons of mass destruction
and whether there's a necessity to do what is being done.
I'm not an expert on that.
But you're supporting the troops end to end.
We understand that, but wouldn't you
say it supports the troops, not to sell Saddam, VX, and sarin,
and then order our troops to blow up the bunkers,
and then when they breathe that stuff in 91,
to not give them treatment?
Because that's a big deal.
That really hurt the troops right there.
Well, that's true.
Of course, we're just country DJs,
and for us, it's about the music, mainly.
Yeah.
They are just country DJs.
This is unfair.
This is a writ.
I like that defense.
Yeah.
I would like to use that.
Yeah, OK.
So my position is that I support the troops.
And your rebuttal to that is making
me own literally everything the government has ever done?
Great.
How about I tell you that I'm a country DJ,
and we move the fuck along, because I'm not
going to litigate every decision the government has ever made.
What a great comeback.
Because what do you expect from a country DJ?
I'll tell you what.
Complicated and clear-eyed views of global international
politics?
No.
And they even express.
We have some fun on our show.
We play music.
We're not all that political.
Certainly, coming on a show, you certainly confuse us.
Why did you say all those words?
I think that that is Alex just trying to take something
from the interview, because it went so poorly.
Clear channel conspiracy didn't work out.
These guys aren't heroes.
They're kind of just morning zoo dicks.
Yeah.
If you have been deflated so completely by these assholes,
then there's also that little bit of Alex's resentment
coming out of like, you didn't give me what I want,
so I will take it from you.
That kind of feel, yeah.
So I think that there's a little bit of a codependency
with the audience.
And this caller who calls in after the interview
wants to make Alex feel better and try and help him
with that clear channel conspiracy.
First of all, the name of the promotions company
is SFX Entertainment is promoting the Dixie Chicks concert.
You go to the website, it comes up Clear Channel Entertainment.
Yeah, that's what I've seen that actually, who was it?
It was Reuters ran an article like two weeks ago on that.
Yeah, SFX, and it's Clear Channel.
And then they start the ban, which then
makes it all go down.
Everybody suddenly wants it.
Then they make more money off of it.
But here's the big scam.
It doesn't matter.
It still creates a chilling effect for everybody else.
Ooh, you better not speak out, because then you'll be banned,
and people never even know it was a scam.
Yeah, second thing, I just kind of wanted to gloss over that.
Does that make you mad?
Yeah, it does.
It really does.
It should.
It does.
It really does make me mad.
SFX Entertainment is Live Nation that
was bought by Clear Channel and then got spun off
into its own thing again.
Yeah, I don't know.
I couldn't go back and figure out if the Dixie Chicks,
all of their events were run through Live Nation.
Sure.
I don't know.
I don't think.
And I also don't care.
It doesn't prove any conspiracy here.
Yeah, I was going to say, on the list of, again, I believe
we are at this moment fighting the literal devil who
is destroying all of Iraq in order,
in service of destroying all of the United States.
So what Clear Channel's doing about the Dixie Chicks
promotions?
Trying to make a few extra bucks on tickets?
I mean, yeah.
Whatever.
Go for it, Clear Channel.
I would say that I'd be willing to stipulate, and not
accept as true, but I'll just go ahead and not even fight it,
that Clear Channel, by virtue of Alive Nation,
is doing ticketing for all of the Dixie Chicks.
Sure.
Sure, why not?
That still doesn't prove the conspiracy.
And now it's just acting like hearing that is like,
a-ha-ha, slim dunk.
True.
Now, I won't put it past the recording industry.
They pull off some bullshit all the time.
Yeah, man.
I saw Josie and the Pussycats.
Yeah, the whole industry's bullshit.
That movie was fraught with scandal.
I get it, all of these conspiracies.
So a caller calls in, another one, and he's got a theory.
But sometimes, Alex's show is being blocked out by waves.
OK.
I think sometimes when you come on air,
they try to block you out, too, because you
hit so much truthful points.
What do you mean they try to block a show?
Well, I know frequencies, I know other listeners
in the area who listen to you at the same hours.
If they're going to listen to you late at night,
they can't get you in, too.
And it'd be a frequency, and you can hear it,
but I don't know if they're trying to block you out or what,
but sometimes, I call other people,
and they get in the same thing, too.
But you can hear us fine during the day, though.
Fine during the day, but at nighttime, when people are home
and want to listen to the radio, yeah, everybody
wants to get the same block out.
They can't get you in.
Yeah, well, that's probably just because AMs
aren't as strong at night.
Listen, thank you for the call.
I appreciate it.
Great, great.
What a bad job by Alex.
What a bad job.
I just wrote down, what do you mean they block us out?
Like, Alex said, what do you mean they block us out?
Not, obviously, they block us out.
They're always trying to block us out.
They've been trying to block us out since I started,
because I know too much.
Well, I think Alex realizes there's not
money in that, probably.
And the only action you might end up precipitating
is harassment of the stations that do play him.
That's true.
And you might end up cutting in.
You might bite the hand that feeds there.
Sure, sure.
Can't do that.
So this might actually just be something like,
it's not even worth it to try and convince people.
Spin this into, yeah.
We're under attack.
Like, what are you going to do?
You're going to end up fucking with the affiliates.
Right, right, right, right, right.
No good.
So Alex gets down to describing his enemies.
See if you hear the devil in here.
It's not a dictatorship of Bill Clinton or George Bush.
They're just puppets.
It's a dictatorship of the military industrial complex
was bankrolled and founded to run this country
by the private European banks.
There's no fight between the EU and the UN in America.
It's all owned by the same private shareholders,
the Warbirds, the Rothschilds, the Rockefellers,
the Dutch Royal Family, the British Royal Family,
the Bilderberg Group, the people that meet and publicly call
for open world dictatorship.
So that sounds astoundingly terrestrial.
Yeah.
That sounds like business interests
who have an idea of working together
to create a worldwide dictatorship tyranny.
Yeah.
It does not seem like it's people
who are in the employ of the devil who has contacted them
via transdimensional demons and offered them life extension
technology if they carry out an elaborate and hyper complicated
plan to slowly and orderly kill off humanity.
Should they fail to do that, they
have a backup plan to just really super bio weapons
and kill everybody off.
It seems like this is a guy who wants
to at least be taken seriously as a not science fiction
writer.
Yeah.
His improvised storytelling is much more like Grisham
at this point as opposed to Philip K. Dick.
This is the firm.
That's what this is.
It's fighting against powerful lawyers,
taking over everything.
No, I got it.
It's not magical realism.
No, no.
Indeed, in fact, it seems like his biggest problem
is ultimately what the end result of capitalism
always seems to be, which is staggering wealth and inequality
leading to an aristocratic business class.
I'd love for you to go back in time
and talk to him about that.
That would be interesting.
So that caller who's talking about Alex being under attack
through waves, right?
Sure.
Man, I thought he was nuts.
Oh, have we changed our mind already?
US terror plan called Cuban invasion pretext.
US military leaders proposed in 62 a secret plan
to commit terrorist acts against Americans
and blame Cuba to create a pretext for invasion
and ouster of communist leader Fidel Castro who they put in.
No, they use the war against the communists
as a way to warp the minds of our military men and our CIA
and get them to do evil things and set up
a culture of evil, which is now used for narcotics trafficking
and money laundering and white slavery,
every other evil you can imagine.
And it goes on.
It's a scalar attack.
Too much truth.
Now, Alex, he plays a song and then he comes back
from break and is like, yeah, we're in Texas
and the satellites in Minnesota, so sometimes there's problems.
He's very just like, eh, it happens.
It happens.
It's part of the gig.
That's fair, but could be an attack
because he's telling too much truth.
Possible.
So Alex has an article in the LA Times
that he's been bringing up a little bit,
and this has to do with our old boy Joseph McCarthy.
Oh, boy.
Continuing with the news, despite McCarthy,
red peril really was.
John Maroney, LA Times.
And it goes on.
It says the document shouldn't be
allowed to undermine the important historical fact
that Soviet communism was a very real threat to US defense
and freedom, and the anti-communist fight waged
in the country was a moral one, even though the Communist
Party succeeded in seducing an estimated 230,000
Americans to its ranks over the course of 40 years.
And it now says that the documents released
show that McCarthy was right.
This article from the LA Times is an opinion piece,
and Alex is actually lying about the main thrust of the article.
The author, John Maroney, is arguing
that there was a point to opposing communism
during the Cold War, but the actions of people
like Joseph McCarthy gave that opposition a really bad name.
Because McCarthy was an opportunist, fraud,
and demagogue. Even in that sentence,
Alex reads the words, quote, the documents
shouldn't be allowed to undermine
the important historical fact that the Soviet communism was
a very real threat.
Like, those words don't make sense.
Sure.
Aren't his listeners curious why this article is arguing
that documents would possibly undermine
that notion if this article is about vindicating McCarthy?
Possible.
The headline literally starts, quote, despite McCarthy.
Yeah.
Anyway.
Those things are in the headline and everything,
because these documents that got released in 2003
were a record of secret hearings that McCarthy held
with witnesses prior to them making public appearances,
and he was attempting to intimidate them.
Yeah.
From an article about the documents from the BBC, quote,
many had only tenuous connections with communists
through family members or book clubs where Marx was read
or unions with left wing leaders.
The new documents paint a picture
of a senator out of control, summoning witnesses
at short notice and brow beating them
with the threat of imprisonment or public disgrace.
But it was noticeable that those he could not
intimidate in private were often not called in public session.
How shitty is our government press
that they're like, these documents show
Joseph McCarthy was unhinged.
Like, I don't know if you were alive when he was around?
They reveal a new level of artifice and craft.
Sure.
The articles that I was reading about this really
laid out how different he behaved in the public hearings
and these private ones.
Sure.
And there was kind of, it almost feels
like a feeling out process.
Like that last sentence there, you
know, the people that wouldn't back down to him
typically weren't called for the public ones
because that doesn't create the public perception that he
is looking to grandstand with.
Sure.
Also from the article, quote, according
to Senate historian David Ritchie,
the private hearings were more of an inquisition
using circumstantial evidence, hearsay, and intimidation
to force people to acknowledge his point of view.
The documents that came out in 2003 paint
Joseph McCarthy as an out of control lunatic
trying to run a witch hunt.
And this LA Times editorial is an attempt
to remind readers that just because McCarthy really
sucked, that doesn't mean that Soviet communism didn't exist.
Hey, Torquemada, what do you say to the inquisition?
If you were really someone who was opposed to communism
and you'd read this article, you couldn't come away from it,
honestly, with the position that it vindicated McCarthy.
The article literally says, quote,
many seem to have forgotten that the Communist
Party was dedicated to replacing our democratic form
of government with a totalitarian state
similar to what existed in the Soviet Union.
McCarthy and those who exploited his excesses
are largely to blame for this.
According to Moroni, McCarthy is a detriment
to the opposition of communism.
Essentially, the only two conclusions
I can come to about Alex's coverage of this article
are the following.
One, he didn't read the article and he
thinks it actually says that McCarthy was totally cool
and he's just making up what the body of the text says.
Two, defending McCarthyism and the tactics of witch hunting
is more important to Alex than actually being opposed
to communism, which makes his anti-communism essentially
tactical as opposed to something that's based on principle.
Yeah, I was going to say.
I'm not entirely sure what I think.
I was going to say, you just read
Alex is also a detriment to anti-communism
in the exact same fashion that Joseph McCarthy was.
So naturally, he would want to defend McCarthy as well.
Yeah, it seems like.
Nobody's like, hey, you know what's great?
It's the John Birch Society fighting communism.
I think they really did a great job.
I think they really got to the points
and they really hammered it on.
It seems like he is, you know, like idealistically
and ideologically opposed to communism and all this.
Sure.
But if he can't do it like McCarthy did it,
he doesn't want to do it.
Exactly, exactly.
Yes, if I can't defeat sex trafficking
with a daring sunlight raid, then I
don't want to deal with that.
I just want to make everybody else angry about it.
Yeah, I get the sense that he would not
be so opposed to communism if his route to do it
was to be an economics professor or a researcher who
got no fanfare and didn't get to do
these bombastic public hearings like McCarthy, which
is Alex's radio show.
If he wasn't able to make a show out of it,
I don't know if he would be as interested.
If leftists weren't as academic and more just shithead
screaming, we might have Alex on our side
is basically what we're talking about here.
Maybe.
Yeah, it's possible.
He just hates theory so much, Dan.
He hates it whenever they get into theory.
Yeah.
So Alex takes another call.
And this guy has a decent point, and Alex
has a terrible answer to it.
And that is, why are we even talking
about the assault weapons ban?
It doesn't even come up until next year.
2004 is when it's up for renewal or let it lap.
Sure, sure.
And so Alex has an interesting answer
that I think is totally wrong and on brand.
Hi, Alex.
How are you doing?
I've reflected on some things over the last 24 hours,
and there's several different points.
First off, something dawned upon me.
Why is the administration dealing with the assault weapons
ban 15 months before the issue even comes due in the middle
of this climate with so many concerns about the war
and so forth?
Why even deal with that out of the blue so far in advance?
That's strange.
Because they want to act like they're right when they
activate some mind control fruitcake.
You know, The Matrix is coming out,
which they say is a big trigger.
Yeah.
Tend to agree.
So he tends to agree that there's probably
going to be a shooting at the second Matrix opening
or second Matrix movie, because it's going to be a trigger.
And then they're talking about the assault weapons ban stuff
so they can be right in advance for this thing that
didn't happen.
Right.
Cool.
And this is a precedent to the way
he engages with shootings in the future.
Like, this pattern of thinking is there all along.
Yeah.
That almost sounds like Norm Pattis, doesn't it?
The caller?
Doesn't that voice almost sound like him?
I'm not sure.
Through a phone, I can kind of hear it,
and I would love to find out that that was actually
a young Norm.
No way.
Like, developing their relationship.
Oh, man.
The vibe that I get from Norm from those early appearances
is either someone who legitimately doesn't really
understand what Alex does or somebody
who really, really wants people to think
he doesn't understand what he does.
I don't know.
It just sounds like we're in a TV show in our eighth season,
and we start doing all the flashbacks.
And it turns out our main characters all coincidentally
met 20 years ago.
We've already done that, though, and in the 2015 episodes,
we heard Owen Troyer call in as a fan.
That's true.
What a weird world.
Yeah.
So here, Alex is wrong about things
that will happen in the future.
In Boston, Logan Airport, and four other airports,
they put NASA brain scanners in to, quote,
tell if you're agitated.
In 1984, they didn't scan your brain.
This is total information awareness, worse than 1984.
Then they say, oh, but it's to keep you safe.
It's to keep you safe, America.
We just want to keep you safe.
The borders stay wide open, and they're putting the Bathys
back in power in Iraq because they're
good thugs trained by the CIA in the 70s and 80s.
I'm really interested.
I know this is getting repetitive in these 2003
episodes, but I'm really, really interested in what's
going to happen when de-Bathification comes around.
Because he's hitting this note so consistently.
On every show, he's bringing up how the Bathys are in charge.
And it's because that's who the US government
and the globalists want to be in charge.
Right, right, right.
He's so insistent about something
that we know for a fact to be 100% diametrically
the opposite.
And he is going to eventually run into that brick wall,
driving at 60 miles an hour.
Exactly.
And that's what I'm so interested to see.
Does he hit the brakes at a certain point?
Or does he just go straight through?
Yeah, I don't know.
So we'll see.
So another caller calls in.
Is he like the Road Runner where he paints the wall,
he paints the tunnel on there, and he goes through it.
You're like, what the fuck?
I feel like that metaphorically is
what he does a lot of the time, just create a fake tunnel.
Drive through it.
So a caller calls in, wants to know about underground prisons
that are being built.
I wanted to ask you if you had any information on underground
prison camps that they're developing.
Yes, I have mainstream news articles.
INS Kentucky poured concrete for two years
under a giant underground old coal mine
and built a supermax on top of it with airfields
and everything.
They're building giant prisons everywhere.
It's the new economy, a giant prison economy
where they literally own us, where torture
is the order of the day and is a virtue.
That's very interesting because down here in Trinidad,
we're having seismographic readings.
And in Trinidad was a site of an old Japanese internment camp,
and it has old mines, but they're
getting seismographic readings, but there's no faults there.
And so I'm going to collect as much heart as I can.
Sir, your Denver International Airport
has pictures of Nazis machine gunning piles of dead bodies,
satanic art everywhere, a giant FEMA camp on it publicly.
Sure.
Really?
Yeah, you ever seen the artwork in the Denver airport?
Bro?
Yeah, so cool.
This is very strange.
This is very strange to listen to Alex
be like, the prison pipeline or the prison industrial complex
is going to eventually become what it is.
Like, he's right on about the prison complex.
And then to hear the crazier conspiracy theory
from his caller.
Like, that weirds me out.
We're living in a complete topsy-turvy world
because normally, nowadays, he would come out with something
like, you know, the devil's killing everybody,
and they're like, yeah, but maybe the devil
is just trying to raise the corporate tax rate.
Like, you know, it's a very weird inversion
of the way this goes.
Yeah, it is true.
And speaking of, like, an inversion of the present,
this next call is fucked up, if you
consider Alex in the present.
OK.
Now, that's what I'm saying.
We need to increase, you know, demanding that they bring
these people to justice, the whole Bush administration
and all these surf minions and bootlickers.
Well, let me ask you a question.
You certainly know that Bush is just a puppet, though, right?
Right.
We need to get his puppet mask.
Well, I would agree that the Rothschilds and others
need to be exposed.
We've got a person exposing them.
They need to be exterminated like they
had a plan for everybody else.
If it's good enough for everybody else,
it's probably good enough for them.
Well, I'm not sure my audio's cutting out,
but I appreciate your call, Omar.
Right.
Your audio is cutting out.
Wow.
Sure.
His caller said that they need to exterminate their enemies.
And the puppet masters of the globalist puppets like Bush.
Jesus.
And Alex pretends that he didn't hear him and goes to break.
When he comes back from the break,
he makes a point to bring this back up.
I talked to the folks running the show.
I wanted to, because I wasn't sure.
I heard what I heard from Curtis.
Or no, it wasn't Curtis.
Curtis is coming up.
That was, I was talking to Omar last segment
from Michigan, and so I did hear what I thought I heard.
My audio was low.
Omar, let me explain something to you, OK?
I'm sure you're a nice person and mean well,
and I appreciate your hard work, and you
say you're waking folks up.
But look, I've tried to make this clear,
and this is what I truly believe and know,
and I know what I'm talking about.
I work on this probably harder than anybody else.
Fighting the new world order, defending my family,
standing against crime, standing against evil.
Have you not learned what I've said here, what history shows?
The globalists carry out violent acts
against their own institutions as a way
to legitimize power and control and domination
and the destruction of liberty.
Violence is not the way to go.
I will say it over and over and over again.
Now, I know that Alex says politically,
I want to kill you in the future or whatever.
He'll give lip service to the idea of nonviolence.
This is an instance where he clearly
was caught off guard by this caller saying,
we need to exterminate these folks,
and then went to break and decided to come back,
re-bring it up to stress that violence is not the way to go.
Dan, haven't you heard the old adage?
If you're not a liberal at 20, you have no heart.
And if you don't want to exterminate the poor at 40,
you have no brain.
Everybody knows this.
There's a real sense that I get that Alex might be a little bit
more keenly aware of how dangerous some
of the people who are drawn to his world view may be.
Possible.
I don't know, though.
It's foreign as hell.
Maybe he just doesn't have the, I mean,
he's just more in a vulnerable position, you know?
He's still got bosses at this time.
He doesn't have complete autocratic, yeah, well,
that's fair.
But I mean, he still has to answer to someone.
There is still someone above him.
And now there is no one above him.
Well, his dad is HR.
I don't know if his dad is still alive.
I think this is a psycho situation where his dad is
actually in his attic a skeleton.
I just think it's very interesting that Alex is,
I mean, it's still, like, obviously this broadcast is
still incredibly irresponsible, but there
is a complete world of difference
between taking a step back to calmly and emphatically stress
that there's no violence.
Violence is no good.
It's not the answer.
And Alex's long pornographic rants
about slitting people's throats and talking
about how all the globalists are already dead and all
this in the present day.
Yeah, I mean, if you want to, that's such a bullshit
argument, cancel culture.
Look at how people act when there are possible consequences.
Look at how people act whenever you just
know that consequences are available versus when you act
when there are absolutely none.
To be done.
There's something to be said for that.
You know, it's there.
It's there.
You act better.
So I think that this leads Alex into.
Or at least psychos do.
Alex, for the rest of the episode,
he gets into a bit of a headspace
where he's saying things that, like, a lot of it
sounds pretty good.
I don't believe him.
And obviously, because I know where his show goes.
Sure, sure.
Certainly don't.
Living in the future is tough.
Don't think that he means it, but.
We have just got to continue to be bold, to be loving,
to stand against this evil.
Hate is not going to power us.
Hate is not going to get the job done.
Now, certainly, you have a right to defend yourself
against criminals and against people that are assaulting you
and assaulting your family.
But offensively, offensively, it is
wrong to go after the illegitimate government
because they want that.
That's the reason?
I guess?
It's really interesting for Alex to say
that hate can't power their movement or whatever.
Because, I mean, I would say that that's
one of the major problems with the right wing
as it exists today.
Yeah, yeah.
Because hate fuels their worldview.
And I think it did, too, for Alex in 2003.
Totally.
Maybe he wasn't even as aware of it.
It's not as overt.
Yeah.
Or he just casts such a wide net,
he doesn't even know the difference
between hate and not hate.
And so, you know, you got this head space
where you don't want to exterminate your enemies.
No, that would be bad.
Alex just wants them to back off.
Sure.
Back off, globalists.
We are not revolutionaries.
We are restorationists.
We want America, the republic, back.
Back.
We just want the globalists to stop what they're doing
and to back off.
And we know that when they see weakness, they attack.
We know when they see ignorance, they move forward.
And I want to advise the globalists right now,
I want to give you some really good advice.
And you can check.
I've done 800 radio interviews since 9-1-1.
800 now.
I've done my own syndicated show on AM and FM's
all over the country.
That doesn't count as an interview.
I have a website that gets millions of hits a month.
Definitely doesn't count as an interview.
Let me tell you, for every 500 positive emails,
I get one negative.
And the people are so incoherent,
they are probably going to be IQs or lower.
I have done 800 interviews.
And one out of 30 callers disagrees with me.
Folks, let me tell you something, globalists.
You're in a lot of trouble.
They're in so much trouble.
Alex has good reviews.
And people often don't find it worth their time
to argue with them, I guess.
But yeah, they just need to back off.
And hey, there's good news.
I've got some advice for Alex.
Back off.
Why would he?
They're winning or something.
Sure.
I would say that if the globalists, when they see
weakness, they attack.
And when they see dumbness, they move forward.
Sure.
The preceding eight years after this
indicate that Alex and all of his friends are dumb and weak.
Yes, correct.
Because the globalists didn't stop anything
according to Alex.
That is exactly what they proved.
That's interesting.
In 2003, it turns out there's not many globalists.
You know what's going on.
And if you sit there and shake and coward and sit there,
you're delivering your children into a living hell,
a hell on Earth, Hades on Earth.
And I'm here to tell you that it's a handful.
A few thousand globalist managers,
a few dozen families that own this thing,
they're counting on you being ignorant.
If you find out they're counting on you being afraid
and being cowardly, you have got to be men.
You have got to be women.
You have got to be strong.
You have got to do whatever it takes
to stand up against this evil and to speak out
and to not be violent and to tell the truth
and let them burn us at the stake
if they want to in the arena, I'm ready.
I believe what Jesus Christ said.
I believe in decency.
I believe in wholesomeness.
Wholesomeness.
Wholesome.
That's how I would describe his show in the present day.
Very wholesome.
Wholesome.
Reminds me of the Buttercream Gang.
That's what it reminds me of.
Yeah.
That's who I think of when I think of Alex, Owen,
Harrison, whites are the best Smith.
I think of the Buttercream Gang.
Yeah, this was just really weird.
Cause it was, I mean, it's fill in time
and it's just a long rant more or less
just about how like we gotta be peaceful.
Yeah.
We can't be hateful.
Sure.
The globalists are in trouble cause we're so popular
and you have to be strong and we believe in wholesomeness.
It's all goodness.
Oh yeah.
And it all seems to be in response
to that caller bringing up extermination
of the enemies.
It does seem like it's genuine too.
I wonder if-
I mean in a certain sense.
I wonder if it's also in part because Alex
was probably pretty excited about getting these DJs on
and it didn't go well.
Sure.
I wonder if that plays into his mood a little bit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Since we know that generally speaking
what comes out of his mouth is the result
of how he's feeling.
Yeah.
As opposed to what's going on.
Yeah, yeah.
And I think that maybe the fact that that didn't
wasn't something he could build on at all
and he's just gonna have to pretend
that interview never happened.
Yeah, that's basically what he's doing, yes.
Yeah.
It's a mulligan or whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I wonder.
That'd be interesting.
Anyway, one of the things that we discovered
through every period of time that we've looked through
at least the last few years.
Sure.
Going back into 2015.
Right.
Even prior to Trump's candidacy, Alex loves Putin.
True.
And Russia.
Loves him.
Big strong man, I think he saw him on that horse
without his shirt on.
Well, he had a stretch where he was like,
it was bad that Putin kills journalists.
Yeah, that was a little farther back.
That was a little bit farther back, yeah.
True, true, true.
That was what, 2013?
Well, here's 2003.
Okay.
Look folks, Putin got caught.
Moscow police arrested FSB, the new KGB,
planning bombs in a fourth Moscow apartment building.
They took him to jail, they had him.
Putin's police raided it, arrested the cops,
took the bombs, that's a fact.
You know, government has to blow up its own stuff
as an excuse to crack down on you.
Figure that out.
In the present day, Alex does not believe this.
Oh no, absolutely not.
He does not believe that Putin was behind the bombings
that were blamed on the Chechen rebels.
No longer an expedient truth to know about.
Now, I think that there's something interesting about this,
and that is, when was the lie?
Was he lying about it being a fact in 2003?
Yeah.
Or is he lying now?
You gotta...
Or does he just not care?
I think he doesn't care.
Yeah, I mean, I think to a certain extent,
like when you think about a lie,
you do think about somebody with malicious intent
or at the very least, like desire to hide information
or something like that.
And to me, what I'm seeing from all of this totality now
is just a man who just doesn't give a fuck
if it's true or not or whatever.
He's not lying, he just doesn't care.
You know, he's just beyond lying or not lying.
He's just making up his own reality that he exists in
from a moment to moment point of view.
Yeah, and there's some things
that seem pretty consistently important.
Yeah.
Like him being left alone, Christian supremacy,
whiteness and guns. Totally, yeah.
And then he's figured out some sort of routines
that work pretty well, like the vaccine lies
and stuff that you just see him doing consistently.
Yeah, anyway, Alex has another caller.
Oh, jeez.
I just keep this in
because I think it makes Alex look like a dick.
Yeah, I want you to take 50 copies of Road to Tyranny
and hand it out to everybody.
I can't, I only have one VCR.
I can't copy it yet.
Need to buy another one, pay the 50 bucks,
buy the blank tapes and do it.
I guess, yeah, I know, but I don't even have 50 bucks.
I'm doing what I can.
Well, go to your neighbor, get it,
whenever you have to.
All right.
What?
Wow, that is presaging his televangelism right there.
Yeah.
He doesn't get more televangelist then.
Oh, sell your home, sell your home.
Give me, ask your kids for money to give it to me.
Go to your neighbor.
I need a private jet.
Go to your neighbor to go get money to buy a second VCR
so you can make copies of my movies.
Which you will give to your neighbor.
Yeah.
Wow.
Oh boy.
Anyway, I thought that was asshole-ish.
That's real dick-ish.
Yeah, I can't imagine the level of narcissistic
you have to be to have multiple follow-ups
when someone's explaining why they can't copy your tapes.
No, I mean, it's sales, you know?
That's that like, Bill, rich dad, poor dad,
like don't take no for an answer shit.
And you're like, no, that's psychopathic, you nutbag.
Back when I worked in telemarketing,
if your calls were monitored, like you would get in trouble
if you didn't have two rebuttals.
Yeah, exactly.
And that seems like what Alex is doing there,
but it's not sales, you're talking to a person.
Yeah, exactly.
But I guess it is sales.
About bullshit.
So we have one last clip here from May 9th.
And again, it's Alex talking about his enemies.
There's no mention of the devil.
Are you sure it's not the devil?
It's like Monday's Night Ritter headline,
Night Ritter newspapers.
Neocons call for New World Order.
Well, it's not the Neocons.
They're just the puppets of the day.
When they say Ashcroft wants Patriot Act Two,
no, the globalists want Patriot Act Two.
Don't be diverted by just these low level puppet nobodies.
Be focused on the real power, the New World Order bankers.
God bless you all.
Have a good weekend.
See you back at nine, nine to midnight.
Yeah, so it's New World Order bankers.
I mean,
I guess.
Multiple times in these two days,
he clearly expresses who he feels he's up against.
Yeah.
And it's all terrestrial concerns.
It's not an elaborate conspiracy of dimensions.
It's not.
No.
It's not metaphysical.
He didn't get any dreams when he was 10.
Nothing.
He wasn't a Satanist.
No.
Nope.
And I mean like this doesn't prove
that he never talks about any of this stuff,
but like a lot of the themes that you would think
might have been important are not important.
And if they normally come up now,
if he brings up something similar to these topics,
there's always that personal element of like,
you know, I was a Satanist.
You know, like that.
None of that shit.
None of that.
None of it.
Brutal.
No talk about Epstein.
No talk about cabals of secret child trading,
blood drinking.
Not even any Bill Gates.
Oh, he does mention Bill Gates at one point.
Oh, does he?
Yeah.
But Gates isn't in there with the Rothschilds
and the Bilderbergs at Citra.
No, this is a side mention of Bill Gates,
but I mean, of course he's been relevant for a long time
and a philanthropist.
And a piece of shit.
Alex hates that because it works counter
to his political positions of doing everything he can
to hurt the developing world.
Right.
Anyway, I enjoyed a little bit of this
in as much as, you know, the Dixie chick deejays.
Yeah.
We're interviewed.
What a bunch of dicks.
But, and I think that it's certainly,
I don't even want to know what Alex is doing
in the present day, quite frankly.
Oh no.
Good God, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm conflicted about whether or not
there's a need to cover present day.
Oh my God.
We will see.
We'll see.
Oh, sweet Jesus.
Anyway, whatever ends up happening, we'll be back.
Yes, we will.
But until then, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yes, we're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledgefight.com.
Go to bed, Jordan.
We're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook.
I too said if you could,
please find a local charity or bail fund in your area
to help out people doing God's work right now.
Yep, we'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundes.
This podcast is secretly brought to you by Clear Channel
and an elaborate conspiracy to sell tickets
to Alex Jones's live cabaret review.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.