N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys.
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight, I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes, I can sit around, talk about how great Selene is, and also discuss Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are, Dan.
Ah, Cult of Selene, whee!
Uh, hm.
See, I wasn't even going to bring attention to it that time.
Harumpf.
Dan!
Jordan.
I have a quick question for you.
What's up?
Uh, what's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, Jordan, is that I survived an ordeal that would destroy a lesser version of myself.
Oh, oh yes.
And that is that the other night, I ordered some food for delivery, and I went downstairs to get it, and I locked myself out.
Oh my god.
Locked myself out of the house at about 9.30 in the evening, and I was terrified.
Uh, yeah.
Because I didn't have my keys, I know my landlord's not going to come over, I don't even know who my landlord is.
No, absolutely not.
No, no, no, no, no.
They're not going to come let me in?
I can't break into my window, because it's not on the bottom floor.
Third floor, third floor is trouble.
Uh, I don't think that I have that kind of parkour ability, uh, to scale the building.
It would be difficult.
And so I was looking at the neighbors' windows, which is never great, and they're all dark.
Everything is dark.
I'm like, I'm not going to hit the buzzer and like wake somebody up.
Right.
That seems like too much.
Could be.
So I walked around the side of the building, and I saw someone's TV on, and I hit the buzzer.
And thankfully they buzzed me, but I was so terrified that I was like, well, great.
I've got my food, but now I guess I'll be-
Well, at least you wouldn't starve out there.
I was going to be eating and sleeping out in the alley tonight.
It was a warm night.
It wasn't too bad.
Yeah.
That's true.
And that might have been part of the reason why I forgot my keys.
Yeah, it could have been.
Uh, because it was just sort of like, hey.
Did you put your shoes on?
I think I had sandals.
Ooh, how dare you.
How dare you.
I know you're not a fan of slippers.
No open toothed shoes.
It's not open toe.
It's closed.
It's closed toe.
All right.
So what about you?
My Bright Spot, Deanne, is currently, as we speak, goes the Eurovision Song Contest.
I know every year you get very excited about, what the fuck?
No, you don't.
No, I don't.
No, I've never really even watched it before.
But this is the first time that I've really decided to dig in and watch some Eurovision.
Sure.
And it is just universally terrible music.
But the pageantry is amazing.
I mean, really, really bad.
But they're given an airplane hangar to do whatever they want with.
And they create some ridiculous spectacles.
And from what I understand, I don't know too much about Eurovision.
But from what I understand, it gets pretty serious, like country against country.
Yeah, everybody's cheering.
Most everybody is doing, like, you know how Americans invented good music?
They're all doing that.
But, you know, through their own lens, that kind of thing.
But some countries do, like, their own shit.
You know, like traditional stuff.
And it's really, really good.
But everything else is garbage.
Nobody has a good baseline.
It's just tragic.
Oh, that's too bad.
Man, there's light shows everywhere.
Well, that's great.
So Jordan, today, speaking of light shows, I would like to let you look into my disco ball.
It is actually a time machine.
Alright.
Okay.
We're going back in time.
Disco ball.
Where are we off to today, Mr. Peabody?
Well, today we are going to May 12th and 13th, 2003.
Okay.
Continuing back in our exploration of Alex Jones in 2003.
And seeing primarily what he's all about.
What are some similarities?
What are some differences?
Where's the devil at?
I mean, that's definitely one of the biggest questions.
Sure, sure.
Does Alex Jones believe he's fighting the devil in 2003?
Has his ultimate enemy been revealed to him yet?
Yes.
Or have the prophecies that he received in his dreams been a little bit muddled?
And a secondary element of that question is,
does Alex believe he's fighting the devil and actively try to hide that from his presentation?
Yes, correct.
In order to be taken more seriously at this point in his career.
Right, right, right, right.
And at this point, we started the beginning of May 2003 and we're now coming to the middle of the month.
And I think it's still an open question.
And we'll learn a little bit more today.
Alright.
But before we do, let's take a little moment to say thank you to some wonks.
Oh, that's a good idea.
So first, if I become a policy wonk, do I get to see exclusive pictures of Celine being excessively cute?
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much!
I'm not sure, but I will send a picture of Celine to Jordan so you can tweet it.
Yeah, there are no exclusive pictures of Celine here.
No, but I could give you a cute picture and you could put it on Twitter if you like.
I'll take care of it.
Next, Louis Box, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you, Louis Box.
Thank you.
Next, TheMorningDude listening on Steve Puchenik's neon nips, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, terrifying nightmare that will never escape my brain.
Next, Joe, my neighbors might think I actually listened to Alex, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much!
Next, I came here to say that you were this close to the joke, not all heroes wear masks, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
I like policy wonk names that are joke critiques.
Really, that one actually almost hits me in the gut a little bit.
That's a little bit like a get off your high horse thing, okay?
Next, EscapedSonOfAPreecherMan, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much!
The only one who could ever reach me was the escaped son of a bitch, but...
Next, ScooterTheCorgi, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Scoot.
Thank you very much.
And, Jordan, even though we're in the past, I should say that something's happening in the present, but not just Eurovision.
Right.
Not just Eurovision.
And that is that some people have some birthdays.
So, in 20...
What have we become?
In 2021, I should tell you, this weekend was chock-a-block with policy wonk birthdays.
Sure, sure.
We got Heather M. had a birthday.
Happy birthday, Heather M.
Happy birthday.
Throwback Zach had a birthday.
Throwback Zach!
Happy birthday.
And Ethan Mary sent a message wanting us to wish you a happy birthday over the weekend.
Hope you all...
Happy birthday, Ethan.
Yeah.
Alright.
We start here on the 12th, and it is a slog.
It is a rough time at the beginning.
But Alex gets around to some actual news, and that is where we will jump in.
You can't judge these books by their covers, the LA Times.
Many textbooks distort history, slamming the US and glorifying despotic regimes.
Last week, the LA Times had an article saying McCarthy was right.
What is going on?
The liberal papers sound conservative.
The conservative papers sound liberal.
I mean, they're really scrambling things right now.
So just a quick reminder, the LA Times editorial that Alex is talking about did not say that
McCarthy was right.
No.
It was in fact a scathing condemnation of McCarthy and his tactics, and a plea not to
throw out all opposition to communism just based on how big a piece of shit he was.
So maybe journalistic outlets aren't as topsy-turvy as he's kind of presenting it.
No.
If you just make assumptions based on headlines and what you think things are, then maybe
things are topsy-turvy.
That could be topsy-turvy.
So I was able to find this article that Alex is talking about in the LA Times about textbooks.
It's by Diane Ravitch, an author whose work is almost exclusively about education-related
issues.
The first thing to point out is that this, much like the other article Alex cites, is
an editorial.
Ravitch is writing in the first person, and it's not a piece of straight reporting.
Around this time in history, Ravitch had just released a book titled The Language Police,
How Pressure Groups Restrict What Students Learn.
The book was about how fear of igniting controversy from both left and right-wing pressure groups
has led to textbooks that give students an incomplete view of subjects like history and
literature.
In her article for the Times, she says, quote, the textbooks go out of their way to sanitize
the very practices in non-Western cultures that they rightly condemn in our society.
For instance, every textbook acknowledges that the enslavement of Africans by the West
was a great crime.
However, when describing slavery in the Middle East or Africa, many claim that it is a path
to upward career mobility or a chance to join a new family.
Slavery is wrong in any time and place and should be recognized as such.
That's a fair enough point, but I want to make sure that we illuminate how this criticism
is different than that that's lobbied by someone like Alex.
Alex doesn't want all cultures to be represented accurately and with proper historical context.
He would want the Middle Eastern or African slavery discussed, but he would also want
the textbooks to ignore American slavery, or if they had to cover it, the focus should
be on how America actually ended slavery.
No, if it weren't for white people, we never would have ended slavery.
Everybody knows this.
Ravitch is pointing out certain textbooks that she's read that are lazy.
Alex just doesn't want history to make him feel bad.
It would make him feel really bad.
It's a very specific difference.
Yeah, yeah, you know, if you're quoting Thomas Jefferson incorrectly all the time,
but it's like, hey, I'm Thomas Jefferson.
I love having slaves.
It'd make you feel like maybe the founding fathers weren't very smart.
Also, I suspect that Alex wouldn't like this paragraph in the Times article.
Quote, the history's treatment of religion is scandalous.
The origin stories of each religion are recounted as if they were documented history
rather than religious myths.
Many publishers have multicultural advisory boards to ensure the textbooks contain
only positive facts about religion or ethnic groups.
I suspect that Alex didn't read the whole article since he definitely would not like
the suggestion that his religious beliefs are a myth.
Also, that clip that we listened to is like a half hour into the show.
It's a real, it was walking through molasses.
Yeah, yeah, that's not good.
It was tough.
That's not good.
But it started up fast after half an hour.
And it got into some, like, really interesting stuff that, like,
when I think about, like, going back in time and looking at these episodes,
this is such a good example of, like, being able to go in different directions
from things that Alex says and learning about interesting stuff like this.
This is now in the Belfast Telegraph.
It is in the BBC.
It is in the London Guardian.
Top double agent in IRA, guilty of up to 40 murders.
Turns out that the top man in the IRA carrying out the bombings,
the killings, the shootings, everything, as we told you last year,
was MI5-6, ultra-secret agent.
Okay. All right.
So what's going on here is that Alex is glossing over an amazing story
just to make it valuable to his worldview when, in fact, it doesn't really work at all.
The IRA member in question here is a double agent for British intelligence
codenamed Steakknife.
He denies that any of this is-
That is not as cool as you made it sound.
Codenamed Steakknife? No, that sucks. That would be terrible.
I don't want to be codenamed Steakknife.
It's S-T-A-K-E.
That's even worse. I don't want to be a pun.
Whatever.
Okay.
So he denies that any of this is true, but it's widely understood
that this was a man named Freddy Scappaticci.
And if his denial isn't a lie, his story is bananas.
So there's a great piece about this by James Harkin in GQ
that I'm taking a lot of the background information for,
and I would recommend people check out that article.
Okay, cool.
Apparently, in the late 1970s, Scappaticci met an army sergeant named Peter Jones,
a guy who's so charismatic that his superiors, quote,
allowed him to wear civilian clothes, don a beard, and develop his own sources.
So he was Sergeant Bilko.
Somehow, through the magic of charm and booze, even though Jones worked for the British Army
and Scappaticci was in the IRA, they forged a friendship that resulted in Scappaticci becoming a mole.
Wow, this is a real Romeo and Juliet situation.
This is kind of a, yeah, I like it.
So by this point, the IRA had become a slightly smaller organization,
which was aware that they were spies trying to infiltrate their ranks and become snitches.
As such, they put together a counterintelligence team,
which was meant to root out any potential spies.
From Harkins' article, quote,
By the mid-1980s, Scappaticci was the deputy head of internal security
and a trusted member of its general headquarters staff.
This story happened so many goddamn times!
Why are you always put in charge of your own investigation?
Yeah.
Essentially, through unconventional methods,
the British government had cultivated a relationship with a double agent
who was placed internally in a position that was almost comically strategically-
It's just ridiculous!
Get the fuck out of here!
Their double agent was the guy in the IRA who was in charge of finding double agents within the IRA.
That's unrealistic in a Bond movie!
You'd be like, get the fuck out of here!
Yeah.
So as is the case with all these sorts of spy-related stories,
everything is morally questionable.
A lot of the story revolves around Scappaticci killing or allowing people to be killed
who could compromise his position as a double agent,
or people who they needed to protect in order to pursue goals of, like, arresting higher-up figures.
Sure, sure.
And unfortunately, some of those people definitely got killed.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Gotcha.
It's messy business, and no one's hands are clean,
but depending on whose version of the story you believe,
this is all made up, according to Scappaticci.
Okay.
Or Scappaticci was responsible for helping disrupt multiple terrorist plots at a horrible cost.
The accusation that Freddy Scappaticci was steak knife came to light in 2003,
and this became a big story, as well it should be.
The important piece to recognize here, though, is that Alex is missing the forest for the trees.
He deprives his audience of learning about this fascinating piece of history,
or from learning about the history of the IRA and the Troubles,
because the headline works a different way for him.
This is a story about a very well-placed double agent within the IRA,
but to Alex, this can prove that MI6 was running the IRA all along,
and the bombings and the attacks were all just false flags.
That's an outrageous misuse of this story, and by reporting it this way,
Alex is actually doing something worse than just ignoring the story altogether.
He's creating a fake version of it for his audience to erroneously convince themselves they understand.
He's like Aaron Sorkin!
Even if all the allegations about Scappaticci are correct and accurate,
he wasn't the top man in the IRA, and he wasn't the one carrying out the bombings.
Alex is embellishing that element of the story because it helps him construct the impression
that the world is all fake, and that everything you hear is a lie.
It's a perversion of skepticism and curiosity.
Yeah, it is really a good...
I mean, as far as storytelling goes, when you reduce it down into this kind of bullshit,
you miss out on a very human story where people are making difficult decisions in moral grey areas,
where they're struggling to keep from being caught,
while at the same time struggling to show that they're trying to catch themselves.
That's a really fascinating story!
The MI6 already running the IRA is a really boring story, actually.
Yeah, but it's much easier.
It has explanatory power over stuff that would be so...
It takes years of study.
You could be a historian at a university with tenure,
and maybe not fully be able to explain it except over the course of a semester.
Right, right, right.
Well, I mean, and it goes back again to how boring it is that your enemy is both everywhere
running everything and is also so incompetent that you can defeat them at any and all times.
Of course.
It's like, that's a boring story! I don't care if Superman can always win.
I don't care.
Sure.
I know, it's boring.
What I was getting at is that it's very unsatisfying if you're a demagogue on the radio
to be like, alright, let's buckle down and everybody take notes.
This is going to take forever.
It's going to require a lot of reading and research on your part.
Instead...
Serial became a huge hit!
Instead, just telling people it's all fake.
The big boogeyman is running everything, who cares?
It's all these globalists.
Serial did become a huge hit.
I don't know...
I'm saying it does both. Never mind. I'm sorry.
I don't know if that was a lecture.
I was playing both sides.
Fair enough.
Yeah.
Also, I should tell you this.
Yes.
In 2018, Freddy Scampaticci's home was searched as part of an investigation into his role
in the IRA, which didn't result in any murder charges, although he did plead guilty to having
at least 329 images of animal porn on his computer.
According to an article in the Irish Times, quote, Westminster's Magistrates Court heard
Scampaticci tell police that he was not sexually interested in animals, but preferred women
with big breasts.
He was ordered to pay a total of 185 pounds, including court costs.
I...
Man...
Okay.
This is why...
This is why journalism has a huge hole, and that is...
Very intended.
I now need to know what they mean by animal porn.
I can't not know.
It's pornography featuring animals.
Yes, but I don't know what that means.
The animal kingdom is large.
How many...
You know what I'm saying?
No, I know exactly what you're saying.
I just don't share your curiosity.
I'm sorry, but I just...
I absolutely do not share.
It's a curiosity now.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I don't know who can get those court files for you.
I don't want to see the court files.
I don't want to see it.
I just want to know.
No, but I'm sure they didn't reprint all of it in the court files.
It just might be more specific.
Well, I would like to...
I would like...
Okay, Jordan.
I'll take a transcript of a description.
Jordan.
I do not want to see it.
I'd like to apologize that my research did not go deeper into this...
I'm just saying.
This postscript on a story.
Okay.
I'm just saying decency rules keep us from getting a full picture of the story.
And it shall continue.
Okay.
So, Alex has used this story about the IRA double agent in order to justify that, like,
everything is a false flag.
Sure.
All of the conflict in Northern Ireland was false flaggery.
And that the British just do it all.
False flagging is a British trick.
Although, it's been picked up by other people that Alex might love in the present day.
This is a British trick.
They have been big in it before the Russians or the US were.
Putin.
Of course, Putin was caught blowing up or trying to blow up his fourth apartment.
Kalden did blow up three of them.
Moscow police arrested FSB in 99, planting the bombs.
And then Moscow GRU, their internal security force, went in and arrested the police and
others that had the hexagon explosives.
They arrested members of the media and that story was shut down quite quickly.
But that is confirmed and members of the FSB and others have now spoken out who fled the
country.
Then Britain moved to have them arrested and shipped back to Vladimir Putin, who was the
former head of the KGB in Stalingrad, Leningrad, St. Petersburg, whatever name you want to
give it for the day.
But it's now St. Petersburg, the old name.
And he was the guy really running things and they were pushing Boris Yeltsin around in
a wheelchair completely drunk and drugged out of his mind who couldn't even speak.
He's been running things for at least the last three years of Yeltsin's tenure.
He was wildly unpopular.
Suddenly, three apartment buildings got blown up outside Moscow in the suburb.
He cracked down, said, I will save you, was a big hero and got elected with a large portion
of the vote and then had a great war against the Chechnyans who screamed, it's not us,
it's you.
Why would we bomb you and bring down your wrath?
This is insane.
So Alex seems to, in 2003, have a lot of reasons why he believes that Putin did this.
Yeah, we're very much in a, he's mobbed up, he's a front man for consortiums on the East
Coast territory in terms of knowledge of crime.
It's strange because I don't think that Alex is expressing like, I think he did it.
No, no, no.
Alex is saying that these people were arrested, planting the bombs.
Sure.
To him, it's definitive.
Yeah.
And somehow that has changed.
Or he's just decided, I don't care if someone falls flags, I'll pretend they didn't because
I like the way that they're strong manning.
Yeah, I mean, I guess it's, if everybody else is false flagging, then I might as well pick
the guy who's doing it the best.
Or doing it in such a way...
In service of my hopeful white nationalism.
Perhaps.
I mean, if he does truly believe that, I mean, it's a short jump from everything is fake
to nothing matters.
Yeah.
That is a very good point.
I mean, if everything is fake and everybody is false flagging everybody, then the ethical
implications of pulling a false flag are really not that high.
Yeah, that's true.
It's really just what the result is.
So I could see Alex ethically being okay with false flagging in order to serve whatever
interests he's most in line with.
I don't know that to be the case, but I could easily see that being something that he could
subconsciously convince himself of.
Totally.
I would argue that there's zero possibility before Alex's life is over that he himself
does not try and carry out some sort of false flag.
Sure, sure.
He's just going to.
Like, that's the narrative arc for him.
Yeah, yeah.
I see him pulling a last season of House.
Yeah.
And taking his own death.
Yeah, the whole thing, yeah.
So he and Steve Pacetic can ride motorcycles around.
And they're hanging out with Aldo Morrow.
Yeah.
So, lest you think that I am just saying that Alex thinks everything is fake.
It's all out there.
Mainstream news.
We haven't found a terror attack in modern history anywhere in the world of any size
or scope that wasn't carried out by the globalist.
When I say globalist, I'm talking about the private banks and their private armies that
control the top cabals, the compartmentalized cabals, and all the intelligence agencies.
So, that doesn't sound like the devil.
No, no.
That's one thing.
That's straight up globalists.
And then secondarily, Alex seems to be convinced that literally everything is the globalist.
It does seem to be the globalist.
There are no real terrorist attacks.
There is no real...
That's, that's in line.
Yeah.
I don't know if he would stand by that today, but that makes sense for the way he acts.
Everything is fake.
If you start from the position of everything is fake, that leaves you with way more options
to occasionally accept things as being true.
If you start with the position that some things are true, for instance, Putin bombed his own
buildings, then eventually you're going to have to change your opinion whenever you change
your opinion about Putin.
And for normal people with shame, that's no good.
That's no good.
Yeah.
And I think that Alex is so sneaky that when he says everything is fake, there's so many
different versions of fake that he has in his mind that you're like, okay, well...
No, the event actually happened and it wasn't orchestrated, but because they knew about
the drugging in advance, they had already prepared for it.
Somebody was on mind control drugs.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Absolutely.
And this clip actually got me into an interesting headspace.
Okay.
The average person in the Pentagon, the CIA, the FBI, even the White House is a good person.
The average Democrat, the average Republican might be corrupt and might be a good old boy,
but compared to the cabals that run things, they are nothing.
And let's make this clear, that we have just a few thousand globalists and a few thousand
operatives who are carrying all of this out and then they have the scripts for the media
with the media ownership, they follow the agenda.
We have the power to save this country and, yes, the world if we have courage and stand
up and tell the truth.
That clip really helped me put into context why it's so much less painful to listen to
Alex's show in 2003 as compared to the present day.
And that is there's a presentation of hope.
In 2003, most people, Democrats and Republicans, even people who work in the intelligence community
or in the White House, are good people.
It's just a couple thousand villains who are secretly orchestrating literally every
terrorist attack in the world and running all governments and financial systems.
It's ludicrous, but from the standpoint of gauging emotional states, there's a perspective
of optimism that you can kind of feel in the program.
Compare that to the modern day where Alex's show is just fucking doom.
In this clip alone, you have a reminder that most people are good people and a confident
assertion that there's a good chance that the world can be saved.
Both of these are completely foreign concepts to Alex today.
Everyone who disagrees with him is a pedophile who works for Satan.
And even if the Patriots are successful, the globalists are still going to kill almost
everyone with a super bio weapon or whatever he feels like ranting about that day.
Part of the reason his show sucks so much in 2021 is that it's actively depressing.
Not just in the sense that it's depressing that someone would believe the nonsense that
he says, but the way the show is structured and the way information is conveyed is a
fucking drag.
I don't believe Alex when he talks about courage or honesty, but I think that he might
respect human life in 2003.
Yeah, I mean, I...
Here's what I would say, all right?
I don't think any show should last longer than, say, ten years.
Because here's... we're getting... this is what's happening.
Iron Man, you're just fighting Hobodiah Stane.
That's the first movie.
You're just fighting some other guy.
It's a real small self-contained story.
Twenty years later, half of the universe has disappeared.
You know what I'm saying?
It's the problem of escalation.
It's like The Simpsons.
They're talking about a family.
And then ten years later, it's like The Simpsons are going to the moon.
And it's like because you just can't keep going at the same level.
But what would happen if The Simpsons went to the moon?
I think everyone wants to know.
I think everybody does want to know.
But eventually, you're going to have to say that everybody's going to die.
If you start out with, there's a few thousand people.
Twenty years later, everybody has to die.
Like, it's just... yeah.
I think that you're right when it's...
I don't know if it's universal, but narrative fiction does have that way of
running into a problem of like, well, we've told this story already.
What other story are we going to tell?
What is Infowars but improvised narrative fiction?
No, I agree.
And I think that that is the same problem that Alex is running into.
How do you keep people excited?
Exactly.
Because I think that you can have other things like the McNeil Lehrer hour
didn't go into it.
Sure, sure, sure.
I realize Carson was on the air for a while.
Yeah, there's other forms of entertainment that don't have the same
escalatory problem.
Nope, everything is faulty towers.
The end, two seasons, get out.
So here is a nice example of the continuing threat of Alex being
wrong in a way that he will soon learn is wrong.
And they are appointing bath party leaders to almost every position.
The people trained by the CIA in torture, espionage, oppression
in the 70s and 80s.
It is a CIA government.
They're appointing the scum again in Iraq.
So we've got these really consistent things that keep coming up on every show.
Like Putin bombed the apartment buildings and they're putting the bath party
CIA agents in power.
I know it sounds like I'm beating a dead horse here, but it's constant.
Not like he's saying it every other minute, but it's every show these things
are touched on.
And they're both not at all, well one's just inaccurate, and then the other one
is something that is exactly the opposite of what Alex will later believe.
Yeah, he doesn't know, we don't know yet that de-bathification is beginning.
No, I believe we're another week or so off of when that conversation starts.
Yeah, I mean it's close though.
I believe it's in May or roundabouts in 2003.
See, now this is one thing that is so frustrating about Alex is that
on that day that he does find out, I would like him to find out on air
and I would like him to deflate like a balloon.
I would like somebody to prick him and he just goes, ummm, like that.
But he's not going to do that, he's just going to include it in some other part
of some, he's going to say no, they're doing it publicly to get rid of baths
to make you forget that they're actually putting the CIA people in there.
It's unfortunate, I want him deflated.
This is wild, I mean we're on May 12th here and I just looked this up
and the first coalition provisional authority announcement that started
the process of de-bathification is the 16th.
So we're four days away from this as we look at Alex's...
Absolutely wild.
So I guess we'll, on a pretty soon episode, we'll find out how he pivots.
I don't know, I'm a little bit older than you and so in 2003 I was an adult.
Yeah, I was not yet.
I was a dignified, I was not.
No, you were not.
But I remember the conversation about Freedom Fries.
Yes, oh, I won't forget that one.
And Freedom Toast.
Yep.
I wasn't even an adult yet and I knew that was fucking stupid.
People, particularly two members who are republicans in the house,
got mad about french fries and french toast being served in the cafeteria
because of course France had not agreed to join in with the invasion of Iraq
and they were cowards.
Yeah, it's never not going to be surprising that we are governed by children.
Yeah.
To Alex's credit, he also thinks that whole Freedom Fry thing was stupid.
Good for him.
Although...
Uh oh.
Mexico opposed the war.
Well, why aren't you mad at them if you're mad at France?
France has three million Muslims by the way in it.
You know why they said no, they'd get attacked.
They didn't by their internal population.
It's just reached new levels of ridiculousness.
Jeremy in Indiana, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Go ahead.
That's not great.
That's not cool.
I didn't even know there could be a racist reason for that being stupid.
Yeah, I...
It's stupid because it doesn't mean anything.
It doesn't mean anything.
It's a Belgian waffle even if Belgium doesn't appreciate what you're doing.
Freedom waffle.
It doesn't matter.
It's stupid on its face because it doesn't mean anything.
It's an empty, meaningless, pointless gesture.
It's not somehow the cause of racism.
Or you said, like, how is that possible?
All things considered, I think I would rather deal with
freedom fries and freedom toast than someone like Alex
who's perpetuating the idea that France made this geopolitical decision
to not get involved in the Iraq war at that point
because they were afraid of Muslim French people attacking from within.
Yeah, there you go.
Yeah, yeah.
That's deeply Islamophobic and terrifying.
And it's at a point in his career when he has the presentation
of not being anti-Muslim.
He's certainly not as aggressively anti-Muslim as he is in the present.
But it seems like those latent things are there pretty clearly.
Definitely.
That's the level of shit where you're like,
there's just no way you won't take it back to racism.
Just like, oh, you know, I think I need a new coffee maker.
Well, that's because of, I don't want to know why,
but it's because my other one broke.
There's no other reason.
The other one just broke.
There's no people behind it.
Are you sure it's not the Turks?
No, damn it!
They're really involved in coffee.
There's no reason to be racist about this.
So one thing, I wish that I had musical ability.
Because if I did, long ago, I would have made a bumper
kind of Sting sound for the Alex telling a story that totally happened.
Sure, sure.
Totally happened.
Because we get them all over the place.
Throughout his career, at any point, you're going to hear stories
that definitely happened.
All right, cue me right before you play the clip.
All right, right now.
Alex's true story.
You know, I have state police majors walk up to me.
I walk into the cleaners.
And I randomly pull in to get my laundry.
Oh, I put it in two weeks ago.
What I'm saying is it wasn't some stage deal
where the major and the state police was waiting to talk to me.
I'm driving back from the studio, a couple months ago,
decided to pull in to get my laundry just randomly.
And there's a state police officer in there getting his uniforms.
He goes, Moosker Jones, can you come outside, please?
And he goes, we were raised that this was the Soviet Union.
We know something's wrong.
The things we're being told are incredible.
And I go, how many of you are awake?
And he goes, most of the senior officers know something is wrong, Mr. Jones.
DPS intelligence is fully aware of what's happening.
And he goes, we know this isn't a conservative administration.
I mean, you know, cops come up to me at the mall.
They're doing security and telling me they know what's happening
with a tear in their eyes.
These cops come up to me.
This is true story.
They come up to me at the mall crying, telling me Bush isn't conservative.
We get it.
Sir, Alex Jones, please free us from the Soviet Union we were raised in.
I saw your eyes get a little confused when he was talking about his laundry.
And I was a little bit confused as well.
But I realized that maybe he's talking about dry cleaning.
Yeah, I was assuming dry cleaning.
Yeah, yeah.
I was totally assuming that.
It seems weird to drop off laundry.
It's a strange random thing to do.
The time frame is really what was worrying to me.
Yeah, that's true.
So yeah, this didn't happen.
So Alex takes a call at this point in the show.
And this was interesting.
This introduces a large theme that we'll run throughout the next couple days.
One more thing, if you don't mind.
Sure.
These drills today that they're going to be doing in about 15 minutes, I guess.
Yeah, the fake radiation attack in Seattle, stuff in Chicago,
all training you to be a federal slave.
These are supposed to take place for five days and raise the alert level, I'm told?
Well, yes.
Now during the drills, they're going to raise the alert level.
Amber Alert will be flashing.
Report gun owners.
Report terrorists.
Yes.
And is this going to continue on for five days?
And are they going to treat us?
Are they going to basically put us under martial law for this?
That's what this is, yes.
This is a practice drill for martial law.
When we get back, I will read you the article.
This is a bad answer on Alex's part, but I kind of see what he meant.
Alex meant that this drill was a part of preparing the public for martial law,
but what the caller was asking was whether or not the drill would continue past day five
into day six and day seven and so on.
Would the drill be how martial law literally started?
That was the question that was being asked.
Sure.
By replying in the affirmative, Alex was essentially telling this guy that this drill
was the beginning of enslavement, which is really bad.
It's hard for me to imagine that Alex misunderstood the question,
except in the case that he wasn't listening at all, which is totally possible.
Most likely.
So I found the after-action report for this drill released by the Washington State Department of Health.
This drill was called Top-Off 2, and it was meant to simulate a WMD attack simultaneously hitting multiple cities.
It began with a bioterrorist attack in Chicago and a dirty bomb going off in Seattle.
In addition to these challenges, quote,
a cyber event affecting the state's communication infrastructure hit the week before.
To further complicate the situation, a hostile takeover of the Washington State Ferry
and a hostage event in Pierce County, south of Seattle, were included.
That probably seems like overkill, but that's the point.
As the report explicitly says, quote,
in all, the event was meant to overwhelm local, state, and federal agencies
with the goal of finding ways to improve preparedness, response, and recovery capabilities in the future.
The goal was to create a fake situation that was too much to handle,
so you can stress test in a fake situation instead of a real one.
This bucket's not done. We're gonna fill it full of water to find out where the fucking holes are.
Yep. This simulation taught the Washington State Department of Health a bunch of important lessons.
For instance, they learned that their Radiological Monitoring and Assessment Center had no reason to be on site,
since it, quote,
became mired in the response organization, which limited its ability to fully perform its work in off-site areas.
That's a pretty important lesson, but probably less critical than them learning that the infrastructure they had in place to transmit bulk data
was insufficient to handle the needs they faced in an emergency.
Maps and data tables that were critical to get to decision-makers were not effectively transmitted given their existing setup,
which is a huge issue that they were able to identify from this.
Uh, turns out, turns out using the Pony Express is not going to do it.
Ladies and gentlemen, I apologize.
You gotta speed this up.
Another thing that's important to understand is that this is just the after-action report for the Washington State Department of Health.
They didn't run the simulation. They were just one of the groups participating in it.
Each entity that took part, they played different roles in the simulation, and they faced different challenges,
and each came away with their own lessons, their own gaps in planning that they could resolve.
I found the after-action summary for the entire exercise from the Department of Homeland Security,
and the Washington Department of Health is just one of 47 state or local agencies that took part in the drill,
along with 41 federal agencies and 21 agencies from Canada that got involved because that bio-attack that hit Chicago,
it ended up spreading to Canada.
Oh, God damn it, Canada.
Yeah. I was reading over this summary, and there's an amazing piece on page 8,
where the exercise ended up teaching everyone who participated about the actual definitions that are in the Stafford Act,
which covers how federal assistance is deployed to states in an emergency.
They found...
I know we were supposed to read it before. I know.
No, they had read it, but it clarified a definition because they hadn't role-played this thing out.
Sure, sure, sure.
They found that as it was written, a terrorist bio-attack, quote,
does not clearly fit the existing definition of a disaster by the act.
This made it so the President couldn't issue a declaration of a disaster in the drill,
but instead the Secretary of HHS could only declare a public health emergency.
They didn't realize this beforehand.
From the report, quote, these two declarations illustrated some of the subtleties of the Stafford Act
that may not have been fully appreciated before the exercise.
Sure, sure.
There's a ton of value to organizations preparing like this,
using fake disasters to learn how to respond better to real disasters.
This exercise was followed by Top-Off 3, which took place in 2005
and expanded to fully include exercises being run by the Canadian and UK governments in collaboration.
Cool, cool.
In that scenario, they came up with 15 scary terrorist ideas and chose three to simulate.
There was a terrorist release of a mnemonic plague in New Jersey,
a mustard gas IED attack in Connecticut,
and then the events in the UK and Canada, which this report doesn't specify,
and that really pissed me off because I want to know what games they were playing.
Yeah, I want to figure it out.
Yeah, absolutely.
This was followed by Top-Off 4 in 2010,
and as of yet, this series of scenario planning exercises has not resulted in martial law.
You would think that if Alex's whole thing about how the globalists used these exercises
to launch their evil plans or something had any merit,
one of these would have resulted in something more nefarious than government employees learning things.
Yeah.
And honestly, I love reading these reports because it's like,
this would be my best day at work.
Yeah, that would be a good day at work.
If I worked in these areas, it would be so much fun.
Oh, totally.
It's the day at school where they're like, okay, today we're going to play Heads Up 7-Up.
You're like, yes, that's my favorite day in school.
Yeah, totally.
Or there was this thing called CASA in Missouri, in Columbia.
It was the Columbia Aeronautic and Space Association.
Okay.
And so what they would do is they would have students come,
and we would simulate running a spacecraft.
Oh, that's cool as shit.
Yeah, and so one of the stations was,
my memories of this are a little bit spotty,
but one of the stations was made to look like the actual shuttle.
And so you're in there and you'd have some responsibilities.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Another one was command, the command center.
And so you were like...
You're Kobayashi Maru-ing it.
Sure.
Yeah.
And I remember that being, that's a day that sticks out to me in my head
from my entire elementary school career
because of just the excitement of going and role-playing this scenario
of trying to make sure we were able to communicate between the two.
And they obviously would throw some curve balls,
like something's going wrong.
Sure, yeah, of course.
You've got to fix something.
Yeah, it's excitement.
So much fun.
Yeah, we had a small six-foot-tall inflatable planetarium.
Mm-hmm.
You could see the stars.
Not quite as fun.
Not, no.
No, it wasn't.
So, I don't know.
I got really into this, and I got furious that the Canadian
and UK scenarios weren't at me.
Yeah, that sounds pretty fun.
Talk about the document because I was like,
I want to know what they were facing.
I kind of want to see if we can orchestrate like a giant national
role-playing game where we just play the exact same thing,
but we're people inside of the simulations,
and we have to act like we're all dying.
One thing that I found that I actually kind of took a little bit of issue with
was that prior to this there was an exercise, the original Top Off exercise.
Sure, sure, sure.
And that one was unannounced, and so people didn't know it was happening.
Oh, man.
And I would say-
They've learned a lot of lessons from Top Off over the years.
The other ones were announced ahead of time.
Yeah, yeah.
And I don't know why they would do it unannounced.
Like, I mean, everyone who was participating knew.
Yeah, but I mean, that happened with the fucking United States Army
in Russia during the Cold War.
They were like, let's simulate bombing Russia,
and let's not tell Russia about it, you know?
They're dumb people.
It seems like not a wise-
It seems like a possibility for trouble.
Yeah.
Anyway, Alex gets another caller, and this guy brings up a question
about 9-11, and I found this to be troubling.
Well, you know, there's one question on 9-11,
so I just got your DVD last Friday.
I've only gone through it slowly, and then I'll go home and park.
But let me ask you, you say over and over again,
Al-Qaeda is a CIA type of trained people, correct?
Yes.
These types of people don't commit suicide.
Well, let me explain that.
A what?
We believe, all the evidence says, those people weren't even on those aircraft.
You know most of the hijackers have been found alive.
Stay there. We'll talk about all that.
A what now?
This is a great indicator of how seriously Alex takes research
into what's supposed to be his primary field of study, the truth about 9-11.
It's a regular talking point in the 9-11 conspiracy communities
that some of the accused hijackers have been found alive,
but anyone who's looked into this with any depth at all
could tell you that this is a simple case of mistaken identity
and the investigative process being judged in the middle,
as opposed to at its conclusion.
Yeah.
One of the men listed as a suspected hijacker was Walid Al-Shahiri,
and just after the FBI released a photo of him,
he made a pretty big effort to stress that they had the wrong guy.
He is a pilot in Saudi Arabia and had done flight training at the same school
in Daytona Beach that the other 9-11 hijackers had,
but he was definitely alive and was living in Morocco.
Sure, sure, sure.
Hi, I did not fly that plane on account of I am here.
So what happened here?
This was a simple case of mistaken identity.
One of the Flight 11 hijackers was named Walid Mohamed Al-Shahiri.
As the man who was alive protested his innocence,
the BBC made an error in their initial coverage,
reporting that a man listed as one of the hijackers was actually alive,
which, while technically accurate,
gave a different impression from what was actually going on.
If you just live and die by headlines and never look any deeper into things,
you could easily think that the person the FBI claimed was on Flight 11
was actually alive, but you would be wrong.
This is a super easy thread to untangle if you want to know what happened,
and certainly all of this information was fully available in 2003.
Sure.
There are a couple other people who were named as hijackers
who initial reports claimed were alive, who actually were alive,
like Abdulaziz Al-Omari and Salim Al-Hazimi.
These two men had something very specific in common,
which is that at some point in the not-too-distant past,
they had their passports stolen.
Al has me by a pickpocket in Cairo,
and Al-Omari in a burglary when he was living in Denver.
Sure, sure.
Each of the instances Alex has of supposed anomalies like this
are actually instances of bad, miscommunicated information
that he never followed up on.
Unlike Alex, reporters for Der Spiegel actually did look into
some of these coincidences to see what happened.
They reached out to John Bradley, the managing editor of Arab News,
where much of the initial reporting originated, who told them,
quote, all of this is attributable to the chaos that prevailed
during the first few days following the attack.
Yeah.
What we're dealing with are coincidentally identical names.
He also made it clear that these articles were being written after
September 14th, when the FBI had only released a list of names
of suspected hijackers.
If there's one area where Alex really needs to be sure he's covering his bases,
it should be 9-11 conspiracies.
But you can see here how sloppy his work is, even on this trademark subject.
Even in 2003, even about 9-11, you can't go deeper than headlines.
Yeah.
I can't imagine the terrible day you would have if your passport had been stolen
and then you woke up the next day and it was flying into a plane.
That would be a real bummer of a day for you.
Yeah.
Man, oh boy.
Yeah, and so there's a combination of a number of different reasons
for these mistaken identities.
There's some that's like identity theft, or at least very strongly
suspected identity theft.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
And then some of it is this other element, this misreported similar names
or the same names.
There's a lot of people in the world.
Right.
Some of them have the same names.
Right, I don't.
And that period of time between when the FBI released names
and when they released photos, there was a great deal of confusion
and sort of the fog of unclarity.
As we see after every great disaster.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So Alex takes another call and this one does not go well at all.
I have one more question.
I'm sorry to take so long.
Are you aware of a guy by the name of William Cooper?
Of course I am.
Okay.
I stole my career from him.
There's something on his website and he has all his recordings from way back.
Yeah, I know.
But he has one thing about you being a liar.
I understand, sir.
That's a diversion.
Total diversion.
I appreciate your call.
Frankly, my show is not about, and most other shows are,
and that's why we never get anywhere,
my show is not about what this talk show host says
or what that talk show host says in the Patriot movement.
I'm sorry.
My show is not the gossip column.
Even before it descended to the trash that it is now,
even in 2009 he spent all his time yelling about Glenn Beck.
Oh, man.
So yeah, I mean, he quickly became the gossip column.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Well, a lot of people, as he stated,
a lot of people really like to listen to the gossip shows.
It's true.
So he was looking more for that.
So this caller has made Alex introspective and he decides,
well, the name William Cooper has been evoked on my show.
I'd better lie about it.
Okay.
William Cooper became unstable in the last years of his life
before he was gunned down by a SWAT team in his Arizona home.
I called the guy up when he was in trouble with the IRS calling
for help and said, I'd like to interview you.
And he began cussing and yelling and saying,
only I have the answers.
Well, I want to just tell folks,
I never got into UFOs and stuff you can't prove.
Cooper did.
And I don't know what Cooper's problem was,
and I'm sad he's dead.
I'm not going to sit here and talk about somebody who's dead.
Here's the issue.
Alex is totally right that Bill Cooper was incredibly unstable
and was a nut.
He's lying about the appearance on the show, though.
We did an entire episode.
Oh, I thought he was lying about how long William Cooper
had been unstable for.
Oh, yeah, probably a bit longer.
The last few years of his life.
Oh, boy, it was a lot longer than that.
I think he did get much worse, though.
Yeah, I believe that.
Yeah, we did an episode that covered Bill Cooper's appearance
on Alex's show, and it does not match up at all
with the way that Alex presents it.
Nope.
Alex was an asshole to him, if anything.
Yep, 100%.
But, you know, Alex doesn't get...
I'd be rich for a guy to criticize somebody
getting into aliens later on in life,
and then later on in life telling me
that interdimensional beings are controlling the globalists.
Oh, and, I mean, he says stuff that's even more ironic.
So, see, what I do on this show is
I don't talk about the visions that some prophet had
out in the desert.
Oh, no.
He said the nukes are going to go off next week.
No.
And I don't talk about Planet X.
And I don't talk about flying saucers.
And I don't talk about psychics.
Oh, no.
And I don't talk about other talk show hosts,
unless there's some national host, like Sean Hannity
saying every child should take a microchip.
Did I get Bingo?
I have a video of Hannity and Combs.
Or if it's Savage saying,
put anyone who disagrees with the government
in a forced labor camp.
I occasionally break my rule for that.
But I don't talk about rumors and trash.
I don't talk about psychics, and then in the future,
I'm a psychic.
Come on, now.
I don't talk about visions.
I have visions all the time.
Actually, the universe was revealed to me,
and my prediction of 9-11 was actually based on a vision.
I have dreams that are prophetic.
Yeah, and a lot of the time, they happen
whenever I'm out in the middle of nowhere.
Ah, what a dick.
What an asshole.
So Alex takes another call,
and this person brings up prison labor.
Sure.
This is bizarre, because I think that Alex's
opposition to prison labor might not come from
the same place that yours or mine might.
Yeah, I would say slave labor is bad,
and I somehow feel like Alex would disagree
with me on that point.
I think he agrees, but the reason why
is where we get into a little bit of a...
I saw him on a colloquy with Mark Saldor
Thursday a week ago concerning the prison industries
and how they're putting our small businesses
out of business, so our people are not...
A lot of good old boys, Jones, say,
hey, make them prisoners work.
The problem is most of the industry is now privatized.
It is an industry.
They're working for an average of 23 cents an hour
competing against your jobs from the lumber
to electronics to furniture to...
To uniforms for our military.
Customer service, everything.
It's taking our jobs.
It's slave camps.
Exactly.
Seven and a half million people in the system now.
I think that opposition to prison labor
shouldn't be it's putting other people out of business.
Yeah, I would say that Alex is now a union man
in about 1845 saying that slavery is great,
but you're competing with our wages.
Yeah, because it does imply that this kind of thing
would be okay were it not to jeopardize
the success of other businesses.
Yeah, and I think...
And I don't agree with that.
The way to put it on an equal playing field
is if they're competing with your business
where you pay people, say, $9 an hour,
what you should do is convert them into slaves for you
and then everybody's on an equal playing field.
That's Alex's solution, I think.
I'm not sure if that is his solution.
I think that's what he said.
But I find this to be an unthought through position.
Or at least...
A psychopathic, self-involved, and beneficial solution.
If that is where his opposition to prison labor
and the system that is in place,
if that is where it derives from, it's shallow.
It has nothing to do with the act
of making people in prison work for very low wages.
Sure.
Just not in industries that compete with American businesses, Dan.
I don't like this.
What makes you not like that?
Anyway, so this caller has heard about a bill.
Maybe. Possibly.
Doesn't remember the bill, but it did something.
And maybe it has to do with prison labor.
Could be.
Well, I wanted to give you the number of H.R. 1829.
What does that bill do?
Well, you know, to tell you the truth,
I was away from my 50th class reunion.
I didn't take notes, but Sauter and the other fellow, Mark Sauter and...
Okay, what did they say the bill did?
They were trying to restrict it in some way.
So it's a bill that expands the prison industry.
They admitted, oh, they're not for it.
They're against it.
Okay.
And plus, they said that they're already,
the government is already building new plants,
new buildings for expansion of the plants.
Yeah, I mean, what did camps do in Germany?
You had a bunch of prisoners next door to a plant.
Right.
It's incredible.
Joan, I appreciate the call.
So that caller had sort of heard something about a bill,
but didn't know what it did or really anything about it,
but someone she'd heard talk about it kind of was maybe into it or maybe not.
I don't know what was going on there.
No, I appreciate anybody calling into a political talk show
describing their political views very similarly
to how my grandma would describe the movie that she just saw a couple of days ago.
It was the one with the, and there were the people in it.
What's the opposite of informative?
Because that's what that was.
Ooh, deformative?
Maybe.
So H.R. 1829 in the 108th Congress was also known
as the Federal Prison Industries Competition and Contracting Act of 2003.
Here's what that was about.
There's a government-owned corporation called Federal Prison Industries,
which is used to produce goods using the labor of incarcerated persons.
I'll read to you here from the C.G.O. cost assessment of implementing this bill.
Quote,
Under current law, federal agencies are required to purchase products from F.P.I.
if products are available to meet the agency's needs
and the costs would not exceed current market prices.
Such products include office furniture, textiles, vehicle tags, and fiber optics.
Under the proposed legislation, this requirement would be reduced
over the next several years, and the share of the federal market
that F.P.I. holds for the products and services it provides
would be limited to 20% and 5%, respectively.
If you understand that text properly, what this bill would have done
is actively reduce the government use of products created with prison labor.
The bill aimed to divert some of this productive capacity
towards making goods that would be donated to non-profit organizations
instead of being sold to the government, which honestly still sucks.
Additionally, there were provisions for funding of vocational training
for incarcerated persons and funding for programs
to test rehabilitative activities that could be productive towards helping.
This caller has no idea what this bill is, and she's telling Alex about it
as if it's something that expands the prison system when in actuality
it was designed to limit the profits that are derived from prison labor
and funneled a fair amount of money towards efforts to help people
improve their lives while incarcerated.
In the House, it's completely bizarre to see how split the vote on this was
and not on party lines.
It got yay votes from Steve King, Nancy Pelosi, and Mike Pence.
Well, they all love slave labor.
But it got nay votes from Maxine Waters
and Walter No French Fries and My Cafeteria Jones.
He was one of the guys who did the freedom fries thing.
I am really struggling with the idea that somebody wrote into a bill
before we've used 100% slave labor for our stuff,
but now we want our slaves to make things to give to nonprofit organizations.
Not 100%, but I get what you're saying.
Can you write that down and think of that as not terrifying psychopathy?
Yeah, it's weird.
That's wild.
What do you think Ron Paul voted?
I'm going to go with Ron Paul voted.
Wait, this would have restricted the amount that the government
could have bought from their slaves, right?
Yeah.
Okay, so I'm going to go with Ron voted for it.
He abstained from voting.
Oh, god damn it. That's because it's screwed with his brain.
He has to hate whatever Nancy Pelosi likes,
but he also wants private businesses to...
In the time of polarization that we're in now in the present day,
it is really weird to look at this and see it being pretty mixed
in terms of parties on each side.
The bill ended up passing the House 350 to 65,
but it died immediately upon being received by the Senate,
and no action was taken on it.
Cool.
Good work, government.
Way to do your jobs.
So Alex ends up talking to this guy named Colonel Craig Roberts,
and he's not the same person as Paul Craig Roberts,
who's a weirdo and guy who wrote for VDARE.
This dude is super into conspiracies like JFK.
Sure.
He loves Oklahoma City.
And the Finders.
Gotta love the Finders.
He's big into the Finders.
Yeah, absolutely.
So they're talking about some child rings and stuff
back in 2003.
Okay.
Alex isn't super into it, and it's not all that lascivious.
Good.
And he doesn't bring up Epstein, so that's interesting.
So he didn't know about Epstein.
He might have.
Could have.
It's not proof that he doesn't.
True.
But it's not something that comes up immediately.
Although Alex does say this in their interview.
It's like, ugh, come on.
Governments always get corrupt individuals in control of them.
They always seek to maintain control and expand that control.
They always flip out and get on power trips and start exterminating their populations
for no reason other than the fact that they serve their father.
We know who that is.
God damn it.
Infuriating.
Okay.
Still could be a metaphor.
It's very unsatisfying.
That's dark.
How dare he say that?
Stop tippy-toeing around it and dip your balls into Jesus, okay?
Let's go for it.
He still talks about Jesus from time to time.
I'm less interested in him being religious.
Right, right, right.
Which does exist.
Certainly not as extremist and overt as it is in the present.
Sure, sure.
But I'm not interested in that.
I'm interested in specifically the literalness of his waging war against the devil.
That like turning into a televangelist type deal.
Yes, yes.
Where everything we're doing is a fight against the literal Christian devil, you know?
So the Craig Roberts and Alex have a conversation that it hits on a number of kind of like,
I don't care, kind of conspiracy topics.
Sure, sure.
And it's, you know, it hits a lot of bases that we've hit before.
And I'm not so much interested in a lot of that minutia because of stuff like this.
Once they put laws into effect, they can say,
well this law is going to sunset for a certain time.
Well a Brady law sunsetted and it didn't go away.
The assault weapons ban sunsetted.
Patriot Act One sunsetted, but now they're saying they're going to get rid of that sunset.
These dudes are being super dishonest about the subject they're covering here.
For one thing, this episode is in 2003,
over a year before the federal assault weapons ban is set to hit its sunset date.
Alex is saying that the ban's sunset provision had just been ignored, which is a lie.
And even if he was just saying that they were going to ignore the sunset provision in the future,
he would be wrong.
The Patriot Act was not subject to a complete sunset clause,
but various sections of the bill were.
However, the sunset date for that bill was December 31, 2005,
more than two years in the future from the point that Alex is speaking here.
In terms of this one, it's a little bit more of a complicated picture.
I'm not in favor of the Patriot Act,
but I don't think that attacking it from the standpoint of sunset clauses
is a particularly effective approach.
There have been multiple bills over the years that reexamined
and reauthorized various provisions and amended some of them as well.
This is a common aspect of bills that have sunset clauses.
You know, it's not like they have a self-destruct clause.
The idea is to set a date in the future to reassess whether or not
the particular bill is worth continuing.
You can take issue with the decision to reauthorize the Patriot Act,
but pretending that reauthorizing it is somehow cheating?
That's a silly argument.
Yeah, that doesn't make any sense.
Both of these examples that Alex uses to make his point that the bills,
they have these sunset clauses, they just never go away,
they're bills that haven't reached their sunset dates yet.
He's just making this shit up.
Now, the case of the Brady Bill is actually a little bit more interesting.
The bill was first introduced in 1987 and was constantly a non-starter.
The Reagan administration didn't appear all that interested in it,
and Congress had a lot of trouble with getting it to a floor vote,
so they would tend to attempt to attach it to larger crime bills,
which ended up being a losing strategy.
All this changed when Bill Clinton was elected in 1992
and voiced support for the Brady Bill
and indicated that he was willing to sign it if it was passed.
This changed the landscape, and the bill made its way through Congress.
Part of the negotiation to get the bill through Congress
had to do with the mandatory waiting periods the bill put in place for gun purchases.
With the technology available at the time,
it could take a while to run a background check,
so a five-day period was included in the bill.
However, gun proponents wanted to strike a deal.
Their long-standing argument was that a provision should exist
that this waiting period would be made null and void
once the technology existed for an instant-check system.
This made some sense, given that the waiting period was largely predicated
on the technological inability to do the checks quicker.
Instead of this compromise, what was decided was that
the waiting-period provision of the bill would have a sunset clause
that would kick in in five years
whether or not there was an instant-check system that worked.
This satisfied both sides, and the bill passed the House and Senate in November 1993.
The Brady bill itself didn't have a sunset clause.
This provision of it did.
The larger bill was permanent, and put in place requirements for background checks
for gun sales made by federally licensed gun sellers.
In 1998, the NICS system was developed, and that kind of made this whole question moot.
The sunset clause came and went,
and now there is no federal waiting period required for purchasing a gun.
Each state has the right to make their own rules on that,
and according to a recent article from ABC News,
ten states and the District of Columbia have waiting periods,
whereas most states do not.
Alex and Craig Roberts are covering the subject from a completely dishonest perspective.
Alex is just making stuff up,
and Craig is pretending that the entire Brady bill was set to sunset
when in fact it was just the specific provision which did in fact go away.
I understand that there's staunch opponents of any kind of gun regulation,
but covering the material this inaccurately feels like it's a disservice
to sincere people who care about gun rights,
and it leads me not to take the stuff that they're saying all that seriously about any other issues.
Yeah, that's frustrating. That's very frustrating.
I don't like it. I don't like it.
Also, I don't like that the waiting period expired.
I think that's stupid.
At the very least, at the very least, here's what we should have.
No bad days waiting period.
You can't have a bad day and then go buy a gun.
You gotta wait at least until your bad day is over.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I do. I understand that position,
and I think that states that decide to pass those things are well within their right.
Makes sense.
The idea of not having a federal mandated waiting period doesn't seem that weird to me.
As long as the background check system does work and it is effective,
which I'm not positive it's fully operational and does a perfect job,
yeah, I don't know. I can see both sides of it, but I don't know.
I think on a state level it's fine for that to be where that lives.
Sure, sure, I see that.
Let's call it the no breakfast of champions law.
You can't have a sudden outbreak of a syphilitic breakdown and buy a gun on the same day.
I think that's fine.
Yeah, in a perfect world I would be alright with that.
Okay, good. We have come to compromise.
Sure.
Now, Jordan, it's time for you to play the theme song for our new segment.
Alright, Alex's True Story.
The one time I got death-threaded by the government was when Judge Walter Smith in Waco case wouldn't allow a jury.
And I don't know who did it, but obviously it was from that quarter.
And I went and we protested, we pointed this out, I was billing that Branch Davidian Memorial Church,
and they got very mad.
And I got little messages that couldn't come from anywhere but the government.
You know, the whole voice changer bit, the whole thing.
You know, the stuff from horror movies.
Anybody can do that.
Stuff from spy movies.
The news does that.
I love my country, you know, so be it.
I told them.
Whatever, you know, I don't know.
And I've been left alone.
I don't believe Alex's version of this story or that it happened,
but even if you take Alex at his word, in 2003 he had only been threatened once.
I just don't like that I know for a fact that they've been doing TV interviews with voice modulators and everything.
Oh, they haven't.
Yes, they have since the 80s.
Even before that.
And Alex is like, only the government has that capability.
Yeah, no one else has a voice box thing.
Yeah, absolutely not.
No, no, no.
There was a fucking vocoder for Peter God-
This is really high-tech stuff, all right?
Only the feds have this.
So he's talking, Alex is talking to Craig Roberts, and this clip really, really was a big problem for me.
Well, remember Chandra Levy, this was even on Fox and CNN.
It ended when it broke that she was involved in some type of weird satanic sex call.
Did you hear that, Colonel?
Yeah, and that didn't surprise me either because of all these other findings we have.
And there is a huge satanic underground movement that's linked to the homosexual community in Washington, D.C.
And we're not the only ones saying this. I mean, this stuff pops up on TV.
Oh, yeah.
Well, here's the first real indication that I've seen that maybe Alex does think he's up against the literal devil at this early stage in his career.
This one sounds pretty serious.
It's still not nearly as overt as he is now, but it's getting close to being disturbing.
The issue that I run into is that based on what Alex is saying, he could very well think that he's fighting a group of Satanists,
and at the same time not think that he's fighting the minions of the literal Christian devil.
True.
He could just think that these Satanists are idiots doing dark, pointless rituals to a non-existent deity,
so I regret to inform you that this is not conclusive enough for me to call this case closed.
True.
So I was interested in the idea that Chandra Levy, be it, was involved in a satanic sex cult.
This was news to me, so I decided to poke around and see what Alex is talking about.
It was also news to me.
This was not a story that broke in the mainstream news, and the reason people stopped talking much about Levy and Gary Condit was because 9-11 happened.
It wasn't like the media was worried that people would learn of a secret satanic sex cult, so they buried the story.
9-11 happened.
It was, well, I mean, that was, it, look, that happened in the morning.
Otherwise it was a slow news day.
I would imagine that not a lot that ranked happened that day after, yeah, I could see that.
So this is a bit confusing, but it appears that this traces back to a post on the website of a guy named Tex Mars.
This is upsetting for a number of reasons, and one of them actually dovetails with this stupid conspiracy that Alex is raising here on this episode.
Tex Mars died in 2019, but up to that point he was an incredibly prolific conspiracy theorist and extremist Christian speaker, coincidentally also based in Austin.
Perhaps one of the most distinctive traits of his, though, is a very clear, very deep, and very consistent anti-Semitism.
Tex still has a website running, and if you go there, you can purchase audio tapes of some of his lectures.
Or maybe they're preaching? I don't know.
Allow me to read some of the titles that you can buy, which I was tempted to buy, but I'm not going to give this asshole or his estate a penny.
Who killed Jesus? How cowardly lukewarm Christians are abandoning the truth and ripping passages out of the Bible in a futile attempt to appease the Jews.
Was that a sequel to Who Framed Roger Rabbit?
Nope.
Here's another one.
All hail the Jewish master race!
I think that sounds weirdly positive, honestly.
Here's a little snippet of the description of that one.
OK.
Quote, first the Romans asserted their superiority. Then came the Nazis and their exalted Aryan race.
Now, now it's the Jews who claim to be the master race.
Tex Mars exposes those would-be gods on Earth for what they are. Arrogant, power-grubbing people ferociously opposing God's truth.
Please, one quick second.
So here's another one.
Quote, Obama tells Jews no more. The president finally stands up to the world's tormentors.
What a weird thing to support Obama for.
This one was apparently about Rahm Emanuel leaving the administration.
Sure. Good for Rahm Emanuel, I guess.
One of them is called, quote, famous anti-Semites whom I admire.
Interestingly, Ron Paul.
That's just a diary entry.
Yeah.
That is just a diary entry. How dare you. Don't you just list that shit. Buzzfeed. Fuck you.
He includes Ron Paul on his list.
Oh, wow. Ron Paul is great at anti-Semitism.
Then there's one called, quote, chimeras, monsters, pizza gate, and the satanic hoodwink of America and the world.
That sounds like a pretty regular TED Talk, to be honest.
The description includes, quote, Jewish scientists are working on DNA that will be inserted into the mind of every person at birth,
ending anti-Semitism forever and creating new races that will love Jews.
That's almost a legitimate possible solution for Jews. I think they should try that one.
One more is called, quote, should Christians burn the Jewish Talmud?
No.
Now, I don't want to order or listen to this one, but I'm guessing the answer Tex comes to is yes.
Based on how the description ends. Quote, if Tex Mars were to declare an international burn the Talmud day,
would you be there to help him toss these trashy devil volumes into the bonfire?
Um.
Sure.
Uh.
Do the people burning holy books think they're the good guys?
Tex does.
Oh, okay.
Also, I should point out that his website also sells a bunch of books about how the Holocaust didn't happen,
including one by a guy named Brian A. Lewis Sherlebot.
That middle name's probably a coincidence, right?
That could be.
Probably a coincidence.
Could be. I doubt there's anything to do with it.
Oh, boy.
Tex Mars is a giant pile of shit, and one of the things that's the most constant theme of his is that Judaism is synonymous with Satanism.
It's something that constantly comes up in his lecture titles.
One is just called, quote, inventors of evil things, how the Jews created Freemasonry, Illuminism, Communism, Satanism, Witchcraft,
and the New Age movement, and what they're up to now.
The description of that tape includes this.
Quote, Jesus said of the Jews, you are of your father the devil, and he spoke absolute truth.
The historical record is clear.
Wow. Good work, Bible.
Now, this also takes us back to earlier, when Alex used, you know, you are of your father.
Little bit.
Little bit of...
Might be some crossover.
...troubling parallels.
Could be something to do with that.
For someone like Tex Mars, all roads lead back to Jewish people being behind the conspiracies that he promotes.
His brand is antisemitism.
It's just impossible to engage with his material and not understand that.
So if Alex, taking this conspiracy about Chandra Levy being involved in satanic sex cults, you know, that's from Tex Mars's website,
if he's taking that seriously, that's an indication of a very serious trend towards antisemitic content on Alex's part in this period.
Tex wrote at least two columns about Chandra Levy's disappearance and murder,
and thankfully these are not behind a paywall, so I could read them.
They're fucking ridiculous.
Okay.
One attempts to make the argument that Levy was a secret Mossad agent.
Quote, an accumulation of evidence indicates that the 24-year-old Levy was a youthful recruit in the Israeli Mossad,
that nation's premier spy agency.
In that capacity, she had served as an intern at the executive offices of California Governor Gray Davis, an Illuminati initiate,
and that is where she first met Mr. Condit, also an Illuminati servant.
This falls just short of being convincing.
Is that an accumulation of evidence or just like a-
It's piling up.
Yeah, okay.
Tex, based on literally no evidence other than his imagination, decides that as a Mossad agent,
Chandra had insinuated herself in Gary Condit's life, then used him to get herself access to the CIA headquarters.
There, she learned of the Illuminati's plan to use fake Islamic terrorists to do 9-11,
and thus she had to be killed so she couldn't spill the beans.
Wow, she's good.
Tex puts it this way.
Quote, as horrifying as the question may be, one must now contemplate the mind-numbing possibility-
No.
That Chandra Levy very well may have been victim to a darkly vicious satanic force.
Damn.
My response to this is, must one?
Yes.
I don't think one must contemplate that possibility.
I don't know, have you started contemplating it yet?
I have.
Okay, see, then you did.
According to Tex, these darkly vicious satanic forces are the work of, quote,
DC's exclusive satanic brotherhood, to which he claims literally all members of Congress have to be a part.
Not that exclusive.
When Tex Mars is discussing these satanic forces, you'd have to be a monumental idiot to not understand he's demonizing Jewish people.
Yeah.
It's really fucking obvious if you know anything about his work.
You could just check out his lecture titled, quote, The Jews Are Preparing a Grave for America,
which warns that, quote, powerful Jewish interests have a stranglehold on American government, the economy, and our culture.
We are in grave danger!
What's the anti-Semitic about that?
On the one hand, it's kind of intriguing to have this first step towards Alex talking about his feelings about the devil and Satanism in 2003.
But on the other, and much more serious hand, it's a real problem when you pull the thread of what he's talking about
and it leads back to another Austin-based conspiracy theory who believes that Satanism is a plot of the Jews.
Yeah, it would be hard to believe that, living in Austin simultaneously, no one brought him up to Alex.
No one brought this guy up, so Alex has no idea who this is, and this is all coming from his own brain.
I know that Tex Mars has been on Alex's show before.
Of course.
Yeah, although I don't think that he plays as much of a role in later times.
I know that the name has come up, but one of the problems is there's another guy who's a conspiracy theorist named Jim Mars.
Damn.
I know he was on Alex's show a lot, and I think that Tex Mars had a lesser, but definitely a still-existing presence.
Right.
And they both created M&Ms together?
Mm-hmm.
Good joke.
Sorry. That was shitty.
So yeah, I'm really troubled by this.
I did not expect that the first sort of fuller overture towards talking about satanic forces and what have you
would be in the context of a story that was widely disseminated primarily by Tex Mars,
who has a tendency towards satanism and stuff being coded ways for him to be antisemitic.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That leads me to be very worried about how much more antisemitic Alex's show may have been in the past.
Yeah, it does seem like...
And it's making me clear that I need to, when I'm looking at these past episodes,
I need to be a little bit more cognizant of that.
Right, right.
Because the question could be raised like, with the globalists,
is he stealing obviously effective antisemitic propaganda in order to rebrand it
and use what is a very effective way to make his own money?
Right.
Or is he antisemitic and he's just camouflaging that same propaganda under the term globalists?
Yeah.
So it's that kind of appropriation versus...
It's a question that we've never really been able to find definitive answers to.
Right.
This does seem like a good...
It's more troubling.
Yeah.
Because I don't believe that anybody, anybody could engage with the work that Tex Mars puts out
and not be aware of the particular character of antisemitism.
Yeah.
And a bunch of other stuff too, anti-Catholic.
He just hates a lot of people.
But I don't think that you could.
And for Alex to, you know, seem to take information from his website seriously,
it makes you worried about what other stuff he might.
Yeah, that's not good.
Yeah.
That's not good.
So we now jump to the 13th because they have such a good time, Craig and Alex,
that they just take calls and...
Sure.
It's boring.
Yeah.
So we jump to the 13th and overnight there was a bombing in Saudi Arabia.
There was a series of bombings.
And based on nothing, Alex has decided that this was a false flag.
Sure.
And he has a list of suspects.
Go for it.
Now, this could be the CIA.
It could be Mossad.
Or it really could be Palestinians that got into the country, got explosives and did this.
There are real suicide bombers.
There are real terror groups.
They are few and far between.
We don't know right now.
We probably never will.
We know Vladimir Putin blew up three apartment buildings to get martial law going in Russia.
That's admitted though.
So that keeps going.
Yeah.
Again.
Yeah, you just gotta toss that in there.
Yeah, that's pretty constant.
It is a really great example of a false flag effectively turning a man into a dictator.
So, there's that.
Yeah, so Alex has these suspects for this bombing and it's just based on nothing.
Like, he has nothing to demonstrate or prove that this was in any way anything other than
suicide bombings.
I don't know.
It feels like maybe it's the CIA or Mossad.
Yeah, probably.
Feels like it could be, Dan.
So, one of the things that we've heard Alex say in various periods of time is conditional
acceptance of wars of regime change.
Sure, sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's something he actually really does believe.
You know, if the government was leaving our liberties alone, leaving our guns alone, leaving
our freedoms alone, controlling our borders, and they said, let's invade Iraq because they're
bad.
Let's invade Syria, Iran.
I could say, well, that violates what George Washington said.
But you know what?
You can't really argue with it too much.
If they were really bringing freedom and all this, but they're not.
They're mowing down protesters.
They're giving them $20 a month to live on.
They're totally enslaving them.
They're grabbing all the oil.
They're enslaving us here domestically.
They got gun bills that dwarf all gun control ever seen that Bush says he's gonna sign.
Again, this is the same thing as the thing about prison labor.
It's somebody who has the same position as you being opposed to prison labor or being
opposed to the war in Iraq, but the reasons are not the same, and that's bad.
Because Alex is conditionally fine with regime change wars as long as people will just leave
him alone.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
Apartheid is bad.
Sometimes.
That's not a good take.
That's not a good take, Dan.
No.
Not a good take.
No, because if you solve the wrong problem, then the bigger problem is okay.
It's still there.
Hooray.
It's okay with Alex.
Yeah.
No, we can't have a dictator in this country.
Well, I mean, we can have my dictator.
Yeah.
That's a good dictator.
I don't mind a dictator as long as they leave me alone.
It's gotta be my dictator who's gonna do what I say.
Yeah.
That's how I want things to work.
I tell people how to live.
Now, I should tell you, I have studied everything about tyranny and I am probably the only person
who really understands it and is a voice against all forms of despotism.
Except for the women that I do.
Right.
Because if you do my dictatorship, you'll never have another dictator.
Yeah.
Duh.
And I think that this is indicative of the shallowness of Alex's opposition and the shallowness
of his beliefs, at least surrounding the issues that he presents himself as being on the marquee
of that.
100 certain.
Yeah.
It's really troubling to me.
And one of the things that I can't really get past is like how obvious it is listening
to this, that even if you didn't know that Alex turned into the biggest piece of shit
in the world.
Right.
If I heard him say that back then, I would be like, wait a second.
Sure.
Wait a second.
You would be fine with this war if you didn't have your guns hypothetically needing to be
registered?
I don't know.
You know?
That's one of those things.
And I think what it is not so much that as it is like I think about going back and watching
a movie from the 90s now and stuff pops up and you're like, I remember this movie as
being one thing.
Yeah.
And now I saw this and I'm like, holy shit.
That's definitely true.
I think if you give somebody the benefit of the doubt, especially during the time period,
you're going to wind up missing or like skipping over in your brain just stuff and being like,
he wasn't really thinking about that.
He's on the radio.
He's just talking shit.
You know, like that kind of stuff.
I guess that's true.
And you can also, you can't account for like how differently you engage with things based
on the time.
Totally.
You know, like watching, I went back and I watched some of the like attitude era wrestling
not too long ago, a couple of years back.
And I was watching it.
I was horrified.
Yeah.
Some of the stuff was like, wow, not realize, oh, you go back and you're like, Jesus Christ.
So Alex has this, this story.
The main story of the episode is the bombing in Saudi Arabia.
There is no real actual discussion of it.
There's no, I mean, there's discussion of it, but there's no information that he provides.
There's nothing.
You can't really discuss that.
It's a false flag.
Every information that you get would be false information, Dan.
So you just got to speculate, right?
There's a lot of speculation and then also this, this is what I think is the most important
thing.
We'll be right back and I'll get into the NRA finally admitting the ultra gun grabbing
is going on.
More on the bombings, more on the terror drills that coincide with the bombings, final control
is needed.
See what happens when you don't become our slaves, the Batman come and eat boom, boom
you.
Operation Northwoods will be back.
So I have to say that this is a pretty desperate attempt to grasp at straws on Alex's part.
In order for his theories to make any sense, terrorist attacks have to match up with drills
and you can see here because he's already covered the top off drill, he'll accept any
event as connected regardless of how weak the argument is.
Oh, totally.
His belief about the whole drill thing is that the globalists use drills so they can
have plausible deniability in case one of their plans goes wrong or, you know, someone
involved in the attack gets caught.
For instance, they'll run a bombing drill when they plan to carry out a bombing because
that way they can plan out the details of the bombing and if anybody asks what they're
doing, they can say it's for the drill.
Sure.
There are also ideas about how the globalists have to tell you what they're doing before
they do it according to some dumb intergalactic contract law.
But generally speaking, this concept that the drills are used as cover is central to
why the connection between drill and event means anything.
Alex's theories about the London 7-7 bombing rely on a misunderstanding about news reports
about a consultant giving a brainstorming presentation to business executives where
he had a scenario planned that closely mirrored the actual events of the bombing.
That's a thin connection to draw, but at least the subject matter of the scenario and the
attack were similar enough that you could see what Alex is trying to say.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
In this instance, there were a number of suicide bombings in residential compounds in Riyadh
that were generally known to be occupied by foreigners, particularly Westerners.
Meanwhile, in Chicago and Seattle, there was an interagency exercise going on that simulated
a simultaneous biological attack in one city and a dirty bomb in another.
These two situations lack the primary piece of the whole drill conspiracy puzzle, which
is that they're used to plan the attacks.
Yeah, that's what they're supposed to be.
Or that there's a connection between the two.
That's what they're supposed to be used for.
This is sloppy shit, and I'm kind of shocked that Alex's listeners wouldn't realize this.
I can kind of understand buying the whole drill conspiracy when there's overlap between
the drill and the event, but even when you accept this nonsense, now Alex expects you
to believe this extends this far?
These completely unrelated and not even thematically connected scenarios in Seattle and Chicago
are somehow related to bombings in Riyadh, like when there's a very unpopular war happening
in Iraq.
That is probably one of the benefits for him of having constant global news at all times
because something is always happening.
So there's always something coincidentally happening with something else that he wants
to claim.
Yeah, but this is, this is soft.
Oh, it's weak shit.
It is weak tea.
It's a ways off.
I wouldn't even, if I were Alex, I wouldn't even try this.
He's a young gun.
He's inexperienced.
He's really giving a shot.
You gotta find your boundaries, and the only way to find your boundaries is to step beyond
them.
Fine.
So anyway, Alex talks about this a little bit more, and my only note on this is that
this is unfair.
Already into the second hour of this worldwide broadcast, wide open phones in the shower.
We talk about the tragic, convenient, right on time bombings to legitimize the police
state and these drills they're running, the FEMA takeover drills, the martial law preparation
activation tests that's going on for the FEMA takeover.
So now the bombings themselves are meant to give credibility to the exercises that are
being run in Seattle and Chicago.
What the fuck?
No, I'm very tired.
You can't.
That exhausts me.
Yeah.
This is pretzel shit, dude.
Yeah, no.
No, you cannot eat your own tail at me.
That's not possible.
Yeah, it's not, it's not fair.
It's not fair.
Either these exercises are used to provide cover and planning for the globalists or they're
part of contract law or they're not actually what's like, sometimes the terrorist attack
is actually about the exercise.
It's actually the reverse.
Sure.
Yeah.
That's what I was thinking.
He like twisted it around.
So now that the, now the terrorist attack is providing cover for the drills instead
of the drills.
I mean, I guess the reality is that when anything is fake, it doesn't matter.
That's a good point.
If you believe or like your editorial line for these narratives is that all this stuff
is fake, it's no longer disrespectful to take something like this and use it however you
want because who cares?
Your editorial position is just expediency.
Whatever's the, I, yeah, I don't know if anybody's ever really truly made a career out of taking
the path of least resistance quite like Alex.
It's just like, I'm just flowing.
You know, he's almost reached a zen position of just flowing through the river.
Whatever bullshit comes out of his mouth, he just rides along it behind him.
He's self-sustaining a fart blimp.
That's what he is, Dan.
I have become one with the wind.
He is the Hindenburg.
So Alex takes some calls and he gets a call from a guy who gets pretty religious with
him.
Sure.
So quick, Alex hangs up on this guy.
Okay.
But I also spend my life also in the scriptures and what's amazing to me, the things that
are being spoken, not only by yourself, but there's a few others like you out there that
the scripture speaks of.
I hear you and I appreciate your call, Nante, and it's good to have you as a listener.
Take care.
If you're dead in Pennsylvania and you're on the air, go ahead.
This caller was saying that you're in the Bible.
Alex, I am calling to say that you're a prophet.
Listen, I don't have that kind of stuff on my show.
Cut to, I am the Messiah!
Yeah.
Wow.
Quite a change.
God damn.
God damn that is fast.
Yep.
In 2003, one of his sort of primary positions and branding strategies is anti-police brutality
and anti-police stuff.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's a quick, easy way to look above the left-right paradigm.
Yes.
Because I mentioned it and it's online at info-wars.com right now.
Councilwoman criticizes action by constables.
This is out of the Morning Call Online mainstream newspaper.
They shot three dogs too fatally when they went to serve a warrant in Allentown for unpaid
parking tickets.
Saying there is a doozy of a problem here, Allentown Councilwoman Gail Hoover expressed
outrage Sunday over the shooting of three dogs too fatally by constables serving a warrant
on a man who had not paid parking tickets.
Obviously, this is not something I'm okay with.
Police should never behave this way, and I think we can all agree on that.
I just find it interesting that Alex ends up taking almost an entire segment on the
show to rant about this story, which is honestly tragic, but definitely doesn't seem like something
that needs to be front and center of the show's news that day.
It just makes me really sad to see him spending like ten minutes decrying the evils of the
police killing two dogs, when in his later career he rationalizes that sometimes police
are right when they shoot unarmed black people.
Personally, I'm opposed to all acts of police violence, but I don't think a story like this
actually ranks as important news for a number of reasons.
The first is that even from Alex's headline, you can tell that the city council person
is upset about this event, and is pushing to take appropriate steps to address the issue.
No, all globalists are evil.
In this instance, you can see unacceptable behavior from the police, but you can also
almost be certain that the victim is going to win a civil suit and have some kind of
restitution.
And that's exactly what did end up happening, when they settled a claim against the cops
who shot their dogs for $320,000.
Money can never make up for the loss of a loved pet, but what can you do after the fact?
Hold people responsible and pay the victims.
Even this story that came out in the morning call about this shooting prior to this episode
that Alex is recording quotes another cop who quote, said he wanted the family to know
that constables carry up to $500,000 in liability insurance.
Quote, we're walking cash cows for a good lawyer, he said.
Even other cops in the department were saying that they needed to do what needed to be done
to make things right.
Wow.
And they had a lot of insurance.
That cop reminds me so much of that Kyle Kinane bit, where he's like, you know, you meet somebody,
you meet enough, you live an interesting enough life, you meet plenty of cops in your day.
And every now and again, you find one who's just like there but for the grace of God,
he's like, I could have been working at the gas station or I could be in a cop pays five
bucks better.
So, oh, man, that's great.
That cop just being like, hey, man, sue the shit out of me.
I don't got to worry about shit.
You got a lot of insurance.
Come on.
So we have one last clip here.
It's another story that Alex is sort of touching on, but he doesn't really know the details.
And I'm driving along listening when I left to the, you know, seven o'clock news or whatever.
But I'm listening and they said that the that the governor with the Speaker of the House
has ordered the arrest of over 80 members of the legislature.
And I'm listening.
No, I'm not kidding.
I'm listening to them reading this, this AP headline national headline, because they say
they've been ordered basically under Homeland Security to follow all orders, the voters
they're told by Washington.
And then you hear this state rep from Houston saying they're taking over.
We won't be part of this.
And that's all it said.
We don't know what they're talking about.
I typed in the article.
It popped up.
It just said they've been ordered to be arrested.
See, I'm so conditioned in this la la land that I'm hearing that members of the House
have been ordered in the Senate to be arrested.
I don't know how you do it.
I mean, that's the fact people are listening right now in Texas, you heard this was on
national AP news, call into the show if you heard it, why I didn't print that article.
I read it online last night when I got home, didn't print it didn't cover it.
I can't keep track of it anymore.
Seems like if it's this kind of story, you probably should have thought to print it.
Yeah.
All right.
So what happened here is that the Republicans had taken control of the Texas legislature
in the most recent election, and they were pushing a hard agenda that included harsh
spending cuts and redistricting.
How funny is it that we no longer live in a world where I can assume after you say the
Texas Republicans took control of the legislature, that it would end in, in an election.
The Texas House requires a quorum of at least a hundred of their members to actually meet
and vote on things.
So 58 of the Democrats in office decided just to not show up, to boycott the agenda that
they were essentially powerless to stop in a vote.
This is something they can do, and in response, the House Speaker has the authority to send
the Texas Rangers out to find them and bring them in to vote.
It's basically hide and seek, but with the government.
Exactly.
52 of the lawmakers decided to get out of the state in order to avoid being arrested,
so the Speaker requested help from other states to get them back into chambers.
Naturally.
An Associated Press article includes an amazingly dishy response from New Mexico Attorney General
Patricia Madrid, who said that she had, quote, no authority to arrest lawmakers who show
up there, but went on to say, quote, nevertheless, I have put out an all-points bulletin for
law enforcement to be on the lookout for politicians in favor of health care for the needy and
against tax cuts for the wealthy.
Ha ha ha ha!
Goddamn!
Woo!
Get her!
Oh, get her on Roast Battle!
Shit!
Yeah.
Goddamn!
The Democrats returned when the time had elapsed for the bill, but it didn't matter.
Governor Rick Perry held repeated special sessions to push through the redistricting
plan and eventually got it passed, thereby gerrymandering the hell out of the state house
districts and giving a very strong advantage to Republicans to remain in power.
Alex is pretending that this is an instance of power-mad folks having their political
opponents arrested and sent to the hole, but the reality is it's part of political maneuvering
that's uncommon, but it's not really outside of the standard rules set forth by the Texas
House.
Yeah, it's power-mad politicians so corrupt that they're willing to destroy their entire
state in order to ensure that right-wing politics rules the day.
Listen.
It has nothing to do with putting your political enemies in the hooskout.
Listen, the gerrymandering and the redistricting stuff is the real issue.
That's the real problem.
That's the conversation.
That's corrupt and power-hungry.
The sending Texas Rangers out to bring people back to vote is a silly portion of the rules
of
Yeah, we live in a weird world.
Yes.
It's a sort of government procedure.
Yeah, there is that, like, I understand that we have those rules, but this is childish.
Sure.
This is silly.
Like how you have to say, like, the good, gentlewoman from New Hampshire.
Totally.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
Shut the fuck up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't need this bullshit.
Yeah.
So, we reached the end of this.
I mean, that was a pretty boring episode, the 13th, I gotta say.
Yeah.
Not much goes on.
It did not feel like it.
A lot of talk about that bombing.
Sure.
A lot of actual information.
But I think that we stumbled upon something fairly important here, and this is
The satanic cabal, living underneath DC, swallowing the blood of our children.
The way that this is characterized, the way this sort of has a little bit of a clue leading
back to Tex Mars is a bit troubling.
And I'm worried about what we're actually going to find through this fanciful and seemingly
fun investigation into when Alex started thinking he was fighting the devil.
Yeah.
The uncovering that maybe this, too, is all rooted in appropriated or exploited anti-Semitic
ideals is not what I would have liked.
It does feel a lot like that day you're like, hey, Carrie Cassidy, kind of an anti-Semite.
And then it all crumbled down and you're like, fuck, all fun things just wind up with anti-Semitism
at the bottom.
Brutal.
It does seem that this might be another indication or another example of that, and we will see.
We will check back in and, you know, we'll see what we find.
I hope it really goes well for him.
Alex?
I have bad news.
He shows up.
I hope he gets his act together.
Oh, no.
Right now, I feel like 2003, there's a bright future ahead of him.
Eighteen years later, he will be on air threatening to eat his neighbors.
There's that.
There is that.
Okay.
I don't think it goes well.
It's at best lateral because he's richer.
That's true.
He's much richer.
In some ways.
Yeah.
Anyway, we'll check back in, but until then, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's at knowledgefight.com.
Yep.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledge underscore fight.
And I go to bed.
And we're on iTunes.
If you could, please find a local charity or bail fund in your area.
Yep.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX.
Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I kind of think that steak knife is a fine code name.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.