N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys.
Dan and Jordan.
Knowledgefight.
Riddleware.
I need, I need money.
Andy and Chanzas.
Stop it.
It's time to pray.
Andy and Chanzas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first-time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your room.
Knowledgefight.
N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey, everybody.
Welcome back to Fight Knowledge.
I am Jordan.
I'm Dan.
This is the podcast where Celine worships at the altar of Dan Friesen, and we talk about
anybody but Alex Jones.
Me and Celine have a collaborative worship relationship.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a real mutual worship kind of thing.
Very symbiotic.
If you will.
Jordan, I have a question for you.
What's that, Dan?
What is your bright spot for today?
My bright spot for today is... I'm not trying to plug.
I have no interest in plugging.
Oh, shit.
This sounds like it's a lead-in to a plug.
We did an episode of the other show that we do, the D&D show.
The Dungeons and Dragons.
Yes.
God's damn wizard.
You are the dungeon master.
Yeah.
And last night-
Slightly competent dungeon master.
Oh, boy.
Flailing about dungeon master.
But last night we recorded, and it had been a couple of weeks since we recorded, and it
was so fucking great.
It was a lot of fun.
To hang out with all of the... with Marty and Liz and Sarah and you.
It's just so much fun to hang out.
Yeah, it is.
It is.
It's a fun social thing that we don't get enough of these days, and we could have been
doing stuff like it this whole time.
The whole time?
Yeah.
It turns out it was always there.
And I admire your effort that you've put into that.
You know, we shit on you a bit, but it wouldn't work if you didn't have a story-
No, that's true.
For it.
That is true.
No, and it's just so much fun.
If you like it, you like it.
That's great.
But I like it, so everybody else can go to hell.
That kind of thing.
Well, your bright spot actually kind of weaves into mine a little bit, and that is that we
did do that Dungeons & Dragons-ish role-playing thing, and it got away from me a little bit.
I had a few drinks, and I watched the White Rapper show on VH1.
For a long time, it was not available anywhere.
I couldn't find the actual episodes, and I started watching some of it on YouTube.
It's now available on YouTube.
Thank God for internet archivists who are just like, yeah, I guess it was a show in
2003.
We're going to find it, and we're going to put it up.
It's going to be out there.
It doesn't matter what it is.
I watched the finale, and John Brown is great.
That's my bright spot.
John Brown.
King of the burbs.
King of the burbs, and king of murdering slave owners.
The two greats of John Browning.
You know what I say about murdering slave owners?
Hooray!
Hallelujah, holla back.
Yeah, there we go.
Well, Dan, for today's episode, episode number six of Jordan Takes the... Well, 5.1 since
we lost five.
Yeah.
I think we have to call this five.
We'll call this five.
But I am engineering this to make sure that audio doesn't disappear.
Yes, I did notice that.
So today we are going to be talking about Nazis and aliens, Dan.
Oh, thank God.
That's what I'm all about.
Oh my God.
I will say this.
I went through-
You told me that you had found something that was really exciting and really interesting.
I didn't know what to expect, and you telling me that it's Nazis and aliens, that is as
good as it could have been as a reveal.
It's about as good as it can get, then.
Thank you, Jordan.
So we will be talking about one, maybe or maybe not, Dr. Joseph Ferrell.
But I think before we do that, we're going to need to say thank you to some people who
have-
Yes, I think we would agree to do that.
So first, let's say what's up to Peaches are Nasty, Plums are Supreme.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
I totally agree with that too.
Plums are underrated.
Yeah, wrong.
Next, SirMcSwagins III.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, SirMcSwagins.
Next, Zach from Texas.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Zach.
This one is a policy wonk and also an added shout out.
Shout out to Basic, and this is the name here.
Fuck you, Myles.
I rode that wave like a dick.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much to all of that.
Next, Sara Cat.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Sara Cat.
word here uh-huh tacos burritos and chimichangas thank you so much you are
now a policy wonk I'm a policy wonk thank you very much tacos burritos
chimichangas and I gotta say we have a we have a technocrat and this is
actually a combo girl with a you uh-huh girl and Edith Beauvoir Beale Napoleon
Moyle you're now a technocrat I'm a policy wonk crikey mate that's fantastic
have yourself a brew how's your 401k doing bro all right we got to go full
tilt boogie on this Watson all right let's just get down to business we ain't
making that money off that heroin why are you pimps so good my neck is
freakishly large I declare info war on you thank you very much to the both of
you Jordan yes sir we are recording this in advance but we're on vacation indeed
we are um and I kind of lied to you oh no yeah what happened well see here's
the thing oh my god have you been dead this whole time yes I'm trying to lure
you to my ghost home I knew it's too good to be true Dan Friesen has been
dead for 17 years no I you know it seemed like just a random vacation it's
like it's overdue let's take some time and have have some fun sure the reality
is that I'm celebrating a couple of walks birthdays okay so I wish I had
birthday to just another Dan okay great name great name I feel like every Dan
should not feel like they're just another day this is another Dan I think
every Dan is special except for Dan Hastert no Dennis Hastert I somehow
mixed up Dan Snyder and Dennis Hastert in my head okay and they're both
monsters so that sure sure and then also Newt I got a fantastic lovely email from
Newt and I'd like to wish Newt a happy birthday although you could go with a
Gingrich on this one but you shouldn't no actually that's my grandfather's name
is that right it is his name I didn't know that oh yeah yeah it's a strange
name it is well he's his birth name I believe is not I believe his birth name
is noble okay and somehow they just started calling him I guess at a certain
point in time Newt was short for noble and so that's how he goes Wow yeah how
about that I don't dislike it as a name and also while we're in Hawaii I will be
chasing down a ton of lizards and newts and for shows oh you got so iguana I
might come back with a bunch of iguanas oh yeah we're gonna get a new thing of
luggage we're gonna poke some holes in it and you're just gonna have a bag of
lizards that you're wandering around with I think that that was one of the
most important parts of my childhood in Hawaii was fine it was so we will
reclaim a little bit of that anyway fun than the plains of central Midwest I
will say that so Jordan I hear I hear that we have a conversation about Nazis
and aliens indeed we do today we will be talking about an interview that Joseph
Farrell gave with Richard Surrett who does the conspiracy show with Richard
Surrett he is also a regular guest host on coast to coast okay so so he's he's
that kind of one of the junior varsity guys yeah yeah I don't keep track of
those guys unfortunately no and we're yeah there he's he's pretty I don't know
we'll see how how much you like him but Joseph Farrell is called a doctor a has
from what his bio says a doctorate of patristics from Oxford University okay
which is basically a theology kind of thing if you go by what many people who
of interviewing have given him credits for he has a doctorate of physics if you
go by other people he has a doctorate of what was it not patristics either
philosophy none of which I think he has uh-huh I kind of don't think that he
went to Oxford mainly because he has one story about his time at Oxford and I can
find no evidence that this Joseph Farrell went to Oxford however there's
another Joseph Farrell with a doctorate of economics from Oxford okay that's
possible and his story from Oxford his years there is he was at a debate at the
Oxford Union Society that lasted for eight days oh my god and it was
sponsored by Heineken for the Ethiopia food relief right right around live aid
all of that stuff and endurance debate yes and here's the thing here's the
thing if this is true then Boris fucking Johnson was there whoa because they were
but Boris was running the Union debate society uh-huh and so we should know
about this were they on opposite sides of the issue or they don't know allegedly
no no what I'm saying is he doesn't mention Boris Johnson at all it seems
like it would be a headline seems like you would know if you were at a eight
day debate with the future fucking Prime Minister of the United Kingdom yeah
the debate went so long that I had to break pencils and make a little fire in
order to keep warm yeah like Wade Boggs exactly yes absolutely he also according
to himself grew up in South Dakota and one fun story he tells is that when he
was growing up he was around six or seven years old and his best friends
there were more than one of them who had fathers who fought for the Germans in
World War two so great bread yeah so he grew up around Nazis yeah now here is
the kind of thing you generally want to keep a close to the vest I don't want to
tell people cuz he and he tosses it off like hey they fought for the Germans
yeah it's weird enough that like you know we we do a show where Alex talks
about like being Confederate Royal yeah exactly that's weird enough but I would
I would think that like I know people and I hung out who's who were not we're
not they were just Nazis yeah no big deal um but he is however a scholar I
think the fact that he grew up around Nazis will explain a lot of his later on
his later life however he is definitely a scholar he's got at least a master's
degree that I can confirm and he has written a total of maybe 40 45 books
that's too many books way too many here's the strangest part though okay
his first books are all about religion he translated the mystagogy of the Holy
Spirit by patriarch Phodios from the Greek and apparently it's a really good
translation and he he's cited writing the foreword in in Christian circles of
the well holy cow this is foreign to our show totally totally he wrote free will
in st. Maximus the confessor which is him trying to deal with Calvinism he
does not do well and then the disputation of Pyrrhus as well as what
was the other one do God history and dialectic which is his final religious
book now that was published in 1997 in 2002 he published his next book which
would begin the future of his career hmm would you like to guess what the title
of that book might be well I mean you've already sort of tilted some of these
cards indeed and I think there's aliens involved probably so I would I would say
that likely it has something to do with space Raptors being involved with the
Holocaust he's a Death Star okay that's right if you thought that the pyramids
were just tombs you're an idiot totally that pyramid is a Death Star exactly
like well the one from Star Wars I would like to bring up that they were for
storing grain during the presidential debates from there he went on an
absolute terror that continues to this day he keeps cranking out books some of
which the titles can be like this grid of the gods the aftermath of the cosmic
war and the physics of the pyramid peoples who not a bad title uh Reich of
the Black Sun Nazi secret weapons and the Cold War Allied legend oh boy yeah
let's see financial vipers in Venice alchemical money magical physics and
banking in the Middle Ages and Renaissance of all of his titles there's
four of them in his early life that are like I am a good Christian I read
theology I'm focused on this and he's a good historian and then he something
happens and he's just off the map yeah like completely off the map and winds
up on the SPLC's hate watch list because he is oh why well you know
that's something that I have been struggling with because I think if
you'll listen to him as we go along he's not a Nazi what I think he is is a Nazi
fanboy that's that can be as bad it is it is weird it is really weird yeah it's
a strange and it's it's not a big distinction it's a strange one in that I
don't think he wants the Nazis to win mm-hmm but I do think he's amazed at how
good the Nazis were at finding alien technology hmm which is a very strange
a subset of anti-semitism sure but it's there it's definitely I'm interested to
see how you lay out this argument well I mean so so he's he's another of the he
talks about globalists makes the makes a bunch of puns about them he's he
fancies himself a bit of a Dennis Miller type sure but yeah I don't know we'll
see we'll see how that goes um then there are another thing there are
another few things that are incredibly annoying about him for instance he
always wears a hat and it is always it is either a Indiana Jones hat or a
classic English bowler this guy's from South Dakota yeah I went to Oxford yeah
I think he might be playing that a little bit well I wore I wore a bowler
for a little while in high school tell people you went to Oxford I had no I
but it was a desperate affectation yeah yeah and here's one that's even worse he
chain smokes chain smokes with a Cruella Deville cigarette holder oh my god I
love this and he does not inhale he chain smokes and he just puffs the smoke
out the whole time so it's it's so infuriating to watch this man I'm just
screaming at him like I quit smoking stop doing this there's a part of me
that kind of enjoys that because it's so intentional yeah it's it's not so
obvious yeah like no it couldn't be more pathetic or or his life is art and this
is a piece of the there's also there's a well we'll see if he was parodying the
type of it's oh if he is doing like a Kaufman thing so say that what happened
after his religious books ended is he was like oh shit actually religion
might be stupid I'm going to create this character and pull off a decades-long
scam to show people just how easy and how similar religion and Giza Death Star
really are what what if he just saw Andy Kaufman do his wrestling totally sort of
stretch it was like totally I could do this but with religion it's not hard he
he was he was on his translating game yeah and he came across a text he didn't
tell anybody about it translated it up right and he's like oh no oh no I must
satirize I got it somebody's got to do it yeah if nobody else is stepping up to
the plate it's got to be me mm-hmm yeah he's he's a he's a real like professor
type but the kind who kind of creepily talks to his students and chain smokes
with a thing but doesn't inhale he says so on and so forth almost at the end of
everything he says it is the most he's just an annoying guy he's just such an
annoying guy you know what though I mean I say be that as it may and totally
interesting like I you can't fault somebody necessarily for their tics those
that you know cliches and now no problem but after every sentence people people
just have ways of speaking and so on and so forth that's fair that's fair and so
forth so on we go I what is going to happen I've listened to probably like
15 hours of this guy talk and none of it was it all remotely usable yeah little
behind the scenes yeah George you you were telling me how interesting this
person is and how much you wanted to talk about him but he's so boring yes
you'd watched hours and hours of stuff there's nothing here and then and then
last night he goes on Richard Surrett show surprisingly enough and there is a
lot of interesting stuff there also in this particular interview Joseph Pharrell
is looking into the webcam on his computer and he is holding an old-time
phone up to his ear like a big old-timey phone like the the peach ones that you
could really slam with a wire cord the ones that had like that you had to put
your finger in and and go around the rotary the whole thing yeah it was it is
it is so ridiculous to watch a man in a webcam holding a phone up to his ear I
like that I kind of do but old man house phone would have been like that's tacky
you should have just done audio that's actually got some Intel on this he has a
hamburger phone it's a house phone but it's a hamburger okay so he threw away
his old Bart Simpson phone yes it upgrade oh yeah so we are going to
begin this interview and you are going to hear Richard Surrett give you some
whiplash if we get they're doing they're gonna open up they say in phases so the
first phase if 60% of the population is vaccinated will give you a little bit of
your normal back if then in phase two if 70% you'll get a little sliver of your
normal life back and then finally phase three we need 80% of you vaccinated I
mean I don't want to argue the efficacy or the safety of vaccines and people
want to have the vaccine that's certainly their business and those that
don't that's their business but this this level of coercion you know have we
forgotten about the Nuremberg Code I mean how can how can people have such
short memories that's I mean that's that's very yeah what's fun about that I
find it so interesting that he is reasonable all the way like you know
what if you want to get the vaccine I'm not gonna be a huge answer it's killing
you and if you don't want to get the vaccine I'm not gonna be like I'll kill
you if you don't well I think that but the Nuremberg Code you know like that
kind of reasonableness is kind of a facade though like I don't want to argue
the time for it right yeah that's not somebody being like I'm on board yeah
that's just like I don't want to I don't want to deal yeah um but like the
Nuremberg Code kind of argument is is very present in Infowars world yeah like
Francis Boyle brings that up a lot yeah it's annoying it is it's just them
saying hey this is how science and math works if we have this level of
protection then you can do this number of things yeah it's not hard the
argument that I would make back to this I think would be like all right let's
imagine a scenario where this isn't all fake or whatever this is an actual
pandemic how does what's going on now look different than what would be the
best thing to do what what is the like do you do you do you accept this
vaccination Quotia quota or quotient is appropriate in the case of a real
outbreak yeah if so then yeah what that that's that's what I would I would like
to do could you plan a better way yeah right so we open the interview and of
course we're gonna talk about you know kovat denialism and the like well we
brought up Nuremberg and that has a new Nazis so I assume you got it so Joseph
p4l has some things he would like to say is he happy sorry Pharrell joke if these
vaccines were so safe why why are they resorting to such draconian measures to
push people into receiving them they're not exactly and the answer to that even
if they were is because of assholes like you who are telling everybody not to get
them I feel like they're being like people are being pretty aware that like
it's important but like you know I I don't know I don't think I've ever seen
anything that would indicate to me like coercion of vaccination I think that
most of the people who I am in social circles with have been chomping at the
bit yeah yeah and and have hunted down no we almost drove five hours to get you
a vaccine yeah and and now you know the CDC had that that recommendation that
people can stop wearing masks in public that that if they've been vaccinated and
that is just a measure of trust yeah you know like if you like that's not like
everyone must wear a special shirt that they only get from vaccination centers
and then they cannot wear masks right or whatever like there's no coercion no
what draconian policies are you talking about recommendation exactly like what
is going on here yeah I honestly think that it could be more dry would almost
agree yes you're totally right you're totally right and it's just that it's
just it's always a trap it doesn't matter it doesn't matter especially with
this guy anything that you say confidently you are either right about
but here's what you're missing or you are completely wrong about and I have a
completely different idea so here is let's go ahead and play this is a long
clip because I want everybody to get an idea of what this dude talks like and
how he talks so just see if he answers this question Richard is going to ask
him how much of this is preparing us for a world without jobs here is how that
goes well I think a lot of it is at least in their thinking but I'll tell
you something Richard there's something very peculiar going on in in railroads
and and people that know me know where I'm gonna go with this because my dad
was a railroad engineer not you know not the locomotive kind but the engineer
that inspects the tracks and so on and so forth when I was very very young and
he got me fascinated with with steam locomotives and if you have been
following what's been happening with railroads in this country the Union
Pacific Railroad has been restoring the steam locomotives at a breathtaking rate
they just finished restoration of an articulated big-boy steam locomotive
4884 to you know haul freight and so on and so forth now the interesting thing
is Union Pacific isn't investing all this money to basically create a
locomotive works in Cheyenne Wyoming to to enhance railroad heritage days
there's something else going on and my suspicion is that with the increasing
reliance of global technology on digital systems they've suddenly realized that
they've exposed themselves and there's their precious systems to a little thing
called electromagnetic pulse or for that matter hacking cyber hacking and so on
and so forth we just saw the colonial pipeline takedown so I think mr.
global Oni is also kind of hoist by his own petard they're trying to put in
digital systems and particularly digital currencies so what you're seeing has
pushback at least here in the States I can't speak for up there for the
Canadian provinces but in in several states in this country we've seen some
pushback of a very unusual nature against this idea of digital currency
South Carolina passed a measure recently to acknowledge as legal tender for all
transactions interestingly enough that the coin had to be denominated in
dollars Texas opened its own state bullion depository and so on and so
forth so you're seeing some very unusual pushback that tells me that somebody at
least in some of these states knows what the game is and they're acting
accordingly to to secure some sort of basis for a currency should they try to
roll out a digital system with their helicopter money and the missing jobs
and a universal basic income and so on and so forth look did he answer the
question yeah no I forgot what the question was right I was I was going
along with what he was saying about railroads railroads rare earths I think
he was speculating that steam engine locomotives could get hacked and I don't
know what was going on with that and that was interesting I was I was
thrilled to find out about steam hacking and then it pivoted to digital currency
yeah I don't know what's going on anymore so the question was how much of
this whole lockdown is preparing us for a world without jobs his answer was all
the railroads well I think yeah a lot of it is at least the way that they say it
and then he goes on for two full minutes about something completely unrelated
actually but I'm not something who is the multiple things that are completely
unrelated I resent this because I'm not interested in the cryptocurrency
nonsense but I am interested in the locomotives would you like to know
about the locomotive yes I would all righty I definitely would like to hear
him talk more about hacking trains well here it well his his thoughts and and he
said that anybody who knows me knows this oh yeah so it's like maybe it's a
big thing this is a big thing of his this is a huge thing of his you know
what you know it's very hackable cool ah you're you've got it backwards he's
saying that Union Pacific is restoring old steam engine trains because they
know that eventually all the electromagnetic trains are going to be
disabled by an EMP oh yeah that actually makes more sense like as a coherent
thought than I thought it yeah yeah yeah well I mean kind of because I thought
he was speculating that like steam would be hacked right it makes sense that it's
like all these trains are digital then we have to have these as a backup
raise these steam yeah it's steampunk yeah yeah and then of course futuristic
giant mechanical robot spiders if we could get some flying steam engines
Allah back to the future 3 I'm gonna be stoked yeah so would you like to know
what's going on with Union Pacific rebuilding those trains this is from
Justin Franz of Atlas Obscura I'll just go ahead and read you the headline real
quick one of the world's largest steam locomotives is about to make a
triumphant return hold on to your engineer caps railroad history lovers
choo-choo does that sound like a nefarious so it's very very simple six
days after six decades after the last big boy was taken off the rails the
Union Pacific is rebuilding one of the famous locomotives in honor of the
upcoming sesquicentennial celebration of the first transcontinental railroad
yeah it's kind of like a tourist attraction yeah or something yeah
absolutely it's a celebration as far as the digital currencies go what he's
talking about is states having repositories for gold bullion and you
know like certain states saying you have to take gold if somebody gives it to
right right and I don't know why he's a bothering about that because you'll
notice what states specifically he's referencing they are states that one are
filled with people who say would rather have the state have a gold bullion
depository then sending a large amount of money to Ted Anderson hmm that would
be that would be smart sure and then of course with South Carolina and the like
they're filled with people who are like the money the dollar is gonna explode so
they might they pass all these laws all the time it's just random-ass nonsense I
would really love for you to sit me down uh-huh with a map of the United States
and tell me state by state what it's full of people who are like ad dollars
gonna explode and this one I know it's just potatoes my version of the
Animaniacs song Africa Panama yeah so yeah that is that is kind of the way
that he talks so past that I've tried to kind of edit it down for clarity yeah as
you will seems he seems like a guy who is boring as hell uh-huh but also is
teasing like slightly interesting thoughts yes yes in a way that's
frustrating and now you realize why I was like I gotta talk about this guy but
he's so goddamn bored yeah yeah yeah so uh this is this next clip is basically
another in a very similar stretch so you mentioned the colonial pipeline and the
the cyber criminals that effectively shut that down and caused you know long
lineups at the the gas stations and so forth and and really kind of a I think a
warning shot of things to come and then then colonial admits that they ended up
paying five million dollars in ransom in cryptocurrency I think we're probably
not getting a full story here what what are you hearing about what really
happened I mean was this really just an isolated you know an incident of some
gang of cyber criminals that decided you know to roll the dice and see what would
happen and lo and behold yeah they paid up I mean what what are you hearing
about okay so that is the question mm-hmm okay yeah very simple long-winded
question it's a long-winded question everybody on these shows also every show
that I think I've seen him do an interview on is at least three hours
long mm-hmm this one was thankfully only an hour and 51 minutes I'll say that
like in terms of like a lot of the stuff that I listen to in conspiracy that that
that sort of sphere I will at least this guy's being precise yes and like it it's
it's not good or all that like I don't know if we're gonna get to any truth
sure sure asking a specific question right right no no I'm going to be said
for that I kind of I I won I like that Richard Surratt is doing a Casey Kasem
impression yes uh so much so much I'm waiting for him to do top 40 hits we're
gonna talk about the going to the left and the right I suspect they paid seven
million dollars and ransom what about you and also here is 303 so why did it
come with 303 really don't know where'd that one come from I don't know man
okay it's trying to think of bad music and it was the first thing you could
have done worse now um so simple question what do you think is what are
you hearing what's going on do you have do you feelers out yeah well I've heard
basically the same thing but I'm like you I don't think that we've heard all
of the story and one of the interesting things about the colonial thing that I
don't know what how it was reported up there but there's some of the media down
here was reciting government officials and so on saying things to the effect
that this is there there will be more of this so yeah yeah so he's citing
government officials saying that there will be more of this and all he's really
responding to him with is yeah I think you're about right there and then he
goes off on a different thing that you didn't know about like that kind of
every time you introduce something or ask a direct question it is immediate
like well maybe and then going off into whatever it is he really wants to talk
about right everybody just listens to him like that's fine
I have watched him talk for almost 10 minutes uninterrupted and people are
wrapped by this and it's blowing me away by people you mean you no no I mean the
the interviewers right right they're all sitting there there's YouTube like this
is not a small thing neither uh-huh these are there's a plenty of people
like constantly doing all those things people aren't cutting him off no like
three minutes in your answer totally you should absolutely be doing that so I the
answer is yes it'll probably happen again obviously well that's that I mean
like what he's doing is playing that game of like the the the government is
is being like hey this is a new threat yeah this is something that we can't
expect might happen again we need to prepare strategies to deal with this
right you are a business like the colonial pipeline that has like maybe
infrastructure related necessity yeah in your operations be aware yeah and
instead he's prepared he's presenting that as like the government being like
and do this yeah this is happening all the time now again I would I would ask
if like this is real and there are these hackers doing this how is that statement
from the government any different than the best-case scenario of a statement
that they would make as a warning what is the differentiation between it uh
well they never do that well fine yeah now I assume you would think hey that
answer is over you've answered the question yes probably and it's probably
a false flag he is not done he's not nope he keeps going about a week after
that story broke there was a story about the interstate bridge on Interstate 40
from the bridge Tennessee the bridge was shut down because they had discovered a
crack in one of the pylons on that bridge and I think pictures of this
crack and the top of the crack is is a perfect straight line now the effect of
that bridge shut down was that barge traffic on the Mississippi River south
and north of Memphis Tennessee came to an absolute standstill so somebody
appears to me to be working awfully hard to take down the the infrastructure of
the United States and in these kinds of creative ways so I think colonial
pipeline is kind of the tip of an iceberg that that they're getting ready
to do something major in order to push their agenda all right yeah get it yeah
see what happened was the colonial pipeline was hacked now what also
happened was surprisingly enough very near to where he lives there was a crack
in the bridge right but the reason that the government gave for repairing it was
pesky barges need to get in and out because it's a massive actually water
ways this is genius okay do you realize tell me on that for the last like 10
years the globalists have been planting stories in the media about how bad our
bridges are subtly warning right that they're gonna hack the bridge you have
to you have to tell everyone you have to give them that cosmic choice there have
been these op-eds about how more resources should be funneled towards
bridge repair that's what they do so sneaky now the real story behind the
hack is actually really really fascinating and if they had bothered to
look into it well that's not the bridge right no not the okay no the bridge is
not interesting just that's just a regular old bridge that's just
maintenance yeah they were just maintaining the bridge I had a hunch
yeah it was fine but you can turn anything you want into a conspiracy
theory if you just go well they hacked the pipeline and there's a crack in my
bridge right the government's working against if you just if you if you play
the insinuation game you can you can make a lot of mileage yeah exactly but
the real story is not obviously they didn't mention any names of the people
who were hacking they they were like oh is it a one-off event or anything like
that this is a hacking group called dark side who've done this they are
ransomware masters they have been taken shit ton of money and then they
disbanded immediately following the colonial pipeline smart theoretically
from what people are saying is after they got paid six million the small
collective of the hackers disbanded and then just took all the money mm-hmm the
way that they normally work is almost 70% of the money goes to all of these
like subsidiary hackers who do all of the the grunt work and and then they
take their cut at the end not so this time so what did they they left the
grunts out to dry yep Wow yeah brutal right no honor not too surprising so
this story actually begins before the colonial pipeline hack whatsoever so
from technology review by Renee Dudley and Daniel golden on January 11th
antivirus company bitdefender said it was happy to announce a startling
breakthrough it had found a flaw in the ransomware that a gang known as dark
side was using to freeze computer networks of dozens of businesses in the
u.s. in Europe companies facing demands from dark side could download a free
tool from bitdefender and avoid paying millions of dollars in ransom to the
hackers that's a great thing right it's a good idea now Dan what should you do
when you find a flaw in a hackers programming wait who am I am I a hacker
you were bitdefender your job is to protect people from hackers well you
find a flaw you should probably try and patch it fix it up they did that they
patched it and they fixed it up okay now here's the problem they released it as a
public relations statement and within 12 hours dark side was like oh they found a
hole in our software let's find another hole find it they fixed it it was over
with mm-hmm so bitdefender has basically and this is happening over and over and
over again yeah it's constant back and forth well and here's the thing though
people who are good at this stuff don't tell anyone and all of these antivirus
scammers basically announced the moment publicly like hey we fixed this the
hackers can no longer get to us and then five hours later it's all right right
so all of these antivirus companies are trying to get the positive you know like
look at how great we are press of like we fix this hole actually antithetical
to their goal exactly yeah you got it they continue to go on and here's it
there's a bunch of really kind of interesting little details here Aaron
Tantliff a Chicago cybersecurity attorney he is he consulted with 10
companies attacked by dark side he said that dark sides representatives were
shrewd bargainers if a victim said it couldn't afford the ransom because of
the pandemic dark side was ready with data showing that the company's revenue
was up like they had all of this they were ready this was a fortune 500
hackers yeah yeah absolutely look I'd like to refer you to the accounting wing
of our hacker collective yeah and not only that but the they have this like
halfway we're we're only attacking corporations that we know can Robin Hood
that kind of thing yeah and yeah they even came up with like actually we do
know how much kovat has impacted your bottom line and we have adjusted our
ransom accordingly so even if you don't want to pay the ransom it's like god
damn it they make a lot of sense listen we're not heartless for hackers we're
not heartless yeah so what wound up happening is a dark side just blew ever
blew them away because bitdefender is very very stupid and they're gonna
continue doing it mm-hmm it's just how it goes and all of this they're talking
about like oh it's conspiracy are these rogue actors or anything if you look
into it you'll see that this is a hugely sophisticated operation right with
people who are incredibly successful at all of this and it's kind of an
inevitability of like digital progression you know like as as there is
more stuff that is is is online and digital mm-hmm there will be the the
highwaymen of yeah the the online space like it's it's just like it's exactly
what you would expect to grow and and get more sophisticated as people who
would robbed stagecoaches turned into people who robbed trains yeah and then
it would turn into a mafia exactly things get more sophisticated and more
organized mm-hmm it makes sense that the inevitability would be something like
this totally and instead they just say they're so boring it's so much more
boring they're bad conspiracy theories then what is a real conspiracy yeah I
feel like this is the exact same thing that we talked about with like that guy
in the IRA yeah you know like it's the reality of it is fascinating and it is a
really interesting piece of how like history and like human interaction works
yeah and instead you're turning this into a conspiracy that's actually more
boring than the actual total world you're trying to fit it into your large
conspiracy theory where it doesn't belong no just be interested just be
curious yeah that kind of thing it's just not hard you don't have to
distrust everything yeah exactly so real soon we're gonna get into space but this
one I just have to this is just silly st. Michael asks Joseph what about the
Apollo oh he wants to to go a secret space program I guess here or something
related to maybe the lunar landing hoax Joseph what about the the Apollo 12
ascent stage experiment crashing into the lunar surface and it rang like a
bell for a long period of time well I don't know that it rang see I'm
accidentally cut it off just a little bit early but he is saying he's he got a
question from the audience Michael st. Michael he's asking Joseph hey how is
this possible and as Richard is answer is asking the question he's like they
say it rang like a bell and he's like oh well that sounds silly it didn't yeah so
would you like to answer the question that I have just negated exactly and
here is the answer dong anyway with Joseph any thoughts on the Apollo 12
ascent stage experiment crashing into the lunar surface yeah that individual
is is actually citing the the language of the scientists that that reported on
that experiment that was their word hello I'm a scientist it rang like a
bell excuse me mr. Surratt it did ring like a goddamn Bell okay immediate
immediate response is just no it read like it rang like a bell that's literal
verbatim yes from this scientific literature despite being physically
impossible in the world we inhabit uh-huh you mean in space yes yeah yeah
in the universe we inhabit apologize so then we have introduced space and this
do what what is the conspiracy here that the moon is hollow you're about to find
out is that the is that the the thrust of it ringing like a bell because there
would be sound vibrations right if it was hollow but then it would also have
to have an opening yes so it's sort of hollow earth but the moon yeah so the
moon is a base okay I'm putting the pieces together okay here I'm gonna spit
ball okay the Nazis are inside the moon okay um you're not far off in fact
you're terrifyingly close go ahead this is basically that movie iron sky he's
almost all like a movie guy yeah love it yeah I think in the early 70s I don't
remember exactly when it was but Sputnik magazine the old Soviet periodical
published a set of articles by some Soviet scientists that actually had the
thesis that the moon was a big huge artificial spaceship because it was you
know it was impossible to explain the physics of how it got there doing what
it's doing on any of the natural models for for its existence you know the
capture model the fission from Earth model and so on and so forth so I you
know I give some credence to those stories and even to that theory because
you know it's it's like Isaac Newton said about the moon the moon's the only
thing that gives me a headache because you have a good way of explaining how it
got there doing what it's doing I mean the guy quoted Sputnik yeah yeah
Sputnik magazine from the 70s or 80s some Russian scientists speculated that
maybe the moon is a spaceship 50 years later Joseph P for L thinks that that's
probably true my friend have you heard that cheese yeah yeah it is it is that
that's the type of thing that we're dealing with you are absolutely right
there are Nazis up there I mean I feel like you know in the 70s it's the late
70s this might have been after a particular Death Star
look sort of like the moon that's not a moon Dan it's a space station they're
really biding their time with like doing anything with it yeah 70s and 80s you
don't know what it's for just yet huh um so yeah at least like the second Death
Star was like under construction and that made yes made sense for like why it
wasn't doing like a space station would have blown up a planet by now or done
something I do I do like the idea that instead of whatever in Star Wars they
like the it's fully operational instead they're like listen we're gonna have to
hang out here for about 50 60 years and then we'll get to him I swear to God
well right there don't fucking move don't leave the moon not just that but
you would need to have like MREs to like so much food but not just that you have
to then say that the moon has always been a space station right so for someone
had to have created exactly I've had to built it pre-earth because everybody is
yeah and there needs to be like some kind of like a biome inside that has
like something there's no light source so you can't like plants having
photosynthesis I don't know how you would keep animals alive that seems like
it would be prohibitive yeah on the moon or in the moon I guess you could
have like an elaborate fungus kind of economy that's true it could be like a
like a lost world scenario where you go in the moon and it turns out that
there's actually brush and beautiful verdant tropical island there I think
you would still need something to give for like energy to that that that flora
and fauna Atlantis and fine oh oh and also Atlantis is also magic Atlantis is
in play thank God so we're at the midpoint they just started talking
about space and now I'm just I love this clip I just love this hey thanks for
inviting me into your home long-haul truck RV camper taxi your parents
well-appointed rec room with the simulated wood paneling electric
fireplace and the painting of dogs playing poker your loft that greasy
spoon just off the interstate and your cabin in the woods hello to everyone
listening in on our flagship station am 749 6.7 FM
zoomer radio here in Toronto and hiya to those of you tuning I just love it it
just reminds me so much of Casey case of yes it's just so much Casey case if I
just love it let me describe a Norman Rockwell painting give a shout out to
the only station I'm on I there's something about that that just reminds
me of literally a long road trip in the middle of the night listening to some
terrible radio station and you hear that and you're like yeah that's what radios
about yeah you're you were saying this guy's one of the like junior varsity
guys on coast to coast and it it shows it smells like totally so the reason
that I wanted to do space is aliens are obviously in the news these days and we
don't get enough of it these these days on the podcast no we just don't um and
then this guy's obsessed with Nazis so why not put them both together now how
might you think that cuz I this is one question that I was interested in
especially is everybody normal now everybody who is not a space weirdo
before is now like holy shit government's saying there's aliens or
something going on here how is the UFO community taking this and false light
and the fact that the government stole UFO from them and changed it out of
nowhere just because they didn't want them to look stupid it's fake yeah right
so let's see okay we have this technology now and and maybe you know
that might explain these the tic-tac UFO videos even though the the Pentagon is
saying they're not ours they're not ours well maybe that kind of blows that out
of the water well the the tic-tac videos you know and all of this stuff I you
know you can go look up patents online for triangular shaped vehicles that use
some form of field propulsion what bothers me about all of this is not so
much that the technology apparently does exist what bothers me is the constant
rush to attribute it to ET and well I mean that's a thought yeah the guy who
just told us that the moon was a fucking spaceship rang like a bell that the
Pyramid of Giza is actually a Death Star right that the Nazis are just fucking
everywhere cloning people all this stuff sure he's telling you people are rushing
to judgment on this ET stuff yeah you don't know you can't tell that sure yeah
yeah he's being real dismissive of this and I will admit if this is one of those
situations too where I've looked into it and these the original UFO folks are now
debunking the government's videos right because it doesn't work for the stories
that they write the folklore exactly but in this situation they're doing a good
job the the government's videos can very easily be explained and it's kind of
disappointing whenever you look into the simplicity of their explanations and
you're like oh shit what a surprise human error and machine error that's
never happened in the military before yeah yeah like a lot of like headlines
and like excitement can get ahead of yourself a little bit and and that's
that's something that I actually think is really fascinating is that like a lot
of these communities are capable of decent critical thinking it's just
misdirected if you're attacking their bullshit yeah they will apply very
rigorous and solid critical thinking skills to your bullshit they can yeah
it's just not usually done exactly yes it is very much never done so that's why
when I hear that clip it's like okay people are really eager to attribute
this to aliens yes they are yes I agree with you I don't disagree with that
statement coming from you exactly yeah exactly and he is he is getting he's
getting a little bit salty these days oh no about his UFO information the the
idea that this was a vehicle reconstructed on the basis of what they
had they had recovered from crashed and recovered UF vehicle UFO vehicles that
to me could be a cover story for what they're really up to in other words if
this might be wholly a human product I don't know but I'm increasingly
skeptical Richard about the ET narrative particularly from governments that have
been willing to lie to our faces about you know masks and vaccines and so on
and so forth so yeah yeah he thinks everybody's job bad what if it's an
actual tic-tac what if it's just with buzz marketing yeah I think it's a do
you think it's like that that time aqua teen hunger force put pictures up places
and then they got bomb threats from whatever what the tic-tac's been biting
their time sure there's a secret program yeah to give tic-tac the power to create
extraterrestrial vehicles I believe it I don't think that's terribly wrong but
yeah everything that you think is wrong everything that they think is wrong and
if you know something you're wrong about it and here's why oh and now he's
starting to get a little bit possessive as well are you thinking that the the
technology exists and that that these are made in the good old USA or are did
this technology find its way into the hands of our adversaries Russia China
well I think a lot of it I go back to what I've been writing about in my
Nazi series of books I wrote a book a few years ago that ufology loves to
ignore it's called Roswell and the Reich and it's about the Roswell incident I
pray that I never do anything that the UFO community loves to ignore I pray I
pray that that is not a fate that I have my career where I'm pissed off community
ignores my book it's very strange that the UFO community is not also willing to
toss the Nazis in with the Roswell circumstances some of them do though
that's true I feel like this guy is being a little bit I don't know salty
like you said yeah I mean like there are that is a that is a conspiracy that I've
heard before sure it's not something that's like verboten in conspiracy and
space communities I have read a little bit of his book though and they made a
movie called I read a little bit of that book and not iron sky the
novelization of the movie iron sky no it's it's just nobody reads my books
that's that's kind of words I relate yeah no I have professional misgivings
about more people could listen or the ufology community is no oh no no no you
would prefer just generally like I think anybody who creates things like we could
have a wider audience or I feel like that's what he's saying yeah yeah but
he's more saying they don't respect me so on and so forth exactly I I'm I just
love it this is this is kind of fun for me just because everything is
everything's obviously a false flag Nazis obviously had et Giza pyramid is a
death star all all of this stuff is true simultaneously but somehow these guys
don't take it to a mean place like even for all their COVID denialism which is
inherently mean and cruel it's not like they're they're not the type of person
that I'm used to hearing talk about this where they almost relish like the the
inflicting of cruelty or the expression of cruelty right like for someone like
Alex it's less about the point and it's more about getting to yell at somebody
about how they're wearing a mask yeah and I think that is kind of a feature of
a lot of the stuff that we see yeah yeah totally and for him you don't think it's
it's not malicious he strikes me more as almost a hoarder of Nazi bullshit like
instead of somebody collecting beanie babies he's collected lore and he's just
hoarded it and so I don't know how much of it is anything about how he feels or
thinks or even has like prescriptions or what we should do I don't think he
takes any of his like here's what we should do seriously right all he's
really interested in is hoarding all of this information mm-hmm none of it is
true but he's so hoarded it over the you know it's just like he did with when he
was a theologian he hoarded all of this biblical knowledge all of this history
and and tightened he wants to be the dungeon master of Nazi space exactly he
wants everybody to kiss the ring because he's hoarded the most knowledge yeah
that's the way that he operates and so yeah in this situation it's just just
ridiculous all right let's see oh you betcha you betcha asks Joseph how do you
compare kovat vaccine passports compared to the long-standing requirement to have
your kids get a vaccine to go to school or vaccines for yellow fever to travel
which is an interesting point so you know in other words why are we getting
all upset about and worked up about vaccine passports right mm-hmm that's a
good question hmm that's a really good question I got excited when I heard that
question because that would be a moment if that shows up on info Wars where Alex
is like I'm sorry we gotta let you go and hangs up real quick cuz it's a very
solid question yeah I I honestly was listening to it and I got lost because
it bored me all right yeah so I was thinking this is great because it's a
reasonable question so the only way out of it is you got to take a big swing
yeah you know I got really excited you got hit hard I got hit hard I simply
don't buy the universality of vaccines I grew up as many people in the United
States did in a state where this was not a requirement in fact the only vaccine
I've ever had in my life is the polio vaccine the Sabin vaccine when I was
very young I've not had any vaccine ever since that so it's not a an entirely
universal experience huh nope no big swing at all he just says I grew up and
I didn't have to get vaccines except for the polio except for the polio one now
why are we not talking about how the polio vaccine is also evil let's not
worry about it he's already had it he got it was he was a kid we're not gonna
deal with that sure that does beg the question are some vaccines good right
but we're not gonna deal with that sure isn't that a real I was so disappointed
I was so disappointed because his answer is just basically like well maybe if I
had grown up in that culture I would understand what you're saying but since
I didn't I don't care mm-hmm that's I wanted I wanted Nazis to be behind it
yeah yeah yeah it is a little bit of a swing and a miss yeah it's a real bummer
it's a real bummer yeah now they that is the interview with the conspiracy
theorist equivalent of stepping on a banana yeah somebody should have thrown
a pie in his face immediately following that yeah put a little comedy in there
come on guys so now we get to some of the things that Pharrell is writing so
he also has a blog and he posts stuff all the way all there and now if you
looked at his blog oh yeah I've read a lot of it does he have any posts about
how no one ever really dies um I don't think he has posts about how no one ever
really dies but any RD the group that Pharrell was oh my god sorry oh my god
sorry you're killing me I'm trying to do this I'm not great at running a show and
dealing with references this is what I have to put up with and you've done it
several hundred times true so yeah they talk about one of the things that Joseph
has written you posted a blog I'm not sure how long ago it wasn't too long ago
discussing some rather interesting formations that you've spotted on on
Mars first there there was some discussion about some ice formations on
the planet and that led you to look a little further and and what did you spy
where you buried the lead yeah you didn't tell me this guy maybe has a
telescope oh he does because that's enough to get him on unfortunately he
does not have a telescope he is talking about pictures posted from 2001 by the
Mars Odyssey spacecraft and Richard sets this up as though this is a very
important article and Joseph's response we're not gonna listen to because it's
eight minutes long and all he's really saying is nothing he's saying stuff like
hey it looks like it could be let me let me read you the caption so the pictures
that Richard is talking about hmm saying this article is very good let me read
you the captions on these pictures quote when I look at this with my layman's
eyes I'm not seeing much about Antarctic ice flows and a whole lot of weird stuff
that borders on things that look like nearly perfect circular whatchamacallits
huh good you think that's good stuff yeah okay I mean look the scientist said
that the moon rang like a bell true and so this seems like scientific language
that's true the doodads well it goes on quote and then there are lots of odd
little bumpy things often neatly arranged in rectangles triangles and so
on and then finally we have lots and lots and lots of rectilinear and
structural looking things as somebody who spends a fair amount of time reading
things in journals I'm used to things being described as bumpy little bumpy
little things whatchamacallits yeah okay so we're gonna have to cut your chest
open and we're gonna perform some surgery on your who's it and then we'll
take the what's a and put it in your whole wall and you'll be good you fell
off this high place and the problem is that really hard thing inside your arm
it's got a you got a crick in your heart thing see all I all I hear is an
unfamiliarity with scholarly writing on your part unfamiliarity with research
wow I mean that's that does that doesn't not sound very it doesn't sound like
somebody should bring it up in an interview and be like now you just wrote
this interesting thing I mean you have an uphill battle whenever you're
starting an interview and being like you wrote a blog yeah that alone is a tough
sell whatchamacallits whatchamacallits great now I'm assuming you're asking how
is it that they can pay for these whatchamacallits bumpy things and
structural looking things who they mr. mr. global annoyed as I think he likes
to instead of saying globalist he likes to Dennis Miller it up with mr. global
annoyed or whatever avoid the global annoyed yeah exactly there we go that
one I got so yeah so now we're gonna talk about how everybody pays for it we
were talking about Mars and a little bit about the secret space program you
mentioned Catherine Austin fits earlier and the missing trillion something like
21 trillion dollars missing from the US government so is it your belief that
that much of this money is being funneled into the secret space the
secret space program for what the construction of deep space platforms and
so forth I know Catherine Austin fits Oh do you a lot personally okay yeah she's
she comes up in various places yeah so she's a former HUD official in the
W administration and then when she left she created a brokerage firm and she
started business doing business with you guessed it the HUD now what was going on
is while she was doing the accounting for these contracts with the HUD and the
Pentagon and that kind of stuff stuff didn't look right it didn't look right
at all things are going wrong and so Joseph is going to tell us what it is
she found so if we go back to to let's say the day about some 2008 they pumped
an enormous amount of money into the system or did they I like that yeah well
they bailouts yeah were for like upgrades to the moon basically now his
theory I guess is that if the bailouts happened then inflation should have
skyrocketed which okay that doesn't exactly work but that's fine what he is
completely ignoring is that the 21 trillion that we're we're talking about
is not missing in the sense that it's like it was taken away and now it could
be anywhere right right it's missing in the sense that the Pentagon by design
does not keep track of where it spends money mm-hmm it doesn't keep track of it
it doesn't they you can't audit it you can't nothing happens they've tried to
have so many accountants go in and just give it a shot right and you can't do it
by design because if you know exactly how much money you're spending you
might get less well there's that and then also I would assume that there's
probably some kind of like national security reasons why you wouldn't want
that information being somewhere where people could possibly get a hold of it
sure sure that I would assume that maybe there's some of that right but I even
then you would have a budget and they do not right they just have money and then
they spend it so even whenever they're talking about passing a military budget
it does it's just it's just there mm-hmm and they spend money and if they spend
more than that budget the government's still gonna pay for it nobody cares
right yeah right that sort of like missing money is is the the same kind of
thing that people talk about with like there's this unfunded social security
and totally totally it's the same misunderstanding of like it's not
unfunded it's just money isn't there yet because it's future exactly it's people
paying into it will pay for it in the future you know like that it's the same
sort of semantical trick that people use to try and argue against any kind of
government spending exactly now although in this case maybe there's more to it
oh no everybody who has looked into it everybody who has looked into the
Pentagon budget has like immediately like they they open their computer they
look at one line and they raise a red flag up into the fucking sky and shoot
flares and they're like this is not good yeah this is a problem it's a it's a
it's a it's a misunderstanding based on like the way it's being described yes
but it's an extra this this is a problem for a different reason yes yeah you got
it now Joseph has a different theory than that so I've actually speculated
that somehow this money may actually be going off world yeah how I don't know
sure sure I'm in yeah I just love that yeah I just love that he does not go
this is the one time that he really doesn't go on further cool here's his
response well um I think it's probably off world and I don't know how it got
there now I should say I got no idea right I'm not even gonna give you a gas
no but I will say that I'm just speculating yeah I don't know it's
probably off world I might be in that empty moon up there I would love to be
the guy doing this interview because my response would be like oh you're
speculating oh oh are you interesting I'm speculating that that money stayed
on world now what we have reached an impasse we must agree to disagree yeah I
mean it's just it's just that so often so what he always is money in space
moon rocks no no no it doesn't mean anything oh yeah yeah no intergalactic
treaties recognize money all right yeah yeah otherwise how could we do business
with the ET if they don't recognize our currency I would suggest we don't please
go on yeah and so that's exactly what Joseph does a with everything speculate
yes the only difference between that clip and what he normally does is the
tricks he uses of being like I'm gonna flood you with names I'm gonna flood you
with information because he's an incredibly knowledgeable guy he's
hoarded all of this information right so he hits you with so much references all
the time that people skip over the fact that most of his responses to questions
are essentially I'm speculating here yeah I don't know anything I might be
making this up yeah totally and it's it it's just mind-boggling how popular this
guy really is it's nuts hmm cuz he's boring and he doesn't have anything to
say it doesn't seem like it and then this is the I believe this is the last
clip because I just couldn't do this after this do one of your blogs recent
blogs on Giza death star calm and this it's entitled precognition and as you
point out it's a it's a wild article that I guess someone shared with you and
it has to do with these scientists who have discovered that the heart and brain
can respond to future events obviously before they happen tell me more well I
find that very interesting because it it seems to present a physiological case
that that the structure of the brain and the heart and they're very very similar
somehow represent or mirror the the fabric of the universe and the reason I
find that very interesting is you can go online and look at pictures of galactic
clusters and what they think are the plasma strands that connect them and
then compare those pictures to actual neural mapping of neurons in the brain
and they're remarkably similar yes you ever see a fractal man yeah that's
that's what I was I was listening to that just going supposedly I'm supposed
to take you as an authority on Eve and this and you're telling me your response
to precognition possibility is to say look at the pictures of the stars and
people very similar yeah maybe we're little little bugs inside a brain like
the universe universe is a big brain yeah and that's just another person or
something fine man but come on come on you're supposed to be the expert in this
shit and you cannot come at me with you know they look alike sure it's so
disappointing to me and I just can't handle it I couldn't handle it past that
point I was like I've heard too many times you just go oh it looks like a
whatchamacallit and then be done with your with your evidence when I tilt my
head up I see the whatchamacallit and it looks like the doodad and so
precognition is probably true or not or whatever yeah it doesn't mean anything
no and he just keeps getting listened to as though he's an authority wearing his
dumb Indiana Jones hat smoking his Cruella de Vil cigarette and he's not
even smoking and so on and so forth I feel like you shouldn't be mad at the
hat and the affectations those are kind of charming do you think that's why he
keeps getting invited probably yeah I might talk to him I might be tricked
yeah no he's uh he's not interesting enough to trick you I don't think you'll
need to worry too much about that oh so yeah talking that he has not been on
project Camelot hey don't think he had well he was interviewed by not carry Oh
by Bill Ryan yes okay I remember seeing that okay and so I was going to talk
about bill is less fun he's much less fun yeah yeah yeah that was not good
it was done in a weird hotel room that looked like a motel six yeah those
they're early aesthetic yeah yeah so that is Joseph P Pharrell the possible
doctor definite shitbag and mediocre writer
Nazis did not factor into this as much as I expected no the problem with the
Nazis is that that is his like I guess mid period work uh-huh you know like now
he's more into banks are killing everybody okay um and I it was about 10
15 years ago that he was all into Nazis all talking Nazis all the time before
the era of podcasts exactly yeah a lot of available audio sorry there were
there were there wasn't more Nazi talk but it was teased but you know what
we're never we never need more Nazi I mean he grew up next to Nazis so we
could probably ask them sure yeah I bet they've got a lot of Nazi content yeah
well this is interesting Jordan yeah I thought it was fairly interesting I
thought he was an interesting guy and I thought we should talk about him thanks
for bringing this to my attention I will I you will so we'll be back I guess I
think we will but until then I'm pretty sure we have a website yes it's
knowledge fight calm I thought we might have been on Twitter at one point maybe
at BB boo boo boo yeah and I think if you wanted to you got it and as always
I am neither neo Leo DZX Clark or Dan Friesen at all and now here comes the
sex robots Andy in Kansas you're on the air thanks for holding
well Alex I'm a first-time caller I'm a huge fan I love your work I love you