N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys saying we are the bad guys.
Dan and Jordan.
Knowledgefight.
That'll hurt.
I need money.
Andy and Kansas.
Stop it.
It's time to pray.
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a victim caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your room.
Knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey, everybody.
Welcome back to Knowledgefight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes.
I'd like to sit around, worship at the altar of Selene, and talk a little bit about Alex
Jones.
Oh, indeed we are, Dan.
Yeah, Jordan.
Dan.
Jordan.
I have a quick question for you.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, honestly, is a little bit of getting back to it, you know?
Yeah.
I think we went on a vacation and getting back to Selene, getting back to work, getting
back into a little bit of... I think one of the things that's one of the undervalued
or underthought about elements of vacations are how much it makes you like, ah, my day-to-day
life is better than I think it is.
You know, I was reading Terry Pratchett while we were on vacation, and he had a really great
quote that I was like, you've never really been anywhere until you get back, you know?
And that, until we got back, I was like, that's kind of a silly thing to say, and now I kind
of get it.
Yeah.
I've been on vacations before.
Granted, it's been a long time, but you know, it's something that I think is also easy to
forget.
It's something that you experience over and over again, and every time you go on a vacation
too, your life is probably in a different circumstance than it was the last time.
Sure.
I think it's time for you to come back and listen to this idiot again.
It was good to take a break.
It really was.
Yeah.
And now I really want to get back to work.
I think there's some things that were dangling threads that did not run into any lizards
weirdly.
No, that was difficult.
I had a perception in my head that there were lizards everywhere when I was a kid, and maybe
it's because I was a couple feet shorter and closer to the ground and I could just see
them everywhere.
You could see them a lot better.
I did not catch any lizards, not a single one.
I got blisters on my feet the first day we were there, so I didn't shimmy up any poles.
Same here.
My childhood home has been torn down and turned into an apartment complex.
It was a little bit like Gross Point Blank.
It was a little bit like that.
Yeah.
At least it wasn't a convenience store.
No, but it was still a lovely time.
Sure.
What about you?
What's your bright spot?
You know, I have a hard time saying anything similarly to you.
You know, I feel like the vacation was great, but my bright spot was, when we got back,
my dogs were still staying with my partner's mother.
Yeah, you had like a whole other day, right?
A whole other day, and they got back today, and the first time I saw, they went so ridiculously
crazy.
I was like, how did I ever leave these beautiful things?
That's very cute.
Oh, you know, you're like, I knew my pets loved me, but after they've been gone for
a week and they saw me again, you're like, ah, this is what it's all about, man.
Yeah.
I mean, that's fairly similar to the experience I had with Celine, but with a lot more yelling.
Well, there's...
She was yelling at me quite a bit.
I got a few more face licks, I think.
Yeah.
That might be the case.
I got some snuggles and some aggressive head butts eventually.
Sure.
And I was coming up the stairs with the luggage, so if I could just hear, meh.
Well, yeah.
A cat has to teach you a lesson before they can re-give you the...
Grumpy as hell.
But I wouldn't have it any other way.
No, of course not.
So, Jordan, today we have a difficulty ahead of us, and that is kind of like we missed
a bit of time.
Yeah.
And so, and also some stuff happened right when we got back.
Oh, of course.
That's very relevant to our business, so I didn't really know exactly what the strategy
was going to be in terms of, you know, do we go back and listen to all of last week?
Sure.
Or what do we do?
Yeah.
Pick and choose, that kind of thing.
Right.
And it's a little challenging.
And so, just spoiler alert, the Fauci emails came out.
Oh, boy.
Yep.
And so I was like, well, I mean, Alex is gonna go buck wild on this.
Of course.
But since the time we've been back, I haven't had enough time to read all of it.
It's like 3,000 pages.
Jesus.
I've read quite a bit.
Of course.
It's boring emails.
I was thinking the same.
I read a few of them and I was like, I'm just not doing this.
I'm not reading business emails, you know?
I've thought that to myself a whole bunch of times because most of what I've read so
far is Fauci forwarding something to another person.
Honestly.
Or it's someone sending a nonsensical email to him and him not responding.
No, half the time I'm looking around, I'm like, the next email is gonna be like, we're
gonna need to refill the toilet paper in the lobby.
You know?
It's like that kind of level.
And then he forwards that to maintenance.
Yes, exactly.
And you're like, okay.
That's why it's in the cache.
All right, we get it.
He's evil or whatever.
But come on, man.
So I haven't gotten a full enough view.
And just like, I think it would be almost impossible.
I don't know, unless you had a team reading them in chunks or whatever, to get through
all 3,000 pages and the time that it would take to...
It's like the Snowden files, you know?
You've got multiple outlets working on that.
Right.
So that was a big priority, but at the same time, it was something that we couldn't really
do yet.
So I'm hoping to be able to do some really current stuff for Monday.
So what I did is I just threw an arrow at a dartboard, darted an arrowboard, whatever.
And May 27th, Thursday of last week, came up.
I was like, we'll do Thursday and Friday.
Thursday ended up too silly, and Friday's off the table.
Thursday's just a mess.
The dartboard was wrong.
Yeah.
So here we go, we're going to do May 27th, 2021, Blackjack.
Ah, shit.
I'm way out of practice.
This is going to be interesting.
Alex is very silly.
Let's do it.
That's what I was hoping for.
I want to come back to silly.
Yeah, I also felt like let's not overburden ourselves with something that's going to be
all day.
Yeah.
Nobody wants to come back to the office the first day and really deal with that stack
of paper that built up.
You get to the top few pages.
It has to be taken care of eventually.
Sure, sure.
But not today.
Half day.
Yes, exactly.
Or something.
Yeah.
So, Jordan, before we do that, let's take a little moment to say hello to one wonk and
then introduce a new development on the podcast.
Interesting.
So thank you so much.
Random dude from Germany feeling better about his national discourse.
Thanks to Alex.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Oh, thank you very much.
I suppose most of Germany.
So Jordan.
Yes, sir.
I have decided that, look, these birthday things, they're never going away.
It's going to be a struggle.
So I have a new drop for us.
Okay.
All right.
To introduce birthday time.
Giving someone life is giving someone death.
You could say that life is death.
Hey, it's time to give some happy birthday shout outs to folks here on the podcast.
Dan, you never fail to impress me.
Never.
You never fail to impress me.
So Josie, my birthday was on the first, Andrew got in touch with us, wanted to wish you a
happy birthday.
I'm going to need some time.
Also like to say happy birthday, Sean, Stalin, Stritch, may your adapt as a start is bring
glory to the Emperor and justice to the globalists.
Okay.
I'm back at it.
So Kit, I had a 30th birthday, Basil sent me or Basil, not entirely sure.
I do think that I have been told how to pronounce it and I refused.
I think when people tell me how to pronounce things, it's like, I'm deaf to it.
Oh no, we're Americans.
It's our God given right to ignore British pronunciations.
Anyway, Basil or Basil got in touch with me and wanted me to wish Kit a happy birthday.
Happy birthday, Kit.
Also, the two of them just got engaged.
Congratulations.
Congratulations on your nuptials, upcoming nuptials, thrilled for you.
And then finally, coming up on the fifth, I guess that's this weekend, this Saturday,
Frank M's got a birthday, 27th birthday, from what I understand.
How about that?
It's almost over for you.
Happy birthday, Frank.
This brings us to a close of the happy birthday shout outs.
Giving someone life is giving someone death.
You can say that life is death.
Happy birthday.
I have a feeling that's going to go down in the Rake Effect Hall of Fame.
Two episodes from now, we're both going to be like, ah, this is normal.
In five episodes from now, I'm going to continue losing my shit every time.
We'll see.
All right.
So the 27th, Alex is in a strange mood and here's another context drop to give you a
little bit of a sense of it.
Oh, my God.
Did I get hired?
No, because that was fake.
That's true.
That is fake.
I do kind of feel personally offended by that laugh.
That was Pillsbury Alex.
Someone was tickling him.
So here we go.
We're going to start the show.
And this is where I actually got on the hook.
Okay.
And sometimes it takes me a little while when I start up an episode for it to be like, I'm
listening.
Sure.
I got on the hook immediately.
Okay.
All right.
I have been brainstorming quite a bit and really thinking about how I want to present
my knowledge, my understanding to the public, what the most important thing for me to do
is.
And a lot of what I'm going to be covering in parts of the broadcast that you've heard
before, a lot of it you're not going to have heard.
And I really just think it's important that I cut right to the chase up front here before
I tell you who's coming up today and get to it all.
So for my ears, I hear this as Alex saying, let's cut through the bullshit.
Yeah.
Look, I got to shoot straight with you.
It's time.
Look, I'm 20 years into this.
It's finally time.
Some of this stuff I've said before, some of it I have not, but it will all be my hand
to God's ears.
Of course, all will be revealed in the fullness of time.
Yeah.
And actually, see, you're saying that like he's been on air for 20 years and he's been
fucking around.
Right.
That's not actually true.
It sounded like it.
Right before we went live about five minutes before, I just got hit with an extreme clarity
of what I was to go on air and talk about from all the knowledge information we have.
And just you call it a vision, but really it's like a computer program that's been working
on a problem, working on a problem.
And then suddenly it's completed the problem.
Sometimes it takes longer than the computer thinks it will.
Sometimes it happens quicker.
Wait, the computer thinks?
It's like completion in the bell dings and the answer comes sliding out and it was just
a whole nother level of exactly what they're going to do, how they're going to do it, how
they're operating.
Okay.
So, again, Alex has had a moment of clarity.
You know, here's what I was thinking.
Every single day.
You know what I was thinking?
This is the first time in a long time that we have taken some time off and Alex hasn't.
So part of me was like, I wonder what he was thinking.
Like I got free reign now.
I don't have to worry about shit.
Yeah.
Parents aren't home.
Yeah, exactly.
Now the kids can play all they want.
Hey, Dan and Jordan aren't listening, so I'm going to speak freely.
Yeah, exactly.
I'm going to cut through the bullshit.
Now it's time to cut through the bullshit.
I wouldn't think that was what was on his mind.
No, sure.
I'm sure.
By now, at 27 years, he's realized that recordings exist.
Doesn't matter.
Yeah.
It's just, I can't stand this asshole every single day having a vision.
I've had a new vision.
Oh my God.
It was like finally all the pieces clicked into place.
Like you can't do this every day.
I do like that the computer thinks it's going to be over sooner, but unfortunately the computer
took a little bit longer than it was expecting.
Hey man, I mean you're joking around about that, but I have been in a situation where
let's say I'm downloading a game off the PlayStation network.
Sure.
And it says it's 33% done.
And then it says it's going to be done in 30 minutes, then check back in, 40 minutes.
40 minutes.
I mean, who knows?
What was that computer thinking?
All of these computers tell you what they're thinking and it turns out what they're thinking
is wrong.
It's terrible.
You know, do robots dream of being late for work?
That's what I was thinking.
Yep.
Do robots dream of excuses for tardiness?
So here's the deal.
I think this is what Alex's vision or his new bit of clarity is about.
It has to do with the globalists and their new plan.
Mic down for this because it's absurd.
The headline I wrote right after I sat there in my office for about a minute staring at
the desk is on screen, transcendent transmission.
The scientific dictatorship controlling earth is preparing to launch the great lie or the
greatest of lies.
And that is to obscure the great truth that is already happening.
And that is our human psyche piercing the veil and connecting in an even stronger way
with God and basically mass telekinesis.
And that's what the system's trying to suppress.
Okay.
All right.
Now that's a stinger.
That is a stinger right there.
All right.
So the globalists are planning something in order to distract from the fact that we've
connected with God and now we can move objects with our minds?
Correct.
Here's, here's my problem.
Here's my problem.
All right.
We live in the future.
Yeah.
So I know that despite him saying that the real goal is mass telekinesis, the next day
he's going to be like Fauci released emails like, Oh, would you, there are higher levels
if you've got mass telekinesis on the way.
Well, I want to be clear about something too, because I'm not an idiot.
I know that he means telepathy.
Sure.
Yeah, of course.
Of course.
Yeah.
You can, you can find connections in that kind of thing.
You can, you can speak without speaking.
So right.
Right.
The way you talked about like how he and Trump have a telepathic connection and like, yeah,
that's what he means.
But he just says telekinesis and imagining like that, that that's what he meant is hilarious.
Yes.
Oh, that's like, that's like Isaac Asimov.
Like all of a sudden our brains just grow a little bit bigger in the right spot.
And it's like, yeah, of course we can move shit with our minds.
Yeah.
I think it was just misspeaking.
And I know that it is, but it's consistent.
We already have mass telekinesis.
Everybody knows it.
Every woman knows it.
Particularly there's even stronger and it it's here and it's not just telekinesis with
each other.
Obviously.
Sure.
So the telekinesis is getting a lot stronger.
Of course.
Whatever reason our genetic development talks to the environment, whatever it is.
The globalists know this, they want to control it and they want to keep the public from understanding
it.
Okay.
All right.
I can't get over him saying telekinesis.
Like seven times?
Like the fact that like just saying the word and then saying, obviously women have it stronger.
Like, oh, that's just so good.
That's such a dumb thing to say.
I also like if you take him just literally at his words and don't, you're not giving
the generosity of understanding like he means telepathy.
Like it's telekinesis, but not just with each other.
Like we can only lift each other.
Exactly.
Yes.
Of course.
It's so fun.
Yeah.
So I think what Alex is gonna get to, I think the point he's trying to make is that humans
have this telepathic connection because of a connection with God and the globalists don't
like that.
They want to control it.
And in order to control it, they're going to come up with a big lie.
And I think the big lie that he's going to say is aliens are going to be revealed.
Sure.
And this is what he's getting at because he says this, and I mean, this is just childhood's
end.
This is really just the book that he read when he was a child.
Oh boy.
The different great lies that they're going to launch is going to be alien transmissions
first.
Sure.
Aliens are going to be communicating with the earth.
You'll be told these are aliens and then, oh, we already had contact and they gave us
technology and that's really where all this came from and all the upheaval and the Pope
will endorse it and say that's our God and this is our group and this is what they want
us to do.
And then, oh, there's all these new technologies where you can cure cancer and cure all these
things.
You've just got to accept and do what these entities want who aren't ready to reveal themselves
yet.
That's just the plot of childhood zone.
Yeah.
Yep.
That's basically it.
The aliens that come down and say that we can't reveal ourselves for 50 years until
you're used to us being here because they look like our conception of demons.
Sure.
No, I mean, no, the only person who can break through the illusion is obviously Rowdy Roddy
Piper.
You know, naturally that's the way it's got to go.
Or our generation's Rowdy Roddy Piper.
Alex Jones.
Yes, of course.
Of course.
Yes.
So the aliens are going to come down, they're going to give the Pope all these messages
and they're not going to reveal themselves because they didn't in the book.
Is the Pope still in jail in this scenario?
Is that a tough question?
I feel like I stumped you.
I've flummoxed.
Yes.
To be fair, I don't know if Alex is talking to Steve.
Sure.
Okay.
That's fair.
That's not a problem for him at this point.
Okay.
So the plan is then once the Pope is doing all this stuff and telling people they have
to listen to the aliens in order to get this technology or something, then there's a threat.
Okay.
All these wonders will be this leader who is able to talk to them and if you just do
what he says, well then everything's going to be okay.
And then we'll learn that this is one of the scenarios they've got so they can play different
ones at different times or all at once, that there's bad aliens coming and we've got to
do some certain things to stop them.
So there's bad aliens that are going to be coming.
Saint Mantis being or shut the fuck up.
That's what I have to say.
If you say bad aliens, you say fucking non-pliadians.
I'm not fucking around with just alien anymore.
What kind of animal do they look like?
Exactly.
Are these the mercantile dogs?
What are we talking about?
I need some specificity in order for this to be any fun.
Exactly.
We've been too far past the aliens are fun.
I've seen people do this better.
Yes, exactly.
Also I thought the plan was plan B and they were just going to give a super bio weapon
in order to kill everyone off.
Why do they need to do that?
Now it's all about theater, Dan.
It's about pageantry, you know, give people a show.
It's bread and circus, man.
That's what it's about.
Then you blow them up.
If the globalists have a plan that was directed to them by the devil that involves a super
bio weapon release that'll kill off the population.
Why do they need to fake an alien landing to get people to do things?
I think we're living in a galactic make a wish scenario.
We're all about to die.
So aliens are trying to give us a good run before we go.
It makes as much sense as anything Alex is saying.
Exactly.
No, it doesn't.
Does not make sense.
No.
So I guess that's the big revelation that Alex had because that's when he starts the
first segment off.
Why not?
Yep.
And then you have some other really big news that he undersells.
This is huge news.
Frankenstein, the archetype of the mad scientist, chopping different pieces of humans together
and running a high powered electricity through it and reanimating a corpse.
Well now they're actually able to do things very, very similar to that in the real world
so many times.
What humans envisioned hundreds and even thousands of years ago, we are now able to build and
we're able to build it on a mass scale.
But great power comes with all of that.
Sure.
Yeah.
So we've conquered death.
Well, only a little bit.
See, what has to happen is you have to play music and then the body will be kind of ambulatory
in a little dance-y way towards the source of that music.
You know what I'm saying?
Sure.
This is a Weekend at Bernie's 2 scenario.
Okay.
The Weekend at Bernie's 1, we're past that.
Weekend at Bernie's is really kind of like the evolution of human technology towards
death.
Well, I mean, I dread Alex seeing that movie and thinking it's a documentary.
It seems a little bit like it.
Maybe he has.
Yeah.
It seems a little bit like it.
So Frankenstein is real cool.
I don't know where the bottom is in terms of, like, there's just things that I could
say as a joke that he thinks.
Sure.
No, he does actually.
No, no, no.
He actually is suggesting these things.
I mean, he's going through the universal monsters kind of area, you know?
We've already got Dracula's, right?
We've already got Frankenstein's.
I think mummies are next.
He's just trying to create the monster mash.
He's just trying to...
He's just trying to convince people that that graveyard smash is real.
It's the monster mash, plan B. Everyone dies.
That's the monster...
There was the monster swim was the second one that Boris Pickett made.
I believe Black Tuesday is called the monster stark market crash.
Stark market...
Ah, damn it.
I blew it.
There was a...
Yeah, so he had a follow-up called the monster swim.
Yes, that's true.
And then years later, he had the climate mash.
I think he had the birthday mash.
I think he went hard, yeah.
He did a bunch.
None of them worked out except for the monster mash.
It is a little bit like if Cisco had done just various colors of the thong song, like
black thong to thong thong thong, and then just released one next month.
Or a song about a negligee or different items of underwear.
I could see him doing that.
I watched that making of the song video on YouTube.
There's a documentary series about these hits and how they came to be, and I saw the one
about Cisco's the thong song, and I could see him making a series of songs about different
undergarments.
Why not?
Yeah.
Everything else he's tried hasn't worked.
Give it a go.
So Alex is a little bit bent out of shape about stem cells.
It's like paint by numbers, you ever see those you buy at the art store for like five bucks
and it's got the little ink or markers that come with it, you just fill in the little
numbers like it says, then you finally see the big picture.
And so I've just been here on air for 27 years researching for more than 30, and I just started
painting by the numbers, looking at what they were really doing.
And I really learned that when you got to white paper levels and international discussions,
that you'll hear a headline about, oh, stem cells.
A stem cell means a 150 pound humanoid, a human chimpanzee clone.
That doesn't sound true, but I could be wrong.
Stem cell.
That's a stem cell, man.
I just don't think so.
Nope.
Sometimes he doesn't paint by the numbers and gets a green unicorn.
Yeah, it's pretty.
Yeah.
See, that's the thing about paint by numbers.
You got to follow the rules or else you come up with the wrong picture.
Yeah.
Why does this just look like brown?
Aww.
Yeah.
Paint by numbers is ostensibly creative, but it's also the least creative thing in the
world.
Yeah.
Because there, if you want the actual picture.
It's already there.
Yeah.
There's numbers.
No.
In the abstract, it exists without you.
You can just imagine that those colors are already there.
You're supposed to.
Also, if you're an adult, you can usually tell what the picture is even without coloring
it in.
That's true.
You've been there before.
Yes.
Yeah.
So humans, 150 pounds in a cage, that's a stem cell.
And this is important because there was just that bill that went through Congress.
Yes.
Failed to pass.
Yeah.
And they go on to say rules on stem cells.
And stem cells are defined as anything that comes from a baby or you can say stem cells
are in fat tissue and other things like that.
But the point is, we're having a debate about stem cells, and what we're talking about is
growing humans or humanoids in labs.
That's the definition here.
And they admit it all right here, and then it gets better.
There's video of this.
Here's the article.
48 to 49, Senate defeats Braun, Republican Indiana amendment to prohibit certain types
of human-animal chimeras.
Sixty votes were needed, but it didn't pass.
So did you hear that?
It's legal right now to create human-animal hybrids because there's laws against human
clones.
So there's two things that are going on that Alex is kind of playing with and conflating
in this episode when he's talking about this.
There's one is the bill that got defeated in the Senate.
That was an attempt by the GOP to criminalize genetic research that involved creating embryos
that were chimeric.
And from what I understand, a good thing that did not pass because it seems like it was
a little bit of a Trojan horsey.
Yeah, it was an excuse to just, something about abortion, you know, it always goes back
to that.
Also, so the other thing that he's conflating this with is a recent move that was made by
the International Society for Stem Cell Research.
They loosened their rules about how long a human embryo can be used in experiments.
Previously, they had a standard policy that studies that went beyond 14 days would absolutely
not be done.
But now reflecting advances in technology, they say that these experiments could possibly
done to quote Stat News, quote, only if lots of conditions are met first.
Sure, sure.
We're not going to suddenly have horse people drawing our cars around.
That's we're going to be fine.
So yeah, there's this, Alex is freaking out about these chimeras and what have you, and
it leads him to go to break.
Pretty extreme, pretty extreme.
They're figuring out how to lock you down, how to train you to behave so they can kill
everybody.
Everybody stay in your houses while that happens, while combat robots go up and down the streets.
And so this isn't something that they're just thinking about doing.
This is all set up very, very soon.
You and your family will be killed soon.
Two years, five years.
I don't know.
The timeline's moving quick, but if we don't hold them back, everyone listening is dead.
Okay.
They're going to kill you.
They're going to kill me.
They're going to kill everybody.
We'll be right back.
Stay with us.
That's a bummer.
That's bad.
To some extent, you know, we live in kind of a fairly mundane world.
To suddenly go from that to like, oh, there's robots in the streets and chimeras in my home.
I think that would be at least a little bit more exciting.
Four days ago, I was having a fun hot dog and on San Sui Beach, I come back and I got
to hear Alex saying that everyone's dead.
Everyone's dead.
It's a jarring.
It's a bit of whiplash.
You doing all right?
Yeah, because I think this is stupid.
I do see your neck perpetually at a 45 degree angle right now, so that might be trouble.
Yeah.
It's, you know, there's that standard thing about like, you know, if you just keep moving,
it's not hard to keep moving, but when you stop, then you start moving again.
It's like, whoa.
Object at rest.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think that Alex is obviously full of shit and everything, but it is, it is a little
bit, it's a little bit a nude after a week of not listening to him to come back and hear
like you and your family, everybody listening to the show will be dead within five years
if we don't stop my enemies.
It's comically overt.
It's like when I take time off, I start to doubt myself.
I start to doubt these like, ah, Alex isn't as crazy as I think he is.
It can't be real.
It cannot be real.
It's not like he says within two to five years, everyone listening will be dead.
Like come back.
Nope, that's exactly what he does.
No, it makes you realize how like, I totally get, when you're, when you've been doing this
nonstop for a long time, you know, you forget how real people react to this kind of stuff
where they're like, you're the one who's a conspiracy theorist.
There's no way that anyone would get away with that.
And then you come back and you're like, I'm a conspiracy theorist.
This can't be real.
So how do we, how do we discuss this next clip?
Let's see.
Um, the globalists, right?
Sure.
They have a plan.
Yeah.
Heard it.
They have a lot of plans.
At least two.
Apparently super bio weapon kill off.
Sure.
Maybe that's plan A and B. Plan C involves aliens coming down and not
revealing themselves through the post.
Then telling us that there's bad aliens that are coming and we've got to do something in
order to stop the bad aliens that will be counterproductive to us.
Who knows?
Yeah.
Turns out there's a plan D.
Oh no.
And that is that they're going to replace us with computers.
Oh, that's nice.
But I mean, it's really very simple.
What humans can envision, we can end up building.
And what we've gotten to at this point is free energy, massive live extension, super
computers, way more powerful than what you're currently even aware exist.
And the decisions have been made to basically go ahead and go operational with a system
that will make us obsolete, obsolete in their words, these computers won't recognize beauty.
These computers won't have our ancient history.
These computers didn't create the computers like we did, but there is a dark anti-human
force pushing this.
And by the way, I could have opened the whole show up and just made this very, very simple.
And that's, we're being replaced.
I know that Alex is talking about robots, but still when I hear somebody who has the
politics that Alex has worrying about, we are going to be replaced.
It kind of, you know, it exists in a certain linguistic space.
It's something that isn't without baggage.
Yeah.
You know, the way he's talking is like a person in like the early eighties who was like, computers
are the devil.
You know, computers are going to the soul, but the devil's mark.
But we don't live there.
He uses computers all the time.
He lives in a world where computers are perfectly fine and people are evil, you know, or the
people he wants to tell you are evil.
Computers are ethically neutral.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I just get, I just get a little worried.
Fears of replacement are generally not, they're not good openings.
Well, you know, what comes after that is usually bad.
It's a little bit like the space racism we deal with where it's like, oh, they're evil
cat beings.
But you're like, that's code for something else.
Like when the great replacement theory, you can't just be like, nah, nah, nah, nah.
It's computers that we're worried about and not have me be like, is this Jews again?
I feel like this is Jews again, you know?
And I know that Alex doesn't really care that much about workers rights, so it couldn't
really be a conversation about like automation in the workplace.
Totally.
No, it's not like there's, we need more grocery people.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's just, it's a word that I don't like hearing.
So we have one, one more thing here about the globalist, okay.
And the globalist argument is if you don't resist this under survival of the fittest
and social Darwinism, you deserve what happens to you.
And so it's all about humans being a commodity, mass smuggling of children for sex abuse,
for slave labor.
But really it's about committing crimes in God's eyes, having you do nothing so that
the spiritual hedge of protection can be removed from us so that everyone can be attacked.
And so this is very sophisticated interdimensional galactic warfare.
And that's what you face.
Oh boy.
Tough, tough to wrestle with that.
Is it?
No.
It's not.
He's so confident.
I feel like I need to ask.
Yeah.
That's part of the trick.
That is true.
Yeah.
So the first thought that he has there is that the globalist believe if you don't fight,
you deserve what happens to you.
That's essentially just something to be cribbed from Silent Weapons from Quiet Wars, which
is the first chapter in Bill Cooper's book, Behold a Pale Horse, that the globalist believe
you're a meat on the plate.
Sure.
You're never meant to be slaughtered.
Yes.
That kind of thing.
Yeah.
And then the second part is just that if you don't defend God's law, then you make us all
susceptible to God's punishment, which the only thing that could really lead towards
is a theocracy, right?
It has to.
I mean, a complete civilization that's designed entirely around adherence to strict religious
rule.
Yeah.
You know.
That's not good.
religious rules are really great when they're in power and allowed to kind of go unchecked.
Everybody knows that from history.
I just hear nonsense here.
Also.
Was the interdimensional galactic warfare part a little bit nonsense or was that the
part where you're like, wow, we don't need to worry about that, obviously.
That's true.
I mean, that's the closest to like, I'll let it slide.
It's arguably hyperbole, you know, it's like, I mean, I know he's not speaking metaphorically,
but you could hear that and be like, eh, whatever.
The other stuff is just like contextually weird.
Yeah.
I don't, if Alex believes that doing things that are against his religious rules make
everybody susceptible to God's wrath because God removes the hedge of protection, then
the only way to keep everyone safe is to make sure that everyone is forcibly adhering to
God's rules according to his version of God.
And to me, I find that to be an incredibly fucked up way to conceive of how society should
be organized.
Yeah.
I mean, the ironic part about it, I think is something similar in practice is what we
all tried to do to defeat a disease to a certain extent.
Do you know what I mean?
Like we have to, we have to allow a certain amount of like, oh, we are locking down in
order to keep, you know, if everybody, if people don't act in everybody's interest,
then the susceptibility of that disease is spread throughout everybody.
So he's fine with the tactics of, I think, I think, you know what I'm saying?
I think your thought is interesting and I do see a little bit of a parallel.
I'm not saying it's one to one, of course.
Yeah.
And I think what I think is most interesting about Alex's conception is the divine rat.
Yes.
As opposed to the actual genomic rat.
The actual causally determinative chain of events.
The obvious wrath.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I don't, I don't feel like it's possible for Alex to contain this kind of thinking
and this, this idea set and also actually believe in the first amendment.
That's true.
You can actually believe in freedom of religion if you believe that breaking God's rules makes
the hedge of protection go away.
Wow.
I mean, one of the commandments is you should have no other God than me.
Sure.
You're breaking a commandment if you follow another religion or you don't follow a religion.
Totally.
I mean, how could you follow, how could you believe in freedom of speech if the government
has to, I guess, murder you for taking the Lord's name in vain?
You know what I'm saying?
The penalty for sin is death, obviously.
It would be, it would be a challenge, certainly, to believe in a republic.
It would take some work.
I think we're seeing a little bit of some flaws.
Yeah.
So Alex has a guest and I just think this is hilarious.
We're not going to talk about him at all, but I think it's really hilarious that this
dude is showing up after the beginning of this bullshit and still expecting to be taken
seriously.
All right, we are back live, ladies and gentlemen, and James O'Keefe is just getting into the
studio.
Put the sports jacket on, I think.
We're going to get him here on in a moment.
Really big breaking news, but please don't forget that it's listeners and viewers like
you that make this broadcast possible and all the incredible breaking news that we bring
out is just critical to all of our futures and the future of our species and all our
children.
So I thank you for your support.
We have a big Memorial Day special to honor the veterans and folks that have served.
So yeah, we got James O'Keefe coming up.
Sure.
James, would you like to talk about how Frankenstein is real?
Yeah.
Um, actually...
Hey, James, you're a real serious reporter.
Let's talk about mass telekinesis.
He did an undercover sting operation inside of Frankenstein's castle, actually.
You know what's ironic?
He could actually do an amazing sting operation on Alex.
Yes, he really could.
He really could.
If he just brought a hidden camera into a regular conversation with Alex, he would get
everything.
Perfectly situated to sting the shit out of Alex.
God damn it.
Somebody...
He can be turned, right?
He can be turned from the dark side.
It's just a matter of money.
Yeah, right?
Just give him two billion and he'll be like, yeah, I'll fucking kill Alex Jones' career.
I don't care.
God, I wish that would happen.
That'd be interesting at least.
Yeah, we gotta get a billionaire on our side to just throw money at fake people.
The further irony, though, is that if he did sting Alex, I don't think I would believe
it.
I couldn't trust it because it's still coming from him.
Ah, the dangers of lost credibility.
Yep.
So I don't care.
Alex O'Keefe has a, I guess, another Facebook story.
I don't care.
Whatever.
And one of the reasons I don't care is because Alex has an interesting story to tell.
They've gone from this all being in white papers and textbooks and, you know, very low
circulation books that these, you know, Zbigniew Brzezinski and people like Klaus Schwab would
write in the past and John P. Holdren and...
Real quick.
John P. Holdren's book, Ecoscience, wasn't a low circulation book.
It was a textbook.
Yeah.
It's not like...
It wasn't a mass market paperback that failed.
It wasn't like a flop.
It was the front of like Barnes and Noble trying to push Holdren to Ecoscience.
Yeah, exactly.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The rest of them, David Rockefeller, Club of Rum documents, secret documents.
I was given a whole bunch of archive secret documents out of the Bilderberg Group, out
of the Senate archives that pulled up a motorcycle in Virginia when I was covering Bilderberg
there and just said, here, have this.
And it was all how in the 60s, the Bilderberg Group took over the US unions for the deindustrialization
project and explaining why they were going to deindustrialize the US.
And we published them on Infowars and no one even cared.
Probably because you got them from a random guy on a motorcycle.
So a random guy on a motorcycle handed me papers and people don't believe me.
It's basically Deep Throat, isn't it?
You meet in a parking garage or a random dude on a motorcycle drives up towards you.
No big deal.
It's like the Yakuza dropped off some papers.
Yeah.
I think that this is probably just like John Birch Society-esque literature and ideas because
it's talking about just like infiltrating the unions, obviously there's workers kind
of ideas of unionization or something that are antithetical to the Patriot movement.
So you might as well say that there's no point in unionization because it's also owned by
or yeah, or it's infiltrated.
Not only infiltrated, it's a plot in order to destroy America.
Yeah, of course.
So I just love the idea of Alex sitting there, some guy on a motorcycle comes up, he's like,
I've got all the archives at the secret globe.
He's just standing there in this circumstance?
He's in Chantilly, Virginia, because I remember when he went there.
I do, yeah.
Also, I don't know, I mean, I've watched the video of him down there.
Certainly a lot of the video of that is in one of his documentaries, I think.
Yeah.
Is it Endgame?
I'm not sure.
I've definitely seen the video of him in Chantilly.
I don't remember a guy on a motorcycle coming up and giving him an archive of secret globalist
Bilderberg documents.
I don't remember him going back to his hotel room and freaking out that some guy on a motorcycle
gave him an archive.
Okay.
Now, we're both imagining this.
How is he holding these documents?
Does he have a briefcase that's like handcuffed to his wrist and he has to go through a process
to give it to him?
Is he just wearing a messenger bag and he's like, ah, here you go.
Is it like in Oceans 12 or whatever where the, you know?
I'm guessing it was Daniel Estelan on a motorcycle and they just gave him his stupid book.
Yeah.
So there's big news on the white supremacy front.
And that is that Alex has found a triangle.
And I mean, it's super interesting to have the overt white supremacy, socially unacceptable
stuff written up by the Southern Poverty Law Center and the ADL now being taught in more
than 20 states.
This particular one is from Maryland and Virginia and it says, fathers are a form of covert
white supremacy.
It says parental.
Parental.
Just parental.
Right here it says parental.
I'm going to cover that later.
Here just zoom in on over here guys.
Right here is the zoom in area.
So what he's got is a triangle and it has like at the top there is a line.
So there's a smaller triangle and then the bottom of the triangle.
Smaller triangle is the unacceptable white supremacy and it's things like the Klan, lynchings,
stuff like that.
And then underneath is the more subtle, you know, it's like that iceberg metaphor.
Underneath is the sort of covert forms of white supremacy and Alex thinks that fathers
are one of them.
Okay.
However, I went and I watched the video because I can't find this triangle anywhere else and
I'm like, I got to go find him.
And I looked at it and it turns out Alex just doesn't know how to read.
Sure.
He thinks it says parental.
It says paternalism.
Oh God.
Okay.
Merriam-Webster defines paternalism as quote, a system under which an authority undertakes
to supply needs or regulate conduct of those under its control and manners affecting them
as individuals as well in their relations to authority and to each other.
Paternalism is essentially believing that you can restrict another person or group's
actions because you understand their own good better than them.
Alex has no idea about the words, let alone concepts he's covering.
He's taking a piece of paper that claims that paternalistic attitudes contribute to covert
white supremacy.
And the way he reports it is that the SPLC and ADL are saying that having fathers is
white supremacist.
This guy's a fucking idiot.
That's a jump.
That is a bit of a jump.
But I honestly don't think he knows that it doesn't say parental.
That would be most likely I would say.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It feels like he misread that, got mad about it.
And whether or not he's realized he's wrong, it's too good for him not to be mad about
it.
Yeah, totally.
It's embarrassing as hell.
No, once he got what he wanted, I'm sure he never read it again.
Yeah.
It's not like he was like, wait, I got to double check this.
That's never happened.
True.
Yeah.
Whatever that is, is under attack.
Sure.
And you're like, well, that sounds crazy.
Well, no, it's not crazy.
They're getting rid of who would protect the family.
Parentalism.
I mean, parentalism isn't just supporting a father.
You can't keep saying it.
It's supporting parents.
Parentalism is believing in the nuclear family.
You can't invent it.
And it says that's racist.
That's not real.
I'm not sure that parentalism is a widespread concept.
I was thinking that he could have misspoken, but still understood the word.
You know, like telekinesis.
Sure.
When he was like, he's using the wrong word.
He means telepathy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then he went further.
And said, parentalism.
And he said, parentalism?
And it's about parents.
So we know for a fact, he does not understand what was being said.
No, but I still think it could be an instance of him misreading the word and then never
checking again.
Sure sure.
Either way, it's embarrassing.
It's pretty funny.
But it is also like, yeah, I'm glad you brought that up, because it is so different than the
other misuse of the word.
Exactly.
Like the telekinesis thing is just funny.
It's like, okay, I get you mean telepathy.
With telekinesis.
Alex is creating parentalism as a thing to be mad about.
Out of whole cloth.
That may or may not be an actual word.
I mean, I could find some uses of it online, but it's definitely not like a word people
use.
No, it's not.
You don't find it cited in psychiatry papers.
Covert rights supremacy would not have that as one of the things.
Parentalistic attitudes, though.
I mean, oh no, I did the Alex.
Paternalistic.
Yes.
I stopped him.
My eyes went wide.
I was like, what's going to happen now?
Oh no.
Alex got into my head.
So most of the middle of the show, middle to end of the show, is about Alex, well, not
most of it, but a good chunk is about Alex talking about Joe Biden, the president.
Sure.
Apparently he's blaming the victims of the Tuskegee experiments for black vaccine hesitancy.
He's blaming the victim.
Well that's what Alex says.
Okay.
I have a hard time believing that, but let's continue.
Well, here's Alex talking about it and then the clip of Biden that's used to rationalize
this.
Okay.
Giving a speech today, Joe Biden blames black vaccine hesitancy on Tuskegee airmen.
The first blacks since the civil war allowed in combat who did an excellent job.
So he blamed black men, some of which had their families injected with syphilis that
came out and killed or tortured over long periods of time, it's very painful.
These were allowed to be infected overall by the tens of thousands that were injected.
It wasn't just blacks that got it, it was everybody.
And Joe Biden now blames them, the victims for what happened.
You say, well, he's an old man.
Yeah.
He should be, you know, at a nursing home, not molesting children, not molesting our
country anymore.
So here he is blaming the very blacks from Alabama, many and more from there, Tuskegee
airmen who were victimized with a secret government experiment telling them it was a vaccine.
For polio when it was syphilis now blaming them for what they did to him.
So even as the demon in him just lies so much, you can't stop here.
I asked one person to do nothing but deal with equity, equity, to make sure that we
were reaching out into minority communities, which by the way, and many of the older members
of that community had memories of experimentation on black Americans that were not told about
like what happened to the Tuskegee airmen and all those tests.
I shouldn't laugh.
It's just so sick.
Yeah.
The Tuskegee airmen, like when their souls were leaving their bodies, when they died,
like Casper, the friendly ghost, they were sure flying high up.
You killed him, huh?
So what happened is that Biden kind of misspoke and he said Tuskegee airmen, which were the
group of black fighter pilots in World War II, when he was referencing the Tuskegee experiments.
This is an unfortunate gaffe and if Alex's point here was that Biden doesn't know the
difference between the two uses of the word Tuskegee, I'd say that's probably a stretch,
but whatever.
I don't really care.
Yeah.
Using this clip to argue that Biden is blaming the victims of the experiment for vaccine
hesitancy though, that's absurd.
That's nonsense.
I was listening to this clip.
It's really, that doesn't say anything close to what Alex is suggesting.
It's very clear that what Biden is saying is that the memory of this, of course, this
stain on American history.
Of course.
This shame is what would contribute to people being hesitant to trust rollouts of large
vaccine programs.
That thought is, it makes sense.
Yeah.
And it's what he's expressing.
No, it's Alex is not missing the point.
He is like cutting the points, Achilles tendons, and then burying it alive in the backyard.
Like this is, this is way, way out of control.
Yeah.
And then a little bit later, Alex makes the exact same mistake by of course, what's the
name of that major rapper.
I listened to him in the eighties, but I told my wife that this rap group that does these
pro vaccines.
She didn't believe until she saw it.
Who are they?
What's the name of the rapper?
I forget.
It's super famous.
Run DMC.
They've got a new one where it shows Tuskegee airmen and our Tuskegee folks and says, yeah,
we injected you, but we don't do that anymore.
We don't do experiments anymore when it is an experiment.
I mean, Alex did the exact same slip that Biden did.
It's an easy mistake to make.
It's unacceptable in one circumstance.
And if you do it like, Oh no, no, no, it was a mistake.
You know, he, he was blaming them and I made a mistake.
Yeah.
It's just a stupid game.
So Rand Paul, uh, he's, he's made some disparaging comments about Fauci at this point.
Sure.
And so Alex believes that he's going head to head with the enemy and maybe that means
that he should be president.
But Alex had a chance to support 2016 failed.
Yeah.
This is Rand Paul who deserves a lot of support on prayers.
He's going directly at the enemy.
It's why he's getting death threats.
He's why he's been shot at twice, been physically attacked twice, twice had his ribs broken,
his lungs punctured.
That was a long argument and he has a good heart.
Very presidential material.
I'd like to see him president in the future.
Maybe him and his Santas make a nice mix.
But I don't care if there were two black guys or two women, I don't give a damn.
There were two black women like those guys.
I'd be all for them.
Vote for them in one second.
But yeah, they're two white males.
I mean, who else, who else is there, folks?
Don't give a damn about them being white.
But the point is, is that, uh, you know, Bolsonaro's white, he's fighting the world order.
I mean, I'm just saying, uh, get some black folks running for office, talking like them,
I'll vote for them.
Uh, but, uh, can't believe we even have to have a discussion about that, about who cares
what color somebody is.
It's about getting the job done.
But I digress.
You do digress.
That is true.
You can't believe that we have that conversation?
Yeah.
You're the one who brought it up.
Yeah, I certainly didn't.
I wasn't like, I wonder if Bolsonaro's white.
I didn't think that.
I wasn't like, that's a question I need him to answer before he finishes this sentence.
I did.
That was not on the top of my mind.
It wasn't there.
It certainly wasn't also my first response that I would have to the idea of a Rand Paul
DeSantis ticket.
Yeah.
My primary complaint with them would not be, it's two white dudes.
There's two white dudes.
That's a big, yeah.
I feel like there would be some policies that I would be, uh, really offended by first.
Yeah.
All I hear is Alex being like, baby, come back.
You can blame it all on me.
That's all I hear.
It's, um, uh, oh, to Rand?
Yeah.
Man.
It's, it's having gone through that, the disenchantment period with Rand Paul during
the lead up to the 2016 election, it's pretty funny to hear him say stuff like this because
he knows he blew it.
Yeah, no, there's, there's just, you'll, you'll, he got off the Paul boat.
I wish I could stop being at least a little bit surprised at how Craven, you know, no
matter how Craven I see them, I'm still like, you're that Craven?
Oh man.
Just, well, in a week he's going to pretend that he didn't say that there's a fake alien
invasion that's coming and they're going to not be able to reveal themselves and then
they're going to tell us eventually bad aliens are coming.
Totally.
Yes.
How can I be surprised?
He expects you to not remember that a week ago he had a big revelation right before he
got on air.
Yeah.
He's got a lot of revelations though.
I think you just expect him to have.
He's jangling keys the radio show.
It's ridiculous.
That'd be a fun, that'd be a more fun radio show to listen to.
Certainly.
Less ads.
Yeah.
Um, so he said a lot of extreme stuff on this episode.
Some of it not as hateful as usual, some of it just kind of dumb.
Right.
Um, but you should know this.
We discredit these guys.
We send them to prison or they're going to kill everybody.
It's us or them.
Okay.
Seriously.
I mean every damn word I'm saying.
Stay with us.
It means everything.
Well, earlier in the show Alex had said that it's going to be open phones in the third
and fourth hour.
He's getting really pumped for it.
Uh.
Can I guess how many calls he takes?
Yeah.
So I'd love that.
Three.
Zero.
Oh.
Damn it.
I was, I was really, I was really going out on a limb going more than zero.
I kind of expected zero, but I was really hoping.
I feel like whenever you take that bet, it should be zero or the field.
Yes, exactly.
The over under is one.
Is point five.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
So he takes none.
Um, and apparently he couldn't have taken open phones in the fourth hour because initially
he had Matt Bracken scheduled to host the fourth hour.
Right, right, right, right.
But apparently there were problems.
Oh.
Matt Bracken had some technical difficulties today.
He does a great job when he hosts Thursday's fourth hour and he's, uh, can't do it.
So Owen Schroyer's coming in in the fourth hour because I've got a bunch of things I'm
working on.
I don't want to host the fourth hour, but I've got big stories we're working on that
are huge, very important behind the scenes.
I'm gonna leave it at that.
He had to go to family court.
Yeah.
Uh, so he's going fishing with my daughter.
This is a, the night I believe that his ex wife was trying to live stream a court appearance
on YouTube.
Cool.
Because as I understand, her argument is that these are supposed to be open here.
Sure.
And people should know what's going on, like what, what's, and so I, I would assume that
that's more what was on Alex's mind than a big story.
Yeah.
He had this court date that was possibly going to be live streamed.
Yeah, that would be, that would be somewhat, I think, terrifying for him.
Yeah, I would think so.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Uh, but look, that's, even at this point in the show, that's in the future.
Yeah, sure.
We have to worry about the now because now it's time to cover news.
Okay.
I got to hit all this.
Um, I got a bunch of other huge COVID news as well, and some really scary stuff that
makes me really mad.
And also the abomination stuff, all this cloning because our cells are designed and the ancients
said this, but now they've mathematically scientifically proven it to resonate with
the universe that God made.
Like we're a musical instrument and the atmosphere is a musical instrument and trees are a musical
instrument is the best way to describe it.
But energetically through the dimensions, it's like a sound wave is, is the easiest
way to describe it.
It's not what it is, but with our limited senses, it's like trying to teach Helen Keller
how to read, write and talk when she couldn't hear and couldn't see, but she finally could
figure it out because there was, it was innately in her.
The archetypes were there, you know, being a very passionate, very well-spoken person
through communication wild, but it could only, you know, took years to get through to her,
but it was there.
So trying to describe this in third dimensional terms is, uh, let's just say, uh, it's, it's
limiting, but trying to describe what I, you know, you know, it's weird.
It tastes like, I just don't know how it is.
He could really somehow be offensive towards Helen Keller.
Like Helen Keller didn't do any work.
It's that the people broke through her, her defenses in order to get to what was already
there inside.
She had to do some work to minimize that.
That's what he said.
Oh, you're being offensive to her efforts that she redoubled and read, you know, like
somehow out of nowhere, you're offensive to Helen Keller.
Yeah, it is.
It is a little, it's, it seems like a stray thought a little bit.
And I would guess that the people who worked with Helen Keller wouldn't say like, damn
just thing.
It's lucky.
The archetypes were there.
No kidding.
Yeah.
I'm guessing that that wouldn't be the way that they would describe it.
I doubt it.
Um, so yeah, the universe, yeah.
Musical instrument.
Sure.
I know that when I like, uh, was, I think it was in fourth grade, my parents made me
learn a musical instrument, but they said I couldn't play like drums or guitar cause
they didn't want me to be in a rock band.
Sure.
So I took up the tree.
I didn't, I didn't know where that was going and you got me.
You got me?
I played the tree.
I'm going to give you that one.
That one's an unqualified win for you.
Thanks.
Um, yeah, so our bodies are musical instruments.
Sure.
There's sound waves, the universe, whatever.
Well, they're not actually sound waves, but that's the best way to describe them.
Look, in the third dimension, it's hard, it's limiting to talk about these things, which
I don't know what these things are.
I don't know what's going on.
I thought we were going to get to COVID news.
This is, I don't know what's happening.
I do.
I do like the, uh, scientists have proved it.
The ancients.
Everything's kind of like sound waves.
Yeah, the ancients said it first.
Of course.
Yeah.
The music of the spheres, Dan.
Don't try and cut out the ancients.
Apologies.
That's very rude.
Yeah, it is.
So what I've done now is I have just made cuts.
Uh, this is just, this is one long statement.
Yep.
Okay.
He is in a weird place.
We are talking for the news.
We are not.
All right.
We are talking about our bodies being musical instruments in the third dimension or something.
Look, dude, this is a mess.
This is a very primitive level of God's creation.
As fantastic as it is, this, um, when it comes to creational matter, very thin, sure.
This dimension is very, very thin and if you call it below that, that's a human term, but
in the lower dimensions, which again exists and have been proven, uh, it's even more empty.
It's more empty in the lower dimensions.
Right.
But that's a human term.
The lower it's up and down, you know, it's just a human thing.
Uh, no.
Yes.
Just refuse.
Like it or not, this is happening.
Refuse.
Now we go back for vacation.
I refuse to hear someone say this dimension is thin.
I don't know what you're talking about.
This dimension is thin on a creational level.
What does that mean?
Look in the third dimension, third dimensional words are limiting.
I don't know what that means.
No, neither does he.
Just saying shit.
Oh, you know, the space below human term naturally more empty.
Is it, is, does that mean it's thinner?
I think so.
But again, that's a human term.
Right.
But I mean, let's...
I suspect.
Let's engage with it on that level.
So we're, we're talking all the difference between the levels of dimension is really
measurable by thin or thickness.
I mean, you know, in the new age communities, whenever they talk about like these higher
vibrations and stuff, it's often referred to as a higher density.
Sure.
So maybe Alex is taking that as like actual denseness.
I really, I really, okay.
That could be what's going on.
You can float easier in the fourth dimension.
I would assume that you can the third dimension.
No, I would, I would assume if you have a lower density, you'd float more, right?
Oh no, cause you're talking about the environment is denser.
Yeah.
I had it backwards.
All right.
I had to stop and think.
Yeah.
Look, we're engaging with too much even cause he's not even taking us there.
He's just saying it's thin creationally.
You don't just get to say that.
Now.
I actually think that the next thing he brings up is a good thought.
Maybe if you're high.
Interesting.
And you're in college and you're sitting around with your friends and that thought is this.
We always imagine that like if aliens were to come down and contact us, they'd be so
much more advanced than us, man.
You know, that kind of thing.
I think we've, we've experienced this in the Aqua Teen Hunger Force.
Sure.
With the Moon Knights.
Yes.
We've experienced this in plenty of media depictions, but yeah, of course.
I mean, we have a bias towards anything that would contact us would have to be far more
advanced than us.
And maybe that's not the case.
Well, I mean, if we can't contact them, but they can contact us, that would suggest that
at least on some level, they have an ability that we don't.
On one level.
Right.
The contacting across whatever.
That's all we know for sure.
And we're theoretically opening the possibility to a intergalactic spacefaring race that still
fights with clubs.
It's possible.
I suppose.
Anything in this great big marble of a world.
Okay.
Anyway, that's the decent thought.
I'm going out of my way to give some credibility or credence here because the rest of this
thought is stupid.
Okay.
So we tend to think of interfacing with other things and like, oh, it must be advanced.
No, anything that would actually try to interface with us without our free will is low.
Wow.
Other than Lucifer, who does come from one dimension higher, down to our dimension to
try to then ally with all the other dark energy or dark's not even the right word, fallen
energy.
Dark is a human word.
Right.
Fallen.
That's their word.
I mean, maybe what he's trying to say is that Satan isn't really a bad guy, but he just
needs to breathe thinner air.
I mean, no, I don't think so.
Okay.
Although that does kind of...
Kind of tracks.
It tracks with some of the other ideas he has.
No, Satan is one level higher and he's allying with the stuff to, who knows why.
No, I'm not messing with that.
Right.
I'm not messing with the why on this one.
No, certainly not.
Yeah.
I got nothing.
Nope.
Let's just move on.
Okay.
Dark's not even the right word.
Fallen energy.
I mean, to a human brain seeing it, it means there's no creation.
What?
Darkness just means devoid of light.
Well, that's not like a black road sign.
That's just absorbing light.
That's not...
So, it's not the proper term, but we have to create our own terms to even understand
an interface with the cosmos, which itself, again, is just an expression of God.
And I'm not an animist.
I'm not saying to these troglodyte preachers that aren't really Christians, but think they
are Pharisees, that I worship the creation.
No, no, no.
I don't worship the creation.
I'm saying God made all this.
And if I create a piece of art, that is an expression of who I am.
I made that.
And that is a very primitive form of, imagine God making us, but imagine making something
that has consciousness and free will.
Well, guess what?
God gives you a little taste of that.
It's why the Old Testament tells you quite a few times, we're made the image of God.
We're not God, but we're little g.
Okay.
What do you take away from that?
Let's see.
What do I take away from...
I think it's blasphemy.
Well, interesting.
Make your case.
Well, the idea of comparing yourself to God by simply changing the size of the g would
still technically really be construed as calling yourself somewhat equal to God, which I think,
now I don't know if I've read the Bible enough times, but that one's pretty big on the don't
do scale.
Yeah.
I mean, you know, what is made in the image of really me and phew.
Telekinesis.
Totally.
Yes.
A million percent.
Yeah.
I was looking for a thesis.
I'm not finding it.
I think that was your mistake.
That was.
And it's a mistake I continue to make.
It's something that, it's a lesson I refuse to learn.
I accept that.
So, you know, you have an interesting perspective that you think that changing the capitalization
on God doesn't mean all that much.
No.
I think Alex thinks it does.
Of course he does.
But also he thinks he's got the personal connection to God that gives him visions all the time.
So there's that.
But he's not God capital.
Sure.
Right?
Satan.
Okay.
He comes down from his address, which is in just the level above us.
Alex has his address, actually.
Right.
No.
It's in the dimension right above us.
48.
Yeah.
He comes down and he's like, hey.
Hey.
How you doing?
You're God.
Satan tries to convince you that you are God.
Does Satan get a capital S in the fourth dimension and a lowercase s in the third dimension?
I never thought about it.
I always considered it to be a proper noun.
Yeah.
Me too.
Like it's a name, right?
But if God's fungible, I feel like Satan's fungible.
Oh, it's too confusing.
We're not God, but we're little g.
And Satan goes all the way and goes, oh, no, no, you're even better than God.
You act.
Well, no, you're fallen.
Okay.
But that's what they tell you in things like 2001 Space Odyssey, that after you go through
this process, you come back as a star child, reincarnated to like a sperm, implant the
egg that is earth and create the new Lucifer race.
Well, that's just satanic poppycock, ladies and gentlemen.
Satanic poppycock.
I thought it was maybe a little bit long, but I didn't necessarily construe it as satanic
poppycock.
Satanic poppycock.
Huh?
Well, that's fair.
I feel like you are not the most reliable cinematic reviewer if you didn't pick up on
the satanic poppycock.
That's possible.
Because it was overt.
Yeah.
I missed that in Ebert's review, but I suppose it was all unspoken.
Right.
Siskel was all about the satanic poppycock.
I give it two thumbs down for Satanism.
Yeah.
Develery.
So it turns out, actually, you know, the stuff in 2001 A Space Odyssey might be just as real
as Frankenstein.
Okay.
Well, that's that's just satanic poppycock, ladies and gentlemen.
But I am explaining that the devil creates facsimiles or counterfeits of what God has
actually created.
And I can tell you the stuff that came up with 2001 Space Odyssey with the primitive
special effects is very close to actually what's going on.
And I'll just leave it at that.
But don't hit all this news.
Yeah.
You need to get back to.
Tell me more about that.
I want to know more about that.
Well, 2001 A Space Odyssey is actually very real.
They were very close to accurate with their rudimentary special effects.
So I got to get back to the news.
Yes, you do.
On a certain level.
For me.
Please do not.
So how dare you say something like that?
How dare you introduce this idea and then be like, ah, what's in the news?
Boo.
So 50 years ago, special effects were very similar to what they had then.
So would you say that special effects have gotten better enough that they are what they
have now?
Or is it like proportional?
Are special effects true to what reality was 50 years ago, and now it's 50 years ahead
of what we have?
I mean, it would have to be, right?
Right.
That's the only thing that makes sense.
If they're implanting, if the evil globalists are implanting secret messages that control
all of cinema and media, it's not like they wouldn't give access to secret technologies
for special effects.
Right.
So Andy Serkis only has a career because of aliens.
I think that's what I'm hearing.
Yeah.
I don't know about that, that whether or not the cinema world is privy to those futuristic
technologies.
I'm just going to go ahead and say Kong vs. Godzilla is real.
Sure.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm getting to get back to the news, that's where this sort of excursion into lunacy
ended.
Boo.
I know.
That weirded me out so much.
Like I was like, what are you trying to express?
It seems like just kind of a bit of standard shit header-y from like new age space conspiracy
communities.
Sure.
I could hear Rogan saying some dumb nonsense like that.
That's not far off from what dumb nonsense Rogan spouts, right?
I could see somebody who wouldn't get invited on Rogan, but really wants to.
Almost there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
On that one tier below where you got to be.
I don't see a lot of depth here.
I just see killing time, rambling about nonsense.
Sure.
And then Alex gets angry about his nonsense.
This is only an experience of free will that God created, because the only thing God can
create separate from God's all knowing, all powerful, all controlling, omnipotent, omnipresent,
beyond 12th dimensional total completeness is creatures with free will that create other
creatures with free will and the capacity to interface with this time space continuum
galacticus beyond.
That is the secret to all of it that we have been made by a all powerful sentient creature
that created everything and doesn't want to be alone.
And so put us on this planet away from other things so we don't kill everything while we
run around inside our nursery.
And what does God put in the nursery to test his creation puts a lot of nasty stuff.
That's weird.
What a weird God.
What a weird guy on the radio.
Yeah.
You know what I was thinking while I was listening to this?
I was like, this, Alex is turned into like the, like, I remember when I was growing up,
there was the small town church that had like 15 to 20 people in it and everybody avoided
them.
And I don't want to know what goes on there.
It's none of our business and we just stay out of it, you know?
It's loud.
Yeah.
There's, there's something going on, but we just, it's a, it's like a black hole in the
small town where everybody just kind of avoids it out of instinct.
I think I might've gone to a couple of those churches and I think I know what you mean.
And then there was one moment in his thing that really hit home, like in that way for
me.
And that is the, like when he's yelling about like, we were created by an all powerful beast.
And then there's the pause and the, who doesn't want to be alone.
Exactly.
It's the anger, the pause, and then the soft delivery of this idea that like created us
to keep him company or whatever.
You can hear it.
Like I've been to a church where there were snakes before.
I've heard this, you know?
Yeah.
That rhythm and cadence is, is, is very a tent preacher kind of, kind of vibe.
And then the other thing that I thought about when I heard that clip was about like the
naming of his website as prison planet.
It's really interesting to me the way that like, if you think that he's just this guy
who's into political conspiracies and like, Hey, if a one world government comes into
place and they turn into a tyrannical dictatorship, right?
We are on a prison planet.
You can't get off.
If there's nowhere to run, if there's a one world government that's in control of everywhere
on earth, it is a prison planet.
But if you look at it the way he's kind of talking now, it's more like, you know, the
earth nursery idea.
It's kind of like, he's saying that like, you know, I'm in a crib, I'm in a crib and
this weird God threw a scorpion in here.
Sure.
Yeah.
You know, Hey, I got pushed into the deep end when I was five and you swim or you die,
you know, it's that kind of thing.
Yeah.
It also implies that there's a bunch of other aliens on other planets or humans on other
planets that have gone through whatever we're going through right now.
Well, I mean, if God's lonely, it stands to reason that maybe he's lonely enough to make
more, you know?
And so he's just running this shell game of the universe all the time.
I would, I would suggest that maybe, uh, how is it possible that if the whole thing is
because God's lonely, why is he still lonely?
It's a, you know, it's escalation, you know, you, you get what you want and you find out
you just want more, you know, that's how it works.
God's not immune to that kind of thing.
It seems like there's a lot of people who've lived.
If you need some company, there's plenty of options.
Yeah.
You know, on the other hand, why does anybody die at all if he's so lonely?
Hmm.
Why not just make some people and keep them around and party?
Well, cause it's a test.
You gotta, you gotta be in the nursery.
Sure.
Gotta deal with the scorpion.
Right.
And then get out of the crib or something.
Yeah.
It almost kind of...
It's babyish.
It's a really babyish idea.
Well, I mean, really it's similar, it's more similar, I would say to the wheel of reincarnation
than anything else.
You know, that idea of like, you're constantly being tested through, throughout time until
you become a full being and then you ascend beyond it.
Yeah, but I don't know, I don't know how Alex's ideas about reincarnation work exactly.
I know that he thinks that you're literally your ancestors.
True.
And all that.
Right?
But I don't know how that works with ancestors that are concurrently alive.
Hmm, that's fair.
I don't, I don't, I don't really understand any of that.
And I don't know where you go in between or it doesn't really articulate a lot of that
stuff.
I mean, I don't know if it is like a situation where, where he believes in, in the reincarnative
tests.
Right.
It's not the good place, you know, that kind of thing.
Yeah.
It's weird.
That is weird.
Anyway.
Yeah.
I think this is dumb.
Yes.
So there is some news and Alex has been building up to this news, but I didn't realize it.
I have such a hard time remembering that this has got a news part on it.
Let me just show you the big news because if I covered this last hour, no one would
care.
So I built it up for an hour so that you would care.
And I'm not mad at you.
I'm the same way.
I didn't feel like he'd been building this up for an hour.
He told me all about the fourth dimension.
Yeah.
I felt like he got distracted about bullshit.
Yes.
He hasn't been teasing it.
No.
He's been ignoring it.
I know teasing Alex.
We've experienced that over and over again on this show.
It's something that he does.
Roll down your windows.
Yeah.
And I will need you to go stand over the highway with your bandung video.
Totally.
Yeah.
Exactly.
That's not the behavior he's been engaging in here.
If anything, he's escapist.
Yes.
So anyway, here's the big news.
Here it is.
But this just broke about an hour ago, or at least when I learned about it.
Major study by the University of Louisville.
Masks don't show any signs or any evidence that they helped stop the spread of COVID.
There it is.
Masks didn't slow COVID spread.
New study finds.
So this is a non peer reviewed study that came out.
And there's people who have some questions about the methodology of it.
And even under ideal circumstances and assuming that it goes through peer review and stands
up to scrutiny, it still isn't saying that masks aren't effective.
It was looking at larger populations and making estimates based on whether or not mask mandates
had an effect on a larger population.
That's a good study.
As opposed to on an individual level, whether or not masks had any effect in terms of actual
transmission.
Right.
There are plenty of studies that have actually looked at the question that Alex is pretending
this study answers.
And they have routinely shown that they do, they are effective.
Maybe not 100% effective, but they are effective in as much as it's something you can do.
Right.
As opposed to nothing.
Yeah.
Anyway.
So this is about something different than what he's saying it is.
And then secondarily, it's too early to really take it as solid, like a bedrock of reporting
because it's just sloppy.
Anyway.
If he says studies say, I always hear you say, he's referencing a non peer reviewed study.
Like that's the next sentence.
That's something that, it's weird.
You know, like when he says a study, it's some non peer reviewed thing that's on like
a preprint or something and maybe we'll get peer reviewed or maybe won't.
And then you'll just forget about it and you'll never know where it ends up.
Yeah.
It's the same thing with bills.
If you look back at these pastimes on his show and he actually talked about news more,
he would have these bills that he'd complain about and they are always things that ended
up dying in committee.
They're always bills that are like, can you believe someone's doing X, Y, or Z?
It's like, I can, but I also know that that is never going to even get a vote.
It's kind of the same thing.
He's preemptively making everything a huge deal.
And that's one of the reasons why I can't do the coverage of the police state three
that I wanted to do.
It's almost entirely about Patriot Act Two that doesn't happen.
Studies say next sentence, non peer reviewed, HB 2033 next sentence died in committee.
So we have one last clip here, and this is a good indication and example of why everything
in Alex's world is a trap.
Biden orders us Intel to analyze information on possible Wuhan lab leak.
That means cover it up, have his hand picked Stooges and now have a 90 day research, which
he ordered it by the way, killed, but now he can organize a new team to lie to everybody.
That's the translation there.
You don't need me to tell you that.
So if, if Biden doesn't investigate the theory that there was a lab origin to the coronavirus,
and it's a cover up, and if he does do an investigation of it, it's a cover up.
Yeah.
It doesn't matter.
The reality and what happens don't matter.
The spin is intact no matter what.
Yep.
The only way Alex would allow for something to be real would be if Trump himself was running
this commission, and the only conclusion that they even accepted from the beginning is that
not only was this a bioweapon release that came out of that lab, but she single handedly-
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
Yeah.
And it actually is a special kind of virus that actually, if you look at the molecules,
it spells out communism.
Yeah, exactly.
It's got Xi Jinping written on the virus, you know, like that level of bullshit.
Yeah, yeah, and that's why, you know, a lot of this stuff is just, it should be taken
seriously in as much as like there's dangerous consequences of it.
Sure, sure.
And it is illustrative of bad thought patterns, certainly.
But like when you hear stuff like that, like you should recognize that like this is how
he treats everything.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Everything is a trap.
Yep.
Doesn't matter.
It's pathetic.
Yeah.
I hate it.
Biden could do X, Biden could do Y, either way, the decision tree for what Alex is going
to say about it is the same.
Yeah, it's like preparing for a disaster.
You hate, you say that preparing for the disaster makes it happen, if it does happen, or if
it doesn't happen, you say that by revealing that the preparation for the disaster would
make it happen, you stopped the disaster.
Yeah, or talking about these bills, the die-in committee, or, you know, like, hey, you know,
the only reason to die-in committee is because we talked about it.
Yeah, totally.
It's just a trap.
Yeah, you create a universe where you always win, and then you never have to feel bad about
yourself, so why would you go back to the real universe, you know?
Yeah, sounds fun.
Anyway, Jordan, this has been fun.
We're back.
It's great to be back, Dan.
You know what?
We had such a good time.
I want you to play the birthday one again, too.
That one still tickles me.
Can't do it.
You have to wait until next time.
Not yet.
Okay.
So yeah, we'll be back, Jordan, on Monday, and I hope to have gotten a little bit more
through the Fauci emails by then, a little more time.
But until then, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yep, we're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledge underscore fight, and I go to bed Jordan.
We're also on Facebook.
If you'd like to tell us, if you could, please find a local charity or bail fund in your
area to help out people doing God's work right now.
Yep, we'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZXClark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I live next door to Satan in the sixth dimension.
Maybe fifth?
I'm not sure.
One above ours.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.