N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledgefight, knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying, we are the bad guys.
It's time to pray.
We are the sustainers.
Knowledgefight.
Dan and Jordan.
Riddle art, riddle art, riddle art.
Need money.
Andy and channels.
Stop it.
Andy.
It's time to pray.
Andy and channels.
You're on the air, thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a system color and I'm a huge fan.
I love your room.
Knowledgefight.
I love you.
Thank you.
And thank you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Tried, I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
Our couple dudes like to sit around and worship at the altar of Selene and talk a little bit
about Alex Jones.
Oh indeed we are, Dan.
Jordan.
Dan.
Quick question for ya.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
Speaking of Selene.
Ah.
It's a Selene oriented bright spot.
Alright.
So one of the things that I've enjoyed over the course of my time living with this animal
is that she finds new places that she likes to hang out, kind of periodically.
Uh huh, uh huh.
Well, you know, like she was on the couch for a while, that was like where I'd always
find her.
Basic.
Basic stuff.
Sometimes on my bed.
Of course.
Totally basic.
Normal.
Lately.
Uh huh.
She's found a new spot that she loves.
Oh, she's going extra.
Every single time I go to the bathroom, she's laying in the tub.
Ha ha ha!
Yes!
That's how you elevate the form of laying in a weird place, Dan.
Yeah, she's a bath cat now.
I like that.
Very excited.
It's gratifying to see sort of this commonality that we have, this bond.
You're both bath people.
Yeah.
I mean, whether, I doubt she wants as much water, if any.
I think none.
I think none would probably be the best, but yeah.
But it's still fun.
Yeah.
It's nice to share things with a cohabitant.
Sure.
What about you?
What's your bright spot?
My bright spot today is I had the chance to break into Robert Evans' home and steal his
manuscript for his book that is being released currently as a podcast or episodic thing,
and I got to read the whole thing, and it's very, very good.
Well, that's great.
I mean, I'm sure it'll probably be the final version that everybody else hears, unless
he takes my advice and rewrites it to be about Mako Sharkrampant.
Right.
Mako Sharkrampant must be represented.
I mean, if you don't have a Mark Richards reference in there, it's like, I guess you're
still writing, but I don't know why.
All art must contain sharkramping.
Exactly.
No, it's very, very good, and there are a few things he does to not glorify the violence
that is just so great.
It's called After the Revolution, and it's really, really good.
I recommend people read it.
It's coming out, like you said, as chapters in audio format and also in print.
And yeah, you can find that pretty easy.
Just go to his Twitter.
Yeah.
It's good.
So, Jordan, today we have an episode to go over, as promised.
Hey.
An episode.
Okay.
So I wanted to check out the day after the Fauci emails got released, because to me,
this seems like the biggest bread-making opportunity of Alex's recent career.
Shouldn't be hard.
There's so many emails, you could say whatever the fuck you want.
No one's going to read them.
No.
So I checked in on June 2nd, 2021, Blackjack.
Now all I'm doing is just screaming Blackjack whenever I realize I'm not going to catch
up.
You just say, bah.
All I've got is vocalizations.
I don't even have words.
You can't block the shot.
Doesn't work that way.
Okay, fine.
It's goal-tending.
Fine.
So yeah, I kind of thought the first was when the initial release came out, and I thought,
like the second, by then he's had the evening to come up with whatever bullshit he wants
to say.
He's got to be aligned.
He's got to run with it.
We're going to see how he responds.
Does he fail even at this?
We will see.
Okay.
But first, we've got to take a little moment to say thank you to some new wonks.
Oh, that's a great idea.
So first, Varnvlog.
Thank you so much.
You are now policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Varnvlog.
Thank you.
Next, use the daddy hole.
Thank you so much.
You are now policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you.
Next.
This is a real name, apparently, and I feel for this person.
Alex Jones, you are now policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, AJ is what we'll call you.
Next, Jordan and I, thank you so much, you are now policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
The sequel to The King and I I'm writing in my brain.
Next, I like this one.
Post-Tribulation Raptor, thank you so much, you are now policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
I like that one, too.
That's very good.
Thank you very much.
And Kit and Kiva, thank you so much, you are now policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Kit and Kiva.
Got a couple of technocrats in the mix, too.
First, Erica and Ian, thank you so much, you are now a technocrat and a loyal servant of
Queen Selene, may long she reign.
Thank you so much, you are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate, that's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why are you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank you so much, Erica, Ian, and the loyal servant of Queen Selene.
Yes, thank you very much.
I like how people are going with the loyal servant of Selene thing.
I feel like we could spiral this out into a cult a lot faster than I would have it,
but you know what the buttercream gang is to regular gangs?
We would create two regular cults.
Do you know what I'm saying?
I mean, this is already going to Selene's head.
She's taking over my tub.
That's true.
This is a mess.
Oh, man, I wonder what her first commandment's gonna be.
Thou shalt stay out of my tub.
Probably.
Thou shalt give me gravy.
I think it's probably actually the first commandment.
That would be a good one.
So, Jordan, now it has come time to check in with some birthday shout outs.
Okay.
Being born is a condition that leads to death.
You can say that life is a disease that ends in death.
If you're paying attention, that is a different drop.
This is a theme that Alex has been hitting lately.
Okay.
So Sam.
Happy birthday.
Yeah.
On the 5th, over the weekend, I had a birthday.
Thank you to Sam for having a birthday, and Matthew got in touch and wanted us to give
you a shout out.
Happy birthday, Sam.
Happy birthday.
And this one's really delayed.
This was back in May, I believe.
Steve.
Happy birthday belatedly, but again, life is death.
Life is death, so birthdays are non-birthdays, too, by that logic.
Absolutely.
Being born is a condition that leads to death.
You can say that life is a disease that ends in death.
Happy birthday.
So Jordan, I told you.
This is the day that Alex should be responding to the Fauci emails, and here's how he starts.
This is after he played a little bit of a goofy meme video about Scooby-Doo.
It's like Scooby-Doo, but they take the bags off the ghost's head, and it's Fauci and Bill
Gates.
It's a lot of fun.
He's promoting that.
The wheels have completely come off the COVID-19 operation.
The globalists are in deep trouble.
We put out that little dark comedy piece that you just saw, if you're a TV viewer, you just
heard if you're a radio listener, that spoof on Scooby-Doo, where Fauci and Gates get caught
running the pandemic, launching the operation, and so they go to prison for it.
And when we put that out a year ago, it was banned on Twitter and Facebook as fake news
when it was obviously a parody, but based on real things they'd done.
But boy, a year later, it's evergreen, isn't it?
Meaning it's more important now than when we first put it out.
Busted Scooby-Doo just solved the COVID-19 mystery.
It's got 200 plus thousand views at Banned.video.
I think it needs a lot more than that, doesn't it?
Wow.
In fact, let's make it the featured video at Banned.video.
Oh, boy.
This is important stuff.
I was a little confused.
I am very saddened by this.
Yes, I was a little underwhelmed by this viewing where we're going.
Not least of which because Scooby-Doo, right there.
Right there.
This old meme spoof is what we need to really push, we need to get this.
Was that in one of Fauci's emails?
Yes.
Oh, okay.
Well, then that makes sense.
The only thing that can bring us down is meme spoofs.
That makes sense.
Yeah, that works.
So I've often sort of wrestled with exactly what it is about Alex's show that I think
is bad.
And I mean, obviously the answer is there's a lot of them.
But one of the things that is sort of central that makes it bad is actually what he articulates
in this next clip.
Because this radio slash TV transmission is not just your regular entertainment.
It's not just your regular news program.
This is a participation sport.
And I think that censored report that you can find only at man.video needs to get shared,
don't you?
The Scooby-Doo.
But this is a participation sport.
That's kind of bad.
That's a bad way of looking at this stuff when you, you know, I mean, granted, if you
go to him under oath or in a deposition setting, he might say, I'm just talking about my feelings.
I don't know about sources.
I don't know about any of this stuff.
You'd have to, you'd have to listen to the whole thing.
You know, like, no, but when he's free and he's on air and he's, this is a, this is not
news.
This isn't entertainment.
This is a participation sport.
I'm trying to incite you to do something.
Yeah.
But that implies that information is a win or lose situation.
Not things are real or not.
You can win with information that's not real.
You know?
It's a participation sport.
It's not about finding what's real or what's true or what exists.
It's about winning.
Don't challenge your notions.
Come up with things that you can misrepresent in the real world that reinforce your predetermined
conclusions and play like hell out on the field to make sure everyone else is forced
to accept those things too.
No, and if you, if you change your mind, you're just giving up.
You are.
You can't give, you can't give up.
You can't be a quitter.
I've watched the challenge.
TJ Lavin doesn't like quitters.
He hates them.
He hates quitters.
You can't throw in the towel.
Uh huh.
On falsities.
Yeah.
So finally, Alex does end up getting to the Fauci emails and does not cover them that
much.
Let me just hit the headlines now.
In February of 2020 email that's public now, Fauci wrote face mask, not effective in keeping
out virus.
Either he wrote though that it has a good psychological effect and even publicly said,
it's about respect, living in fear, keeping everybody scared, total open and shut.
You should be able to use any of this in court.
There's cases all over the country where they're trying to make people still wear mask in schools
and businesses.
Boo.
So in the emails early on Fauci did say that there wasn't good reason for everyone to wear
masks.
That was because at the time they were unaware of a number of variables that existed with
COVID-19.
In an interview with CNN after the emails got released, Fauci was asked, quote, a lot
has transpired since then.
If you had to go back and do it all over again, would you tell her something different?
Do you regret that?
Here's his answer, which I think is great.
Yes.
Quote, let's get real here.
If you look at scientific information as it accumulates, what's going on in January and
February, what you know as a fact as data guides you, guides what you tell people and
your policies.
If March, April may occur, you accumulate a lot more information and you modify and
adjust your opinion and your recommendation based on the current science and current data.
So of course, if we knew back then that a substantial amount of transmission was asymptomatic
people, if we knew that the data showed that masks outside of a hospital setting actually
do work when we didn't know it, then if we realize all those things back then, of course,
you're asking a question, would you do something different if you knew what you knew now?
Of course people would have done that.
That's so obvious, right?
That's a great answer.
But do you know what that is, Dan?
That is losing the participation sport.
No wonder we never win because he's learning and growing and then regretting actions from
before.
What he should be saying is, no, I'm so stoked all those people died because of stuff.
I didn't know that I told them.
That's what I wanted.
I just think that there's something to delineate there though, that it's not, I don't think
it's regret necessarily.
No, I understand.
Maybe a hope that more awareness had or more information had been known at a certain time,
but based on the information that was available, that's what was the solidest recommendation.
Totally.
And then the, the thing about psychological stuff that Alex brings up, from best I can
tell, like that was something that was going on early on.
I don't remember this.
This was when they were talking about like, so when there, there wasn't an awareness of
the asymptomatic spread, right?
There was discussion of if you're sick, you should wear a mask, but if you're not sick,
you shouldn't, you don't really need to, but that puts a stigma on anybody wearing a mask
because then now if you wear a mask, everyone's going to assume you're sick.
And that could lead to people being disincentivized to wear masks when they should wear masks.
No, I mean, leper colonies worked well.
Everybody with leprosy was like, I'm definitely going to go right to this leper colony.
I don't want to hide it and keep people from knowing that I'm a leper because you know,
I'm treated so well in leper colonies.
Yeah.
The, the, the psychological benefit of widespread mask use is that you kind of make it easier
for people who do, are at a higher reason to wear a mask, according to the understanding
at that time, to follow public health advice.
And it works out better for everyone.
If you de-stigmatize these things and make it so everyone just, I don't know, I, I, I,
I have not read all of the Fauci emails.
I've read all of the ones that like get pointed out as like, ah, ha ha.
I've read a bunch of the ones that no one's pointing out.
And I see a nothing here.
And I think Alex does too, because here's what he does immediately instead of going
more into these emails.
And by the way, let me, let me hit the Fauci news here in a minute.
Let me, let me get back into all these COVID news next segment.
And let me just tell you some of the other stuff coming up today.
And then I'll go into each area of the news and tell you about the big guests we've got.
But, but, but, but first I went over to my parents on Memorial day, my dad grilled hamburgers
and my mom made baked beans and deviled eggs.
It was all delicious.
We swam in their swimming pool, myself and my children and family, my wife.
This is a great story.
And there's an old family friend that I've done some three years old, she's a great lady.
And she came over to the house and I've been friends with her son and, and, and her daughter
more years old again.
And so when she tells me a story, it's, it's accurate, of course, but I know her sister
very well.
And I know her daughter very well.
I guess I've gotten old, old enough now where, you know, my friends are 70 years old, but
she has a granddaughter or her sister does, uh, my friend has a granddaughter.
So this is fucking annoying.
I can't, I can't, I stopped it.
I can't listen.
I can't keep track of all the variables.
There's so many relatives.
There's so many people who don't factor into this story at all.
This is not the Bible.
I don't care who begat who get to the meat.
Well, you're, you're going to wish for more set up when he finally gets to the actual
story.
Okay.
Well, but I, I'm, so I'm friends with the family going way back and we vacation together.
We camp together.
So they're our best friends as a family and they live in Rockwall where I grew up.
That is her sister does, and they're evangelical Christians.
They're very nice people, very successful in business and one of the daughters, the
granddaughter was arguing with her mother about issues and they weren't even that big
an issue, but the mother said, Hey, why don't you go to your school counselor and ask them
about some of your boyfriend problems?
You know, we're not going to go pay for you to go to some counselor in town or whatever.
It's not that we're against the money.
It's just, Hey, go to the school counselor.
We pay property taxes for this.
So this is the same high school.
She's a freshman that I went to for the first few years of high school.
Well, I moved to Austin when I was 16 and she goes into the school in Rockwall and it's
a male counselor to a 13 year old girl.
And she told me the whole conversation because her, her, her niece repeated it to her.
She was shocked and he says to her, well, don't you think your problem is you're really
a man?
Oh boy.
So this is, this is where the story is.
I would like more preamble please.
Yeah, exactly.
I would definitely like more preamble.
I would like more preamble as opposed to this clearly not true story.
What are you talking about?
This is made up bullshit.
Oh man, it gets so much...
How is it that you can think it's a great idea to give that much of a preamble to a
story where all you want to be is just transphobic and mean?
Right.
You want to be a real dick and, you know, really try and demonize a certain population.
And in order to do that, the best you got is a third hand story maybe?
Maybe?
A fan?
You have something on the family tree that's a long branch away from you, that's for damn
sure.
Yeah.
I would believe that there's a possibility that somebody who is in a school counseling
position could, you know, if someone were to come to them with gender issues or something
could be empathetic and try and help them.
But I don't believe this.
She goes, excuse me?
He goes, yes, you're having problems with this boyfriend here at school because you're
really sexually confused.
And she goes, no.
He goes, yeah, I think you're a boy.
And she goes, are you joking?
He goes, no, I want to get you in touch with the group.
We need to put you in counseling.
They'll pay for it off site.
You really need this right now.
And she goes, no, I'm a girl.
He goes, no, you're not.
And she pulls her shirt forward, looks down and says, no, I'm a girl.
And says, I'm getting out of here.
What?
This is a fucking, this is that same meme where like the, this is a joke meme where
the soldiers and the professor's like, liberals are good.
And the soldiers like, I killed everybody in America's the best thing ever.
And the liberal professor cries and he's like, you're correct all the time.
This is a made up nonsense story conservatives tell themselves.
This is the boogeyman story.
This is bullshit.
I mean, quite frankly, if this happened the way Alex is describing it, she should own
that school.
That guy should be sued into oblivion.
This didn't happen because it's such an open and shut clear case of malfeasance by someone
who works at the school.
Like this would be very easy to get to the bottom of.
What a lying piece of shit.
And it gets worse.
Oh God.
But imagine she's not a troubled child, had a boyfriend issue.
When you're 13, you don't want to so much talk to your mom.
You know, who's the right wing, you know, Christian, but she's conservative too.
So talk to the counselor and you don't even expect in Rockwall, Texas, a suburb of Dallas
that you go there and a man is pushing on you.
It went on and on for like 30 minutes him saying you are by the end of it.
He's like, you are a man.
You are a man.
You are a me.
You need to go to this place.
What an odd counselor.
It's a whole agenda to destroy everybody, men, women, everybody.
It's sick.
It's how you depopulate.
This is outrageous.
Um, and the only real question that I have is how much of this is the story that someone
told him at a cookout and how much is just Alex is like, I'm going to punch this up a
little.
It was a half hour.
He was just yelling.
You're a man.
This is, this is, it's either that or like he's half remembering Austin Powers or something.
You're a man, baby.
That could be.
He might've taken some scissor and watch some old Mike Myers movies.
What kind of lunatic would believe this ever?
I imagine his audience.
You're a man.
It's a ridiculous story.
And then the, then the entire school got gathered around.
They had a big, uh, assembly.
The principal got up and he's like, everybody champ, you're a man.
You're a man.
It's all the schools are just out of control now.
They just brainwash all of these kids to scream, whatever the principal tells them to, as we
all know, children do.
Yeah.
Jesus.
I don't know.
I don't know if things have changed literally entirely since I was in school, but I do remember
the counselors, um, at every school that I went to, uh, being the sort of folks who just
listen and roll their eyes.
I don't kind of believe you, honestly.
The counselors are not really actively engaged in a lot.
I mean, I'm sure they mean well for the most part, you know, it's a thankless position
to be in school counselor, but, uh, yeah, I don't, I don't remember them being all that
much like working across purposes, trying to make conclusions for you.
I did find it weird when I was in third grade and the school counselor put all of us under
the sorting hat and determined whether we were man or woman.
That was a, that was an interesting day, but I guess that's part of the counselor's job
now.
So this story, I mean, first of all, a hundred percent, absolutely not true, but it leads
me to believe that Alex doesn't really want to talk about the voucher emails that much.
I think even he might think it's a little bit weak.
Well he read some of the email, well he didn't read them, his actual, uh, great grandfather's
nephew.
Uh, he knew him from back when they used to go hunting and fishing.
He knew his son too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now his son, you don't even want to know about his son.
That guy got caught, um, you know, with his, uh, diddler and the sheep on the other side
of the things.
But that's a different story.
We don't need to talk about that.
This story is about my great grandfather's nephew and how he had a son and his son was
married to this woman.
That was his first marriage and second marriage.
That was a disaster, but his first marriage, they got married again.
It's like Grover Cleveland, non non-consecutive marriages kind of thing.
Right?
Uh, I don't know how much longer I can keep going.
You're really letting me, you're leaving me out to dry here.
I was kind of hoping you would get into how the second marriage ended up falling apart
because the woman was in an importing exporting business that was actually getting antiques
and relics from foreign countries that were stolen and being, uh, trafficked.
They belong in a museum.
Right, right.
But she was only doing that because of her second cousin who was really in debt to the
mob.
Right, right, right, right.
What was this story about again?
Fauci's emails.
It was great.
It was a good story.
So, also not to do with Fauci's emails, but Alex has a new shirt that's really popular
and Alex is going to plug this and, uh, keep, pay attention to who this shirt is popular
with.
Okay.
I designed this shirt.
I'm just telling you.
Not, not bragging.
Uh, and I think it's one of my better designs.
Looks like an iron cross.
The concept team, Robert and others over there, and it's just incredible.
And I didn't intend for it to basically glow in the dark like a, like a tree frog can do
in the species, but it actually glows, uh, under these lights, under regular lights.
We've got a black shirt, a green shirt, and a cream shirt.
And on the back it says, save the frogs info wars.com.
And on the front of the shirt, it's got the same little symbol over your heart.
And I'm telling you, we've had these shirts in for almost a month.
We hadn't gone on sale until a big shipment came in cause you get a test shirt, see if
you approve it.
And as soon as I wore this out, everybody goes, what's that shirt?
I liked that shirt.
John the boom operator never talks about my shirts.
He goes, what's that shirt?
I love that shirt today.
He wants one.
My son, I was going to shoot an ad for these yesterday.
He works up here.
He comes in my office.
He's done this since he's been as big as I am for years.
He's 18 now, but by the time he was 15, he's as big as I am now.
He's huge.
Uh, he wears XXL and I see him walking around in my shirt and I said, Hey, you go to the
warehouse down the road, you get one.
You don't steal my shirt.
So I'm telling you, this shirt is so popular that everybody's going crazy over it.
I don't know why.
This shirt is so popular with my employee and my son, this is not a good market sample.
You've got some brand new market research people who work for me like this shirt.
Yeah.
People who work for me or I created, listen, we can't keep them in stock.
They're stealing them from us.
My son is stealing them, but they're stealing them.
So like it's just, they're going like hotcakes.
I wore them out and everybody, including the people who work for me only, and only the
people who work for me just love these shirts.
They're just amazing.
It's got a frog.
The end.
Yeah.
So I think that this was just also a nice way for Alex to weave into talking about some
more of this, you know, like the, you know, they're turning the frogs gay.
That's sort of his bread and butter when everybody loves to, it's the meme machine.
Don't make memes out of this stuff.
Memes, memes, memes.
And so I think he's trying to do a little bit more of that.
They were cloning animals and humans before I was born.
Hitler was cloning rabbits in 1944.
They've been splicing animals and humans.
It went on sale this week, salmon that weighed twice as much than our salmon that are part
insect and part asparagus for whatever reason.
Whoa.
So we get part asparagus salmon.
I tried that.
Yeah, Alex is talking about a new genetically modified salmon that's being bred by a company
called AquaBounty.
And it's actually now really new news, like 2015 they got approval to like create these
genetically modified salmon and it's just like it came to market, but like almost nobody
is buying it.
Okay.
So most people are like, I don't know.
All right.
I'm going to pitch them on a product real quick.
The quilted puffer upper.
All right.
It's a puffer fish that also uses a sponge.
Yeah.
So I'm going to say this right off the top here.
I'm not sure that I'm okay with what's going on here for ethical reasons, but Alex is still
way off on the details.
The fish don't grow to twice their normal weight.
They grow to their normal weight twice as fast.
This is achieved by splicing into Atlantic salmon, a gene from Pacific Chinook salmon
that make it so the fish produce growth hormone all year instead of part of the year.
Additionally, they added a gene from another fish, the ocean pout that essentially act
as a stabilizing thing for the hormone.
I've not been able to determine if the salmon is part asparagus, but I do know that if you
look into it, you can find some interesting recipes where salmon is paired with asparagus.
Okay.
All right.
Alex might have done that at this cookout of his over the weekend.
A little butter asparagus, put some salt and pepper on there.
Maybe braise it even.
That's not a bad idea.
I'm not sure I'm comfortable with this stuff entirely.
I'm not sure.
I'd have to think about it a little bit more, maybe have a conversation with somebody about
it.
Yeah.
And apparently most food retailers in the United States agree and they aren't selling
this salmon.
Sure.
This may be like one of those fun instances where I kind of agree with the conclusion
that Alex has that like maybe, maybe this isn't cool, but I think that the way that
he reaches his conclusion is childish, stupid, and a disservice to anyone taking these issues
seriously.
Yeah.
Ridiculous.
And what I'm really into that is as the science fiction fan, I was when I was eight years
old where I was like, yeah, fucking splice everything together.
Let's see what happens.
And now that I'm an adult, I can realize that maybe that kid shouldn't be in charge of gene
editing research.
Sure.
So maybe we have to hold off on it.
And one of the things that I am concerned about, obviously, and I don't, I don't know
enough, I tried to look into this a little bit, but I don't know if I could even find
a clear answer.
How much does that growing twice as fast, like affect the life experience of these salmon?
Sure.
You know, cause that seems like it could be hellish.
Yeah.
And I think that I don't know.
Or not.
I don't know.
Yeah.
And then you unpack that, you open it up to the whole like, well, you're going to eat
them anyway.
See, and then you get into, yeah, no.
It's a mess.
Yeah.
I don't want to wade into it with a hard take.
So Alex talks about these salmon and then he jumps into another story about catfish
in Japan.
And I did not actually pull this clip.
I regret to, one of my, one of my bungles.
But I want to talk about it a little bit because it is also fairly interesting.
But again, the thing that Alex is talking about is nonsense.
Is this like the Nigerian email scam?
He got catfished by somebody in Japan and he's creating a story about that?
I wish it was.
No, he's found an article in Japanese about a Japanese science research project and what
they did is they found a way to make catfish female.
Okay.
Essentially using something that they derive from soybeans.
Already mature catfish are turned into females or in the embryo, no matter what, it will
be a female catfish?
It is, I don't know if it's fully adults, but they are actual catfish.
Okay, gotcha.
This is another story about people trying to find ways to make fish bigger quicker.
Female catfish grow at much faster rates than males and in farming situations, often males
are just thrown out since raising them to the point where they can be used for marketable
product would cost more than would be brought in.
Researchers in Japan recently found that if they kept the fish in a tank that was full
of water with different things dissolved in it, they could create a more female dense
population.
The use of actual female hormones is not allowed for animals being raised for human consumption.
So the researchers explored isoflavone, which is a chemical that's found in soybeans.
They isolated a compound called genistein, and this is derived from isoflavone, and they
found that if you had a tank of water with 400 micrograms per liter, this resulted in
a tank of catfish that were 100% female.
Wow!
That's wild!
This is interesting, and it's obviously of concern to people who raise fish for a living,
but I think that pretending there's a one-to-one parallel between humans and catfish is a little
bit suspect, which is what Alex is doing.
So also, even if the catfish and human were biologically similar to the point where it
was relevant, this would still seem to suggest that humans would need to swim around in and
breathe water full of isoflavone to have this kind of effect happen.
It's nonsense.
This is, as all too often is the case, it's just an attempt by Alex to take a headline
misrepresented and use it as a weapon against trans people.
He's trying to make the fact of trans people's existence into some kind of a conspiracy,
because this is what they're doing with soy, and all that, and it's like, ugh, I don't
know about this.
This is bad.
That's, ugh, I don't want to, I want a big no on that one.
Yeah, and it's interesting research from what I was able to find, and I don't think it applies
to humans, but Alex tries to get a little bit closer by taking another soy-related story,
this time about monkeys.
They also tested this on monkeys, three different species, and found that they make the same
weird smiling face, they're aggressive and hateful loners, very unsuccessful, and tend
to try to then kill females.
Think I'm joking?
Long-term soy consumption makes monkeys aggressive loners, shocking study with possible human
implications, there they are.
So not surprisingly, Alex has some details on this study wrong, it was done, also this
study is from 2004.
The headline he's reading is from a website called herculeanstrength.com.
Okay, well I'm already out.
Already out.
Seems to be where he's pulling this from.
I'm sorry, a men's rights activist's name is kicking me out.
Their tagline is, become a demigod.
There we go, that's all I needed to hear.
This is a bodybuilding site that's very into testosterone, and from what I can tell they
have a pretty anti-soy editorial position.
Interestingly, they also posted an article about that catfish study, so maybe Alex just
hangs out on bodybuilding sites to get his health news.
That actually does make sense.
Yeah.
So this is actually an interesting comparative study, but here are some of the things Alex
fucked up.
One, there wasn't three species of monkeys, there were three groups, two experimental
and one control group, but they were all male macaque monkeys.
Two, all the stuff about the weird faces is made up.
I think Alex is just taking that from pictures of the macaques that were on the bodybuilding
website.
Right.
They just put random pictures of monkeys.
So they had weird faces and he was like, they all make weird faces.
They were not pictures from the stuff.
Right, right, right, right.
Of course.
Alex probably just thinks that monkeys look like demons or something.
They were fucking Getty Images, yeah.
Three, I have no idea how Alex is gauging whether or not these monkeys were successful,
regardless of their soil intake.
I don't know what the standard for that is.
I forgot about the successful being part of it.
Or, I don't see anything in there about killing females.
The study itself did find that there appeared to be behavioral changes in macaques based
on the amount of soy that they were eating in their diet.
Alex is focusing on the aggressive tendencies, but the study actually found that the opposite
was more often the case.
There was a 67% increase in aggressive behaviors, but a 203% increase in submissive ones.
This is an element of the study that Alex is choosing to ignore because he's just going
a different direction with it.
The stuff about increased solitary behavior does match up with some of the stuff found
in the study.
Like, approximately there was a 30% increase in time spent alone for the group that had
a higher soy intake diet.
One important point to bring up here, though, is that there was almost no difference found
between the control group and the low isoflavin diet group.
So there were two experimental groups, one low and one high, and the control group and
the low group were almost not, you couldn't tell the difference.
In order for humans to mimic the levels of isoflavin consumption in the high diet group
that they were getting for 15 months straight, it would be next to impossible for humans
to do.
It would be the equivalent of humans swimming around in isoflavin saturated water and breathing
it in our little gills.
You're not going to be able to get a diet that controlled to get any of the kind of
marginal effects that were found.
It's interesting, though, still, whatever they're looking at.
I don't know how conclusive it is, and I certainly don't know if it applies to humans.
Yeah, I mean, to a certain extent, that does also have the flavor of a study that's like
a non-consensually changing diet of animals causes different behaviors.
You know, like, no, I get it, but I don't, I mean, okay.
Sure.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
I found it really interesting that instead of really getting into the Fauci stuff, Alex
instead goes on all these weird sort of animal genetics news items that some are current
and some are old, and they're all bullshit.
I mean, aside from the transphobia, that's more fun, I suppose, because the emails, talking
about emails is still boring, and we're already, we're still rolling from Hillary's emails.
You've got a high bar with Hillary's emails.
Yeah, we're not going to beat Hillary's emails.
I don't think you're going to find anything.
You're not going to be able to Podesta this.
Right.
You're not going to be able to pizza gate it.
You need a pizza gate if you want emails to be exciting, and there's no pizza gate here.
Yeah.
There's just like, I don't know, maybe we don't need masks.
The conspiracy theorist community, I think, has burned out the pleasure centers of their
brain that come from this because they went too hard on pizza gate.
Yeah, totally.
Oh, well.
So, one of the things that we know from listening to various periods of Alex's career is that
what's the summer for?
Rage.
Let's hit some of these headlines right now.
We'll get more into this after I cover the race war they're trying to trigger this summer.
They got a good chance of doing it.
We got to stop it.
That's coming up the first 30 minutes of the next hour.
We got a summer of race war rage.
Oh, boy.
Mm-hmm.
For the 27th consecutive year this summer, coming to every city near you, a race war
summer of rage.
It wasn't always a race war, though.
No, that's true.
There was just like financial collapse or like there was something.
Summer of rage 27, the race war time.
Well, I think the last like five or six have probably all been race war related in his
mind, but yeah, it used to be just kind of like it could be a number of different things
and now it just feels sort of one note.
It's just race war.
Yeah.
Anyway, Alex gets to talking about Fauci, but not about the emails.
Instead, he talks about how he thinks there's a pretty good chance that Fauci is going to
get hung.
That's fast.
I think when I was listening to this, I feel like this clip is really a good isolation
of why people listen to this show.
This satisfies some emotional needs that these listeners have.
All right.
Under the Nuremberg Code, if you're tried and convicted, you get walked up to the gallows
pole because the time is coming when people that do this stuff will be punished, not by
me, but by justice through the courts, and I told you it would come a year ago and you
see it starting, don't you?
The snowball's too big, too much energy.
You killed too many people, Fauci Gates.
You will pay.
I see it in the stars.
I see it in the cards.
I see it in the tea leaves.
I see it in the bones, in the rooms, my dear, your fall, your destruction.
Violence is right.
It is coming.
I think people just have some sort of a gratification of hearing someone say that violence is coming
to the people that they've been trained not to like.
Yeah, it seems like it.
That's very televangy, televangelisty to a realty.
Also so false.
Yeah.
It was very, very fake.
At least Sinner in the Hands of an Angry God felt genuine.
Yeah.
Alex knows he doesn't have to try.
No.
So one of the things that I think is always tough to suss out is like, who's on what side?
We've had a lot of changes over the years.
Yeah.
So I regret to inform you.
Is Bill Maher still on the side of secret patriots?
No, he had a one day redemption where he was a secret Tucker, and now he's back to being
evil.
Oh man, I hate it when shows do that.
Listen, I don't want to talk about celebs.
Okay.
I want to talk about geopolitics.
Yeah.
Okay.
Now we know that Alex thinks the literal devil is behind his enemies.
Yes.
So that must mean that all of the people who are on one team, they're with the devil.
Right.
And then the people are on the other team conceivably with God.
Yeah.
They try and avoid moral gray area.
It's very complicated.
Certainly.
Yeah.
And we did have the UK was looking good when Brexit was going through, but apparently Boris
Johnson is a traitor.
Sure.
Yes, there was that.
And so now they're up in the air.
Yeah.
It's unclear where the UK is going to fall.
Right.
So we should not forget that the queen hit the dictator button.
I forgot about that.
Like a year ago.
There's so many spinning plates these days.
So many spinning plates.
Yeah.
The queen is a secret Patriot.
I forgot about that.
I would like to, I would like to know if the Pope is still in jail.
I need to know, did he, did he change his ways?
You know, or has, is the cause the Pope hasn't said like new things that are more conservative
than they were before.
So is the fake Pope even a, like an actual clone who's just unable to break the programming
of being the same old Pope?
I need to know this.
I don't know.
We'd have to ask Steve.
Anyway, here are the teams.
We have a, we have a layout of who's, who's good, who's bad.
And boy, it's not surprising because it's the Islamics with communist China, the EU,
Hollywood, the blue cities, the blue states, the UN all against America and Russia.
Wow.
And that means the American people and the Russian people and the Brazilian people.
Okay.
So you got Brazil in there.
Wow.
It's Russia, the United States and Brazil, Jesus Christ versus everybody.
And a verse, a lot of people inside the United States, I would say about half the country
at least.
I would say that it doesn't get more above the left, right paradigm than that.
Yes.
That's about the most, uh, here's, here we, here's what we got going on.
Okay.
We've got, uh, we've got everybody and then we've got Russia, United States and Brazil.
Definitely not the new axis of evil.
That would be a crazy thing for someone to say that these countries are very similar
right now to Italy, Germany.
Okay.
Yeah.
I, I find, I find it interesting.
I mean, not, not the sort of other countries that Alex feels kinship with.
Sure.
That doesn't surprise me at all.
No, of course not.
Those are, those are like his guys, Putin and Bolsonaro dictators, but I find it interesting
the way he, it's the rest of this is so stateless.
It has to do with the blue cities, the blue States, Hollywood, and like so, so much of
it is like half of this country is going to have to go down if you know, we're gonna be
able to make this the America make it America again.
Yeah.
I mean, it's honestly, I, I serious question, uh, that, I mean, obviously you can't answer,
but if MBS sent Alex like a letter that was just like, Hey, I'm a secret Christian.
We're not going to pro persecute Christians in Saudi Arabia anymore.
He would totally be like, I love MBS now.
Right?
Yes.
He would have to.
He loves what MBS does.
He did killing Khashoggi, I think that even if MBS didn't go that far, I think that he
just made an overture and said, you're right about the globalists totally.
I will.
I will not join your religion, but I will follow you against the demonic globalists
or whatever.
Yeah.
Alex would be like, yeah, Saudi is pretty cool.
I, you know what?
I heard a lot of stuff about, uh, about them in the past and it turns out that was all
a, that was a psy-op, you know, I didn't like Putin before, but now, you know, I've
seen that Putin is a good Christian.
I might've spent a long time back in 2003 talking about every day about how evil Putin
was and never taken back any of those comments or suggested that what I said was not true.
Psy-op.
Just don't care.
So, uh, Alex spends an entire segment talking about China and it's exhausting because it's
all kind of the stuff that we've gone over in the past.
Yeah.
And his grievances about Chiang Kai-Shek.
Right, right.
Yes, of course.
And what have you.
Of course.
Uh, and this is how it ends.
Apparently China has double-crossed the globalists.
Okay.
And China double-crossed the globalists on multiple fronts.
They're not doing the one-child policy.
They're, they're, they're, they're expanding their military, not just dominating economic
systems and Biden can't serve them enough when he announces, Hey, we won't build any
of our own batteries.
We'll only buy it from China.
We won't let Americans mine and I'll shut it.
And now Biden announced a plan to shut down 30 plus other big pipelines, giving the States
the power to shut down existing pipelines and to give Whitmer the power to violate a
U S treaty and shut off the main pipeline to the Midwest out of Canada.
I mean, we are under child calm attack.
So of course he's running to Tulsa a hundred years ago.
People killed each other.
Hundreds dead.
Let's have a race war.
How obvious is this?
I'm going to go to break.
We're going to come back.
Don't forget.
We're extending the store, free shipping and double Patriot points until Sunday, DNA force
plus.
Yeah.
So apparently Alex is pretty mad about Biden going to Tulsa to celebrate or pay respects
to the anniversary of the Tulsa massacre.
Yeah.
Weird.
I'm surprised that Alex would not want to to have that talked about or even mentioned
or recognized or even have it exist within the records.
Now you know, what's weird.
Last year, Trump scheduled a campaign rally in Tulsa on June 19th, which understandably
seemed a little not great because June 19th is Juneteenth, which is the celebration of
the ending of slavery in Texas, which is the last state where it was still taking place.
Now Tulsa is the site of the Tulsa massacre, which occurred on May 31st and June 1st in
1921 when mobs of white people destroyed the Greenwood district in Tulsa, the largest concentration
of black wealth in the United States.
So obviously the combination of Trump going to Tulsa on June 19th seemed like a little
bit of a eh.
And not just mobs of white people, organized mobs of white people with the fucking military
on their side.
So yeah.
So Trump ended up rescheduling that event after some very understandable backlash, but
he did say in a subsequent interview, quote, I did something good.
I made Juneteenth very famous.
It's actually an important event, an important time, but nobody had ever heard of it.
Wow.
Ah, man.
Alex didn't have any problem with any of that, but for Biden to visit the Greenwood district
and pay homage to the Tulsa massacre, that's a huge problem apparently because I guess,
I don't know.
I mean, I think one of the main reasons that it is such a huge problem for conservatives
and why they absolutely do not want to discuss it whatsoever is because it is the marriage
of two things that they love the most at cross purposes, which is white people and wealth.
And they can't say that it's okay for the wealth to be wiped out without saying that
it's their giant fucking racists.
And they can't say that it's not okay for white people to murder en masse because they're
giant fucking racists.
So they're just trapped in this space of like, you can't earn your way out of racism in America.
That's what they're saying.
And that's their message is always, you're like, no, you can pull yourself up by your
bootstraps.
No, the real message is if you do that, you will be murdered and slapped down again because
that's what they need.
And one of the other things too, not to, not to totally jump off subject, but when, when
he was talking about these pipelines and stuff, shouldn't his politics be that States can
opt out of pipelines?
Why is he mad that Biden is saying that States can not participate in pipelines?
I don't know.
There's just no, there's just nothing.
There's just nothing.
I don't understand how that wouldn't be like exactly what he would, like, if Trump did
that, he'd be like, fuck yeah, everybody needs to have the power in the States.
So there's a big news breaking in the middle of the show.
And that is that someone in China made a comment, watch out.
So when you see the communist Chinese come out in their official publication and say,
if you investigate the lab, we're going to nuke you.
That's what they said today.
And China paid American media outlets millions to publish propaganda.
We're going to list those groups for you when we come back, who the traders are.
I definitely don't like the idea of someone airing a list of traders on their show, especially
Alex, someone who has a participation sports philosophy towards his show historically listing
traders is usually a good idea.
It's not.
So this story about China paying for articles and some Western outlets, that's not news.
That's an old story about an English language paper in China controlled by the government
called China daily.
They paid to have articles placed in outlets, but all of those would have had to have an
alert informing readers that this is paid content.
I don't like it, but it's definitely not the smoking gun and like huge deal that Alex is
making it out to be sure.
As for the nuclear war thing, Alex is lying.
It's true that there's a Newsweek headline that says, quote, China state media says country
must prepare for nuclear war with us after Biden asks for COVID probe.
But that's not a statement that's meant to convey a causal relationship between the two
things, which is what Alex is reporting.
Okay.
He's saying that the Chinese government has said that they'll nuke us if we investigate
the lab, but that's not what this article is saying at all.
And this article is his primary source.
Right, right, right.
The article is about comments made by Hu Zhijin, the editor of the global times.
The comments had to do with how there was growing tensions in the US-China relations
and that, quote, China sees much of America's actions and comments to be an encroachment
on its sovereignty.
Hu wrote an op-ed that essentially boiled down to this, quote, the number of China's
nuclear warheads must reach the quantity that makes US elites shiver should they entertain
the idea of engaging in a military confrontation with China.
The comments were an escalation and an arms race kind of thing that I think sucks, but
they also weren't comments that were being made as a threat if we investigate the lab
theory.
Jesus.
Yeah, that's nonsense.
But it's right in line with Alex's narratives that he's been building, so that's going to
take precedence over the reality of the situation that, honestly, we should not be thrilled
about.
I mean, wild, wild to have the headline be, Chinese man says Reagan had a point.
You know, like, I don't understand, yeah, of course.
Historically, you should have more nuclear weapons to keep the United States from invading
you.
I don't want people to have any, I don't want nuclear weapons at all.
No.
Absolutely not.
Yeah, it does make sense for a power in the context of, like, heightening tensions to
be like, we should make it so no one will attack us because it looks like someone might
attack us.
America's on their fucking bullshit again.
Yeah, everybody's pumping out Iraq war propaganda about the, oh, Jesus.
I understand that.
I would prefer we take another direction with it and de-escalate things on a larger scale,
but I get that thinking, and that's the thinking that is behind that comment.
Not that if you look into the lab, we'll nuke you.
Yeah, no, no, no, no.
It's so ridiculous.
Yeah, no, it's global realpolitik that, again, Kissinger was like, we gotta have this.
And this, too, is why listening to Alex is kind of a dead end, because there is a reality
that you should be aware of in this Newsweek story that is, yeah, these kinds of conversations
are happening.
Some people are making comments, be it in official outlets or in op-eds that are like,
we should bulk up our defenses to make sure that no one attacks us.
That's fucked up.
It doesn't necessarily reflect a government policy, but it is something that is worthwhile.
If you listen to Alex, the way that this story is going to be presented to you is, the Chinese
are so afraid of us investigating the Wuhan lab that they will nuke us if we do it.
And that is a dead end, because what do you do with that information?
It's not true.
It's ridiculous.
No, it's just you saying, see, they're so overreacting to it, it's obviously true.
He's not asking a question, he's not saying anything.
What he's really doing is, hey, they wouldn't act like this if they weren't the cause of
the Wuhan lab leak.
The end.
You know?
Basically.
It's proof.
Yep.
So on this episode, Alex is really obsessed with an interview that Judge Joe Brown did,
and I don't care.
No, no, no, you cannot.
The only point of it is that Judge Joe Brown thinks that Biden's a racist, and, all right,
Joe Brown.
Yeah.
I used to watch Joe Brown a lot.
Did you?
Judge Joe Brown?
Yeah.
And me and my friends would sit around, get high, watch judge shows, and I love Joe Brown
because he always looked like he just got up from a nap, because he was so annoyed by
everybody in the courtroom.
He was very annoyed by everyone.
It's like, you mean to tell me?
I liked his demeanor quite a bit.
Okay, so, but here's my, okay, so Judge Joe Brown says that Biden's a racist.
Right.
If Judge Judy comes out and says Biden's not a racist, what show do they go on?
We got to go to Judge Mills Lane, obviously.
My bad, my bad.
That was too obvious.
And settle this in a celebrity death match.
Yeah, I mean, look, no disrespect to Judge Joe Brown.
He is a judge and all, but I think when it comes to-
Is he a real judge or is he-
I don't think you can be on those shows and not be a real judge.
I think you have to be a judge.
I don't know if that's true.
That might not be true.
I feel like that is definitely not true.
Judge Judy is a judge.
She is a judge.
Right.
Ooh.
Judge Mathis is a judge.
Maybe Judge Joe Brown is a real judge.
I think he is.
How do you get to be a judge and then get on TV?
We should explore this more, but we don't-
That sounds really fucked up to me now that I think about it.
So they've been practicing judges on the bench for a long time and then they get a TV show?
That seems wrong.
It seems strange, but it also is a good career path.
Well, you're not wrong.
Okay.
Judge Joe Brown.
Is he-
Real judge?
Question mark.
Judge Joe Brown is a former American lawyer and television personality.
Aha.
Oh, he is a former Shelby County, Tennessee criminal court judge and a former arbiter
of the arbitration based reality show Judge Joe Brown.
Okay.
So yeah, he was formerly a judge in Tennessee.
All right.
Okay.
Yeah.
I would imagine that if you're ever on one of those shows, you're not an active judge.
I think that's where I got confused.
You're not moonlighting.
I think there's a part of me that like when I filled out my Chicago ballot and I was voting
for judges, then that connected to my mind, well, obviously I was voting for Judge Mathis
or Joe Brown at some point.
No, I think it's a good sort of late career move if you're someone who has some charisma
and can make court hearings fun.
Absolutely.
Yeah, we will need a judge to settle this next issue.
Okay.
Alex is escalating this whole thing about Fauci getting hung.
And now it's going to happen in public.
That's not good.
Fauci and Bill Gates are being destroyed as we speak.
I told you months ago, they will be politically annihilated bare minimum.
And I, I just go with my gut and the analysis, I think they're going to go to prison.
I think if we work hard, we expose them and we're diligent, we pray, I believe they'll
be convicted and that someday I believe we'll watch them both hung in public.
I really do.
They launched this attack with communist China.
You know, you think that's strong rhetoric and it's not.
Communist China just threatened to nuke us if we keep investigating the Wuhan lab.
They did this on purpose with the UN.
See?
Wow.
See how that information ends up being used?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's silly.
Does everybody know that, that like now in the, in the modern world when, when they see
like public hangings in a TV show or in a movie or in real life, those are the bad guys.
The good guys are never doing public hangings.
Hmm.
Yeah.
It seems rare.
That's fucked up.
Yeah.
I mean, look, I, I, I, I, I struggle with this because on the one hand, if anything
that Alex was saying were true, these people are enemies of humanity.
That is true.
No, you're not wrong.
You're not wrong.
That's true.
I mean, if they are wiping out millions of people, that is true.
I do think that you should probably, you know, that's a hangable offense.
I think so.
Sure.
I think that there's a narrow area where death penalties might be, maybe we go ahead and...
Genociders can get the death penalty.
I'm fine with that.
I feel like that's inarguable as a, as a relatively fair solution.
Sure.
I don't know about the public spectacle part.
I, oh, I, I certainly don't think that would be healthy.
Yeah.
But I also, but if you, but if you didn't do that, everyone would come up with conspiracies
about how it didn't really happen.
They're going to come up with, JFK is going to, JFK is still alive, according to some
people.
His head blew up on TV.
Look, we're not going to be able to negotiate this and thankfully we don't have to.
That's a good point.
We don't have to because Alex has indicated that he's okay with a lesser punishment.
Okay, good.
You have to say it.
I don't want any harm against Bill Gates or Fauci.
That could turn them into heroes.
That could turn them into martyrs.
No vigilante violence.
I want them arrested.
I want their records brought out.
I want public trial and that I want a jury to find them guilty because the evidence is
overwhelming.
And I will take life in prison.
They are incredible villains.
And so I don't think execution would turn them into victims, but maybe let them spend
the rest of their miserable lives on public display.
Like you put animals in a cage, you want us to live in a cage.
How about we throw Joe Biden in there with them?
All right, man.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
What a gracious guy though.
He's offering life in prison.
It is nice to, to say, look, look, look, this requires a public hanging.
God's justice demands a public hanging, but we will keep you in a dog cage for the rest
of your life and have people walk by and spit on you.
Yes.
Yeah.
That is what happens when you release plagues.
We put you in a box.
Yeah, that's about right.
So Alex has the Hodge twins on who are a couple of twins as their name suggests.
Yeah.
They are conservatives.
Is Judge John Hodge been a judge?
Nevermind.
That was a joke.
It used to be.
So Hodge twins, they have some bad opinions and here's one of them.
Black people are so upset about Christopher Columbus.
You don't want to celebrate that, but why y'all want to celebrate something that happened
over a hundred years ago.
They're talking about the, uh, the Tulsa massacre.
Yeah.
The only reason why they want to celebrate these things is because they're asking for
something and they think Joe Biden and the Democrats and people on the left is actually
going to give them reparations or restitution.
They're not going to see any, any of that.
They have not till this day, black folks, black liberals have woken up and realize what
these people are doing to them.
They're using them mentally enslaving them or vote.
That's the only reason why Joe Biden's there.
Yeah.
They're actually asking for reparations for what happened in Tulsa.
There's only like two survivors left from that.
Yeah.
And I say fine.
Give them, I mean, sure.
The state or somebody should try to help them out.
But the point is, is he's there to open old wounds and distract from what he's doing to
all Americans shutting down the pipelines.
Now Trump, Trump wasn't opening up old wounds last year.
No, no, no, no.
He wasn't doing that.
I don't know.
That'd be weird this time.
Joe Biden always opens up old wounds.
I think that it's horseshit that Alex is saying like, yeah, of course.
Give them repar...
Why?
Why Alex?
Yeah.
You don't believe that for a second.
No.
You're saying that because you know that like saying don't, it would sound like shit.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Now.
A baseball should go whizzing right by his head just as a like warning shot.
Do it again, man.
Do it again.
Yeah.
Claim that you're fine with giving some people reparations again.
Feel that break through the air.
Now one of the reasons that the Tulsa massacre in particular is something that is brought
up in the conversation about reparations is because it was not just an attack on people.
It was an attack on black wealth.
Exactly.
And you know, one of the reasons that some of these issues have rippled through our country's
history so resonantly is because of the exclusion of nonwhite people from participation in the
market.
Yeah.
Exactly.
And this is a, that was a giant attack on exactly that.
Yeah.
And I think pretending that you don't understand that is a little bit silly and I think if
you're a commentator then you're going to come around and say that people only remember
that event because they want something.
Yeah.
They want to guilt Biden into giving them something.
I think you're a piece of shit.
I think that's a shitty opinion.
And that, that like idea of Alex even being like, well, you know, there's two survivors,
so yeah, the government should help them out or something like that.
That's absolutely missing the point of wiping out generational wealth.
You did, there are not two survivors of that massacre.
There are countless survivors of that massacre.
Yeah.
And that's, that's the point.
That is a point.
Yeah.
Well not, yeah, not the point.
Apologies.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's the point that he's avoiding.
Yes.
That's what he's basically and kind of like detracting from is what I was trying to say.
While at the same time confusingly saying that it's okay to give something to those
two people.
Right.
Which again, I would just ask if I were, anyway, if I were in a position that these hodge twins
are in, I would just be like, why?
Yeah.
Please say why.
Tell me why these two are fine.
That's okay and it's not okay in other circumstances.
Absolutely.
So, so these people, these people had something taken from them.
Right, right.
And so they deserve recompense in some form.
Correct.
Okay.
Let's take this a step further.
I don't understand.
There are more steps?
Let's not.
Hmm.
So there's been a lot of talk about how there's a coming indictment for Trump.
Sure.
Trump's going down.
Roger Stone's been playing into this quite a bit.
Alex has been warning people that he's going down on the 4th of July.
No, I thought he was going to be reinstated.
No, no, no.
That's the, maybe who knows.
Maybe they'll indict him and magically like a, like a Phoenix rising from the ashes who
will become president.
That could be.
Maybe.
Maybe the Democrats just want a third go at impeachment, you know, like they fucked up
the first two real bad.
Third tries a charm.
However, the Hodge twins, they do not think that this is real and they think it's a distraction.
I don't, I don't think they're going to get an indictment on him.
I mean, he's the most vetted president we've ever had.
Everybody's investigated this man.
They have found nothing.
I'd be shocked if they found anything.
Yeah.
I think more than anything, Alex, it's just a distraction because they're doing the audits
in Arizona, in Nevada.
That's what they're really doing.
It's just a distraction.
What Biden's doing in Tulsa.
I mean, everybody on mainstream media on the left is just lost their minds talking about
when they started actually auditing the results.
I'm like, I don't understand why they will be so upset unless they trying to hide something.
If you're so sure if Biden won that election, honestly, why don't you let everybody go in
audit the results and just show and tell everybody that's on the right, how stupid and naive
they are.
I mean, you have a goal and opportunity to show everybody in America how lost Trump supporters
are.
Yeah.
I don't be willing to show that, Alex.
Look at the results.
He won here.
He won here, but they don't want to do that.
They don't even want to investigate the results or audit because they're scared what's going
to be uncovered.
I mean, that's just a dumb argument and you can, you can take the exact idea and just
place it wherever you want with the story that you've written for yourself.
You know, a good example of this, whether or not there's any truth to it is, Oh, why,
why won't Trump release all of his financial information if he's, Oh, he has to be afraid
of what's in there.
And that's a story that you can write for yourself.
It may be more likely than this whole election was a fraud or whatever, but it's, you know,
pretending that, you know, what would be found if someone looked at something and that's
why they're not looking at it.
Sure.
Is just a dishonest, uh, kind of game.
Yeah.
I mean, the thing about that though, is it's eminently reasonable from what we do know
is that if you really went through just about any billionaires, no, any billionaires finances
sooner or later, you would find some crime.
I understand that.
Not like, not like maybe not a big crime, maybe not nothing, but you'd be like, there's
no way that you can get to be a billionaire without something along the way being fucked
up.
Yeah, I understand that and I think that you could make an argument for what you might
expect to find, but I don't think that you could argue definitively in the way that they're
arguing definitively.
Sure.
This is what you would find.
You would find that Trump won the election.
And what we know from history about elections though is, especially this one, it is really
hard to cheat the entire country.
Yeah.
Really tough.
Maybe impossible.
Yeah.
Also this same pattern of why won't you let everyone investigate this?
You must be afraid of what's underneath.
Sure.
If you were just to apply that to Trump, they'd be like, no, no, no, he can't have it because
XYZ.
Exactly.
There'd be a hundred reasons why this is not the same thing.
Yeah.
Who cares?
And your, your bullshit argument of like, they have a real opportunity to make conservatives
look stupid here.
And you're like, no, get the fuck out of here.
That's trolling.
Yeah.
Shut the fuck up.
You dick.
Speaking of trolling.
I agree.
And I don't go off color.
I go off people, but wouldn't Allen West make a great governor of Texas?
Oh, hell yeah.
Yeesh.
Oh my God.
Just after this episode was broadcast, Allen West resigned as the chair of the Texas GOP.
It was probably at least partially due to fallout from him attending and speaking at
that QAnon conference last week, where Mike Flynn said that there's no reason that what
happened in Myanmar shouldn't happen here.
He didn't serve for chair as long, uh, for a long time.
Uh, and in his time in that position, he changed the GOP of Texas's slogan to we are the storm,
which is about as overt a reference to QAnon as you can imagine.
Wow.
Allen West is a terrible, terrible choice for a leader, but given Alex's embrace of
Marjorie Taylor Greene lately, it seems like he's kind of seeing the political utility
of seeing these folks as like a new tea party.
I think that you might, uh, you might expect to see more of that.
50, 50 shot Cornel West could become governor of Texas by accident.
Like that is honestly, they don't know.
They don't know.
So Alex wants, uh, Trump to get back on social media and that's something that they spend
a good bit of time talking about.
Everything was better for us when people were constantly talking about Trump.
And that's the same argument that they make about the media, uh, saying like Trump is
going to get indicted.
They're like, Trump is driving ratings.
He's good for ratings.
So they talk about Trump.
It's like, you know, you're doing the same thing, right?
You know?
Yeah.
So anyway, they want him to get back on social media and the Hodge twins have a interesting
theory as to why that hasn't happened yet.
He doesn't even have social media.
He has 2 million followers on gab.
If he joined gab tomorrow and get 10 million, the site works good.
They've gotten the bugs out.
We need to get a message to Trump.
I don't have any stock in gab.
I have a site on gab, hundreds of thousands of followers, but, but, but he's deplatformed.
He needs to get on these other platforms.
Now he needs to be on rumble.
He needs to be on gab.
He needs to be out there instead of, I know for a fact there are people around him that
are quietly sabotaging him.
Right.
Yeah.
And big techs behind it.
That's why they banned him from every social media platform that's out there because they
don't want him to be able to communicate with other consumers and other like-minded Americans.
Yeah.
Maybe he's, uh, I thought he had some kind of social media platform in the works.
Maybe that's what he's waiting to let everybody see and not somebody else's platform because
you know, Trump, he wants his own thing.
So Trump had claimed he was going to roll out his own social media site, which ultimately
turned out to be a blog on his website that was so roundly mocked that it was taken down
permanently less than a month after launching.
It was so poorly done that Trump's staff have had to claim that there's a different social
media thing he's working on.
And this actually wasn't an embarrassment after all.
And it's a mess.
Wow.
Yep.
It was the blog version of the four seasons, my friend.
That's what it was.
So, I mean, this is it for the episode and like, honestly, he just interviews the hodge
twins for the rest of his time and then Gerald Cilenti takes over.
It's like, there's, this wasn't about Fauci's emails.
I would say, but his emails, Alex, come on.
I mean, wow.
That is about as stirring an admission of the emails being a giant nothing as you could
possibly get.
Like, yeah, because they don't, it doesn't even need to be true.
It's never needed to be true.
That's the, you can lie about any of it.
And they're still just like, I don't think this one has legs.
That's I feel like that's what people are coming to the conclusion right now.
It does feel like a big whiff.
And you know what, here's the thing too.
Like the way that it feels like a big whiff from everything that I've been able to tell
the things that I've read, Alex's response here.
That's a real problem because there should be something in there that's really damning
if any of the stuff that Alex was saying is true.
Like there should be something that is fucked up.
There should be like a message between him and his Chinese handlers.
Totally.
Because then what you're saying, like the, okay, okay, so you got all of his private
emails now.
They were leaked, man.
You've got all of this information.
This is the proof that you are looking for.
And none of it backs up what you're saying.
So you then have to say like, no, no, no, no.
So where is it?
He's got a secret email address that he can, and it's like, then, then what's the point
of ever leaking anything if it doesn't prove what you like.
And then you're just going to say it's secret that it goes back to the goddamn hodge twins
being like, you've got a real opportunity to prove that conservatives are idiots right
here.
You guys have been doing it for us for so many goddamn years.
Yeah, if you have this giant tranche is a word that Alex loves to use.
It's a great word in his defense.
Of emails that have come out that, you know, you'd think would be something that you could
use to build the narratives that you've been building forever.
Totally.
You'd think that this would give you some kind of an insight into what was going on.
And instead, so much of the emails that I've read are very indicative of learning along
the way and like the changing awareness is and like at the beginning, people did not
know a whole lot and it, I don't know, it kind of weirdly reinforces reality.
I mean, from, from what I understand, it is really like reinforced my, I suppose, confidence
in the people who are doing this, because at every point in time, you know, obviously
looking back, you would say obvious.
If we knew everything, we wouldn't have done it differently or be able to handle that better.
Duh.
But the way that you see the progression there is exactly how you would want people to do
it.
As we get more data, we're finding out whether or not this data is useful or non useful.
We're taking the data that we can use and we're using it to refine our process.
We're taking that refined process, putting it back into the system, getting useful and
non useful data, and then refining it still further.
And it's like, that's exactly how I want people to work.
That's how I want like science to work.
Exactly.
It's how it works.
At no point in time, did you hear anybody just making these giant guesses?
I did.
I heard one guy.
Oh yeah.
Alex.
Yes, exactly.
No, at no point in time in the emails was it like, Hey, we don't know anything about
hydrochloroquine or how it works just yet, but let's just go ahead and say it's great.
You know, like it didn't happen like that.
And the fact that it happened for other people like that should give you giant realizations
that they're dumb, but that won't happen.
Probably not.
Because it would be hard.
You'd have to think.
Yep.
Anyway, it was kind of a bummer because I was hoping for a little bit more stuff to
dig into as opposed to just new salmon.
Yeah.
Just so that you read all those emails.
You got a lot of ammo in your gun for a werewolf that ain't coming.
To be clear.
First of all, I love that metaphor.
That was a good metaphor.
I'm surprised.
That was off the dome.
Yeah, it was nice.
But I also like, I didn't read all of them, but I read enough to get a very general sense
of what a lot of these are and what the people are talking about in the conspiracy sites.
And Alex is just doing nothing here on the second.
Bummer.
Yeah.
Maybe later he'll get to it.
Maybe Leo Zagami will come up with something for him to work with.
Let's hope.
I need a big swing out of these emails because this isn't even a check swing.
This is a whiff.
Yeah.
And this is also still a little bit on the shorter side of an episode.
And we're still getting back adjusted after vacation.
Sure.
I had not been on vacation for a very long time and I did not realize some of the sleep
disturbance, some of those challenges.
And so I appreciate folks giving us a little bit of a, you know, I understand this is only
like hour and 15.
We'll get you on Friday.
We're getting in.
We're going to get there.
Come on now.
And we'll be back for that.
But until then, Jordan, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yep.
We're at Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledge underscore fight and I go to betjordan.
We're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook.
It's knowledgefight.
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work.
Yep.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
I am part asparagus.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.