N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledgefight, knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying we are the bad guys, knowledgefight.
Dan and Jordan, knowledgefight, need money, Andy in Kansas, stop it, Andy in Kansas, it's
time to pray.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding us.
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan, I love your work, knowledgefight.com,
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to knowledgefight, I'm Dan, I'm Jordan, we're a couple of dudes
like to sit around, drink novelty beverages, worship at the altar of Selene, and talk a
little bit about Alex Jones, oh indeed we are Dan, shit, ah come on, I wasn't going
to talk about it, you added it, you barely added a little thing, we were going to just
ride it on through, old habits, old habits, die hard, what are you going to do Dan, I
don't know, I have a question for you, okay, I'll do that, I'll answer that question,
what's your bright spot today, my bright spot today Jordan, I mentioned this to you, I decided
that I was going to give Assassin's Creed Valhalla another chance, I mentioned on the
show that I started playing it and I was enjoying it enough and then I just sort of lost interest,
and I did not make it very far into it, and you were telling me that there's this new
Ireland DLC, and so I decided I'll give this a shot, and you buried the lead, holy shit,
I went to Ireland, and almost immediately, instead of a horse, you now can ride a giant
cat around, I know, so my bright spot is now I'm riding around on a giant cat, I was hoping
you would discover it on your own, because I knew you were going to blow your mind, it's
the best, I have a giant cat that I'm riding around like a horse, and I couldn't be happier,
that's all you need, that's all you need, that's all you've ever dreamed of, that's
all you, yeah, no, absolutely, now the game is back in my good graces, and I will probably
finish it, because I have a giant cat friend, that is why I have tried to throw as many
pets at you in the other show we do, so that is nice, I like that, yeah, what about you?
My bright spot, Dan, as you may know, or probably don't, the French Open is going on right now,
oh no, and while you are listening to this, there's a good chance that Rafa and Djokovic
are meeting for their roughly 600th time, Djokovic I think is ahead by one win, they're
so close, they're the Kevin Owens and Sami Zayn of tennis, they've been going back and
forth for a decade, they're destined to fight forever, forever and ever, they're the two
best that ever lived, along with Federer, and it's just going to be great tomorrow,
or today, or whatever you're listening to, I imagine Rafa's going to wind up winning,
because Djokovic just looked a little bit shaky, but you never know, although you do,
because Rafa has won the French Open 13 times, I feel like the French Open was happening
like a week or two ago, I feel like this just keeps happening, it never stops, it's every
year or so, no I just feel like there's some tennis thing that I just always assume is
the French Open that's happening, yeah, well I mean, it's hard for me to tell the difference
between any of this, if you talk about Rafa, you eventually mention that he won 13 French
Opens, true, so Jordan, today we have an episode from the past, no, that's where things are
better, I got sick of Jordan's shit, well that's fair, I got sick of Alex's shit in
the present day, and you know, one of the things that was like, alright I'm definitely
doing an episode about the past, was that I kept seeing people posting that picture
of Alex at a strip club, and I just lost my patience with the present day, I don't understand
how that ends up being like, a viral tweet on Twitter, like I don't, who cares, yeah
that's my instant reaction, a lot of people were telling me about it and I was like, that's
okay, he's a monster, good for him, he can go to, we can all go to a strip club whenever
we want, whenever we want, that guy's a monster though, I don't care if he's at a strip club,
it doesn't really, it doesn't really make anything, it doesn't make any larger point
other than like, I think there's something weird about going to a strip club, I mean
I suppose you could probably try and make the argument that it's hypocritical for him
to be God-blasting all day, every day, and then be at a strip club, but yeah, it's so
easy, it's stupid, you could say like, look I'm a man, or you could say, I went there
because I had a business meeting and the people I was with wanted to go, you don't understand
what it's like to be in the higher echelons of business, you're running your own business
sometimes, you know there's a hundred ways you could get around the quote on quote hypocrisy
of it, and I don't know, I didn't look into it too much, but it looked like he was in
a bathroom, and look, I hate Alex Jones, I don't even know if that's a strip club, well
I hate Alex Jones, and I will say that if someone was taking a picture of him in the
bathroom, I think that is a violation of someone's rights of privacy, sure, and like, I don't
think it's cool to take pictures of people in a bathroom, yeah, I think you're right,
anyway, that's a good point, I was like, I don't know, I imagine maybe he has a rebuttal
to that, but I don't want to talk about it, I just don't care, yeah, so today we're gonna
be in the past and we're gonna be talking about May 15th to 20th, whoa, that's a lot,
2003, oh, blackjack, dammit, that's the wrong one again, roulette, this is a period that
I've been looking forward to covering because as we know, the de-bathification begins, yes,
around this time, he's been screaming about how they're gonna let the bath party run,
everything, the baths are taking over, that's Bush's and the globalist's plan from the beginning,
yes, they're going to be in charge of Iraq because they're basically CIA, exactly, and
so I was interested to see how that would be affected by, you know, how Alex's rhetoric
would be affected, yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, and then the second thing is that this is
over the weekend, and this is when Alex goes to Kansas City to do that local radio station
gig, that's right, we have a couple of dangling threads that are gonna come together in this
episode and I'm excited to get to it, but first, let's say hello to some new wonks,
so first, possibly Pluto, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk, I'm a policy wonk,
oh, thank you very much, dwarf planet, thank you, next, I like this one, W Neon Skousen,
thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk, I'm a policy wonk, I like that one too, I
would go to a CPA named W Neon Skousen, I would go to that if it was a Cold War themed
laser tag place, that would be awesome, that would be dope, next, Liam, we know your favorite
food is pickles, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk, I'm a policy wonk, thank
you Liam, yay, next, Omar Cha Cha, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk, I'm a
policy wonk, thank you very much Omar, thank you, and this is a shout out that a wonk asked
us to give as a policy, honorary policy wonk I guess, that's Bunny Brigade Pennsylvania,
Bunny Brigade PA, it's a bunny charity, like a rescue animal charity, oh okay, yeah, yeah,
I'm way ahead, they're apparently trying to expand and you can go to their website and
donate if you want to help save some bunnies, hell yeah, I was very close to trying to adopt
one of them because I looked at the website and there's a couple that were very cute,
of course there are, of course there are, you can't not adopt a bunny, no, anyway, Bunny
Brigade PA, you're now a policy wonk, I'm a policy wonk, thank you very much, and then
a couple technocrats here Jordan, we got Just Listen to Jordan stand up on YouTube and really
enjoyed it, you're now a technocrat, and Derek's brother Connor, you're now a technocrat, and
Derek hey, congratulations on your engagement recently, I hope you and Mallory have a great
time with your lives, I don't know how to say words, you're now a technocrat, I'm a
policy wonk, crikey mate, that's fantastic, have yourself a brew, how's your 401k doing
bro?
Alright, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this Watson alright, let's just get down to business,
we ain't making that money off that heroin, why you pimps so good, my neck is freakishly
large, I declare info war on you, thank you all, yes, thank you very much, especially
to me for donating to our show, just to make sure everybody knows that I might have a stand
up video on YouTube still, and I'm not sure if I do, but okay, so Jordan, we're gonna
get into this here, but first, here is an out of context drop, man that was a good show,
didn't cover all the news, covered a lot of it, okay, okay, okay, man that was a good
C+, got a 75%, I'm feeling solid about this math test, holy shit, I nailed it, I did some
of the things, that to me felt like really Alex Jones, that's very good, I do appreciate
that, hey this is a good show, also I set the bar low, anyways, onto tomorrow, you gotta
love yourself, you know, so we start here on the 15th, this is a Thursday, and Alex
is still covering the bombing in Riyadh that had happened recently, if you recall it was
a residential complex compound kind of area where a lot of Westerners were known to live,
in the intervening time since then, some more information has come out about the particular
Westerners that were living in these compounds that appeared to be the target of that, and
so this is the direction the story is going to go.
Local companies' employees die in Saudi bombing, now I had this on Infowars.com yesterday,
I briefly mentioned it, I said two days ago, before it was even in the news, on my website
and it's posted, the headline, you saw it, where I said, hmm, I bet the Carlisle Group
is going to be involved, I bet they're involved in the rebuilding, well guess what, guess
who owned the company and it just gotten done selling it and it still had connections to
it as a subsidiary, the Carlisle Group, the Benlodons, the Bushes and the rest of them.
So the company in question that were apparently the targets of this 2003 bombing in Riyadh
was the Vinnell Corporation, it's a construction business that was founded in 1931 and has
a deep history of international contracts for U.S. interests.
For instance, during the Vietnam War, Vinnell was tasked with maintaining power plant systems
over there overseas, they're actually pretty well known for this because in 1967, approximately
2,000 Korean workers at a Vinnell plant in Cameron Bay were dissatisfied enough with
their conditions that they rioted.
From Shelby Stanton's book, The Rise and Fall of an American Army, U.S. Ground Forces in
Vietnam, 1965 to 1973, quote, the primary cause appears to have been dissatisfaction
with the food served them, particularly the shortage of rice.
The Koreans refused to eat their Saturday meal on November 18th and went to the Vinnell
Mess Hall where they turned over tables and attacked several Americans.
They forced the American project manager to eat some of their food to show them how bad
it was.
A Vinnell Corporation civilian took out his gun and shot three Koreans.
He was then mobbed and severely injured and a Korean shot another American.
The riot ended up lasting four days.
Yeah, I was gonna say, like you say a company that does stuff for American government since
1931 and I'm like, I'm probably bad.
Not since 1931.
They were founded in 1931.
But they have a long history of performing government contracts in what are probably
war zones or a lot of the time.
So they're bad.
Yeah, and their involvement in government contracts began during the Chinese Civil War
when they were hired to ship supplies, meaning weapons, to Chiang Kai-Shek's forces.
Oh shit, was Alex right about everything?
No.
Oh, okay.
Because they were sending weapons to Chiang Kai-Shek.
Yes, I know.
It was fighting against Mao.
So I don't know, Alex has got a tough point there.
What's really most notable about this company, however, is that in 1975 they landed a very
lucrative contract to train the Saudi Arabian National Guard.
This is almost certainly- Can they do that?
Apparently they can.
This is almost certainly why their building was a target for that attack in Riyadh.
Not some obscure connection to people Alex is insisting on connecting everyone to back
in 2003.
In fact, their headquarters in Saudi Arabia had been bombed back in 1995, too.
This is something that I think people know to do.
Yeah, I mean, you're bad, so this happens.
I think that the people who would be trying to attack the Saudi Arabian government, maybe
some rebel types or terrorists, would know enough to be like, well, let's not just attack
the government.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, they're not using them with material stuff.
It kind of makes sense.
Yeah, yeah.
Here's the connection between Vinil and Carlyle Group.
In 1992, Vinil Corporation was bought by BDM International Incorporated, which in turn
was owned by the Carlyle Group.
However, in 1997, BDM was purchased by TRW Incorporated, which represented the end of
their association with the Carlyle Group.
According to an article in the Washington Post from 1997 about the deal, Carlyle had
agreed to sell its entire stake and shares in the company to TRW in the acquisition,
so there isn't even some minority ownership remaining the way Alex is pretending.
Right, right, right, right.
Then in 2002, TRW was bought by Northrop Grumman, so at the time Alex is recording this episode
and he wants to talk about this company in the context of the military industrial complex,
this would be the angle to take.
It seems really simple, too, which is why you can't do it.
It's too easy.
By pointing fingers at the Carlyle Group, Alex is making this piece of information fit
his pre-written narratives about Bush, but he's depriving the audience of access to any
real context for the subject that he's covering.
At the point Alex is on air here, the Carlyle Group was six years removed from selling Vinel's
parent company, and even if they were owners of Vinel's parent company, still it wouldn't
prove anything.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
I mean, to a certain extent, I think once you're talking about a company that's been
bought like three times in six years, I don't even know if any of these people have any
idea what it is they're buying or selling at that highest level.
You know what I'm saying?
What do you mean George W. Bush knows what's going on or anything like that?
He's got people who are just like, ah, we'll do all that stuff.
He's bumbling around like a fool.
I don't know.
They don't know what they're doing if they're buying those kinds of companies and then selling
them a year later.
Well, from what I understand from reading some of these articles, it was a period of
time where there was rampant consolidation and merger and going on in terms of these
international contractors.
Right.
Right, right, right.
And so that kind of explains a little bit of the moving around.
Right.
Right, right, right.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's not compelling.
Just because you see the name Carlyle Group in the past of this company.
Right.
Right, right, right.
I don't know.
It's soft.
Northrop Grumman is probably an easier name to just pull and be like, problem.
Doesn't come up at all.
See?
No, but problem.
You know?
Weird that it doesn't come up at all.
The name Northrop Grumman doesn't come up at all in Alex's conversation.
I thought Alex has a stake in Northrop Grumman.
No.
See?
Anybody can do it, Dan.
Anybody can do it.
Alex owns part of Northrop Grumman.
So it's all a conspiracy that he's trying to get people to hate the, it's, anybody.
As founded as anything else.
Done.
Yeah, anybody.
Anybody.
Apparently this Vinnell Corporation is also apparently a front for the CIA.
Oh, okay.
Turns out the firm was a cover for the CIA too.
Oh, lo and behold, what got bombed was the CIA, hence the Times of London, and the Vinnells
one-time owners of the Carlyle Group, shadowy CIA operations.
Here are the mainstream articles, NBC and the Times of London, on the website Infowars.com
right now.
One of the things that I've learned to be very careful about when dealing with speculative
information is claims that people or groups are fronts.
This is an accusation that's really difficult to work with because generally speaking it's
a claim that's made constantly without proof, and people who make the claim often seem to
think that the burden of proof is on you to show that some group isn't a front, which
is a trap.
If you read any John Birch Society text or book from the anti-communist crusaders that
Alex loves, one of the first things you'll notice is that every single thing is asserted
to be a communist front, and none of it is ever substantiated.
Gary Allen's book, Communist Revolution in the Streets, accuses literally every civil
rights organization, every student activism group, and most bookstores of being communist
fronts.
And not in the sense that some communists might gravitate to these things.
He's claiming that these exist explicitly as props of the communist party.
It was Barnes and Nobleski, if you, alright.
So anyway, my point is that it's one of the rhetorical tricks that I have the least interest
in, is like an unsupported allegation that something or someone is a front.
Nonsense.
The question I just wrote down is like, after all these years, what does Alex think the
CIA's portfolio actually looks like, like if there was a balance sheet of all of their
fronts?
Jesus.
So in the case of Vinnell, there is an article in the London Times about how they were formerly
owned by the Carlyle Group, and that the Carlyle Group had a history of contracting with intelligence
organizations.
Sure.
Sure's the headline that Alex is talking about.
Now, here's the thing.
I would never come to you and say that Vinnell absolutely hasn't done some work with groups
like the CIA.
Sure.
That's almost a certainty, considering their longstanding contract to train the Saudi National
Guard.
And allegations have been made.
From a 2003 article in the LA Times, quote, in a memoir, former CIA operative Wilbur Crane
Evelyn described using his title as Vinnell vice president as a cover while working in
Africa and the Middle East in the early 1960s.
It's definitely conceivable to imagine that at times people who work for the CIA have
used fake employment at Vinnell as cover, but that alone doesn't demonstrate that the
entire company itself is a front operation.
I'm going out of my way to provide explanations for why Alex could be right, and I still don't
think his argument stands up to scrutiny.
No.
No, I mean, here's what I get from all of the evidence.
Something shady could be going on here.
Here's what I get from Alex.
It's the fucking globalists inside everybody.
And we've proved it.
Yeah, exactly.
And it's like, man, I'm not saying nothing shady's going on, but I'm not saying nothing's
not going on.
Initially, after the bombing, it was suspected that the attacks were on a housing area known
to be used by Westerners living in Riyadh.
As more details came out, it became more clear that this was likely a targeted attack aimed
at Vinnell.
What makes a lot of sense is that, from the standpoint of people who might attack the
Saudi government, like we were talking about, they're assisting and training the National
Guard of Saudi Arabia, and you might see that as a high-profile target.
If you're a rebel, it's hard not to view that as a combatant target.
The CIA could outright run Vinnell, or they could just be a company that had close ties
to the government and allowed CIA agents to use their business's name as part of the cover.
Either way, I'm not sure it really matters, because the thing they're doing sucks.
There's a much larger problem here with this entire state of private armies and war contractors,
but instead of dealing with those things realistically, Alex just wants to jingle around keys like
the CIA and Carlyle group, because distracting is easier than wrestling with difficult information
and looking at the reality.
That's what he's doing, and it's wild.
I mean, then again, to a certain extent, it's hard not to look back in the context of, like,
when he has Trump, he's fine with so much of this shit, you know?
He likes Blackwater now.
Yeah, he loves all of this stuff, so, you know, maybe part of the reason-
He thinks Prince is a hero.
Part of the reason maybe that he's doing all of these jangling keys kinds of things is
because he wants the fundamental problems to stay the same, he just wants to be in control
of those fundamental problems and how we react to them, you know?
He wants to have a private army.
So why would he complain about people who have private armies unless it's within the
context of jangling keys over here, you know?
Well, I mean, certainly, you know, libertarianism is not averse to private armies.
No, no, no.
Most libertarian thinkers seem to-
As long as you get to join.
Yeah.
So, anyway, Alex has some more conspiracies about this company in Saudi.
Turns out that 50 plus of the 70 employees were gone on a training mission and-
So he's saying that 50 of the 70 employees at Vinil were gone on a training mission,
but what he's doing is he's trying to create the false impression in the listener's head.
Whenever there's an attack, you'll always hear claims that some select group was warned
not to be there or had been removed from the area beforehand because claims like this seem
to be really strong indications of foreknowledge and probably it's a false lie.
Of course.
Alex wants you to think that 50 of the seven employees there weren't at work that day,
which is suspicious, but that's not the situation.
The buildings that were bombed were a residential compound where 70 American employees lived.
I'm not sure where Alex is getting the 50 number from, but nine employees died and 15
were hospitalized, not counting many who were merely treated for minor injuries.
Jesus.
Also, if people who worked at Vinil weren't at home, they almost by definition would be
on a training mission since the reason they're in Saudi Arabia is a training mission.
The words Alex is saying actually mean nothing, but they're meant to create a denser air of
suspicion around the bombing, which is unearned by the information that he's actually presenting.
It does seem like he's even presenting it the exact opposite way in as far as they were
just at work.
He's like, they're on a training mission, meaning they're not at work, but in this circumstance,
they're at work.
They're not at home.
Yeah, he's meaning it to be like they were sent to UAE.
Right, right, right.
He's trying to sell it like if the Pentagon got exploded tomorrow, but all the top generals
escaped miraculously the day before, you're like, well, that's suspicious as shit instead
of like-
That's exactly what he's doing.
They all just went to work that day.
It was a normal day.
He's saying all the higher ups were gone, and he literally does say a couple of times
like, the janitors were the ones who were-
Okay.
I don't know about this.
So Alex jumps off this topic, and he reads a bit of an op-ed by Joseph Farah, the guy
who runs WorldNetDaily.
Sure.
I bet it's great.
Well, one of the things that I think is really fascinating about this is that Alex doesn't
seem to like WorldNetDaily in 2003.
I'm just so confused.
He doesn't consider them allies.
I'm furious.
So anyway, this is going to start with him reading from the article and then expounding
a little bit on some of his feelings.
Most people need to rethink their notions about the political spectrum and the left
end.
Most people agree you have communism, total government control over the means of production
and property.
It's the other end of the spectrum that many get confused.
Ask most left-wingers, and they'll suggest that fascism is on the extreme right, 180
degrees from communism.
Uh-uh.
Wow, Farah.
You've been listening to the show.
We know a lot of WorldNetDaily writers listen, and you've admitted that.
I've got news for you, friends.
Fascism and communism are ideological kissing cousins.
Boy, you said it.
I would place fascism and socialism just a few degrees to the right of communism.
No, Farah.
It's not left-right.
What?
Fascism, communism, socialism, all on the command and control, tyranny, serfdom, feudalism,
and republics, constitutional republics, are on the other end of that spectrum.
Get a little more sophisticated.
I think you are.
I think you know.
They've got to keep you in that left-right.
You think you get a choice when really you're on the big government side.
That's weird.
Words, words, words, words, words, words, words, words, words, words.
Yeah.
Alex loves WorldNetDaily now and has over large stretches of his career, but he seems
to think that they're neo-cons at this point, and he thinks that this op-ed that Joseph
Farah wrote is an indication that they're coming around or something, and so he's excited.
I'm less interested in that op-ed than I am in Alex's discussion about some of the more
the specifics about his belief that the right-left paradigm is an illusion.
I'm a big fan of how he confuses economic systems, government systems, any number of
different things.
Listening to mostly more current episodes of Alex's show from the past five or six years,
you get the sense that that idea had something to do with political parties.
Even at the end of the clip, he's making reference to the left and the right having something
to do with giving you the illusion of having a choice, which feels like he's talking about
voting and political parties.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
However, listening to these 2003 episodes, the concept has sort of taken a different
shape.
Since Alex talks a little bit more about what he actually means back then, and I have to
say that I think it's actually way stupider than I thought it was, it actually seems like
a political philosophy that's tailor-made to be defined by opposition, which goes a
long way toward helping make sense of how the show seemed nonsensical in the Trump era
and now.
When Alex is discussing the illusion of the left-right paradigm, I believe you have to
just completely get ideas of liberal or conservative politics out of your head.
I think Alex is operating on a completely different axis, which is essentially just
government is bad.
It's a pretty childish thing to express as your fundamental political belief, especially
if you don't have the courage to just come out and be a full-on anarchist.
If you're against big government, then I'd like to remind you that small government is
fucking huge compared to no government.
Leaving that aside, I want to discuss for a second why Alex's conception of this being
the only relevant excess in politics is woefully dumb and not the way to look at the world.
The sole factor Alex considers in terms of ideology is whether or not something is a
system that includes government control of the public, the command and control aspect.
On the one side of the spectrum, he puts communism, socialism, and fascism as systems with high
government control, and at the other end, he has this idealized version of a constitutional
republic, which I guess is supposed to have minimal government control, I guess.
I don't know.
If that's the only factor that matters, then there should be no difference to Alex between
anarcho-capitalism and libertarian socialism.
Both advocate for the elimination of the centralized state, which would result in a system with
even less governmental control over the public than exists in a republic.
Both are conceived around people existing in a stateless world, characterized by voluntarily
constructed groups.
But obviously, these two ideologies have stark differences.
One of the biggest is their stance on private property.
Anarcho-capitalists believe the right to private property is essentially the bedrock of society,
whereas libertarian socialists would view the accumulation of private property to be
an instance of the same oppression one might face from the state, just being carried out
by a private corporation.
It's very obvious if you look at these two systems that Alex isn't really being honest
about his political preferences.
If there's two schools of thought which both eschew centralized governmental control, there
are still political preferences that Alex has that are on the left-right spectrum.
Private property is a matter of the left-right spectrum.
While it's true that most center-left and center-right people tend to agree that private
property ownership is good, that's not true when you go to the further ends of the spectrum.
Further-left ideologies tend to favor communal ownership of private property or democratized
workplaces.
Conversely, further-right ideologies tend to believe that private property rights are
inalienable human rights, and they have no problem with exploitative workplaces because
employment is a voluntary relationship.
Alex presents himself as being above the left-right paradigm because he wants you to think that
he's talking about democrat-republican two-party system stuff that exists in the United States.
He wants you to think that because most people are disenfranchised with that two-party system,
and it's an easy thing to find agreement with.
Most people would be like, yeah, you know, these aren't fully, they don't fully encapsulate
my ideology.
And if you look at it as like a line between the two parties, yes, that is an illusion.
That's what he wants you to think, but that's not what he's talking about.
It's important to recognize that, and recognize that he's a liar.
When he says that he's above the left-right paradigm, what he's actually saying is that
he hates government, that he lacks the political depth to coherently advocate for the form
of anarchy that he would prefer, and so he just pretends that the answer is a constitutional
republic.
Yeah, I mean, I would also add into that, that level of, you know, the type of person
who wants capitalism, but you know, they're not going to be the people grounded underneath
the boot of capitalism.
You know, look, listen, I think, you know, people shouldn't have all of this money.
I mean, I should have all of this money, obviously, but people shouldn't have all this money,
you know?
Because again, you want to preserve so much of the system that gives you power over everybody
else, instead of being like, look, I don't want any government, whoa, whoa, whoa, then
people might steal my expensive things, you know, like that kind of feel.
If you created his kind of left-right paradigm world within there, there'd still be fucking
cops to protect his shit, so he doesn't have to.
Like that's the kind of anarcho bullshit he's peddling, so yeah, fuck off.
Yeah, I mean, what I would need from him is, okay, so if the question is command and control
nonsense and like what amount the government controls the population, right, that is the
relevant access upon which you can judge politics.
That's it.
If that's the case, then you need to explain to me why a constitutional republic is more
preferable than an anarchist state, because that would be the complete elimination of
this thing that you think is the bad.
And then you'd have to argue, I guess if you're Alex, that a certain amount is important.
And then, okay, why?
He's like, well, because I like to control things or something, you know?
Yeah, exactly.
Because I want stuff.
Yeah.
And this doesn't even get into differentiation between personal and private property and
how many left ideologies still believe in personal property.
And the right does try to muddle those things a little bit.
It's easy.
But yeah, and I mean, this also isn't even getting into the differentiation between political
and more economic models and how Alex is just playing fast and loose between all of them.
You can have a fascist communist state.
There's a government and an economic model there that's not a fascist or communist state.
That's not how it works.
And, I don't know, I just think when you hear stuff like this, what it does is it helps
me understand a little bit more about these sort of elements of Alex's costume that he
wears to try and trick people into thinking he's sensible.
And that being above the left-right paradigm looks sensible, because you could say, Republicans
and Democrats are all the same.
They're beholden to corporate interests, special interest groups, and you can say that.
And I think you can get a lot of people to be like, yeah, you know what?
That makes some sense.
But that's not what Alex is talking about.
No, no.
It's just a little bit of a disguise.
Yeah.
I mean, you can call yourself above the left-right paradigm fairly easily because a winning strategy
for both Republicans and Democrats is to say, listen, the Republicans and the Democrats
fucking suck.
Elect me to be one of those Republicans or Democrats, you know, like it's a winning strategy.
It kind of is.
It's not hard.
Yeah.
It does.
It helps.
What a pathetic world.
But anyway, labels and words mean nothing.
Yes.
Communism, fascism, it means nothing, nothing.
It's all strong man, thug, empire, get it straight.
If your goal is to enlighten an audience or help them better understand the world around
them and the political conversations that they're hearing, this is exactly the opposite
of what you should do.
Communism and fascism do definitely mean something.
They are just words that describe imperial strongmen wearing different colored hats and
convincing audiences that that's the case makes them entirely unprepared to deal with
challenging political issues.
Also, if you take Alex at his word, then the hallmarks of the sort of government that he
hates and he does not want to exist is one that's run by a strongman or thug, which is
an empire.
I know hypocrisy means nothing, but by these standards, Donald Trump is precisely the candidate
2003 Alex Jones would strongly oppose.
In 2015, Alex knew Trump was connected to the mob and presented an image of a strongman
as a facade.
He put on this image.
He was a fake strongman.
Yeah.
During the campaign, Trump made signals to being open to empire and Alex even defended
Trump's desire to buy Greenland and claim space in the name of the United States.
Come on, you want Greenland, you want space.
Trump fails Alex's imaginary test that's allegedly above the left-right paradigm, but Alex still
supports him because he actually passes Alex's real litmus test, which is heavily dependent
on the left-right paradigm.
Oh yeah.
That's important to keep in mind, but it's important to remember that that's really what
motivates him.
Yeah.
It's such a bummer that these concepts like communism and fascism and all of that stuff,
things that really do take a book or multiple books or many, many books to understand clearly,
let alone try and implement.
And then you've got people who are just like, communism is this in a short sentence.
That's going to muddy the waters.
Nobody wants to read many, many books.
Yeah.
And I think you have that same problem on the reverse side.
Oh yeah, totally.
People promoting certain ideologies or systems, doing it overly simplistically.
I think you run into similar issues of watering down meanings, confusing people.
Yeah.
And there's a lot of complexity and I'm not even sitting here pretending I understand
fully every intricate aspect of theory.
Right, right.
No, no, no.
Absolutely.
It becomes, you know, why did Marx write Das Kapital?
It's so big.
He should have written a one page ad in the New York Times and we all still would have
gotten it, right?
That's how simple theory is.
Hey capitalism, I got two words for you.
Suck it.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah, done.
So Alex jumps off this and goes on to another headline that I guess is the big news.
But the big news when we get back, dead man left on gym floor while others exercise, just
how people don't care anymore.
This is a sad headline, but...
That's the big news.
Yeah, I'm not sure there's any place being part of the news roundup of a national radio
show.
I don't know.
Single person hurt in accident.
On shows like Alex's, you'll hear coverage like this a lot because it serves a couple
of important emotional purposes for the audience.
The first is that a straw man is created of the heartless people who could just exercise
while a person next to them was dead.
The listener gets to imagine how horrible these people are and feel morally superior
to these imaginary people.
The second is to demoralize the audience about the state of the world and erode their belief
in their fellow persons.
The goal is to present a situation where the audience hears this headline and they imagine
that these people in the gym continued to work out fully aware that this person was
dead because that's shitty of them.
If they didn't know the person was dead and thought possibly he was just resting, then
you can't really paint this as a story that highlights the moral degradation of the broader
culture.
It's really more just a situation where people are minding their own business at the gym
and there's a tragic coincidence.
People not bothering stranger.
Yeah.
It's sad and it's unfortunate, but it's not like...
This is not a news story that illustrates how bad people are.
Yeah, no, it's like he's trying to do a sequel to Boondock Saints, but it's about people
at the gym who are just minding their own business.
I've been to the gym many times and people could have been dead.
There are people who I've seen laying, like, and your favorite word, supine.
Supine.
You're never gonna let me live that down.
Nope.
They're just laying there and obviously, you know, if you want to go poke them, you can,
but also every time I have been around, they eventually get up because they've just been
tired because they're working out.
Imagine how many years someone does that.
If you're listening to Alex Jones in 2003, right, and you're like taking this one story
to heart.
You've missed everything else he's ever said, but you got this one story.
How many years are you poking people at the gym before maybe you find a dead guy?
You know?
Your whole life.
You're never finding a dead guy.
You're not finding people now.
I bet you're not.
You're an asshole.
Yep.
So Alex has Craig Roberts back on.
And you'd have to try and explain it every time.
Yeah.
Oh, sorry.
I thought you were dead.
Sorry.
In 2003, Alex Jones had this story where people watched everybody die and I'm just not gonna
let it happen.
Alex Jones convinced me that the only way to be a good person was to poke everybody.
Exactly.
So Alex has Craig Roberts back on, who is the conspiracy theorist type, and he was on
partially because he's gonna be in Kansas City with Alex in this speech.
And so, you know, there's a war going on in the world.
This is obviously just a distraction from the financial collapse that's happening tomorrow.
Gold.
And then we hit a common theme.
If they can keep us in a war, that'll divert us off the plunging economy and the shopping
malls being empty.
Because this, it's not just oil or weapons sales, it's about a global police state.
From Russia to the US, governments are using the terror as a massive crackdown mechanism.
We know Putin got caught blowing up buildings in Russia.
Well, it's order out of chaos, not decaled.
That's their motto.
Every day, Putin and the apartment buildings come up.
Every single day.
In this stretch?
Yeah.
Every day.
I have been keeping track.
Not a single episode has gone by that hasn't come up multiple times.
It makes me so mad.
That's a cornerstone of his sort of reporting at this point.
You can just do whatever you want.
You certainly can.
That's the lesson of America.
If you're a psycho, you can do whatever the fuck you want.
So at this point, Alex, he has his interview with Craig Robertson.
It's kind of short and I don't really care.
I don't find that guy very interesting.
But what is interesting is that Alex then has an interview with his water filter sponsor.
Oh no.
Bad news coming out, bad economy, and people putting their money back in.
Public indicators, there's no one at the stores.
I go to CompUSA to buy something computer-wise.
I go to the mall.
There's no one there, Jim.
Well and that's what, that's basically the story all the way through the economy.
And they're saying is brace for massive terror attacks.
We're going to get hit.
Blah, blah, blah.
People, you better get essentials.
You better pick up the phone and get these water filters.
You are nuts if you don't.
Jim, tell them about the new.
That's shameless.
That's what they knew.
That's an incredible new product.
Yeah, it's pretty, it's pretty shameless.
That is, that is without shame.
That is the definition of shameless.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's get those water filters and the sponsor on to scare people.
They're going to be terrorist attacks.
They want to scare you with all these terrorist attacks.
Let me tell you something, people.
The economy's collapsing so you need water filters.
I'm not trying to scare you with terror attacks.
I think that, you know, I think we've talked about this a little bit in the past, but I
think it's been a really long time.
Like, I think that there is a way to do what Alex is doing in a responsible way.
You know, like be like, hey, you know, there, there are dangers in the world and you know,
let's say if you have a family, it would be good to have a little bit of food stored in
case of a natural disaster or something like when I was growing up, there was a worry about
tornadoes in Missouri.
Yeah.
And so my parents had some canned food and water in the basement just as a, like, we
never ended up needing it, but just in case it's there.
Exactly.
I always have an extra big bag of cat food on hand because I have a cat.
Of course.
And I don't want to run into a situation where something could happen and I'm not able to
take care of this thing.
Totally.
I think that there is like a way to, it's not this though.
No.
This is exploitative and playing on people's fears.
Yeah.
There, there's a, there's a version of this that is like looking at life responsibly and
trying to be like, well, you may need this.
Right.
It's, it's not a terrible idea just in case.
And the other side of it is this, like you're, you're stupid if you don't get these, these
water filters because there's going to be terrorist attacks and the economy is going
to collapse.
Yeah.
It is unfortunate that that's like that combination of when commerce and capital met psychology
and turned it into advertising and they're like, we can get more stuff if we emotionally
manipulate people than if we provide them a rational argument.
So we're going to emotionally manipulate them.
The end.
So the filter sponsor, he apparently just got some big news from a major scientist about
how great his filters are.
And Alex tries to set this up.
Please tell me it's Dr. Fauci of all people.
I wish.
Why not?
Let's throw that in there.
No, I'm not that big of a witch.
Um, no, but the, the, the filter sponsor doesn't have time to talk about this and listen to
Alex's disappointment here.
Okay, let's hear this.
So it's really, you had a famous scientist do the test.
Uh, that's correct.
And um, well, Alex, I tell you what, I'm, I'm on a business trip and I've got to be
somewhere in about 15 minutes, but if I can, uh, I'd like to give a little special out
here.
Sure.
Go ahead, Jim.
Okay.
Very disappointed.
Who is the famous scientist?
One thing to say, you said a famous scientist, say the name, then give the ad.
Yes.
The end.
This has been approved by Mary.
Something, something, yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
Watson and Crick.
Jonas Salk approves of my water filters.
Now we have a special running.
Naturally, naturally.
Anyway, Alex is another guest and this is something that he's been promoting all day.
He's so excited to have this guy on.
He is a Canadian journalist named Barry Zwicker.
Okay.
Uh, and uh, he does not like 9-11 and thinks 9-11 was an inside job and what have you.
All right.
And he's been playing him up as like the biggest deal, like a huge Canadian journalist, one
of the most important in the world.
Okay.
And uh, so here's Barry's introduction to the proceedings.
Well, listen, it's a real pleasure, Alex, I, uh, I, I encountered your face for the
first time at the end of that new video, uh, called aftermath, you know, questions, unanswered
questions from 9-11.
I saw that video in San Francisco last month and I really liked what they had you as the
last guy punching out a real call for people to wake up and uh, I really admired that.
So Barry Zwicker is an interesting fellow.
From everything I can tell, he was a pretty standard and accomplished Canadian journalist.
He'd worked for mainstream outlets and then 9-11 happened and everything seems to have
fallen apart.
Uh oh.
Zwicker decided that...
He's like Dennis Miller.
Yeah, yeah.
Except I don't think that Zwicker's gone full hard right.
Or that Dennis Miller was ever funny.
I don't know if Zwicker's funny either.
Fair.
He decided that the mainstream media story about the attack wasn't real, but he did have
a bit of a different angle on it than Alex.
According to what he told reporter Terry Glavin in a 2006 interview, the end goal of the attack,
carried out by the White House, was to create a war against Islam.
Okay.
That was the conspiracy.
Well?
In 2004, he would go on to make his own 9-11 film titled The Great Conspiracy, the 9-11
news special you never saw.
It's just as good and just as bad as every other 9-11 documentary and has a title that
bears all the hallmarks of the early days of internet clickbait, before people really
got good at it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Before it turned into an art form into itself, yeah.
Over the years, he's continued to be a 9-11 truther and generally the sort of person you
can count on to call just about anything a false flag.
I found a recent interview he did with the Global Research News Hour where he was discussing
how the storming of the Capitol on January 6th was a false flag.
Sure.
I know you expected to hear him doing some Alex shtick, but it's the exact opposite.
He was saying that the event was a false flag inspired or directed by Trump, which honestly
makes no sense.
No, I love it.
The term false flag comes from the idea of a ship attacking someone while flying a different
country's flag so that country gets blamed.
If Trump had a bunch of people storming the Capitol wearing Trump hats, that's not a false
flag.
It's just a straight up correct flag.
It does seem like that, unless you are implying that...
So he's saying that Trump was also in on the setup of his own supporters in order to discredit
his own ideology and support.
No, I don't think so, because he doesn't like Trump.
Right.
But how could Trump be in on a false flag if that...
That's what I'm saying.
Semantically, it doesn't make sense.
No, of course not.
It's tough for me to say, but listening to that interview, it kind of feels like Zwicker
is like an Alex Jones, but with opposite politics.
He's making wildly unfounded assertions and claims that don't make sense, but he's also
staunchly opposed to Trump and recognizes that systemic racism exists.
Sure.
Hooray.
Yeah.
His appearance here on Alex's show is a real moment that was possible in 2003, but probably
not much later than that.
Not these days, yeah.
They felt like they were in agreement as far as 9-11 conspiracies were concerned, but they
actually didn't agree on anything, because they're dreadfully far apart on the left-right
paradigm.
The left-right paradigm is fairly important in reality.
It seems to be.
If you judge everything based on something's position in terms of the right and left spectrum,
then maybe that's a little bit reductive itself.
Yeah.
There are multiple axes upon which things can be judged, but pretending that that one
doesn't exist is a real limitation.
Fool's game.
Fool's game, yeah.
So Barry, oh boy, bam.
Barry says something in this interview that if it were present day, Alex would lose his
goddamn mind.
Okay, I want to hear it.
I happen, my hero happens to be a guy named Bertrand Russell, a dead British white philosopher,
and he had his own Ten Commandments, and his first commandment is never lie to yourself.
And I think that is the first and foremost commandment.
Don't lie to yourself.
Bertrand Russell, you got this left-wing globalism arm, and that's how they catch us all.
They got the phony right wing, they got the phony left wing, but that's it for another
discussion.
But that is another discussion.
So that's a huge tell for me that Alex doesn't believe his own bullshit.
Yeah, what a cheater.
According to Infowars lore, Bertrand Russell's writing outright admits that the globalists
plan to drug, sterilize, and kill off most of the population.
Russell is one of the old school globalists, according to Alex, who is instrumental in
coming up with and publicizing their evil plans.
I can understand wanting to have a polite interview, and I do think that there are times
just to agree to disagree about things.
For instance, if Barry thought that the 9-11 planes were remote controlled and Alex felt
they were piloted by the hijackers, they could go ahead and agree to disagree without having
a gigantic problem sitting on the table.
They may have a disagreement, but not a fundamental contradiction.
Not a deal breaker, if you will.
Right.
Barry isn't just saying that he kinda likes Bertrand Russell.
He says Russell is his hero.
Barry is a guy who's worked for major papers, and he's taught college courses, so it stands
to reason that if he says that Bertrand Russell is his hero, he's probably read as much or
more of his writing than Alex has.
This is why, to me, this cannot be an agree-to-disagree moment.
In order for Alex to maintain all the narratives he has in play, he has to be agreeing to disagree
about his guest hero-worshipping a guy who he has read, discussing the plans to kill
off most of the human population.
There's no other reasonable conclusion to come to with the information provided, other
than that Barry is an enthusiastic fan of globalist conspiracies.
He loves him.
Alex should want to fight him.
It does seem like Alex is like, okay, okay, I get it.
We agree that 9-11 was an inside job.
So I'm going to gloss over the fact that your hero is the architect of killing everybody
so we can really get to the bottom of this 9-11 thing.
You might be missing the forest for the fallen trees, if you will.
Yeah.
Alex knows that there's nothing he can do, and he can't really fight him on this, because
he knows that Barry's read Bertrand Russell.
Yeah, he doesn't know anything about Bertrand Russell.
He's probably way more conversant on the subject than Alex is.
It'd be very embarrassing.
But Alex also knows that if he presses the issue, he risks revealing that his shit about
Russell is made up.
But he also knows that he can't just let a statement like that stand.
And thus, you end up with his middle ground, his spineless agreeing to disagree about one
of the top thinkers of the gigantic demonic conspiracy that Alex has made his entire career
about fighting happening.
It's ridiculous.
Yeah, yeah, because if you're saying that you're above the left-right paradigm, you
should be more unhappy with the plan instead of being like, well, there's globalists on
the left.
There's globalists on the right.
What are you going to do?
Hey, you win some, you lose some.
Stuck in the middle with Barry.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
I think that, I mean, obviously this is me just sort of spitballing and coming up with
what I think is the most likely explanation for this.
And that is that I think that Alex's branding at this point is so dependent on him being
able to pretend this left-right paradigm thing is an illusion.
So for him to have someone who's ostensibly a 9-11 conspiracy theorist who's on the left,
or who has left tendencies and left politics, I don't think he wants to fight with that
guy.
I think it's really important for them to have some kind of an appearance of an alliance,
especially with the way that Alex has been building him up as this big, giant reporter
and super important person in Canada.
And so I think that that takes precedence over this guy's hero is one of your main villains.
He can't think that Barry isn't aware of Bertrand Russell.
He can't think that he hasn't read the same things that Alex has read.
Right.
Well, I mean, because Alex is taking advantage of that.
So the enemy of my enemy is not my friend.
And you can prove that because Alex is taking advantage of people thinking that the enemy
of my enemy is my friend.
Yep.
It's fairly simple.
Open and shut case.
Yeah.
So they take some calls with Barry and this guy really, really creeped me out.
This guy is so creepy.
Let's talk to Bill in Alaska.
You're on the air with our guests.
Go ahead.
Yes, sir.
Alex.
I just had to call in.
I got an enemy that hasn't been mentioned yet on today's show.
And the American people want to know why this is like this.
All they got to do is look in the mirror.
Jim Jones in the case in point, I don't believe he was as guilty as the people that followed
him.
Oh.
He couldn't have been a bad leader if he hadn't had followers.
Okay.
Creep.
Wow.
You're going to need to sell me a lot more on that one.
He does not.
You're going to need a lot more salesmanship on that take.
I will tell you delivery and content both creepy as hell.
Yeah.
That's no good.
I don't like a fucking bit player from Bonanza from Alaska telling me that Jim Jones was
a good leader.
Hey, in terms of death cults, man, in terms of like mass suicide cults, don't hate the
player, hate the game.
What is happening?
I don't know.
Here's the problem.
People follow Jim Jones.
If he wasn't such a good leader, then they wouldn't have followed him, so it's their
fault.
What?
Okay.
All right.
I'm the Alaskan cowboy here to tell you about death cults.
So the rest of the calls are kind of boring, but then the interview takes a turn hard south
when Barry starts talking about his new DVD that he's been selling.
Okay.
We're having an incredible...
It looks like we're moving toward 500 sales.
We have an equation here in Canada, it's called the 10% thing, because the population of Canada
is about one-tenth of the population of USA, so whatever happens to the states, we usually
divide it by 10 and figure that's normal.
Okay.
For those that don't know, you're a national television host.
You do this on your own and you write for newspapers and you just put together this
video and believe me, it'll be a lot more than 500 if you get the word out, but...
That is awful.
Like Alex straight up laughs at him.
He's a little 500.
Yeah.
Yeah, that was not a, I'm laughing with you.
No.
That was an, I'm laughing at you.
That was an almost uncontrollable response to like...
You fucking shit.
Oh no.
500.
Get out of here.
And there's also the problem of like, alright, even the rule of tens, he's a little 5,000?
That's still not great for what Alex is presenting.
No.
And so what that does is it pierces the illusion that Alex has created about this guy throughout
the...
He's a national writer, he's been on TV, he's the biggest, most important journalist in
Canada and he can get upwards of 500, well upwards of 499 people to really get these.
Yeah.
And it really hurts the facade, and you can tell that there is a tonal change in Alex
after this specific number has been given, because it's like, I can't, I can't...
Now you're nothing to me.
He can't pretend that he is Rush Limbaugh of Canada if he's only moving those many units.
My audience just, I can't deny that math.
And so it's, you know, it is what it is, and it doesn't go much longer.
But Alex does finish out this episode with some fairly standard complaining.
A number of people detained is on the rise in Russia to Stalinist levels, it says here
in the Moscow Times.
Just total slavery over there, but they don't call it communism, they call it crony capitalism.
Same thing, command and control.
Alex brings up the Putin bombings at least four times in this episode, like it's really
excessive.
And then he says this about the Russian state, I find this fascinating because in the present
day when he's trying to defend Putin, Alex will say that Russia isn't a globalist country,
it's a system of crony capitalism, it's a positive thing now.
Or at least it's not as bad as globalism.
Crony capitalism isn't a negative command and control system in the present day to Alex.
I could speculate about what the reason for this change is, but honestly I would just
be guessing.
It's a glaring difference though.
Yeah.
It's pretty weird.
Pretty weird.
I don't know.
Yeah.
So the 16th is Friday, and Alex is en route to Kansas City.
Sure.
He's going to speak at the local radio station, and he's not in studio.
What's that, a six hour drive?
From Austin?
Yeah.
I have no idea.
And I think it's more.
I think it's probably more.
It's probably more.
It's probably a nine hour drive.
I don't know if he's actually driving, because I think he said he flew back.
I don't know.
I don't care.
Anyway.
The point is he takes Friday off.
I'm just here to distract you with weird questions.
Yeah.
He takes Friday off, and then he comes back on Monday, because I don't think he has a
Sunday show at this point.
So he comes back on Monday, and here we go.
Completely different subject.
There are now mainstream news articles reporting on what we've been saying for years.
The evidence of mind control triggers in the Matrix films.
And here it is.
We've been saying this for about three years.
And here it is in the mainstream news.
Did you know that Malvo, the supposed sniper who looks like a mind control victim, is out
there now saying that that is certainly involved.
Wonder how we knew about this three years ago.
Well, there's just a lot of key indicators, and of course Harris and the others involved
there in the Columbine situation were obsessed with the Matrix.
And we'll be discussing it a little bit later.
It could be a coincidence, but somehow I doubt it.
Okay.
Could be a coincidence, but I doubt it.
This is nonsense.
I gotta tell you.
The first hour of this show is basically just Alex saying over and over again that the new
Treasury Secretary has been bad-mouthing the dollar.
And this is leading to it collapsing in relation to the Euro.
Fine.
And this is the only thing that seemed actually even interesting in about the first hour.
It is a desert.
Wow.
19th was a tough walk.
It's so great whenever people are like, oh, the Matrix is mind control.
And then you're like, okay, well, 20 years ago the Manchurian Candidate was telling us
that the mind control is happening, and then 20 years before that, and you're like, I just
don't care what you think about movies.
I just don't care.
And look, I would say that probably the Matrix has some ideas that are explored, maybe not
as eloquently as they could have been, and maybe that confuses some people.
Further, it has an aesthetic that a lot of people adopt, and maybe you could trace those
things to some of these shooters.
I don't know.
I also think that, generally speaking, when you have somebody, like, there are a couple
stories that Alex brings up, and it's people who shot somebody and then said they were
trying to flee the Matrix in order to get an insanity plea.
I'm not positive necessarily how these cases shook out, and how much of that was just a
defense argument.
Right.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
Seems like something that could have been a popular defense.
I'll toss that out.
What if I either plead guilty, because everybody saw me do it, or I'm going to shoot my shot.
You know, your shot, you miss 100% of the shots you don't take, though, Dan.
It's true.
Gretzky.
That's what everybody else, that's what they're saying.
Anyway.
Gretzky's dad.
Dad Gretzky?
So, yeah.
I was excited, at least, to hear about Alex's thoughts about the Matrix.
Sure.
He doesn't get into them.
Of course not.
It's a real desert.
I was walking around-
Wait, this is 2003, so Reloaded hadn't even come out yet, right?
It's about to.
I think it just came out.
It just came out.
That's why he's-
Alex does say, like, I'm going to try and go see the Matrix tonight.
Sure, sure.
So it is out in theaters, but, yeah, Reloaded didn't just come out.
And actually, I was going back through it, because I was looking over the plots of those
movies and I was like, I'm not sure I saw the third one.
This plot seems foreign to me.
Oh, look, you could watch it again and you'd be like, I don't think this is- and then you
would forget it tomorrow.
I definitely saw the second one, because I remember The Architect.
Yeah.
Like, I remember that stuff.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I-
Vocabulary instead of writing?
Hmm.
I- sure I saw the third one, because I know if I saw the first two, I would want to finish
it.
Oh, the third one, you know, it's Jesus and then you move on.
But I don't- I was reading the plot, I'm like, I don't remember that.
Yeah, no, I think- okay, let me see if I can-
I think I've seen the final fight scene, like, just in a YouTube video or something like
that, but I don't think I've- I saw the plot, I'm like, I don't remember that.
How much do you remember from the plot that you read?
I'm going to see if I can't off the dome the third Matrix, alright?
I remember broad strokes of it.
Okay.
So you can give it a try.
Alright, here we go.
It opens up, Neo had just passed out, because in the second one he turns out he can use
electric powers in the real world.
Right, right, right.
They wake up and he's actually in the Matrix, even though he's not plugged into the Matrix.
Because he's in the sickbay or whatever.
Exactly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So then, eventually he wakes up and blah blah blah, they meet in the Matrix, they come out,
he and what's-her-face, they both go on Trinity, they both go on a suicide mission into the
evil place, right?
They fly up over into the sky and they're like, ah!
In the meantime, at Zion, the final attack is going on and all the fucking, oh no, and
there's all these blah blah blah blah blah, and that goes on for a while.
From what I understand, so far, so good.
Yeah, there's a guy and he's like po cho cho cho cho, and they got these weird mech suits
and then there's some heroic action because it's a war and it's a movie and you gotta
do that.
And then Neo and Trinity, they make it through, Neo and the AI are both like, hey man, this
Agent Smith dude is fucking out of control, right?
So the AI plugs the Neo into the AI and they're like, you better solve this fucking problem,
right?
So he winds up being absorbed by Agent Orange Smith after a massive, useless, pointless
fight, and then the AI is like blowing them all up and they start over and everybody finally
breaks the cycle and everything's cool for a while at least.
I think that's basically it.
Yeah.
I'm out of breath.
The part that when I was reading over the plot, I was like, I don't remember this at
all.
What's that?
Was Neo negotiating with the robots.
Oh, you don't remember?
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah.
And the robot's face comes out and it's all like, and the robot's mad.
No, I don't remember that.
It was terrible.
I don't remember that at all.
Yeah.
It was weird.
The robot AI did a lot of roaring, which seems like a weird thing for the AI to be
into.
No, because the AI would know what would intimidate a human.
Yeah, but it seems like, I don't know.
He doesn't even have eyes anymore.
So why would you?
He can see.
I'm excited for the fourth one.
That's all I'm saying.
There's a fourth one?
It's coming.
That's right.
I remember hearing that.
Yeah.
I'm going to watch the third one and see if I've seen it because that seemed like, I can't
believe that was the plot.
Oh, it's bad.
I don't know.
It's real bad.
I don't know if it sounded bad on paper.
Like it sounds bad.
In execution?
It does.
It's bad.
I do wonder if the, like, I don't, I don't think, I mean, I'll defend slightly reloaded.
Like I think that's not as bad as maybe some people have said.
I mean, there are some fun things.
The twins were cool.
Sure.
They, they turned invisible for a while and then they showed up.
That was fun.
Yeah.
I got to watch that third one.
We should do that as like a live stream.
As a live stream?
Yeah, I'll do that.
I'll watch the Matrix Revelations video.
See if I actually saw it when I was younger.
I'm in.
Anyway, Alex doesn't get into talking about this much, but he does have some other news
that's fresh from the Bureau desk that's in his imagination.
Okay.
Another saying, forget about ever capturing Saddam.
These are all staged events.
Saddam worked for the CIA starting in 1958.
Looks like they gave him the amnesty deal and, uh, during the campaign, he had requested
it and been refused it and told that if he tried to flee, he would be arrested or assassinated
and looks like in the midst of the war over there, uh, they cut a deal and all resistance
melted away.
So Alex is reporting, uh, basically that, uh, you know, Saddam got an amnesty deal.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
Oh, I don't know who negotiated that one.
I think they left a few people out of the negotiations if he got an amnesty deal.
I think Alex negotiated this with himself.
I think that might've been the case.
So here on the 19th, we've got another familiar theme.
Vladimir Putin was caught in 99 attacking his own soft targets.
That is apartment buildings.
Rebuildings were blown up.
They said the Chechny and the Chechny and screamed, why would we do that and bring on
an attack?
No, the Russian government's doing it.
And then Moscow police, not knowing what the other hand was doing, the left hand, not knowing
what the right hand was doing, caught members of the FSB, the modern KGB that Putin was
heading up for Boris Yeltsin, caught them in the building, planting hexagon explosives.
They got the explosives, arrested them, and then they were raided by, the police station
was raided in Moscow by paramilitary forces from the KGB slash FSB GRU.
So here's the thing.
When Alex talks about these ideas that he has about Putin, he is not talking about just
like, I have a vague sense that that guy's bad.
No, no, no, no.
He's talking about things that are concrete events that he knows to be true.
Now, for him to change his position on this, he needs to show his work.
He needs to explain why is that no longer true?
Right, right.
Were you wrong here or did these events, do you have a new explanation for all of this?
Sure, yeah.
And he doesn't ever do that.
He just sort of switches.
And it's nuts to me to go back and listen to this and see just how consistently it is
just like, fucking Putin, he's false flagging around.
Yeah, it would be ironic if what seems to be one of the main pillars of his everything
is a false flag thing, because these are documented events where you're like, yeah, Putin did
that shit.
So his main evidence that you can follow up on is now not at all mentioned and wiped away,
despite the fact that he still claims that everything is a false flag.
Just not that.
That's strange.
It would be ironic if you weren't aware that he's just a psycho, that none of this matters,
and he's going to use whatever he feels like using however he feels like using it.
So it's completely within his character.
And this also seems a bit more like what you would expect from somebody who's like this
anti-communist crusader type, you know, like Russia and China are evil, as opposed to like,
ah, China's evil, but Russia's actually really cool.
Yeah, Russia's pretty sweet.
Yeah, I don't know, it's, I want to learn more about this.
I like how they keep those women from talking in churches, it makes me feel good.
I want to learn more about this, but I don't really know much more than Alex will not stop
talking about Putin blowing up the apartment buildings in 2003.
There's not really a lot more, like sort of detail to it, but I'm keeping my eyes open
and I'll let you know if anything comes up.
In a very short, has he already been on RT a bunch, or is this, is like in a very short
period of time he will go on RT a bunch?
I'm not sure when he started appearing on that, I know he does after this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I would imagine after.
I doubt he hasn't been on yet.
I doubt they're like, eh, let's see what Alex has to say today.
I would guess not.
So Alex is another guest at this point, it's Dennis Cuddy, he's another conspiracy New
World Order guy.
I love his kids' music.
Basically, Kid Cuddy?
I like his wife, Dr. Cuddy, from House of Beads.
There we go.
Now you're playing the game.
So he's on for like the rest of the show and it's just rambling about basic ass New World
Order conspiracy talking points.
It's a lot of the same stuff we covered in the Endgame documentary and it bored the hell
out of me.
That said, it's a far cry from the content that Alex produces these days.
This is at very least a show that's striving to be about an alleged conspiracy.
It goes off track pretty regularly, it provides horrible information, and it ignores stories
in favor of headlines, but huge chunks of time are devoted to talking about a vague
unsourced accusation about like the Bilderberg Group and Bohemian Grove.
So we're not going to talk too much about this interview, but there is one very important
moment.
Mic down for this.
They used facilitators through various Delphi techniques to do this, and Edward Bernays,
who was hired by William Paley in 1928 as his chief advisor with CBS, wrote a book called
Propaganda.
And in that book he said, we're like an invisible government, we know how to manipulate you,
and at the end he says, sort of like Ross Perot, he says, we need a businessman politician
type to say, I must lead the people, am I not their servant?
Here's what you say you want, and it's really facilitated.
Please continue.
Alex is eating.
Alex is eating!
I'd not heard that in 2003.
Please continue.
Yeah.
So Alex is clearly eating there, but also that also is funny.
Love your stuff, keep growing, keep growing.
Also the content of that is pretty funny.
Yeah, that he's, it's kind of funny that I already brought up advertising and psychology
and then 20 minutes later he's like, Edward Bernays!
And also the businessman leader.
Yeah, that one is hard to look away from.
Yeah.
Alex should listen to some of his old episodes, I think he would be horrified.
So a caller calls in, he and Cuddy take calls, and one of the things that I noticed actually
when I was listening to this is like, Cuddy is old school, like with his New World Order
stuff.
He has the, all the talking points that you'd expect to hear on old time New World Order
conspiracy shows, and I was like, this guy, I bet he knows Bill Cooper.
And so I was looking through the Hour of the Time archives, and he's been on, like back
in 96 he was on Hour of the Time, like yep, that checks out.
Wow.
Yeah.
I wonder what he does for a day job.
I think he writes books, probably goes on speaking things, I don't know.
How do you get that scam?
Anyway, there's a caller who calls in, and Alex has reported that Saddam Hussein has
got a plea deal.
Sure.
And this caller says that one of our old friends, Joel Skousen, is reporting on something a
little bit different.
Skoulnik is reported by Joel Skousen as saying that Saddam Hussein has been moved and is
located now in the side of the United States.
Well, the evidence from the evidence, John, the evidence shows that he was probably taken
down to Russia.
They probably gave him the amnesty deal in the middle of the fight, they can still try
a double though, so look out.
So this is the first reference I've had to someone bringing up Skousen, which is interesting,
that it's taken, you know, we're 19 days into the month of, you know, where we begin in
2003, and you know, such a familiar face in other periods of time, and this is the first
reference to him.
And he thinks that Saddam's in the United States, Alex says nah nah nah nah nah, Russia.
So they're both wrong.
Oh man, these guys, these guys, and also that ending of just leaving it open for, now there
could also be a double cross, you never know, anything could be true.
Right now the evidence of which I have none is all pointing towards this place that I
just made up, so there we go.
So you have, you have Cuddy, who's been on in the month of May 2003 already, and you
also had Colonel Craig Roberts, who was on, who's been on before, so you have some familiar
faces starting to, like, appear to be there, but none of the familiar faces that we know.
You know, I haven't seen any mention of Steve Pechenik, I haven't heard anything about Joel
Skousen, well I guess we just got some Skousen, but Paul Craig Roberts, you know, couple of
other folks who were like, Webster Tarpley, these kinds, Jerome Corsi, these folks are
not figures in Alex's world at this point, or at least have not made themselves known.
There's another person who also has not made himself known yet, and I found it very confusing
that this is the first mention I've seen of him.
Yes, very good show today, my question's a little bit off topic, but I was wondering
if either one of you happen to know what might have happened to Bob Chapman, the gold expert?
No, I don't.
No, I don't know.
What?
We've had Bob on as a guest, but he's still writing his newsletters, basically he's been
criticizing the bankers and they're a little bit angry with him, but go ahead.
Okay, that was basically my question.
So I find it very curious that Alex takes this tone when this caller brings up Bob
Chapman.
For those who haven't heard the episodes covering other periods of time, Bob Chapman is one
of Alex's most regular guests for a stretch of years leading up to his death in 2012.
He's an alleged precious metals expert who Alex used as a scene partner when doing extended
commercials for Midas Resources, the gold sales company that syndicated Alex's show.
Also, Bob claims to have been invited to a screening of a film of Ronald Reagan getting
pegged.
True.
For years, Bob was on Alex's show every Friday.
Outside of people who host the fourth hour, it's tough for me to think of anyone else
who had what amounts to basically a standing engagement on Alex's schedule.
To hear Alex saying he doesn't know what's up with him and sounding like he doesn't want
to talk about it in 2003 is really weird.
Things get even weirder when you consult issues of his newsletter, The International Forecaster,
from back in 2003.
They're not all available online, but there are two that I could find from 2003, January
2003, and even back then, Bob clearly had a working relationship with Midas Resources.
Quote, special offer, you may also order it, and it's in reference to the book The Beast
from Jekyll Island, by calling Midas Resources Incorporated.
Midas Resources will give you a silver dollar from the early 1900s, a $12 value, just for
purchasing the book at its normal price of $19.95.
It seems clear to me that this business relationship with Midas is intact at this point, even prior
to this episode that we're listening to now, so whatever weird energy Alex is giving off,
it seems like it's probably personal.
I read over Bob's newsletters to see if I could find any reasons that Alex might not
want to associate with him at this point.
I'm not sure if I see anything.
In one of his January issues, he predicts an imminent return of the gold standard in
the United States because of the war in the Middle East.
What a surprise that he would want or predict that.
Yeah.
The war is going to put pressure on economies, you know, that's fairly standard kind of stuff,
you know, you could see Alex not disagreeing with that.
He does say, quote, the Muslims believe they can destroy capitalism by forcing gold to
the forefront, and we agree that this could and probably will be successful.
Which is a little weird, but it does not seem like it's outside of Alex's wheelhouse.
It doesn't seem like you'd burn a bridge over that.
What a wild thing to think slash even wilder to say.
Uh-huh.
Some of the next issues that I could find were from July 2003, and honestly, it just
kind of sounds like a transcript of something Alex might say at some point in his life.
Quote, all we can say is buy gold and silver coins and shares as fast as possible.
The ship is sinking and there's no sense in drowning with the rest of the idiots.
Incidentally, exercise your constitutional rights and legally arm yourself and your families
to the teeth.
Whoa.
This isn't going to be nice.
Jesus Christ, I just want to buy some gold, man.
The only thing I can find in there that I could see Alex being pissed off about is that
Bob advises his readers to buy gold and silver, but if they have to invest in currency that
they are going to hide, they should favor the euro or Swiss franc to the US dollar.
I could see Alex thinking this was bad-mouthing the dollar like the treasury secretary was.
Yeah, that would make sense.
I don't know, but that's the only thing that stuck out to me as like, eh, Alex would not
like that.
You should always favor the dollar if you're going to favor currencies, especially not
the fucking euro.
It does seem that when they say, like, what happened to Bob, what they're suggesting is
like Bob went off the rails somewhere and saying that the dollar isn't the single greatest
thing in the world is probably, that's probably enough.
All fiat currencies are evil, but if there must be one, you have to protect the world
reserve currency status of the dollar.
Right, right, right, right.
I don't know.
I could see that being, and I did also get that sense that like something had happened.
There was some problem.
I can't get any sense of like what that's in reference to, but it could be that.
Yeah, because Bob can't get out of pocket, you know, like Bob is expendable.
Maybe.
Yeah.
Maybe not.
He saw a video of Reagan.
That's fair.
Incidentally, Bob Chapman's newsletter is definitely, without a doubt, written by Bob
Chapman.
You know, there's a lot of these folks who have these newsletters that are like, I don't
know, someone just writes it, my name's on it, like Ron Paul.
Bob cannot claim that.
He calls people who don't take his financial advice idiots, and he's basically just fucking
with his readers, quote, don't forget, as interest rates go back up to say 7 or 8 percent,
you will lose money on the value of bonds unless you buy at par and hold to maturity.
Most of you may be dead by then.
We don't have all the answers, but this is the way we see it.
We've been making these kinds of decisions for 43 years, so we guess this qualifies us
to voice our opinion.
It's outrageous stuff.
Considering this is like, it's supposed to be a financial advice newsletter, not a, you're
all gonna die.
Put a hundred dollars in gold and die, idiot.
Yeah.
Whatever, it's life or death.
Bury some Swiss francs and get a gun.
Yeah, what are you doing?
Why is this good financial advice?
Yeah, I have no idea what happened to the two of them, but it's an open question that
I'm excited to learn more about as we proceed.
But we see him later on.
Yeah, I know.
We see him in 2009 at least, you know?
No, definitely.
Yeah.
So I know that there is some sort of a coming back together, and I'm gonna guarantee that
at no point do they discuss what their differences were on there and hash it out.
No, absolutely not.
No, no, no, no.
But I wonder if I'll be able to learn more, like if another caller calls in and brings
up specifics or something, I'm gonna keep my eye open on this one.
So one of the other things that I'm tracking very closely, trying to understand, is whether
or not Alex Jones believes he's fighting the literal devil in 2003.
True.
We know in the present day he believes that the devil is the head of the globalist conspiracy.
That he's speaking to him extra-dimensionally or being possessed by demons.
True.
I'm not entirely sure if that is the case in 2003.
So every time there's some kind of an indication of something, I like to bring it to the forefront.
And I don't know if this says anything about Alex, but Cuddy definitely believes in literal
biblical prophecy.
Hey, alright!
New York is defined in the federal regulations as the United Nations.
And when Rudolph Giuliani stated on C-PAN that we're the capital of the world, yeah,
New York City was the capital of the world, end quote, he was correct.
And that is found at CFR chapter 111.
Dr. Cuddy, any comments to what he's saying?
Well, even taking that one step further, in terms of just biblical end times, you know
Revelation 18 and what happens there, and it has to be a port city, and everybody says
New York, and everybody says, well, that was the World Trade Center.
I don't think so, because when you get around verse 22, remember it says, and a candle would
be seen no more, and that would be symbolic of the Statue of Liberty.
Okay.
So something may be coming up.
Thank you very much.
Amazing information.
So Alex doesn't necessarily jump in with him in the, let's decode, end times.
Revelation, yeah.
But he's also like, oh, that's amazing information, that, you know, like, he's encouraging of
it in the guest, but he's not engaging in it himself.
I find that interesting.
Yeah.
It does seem like he's, I mean, from what we've seen, he's allowed other people.
He's platforming a hell of a lot of it.
He's platformed a lot of biblical talk, but he's always been reticent to jump in on his
own and really give people a full throated, hell yeah, Revelations 18 is how we're going
to get through this, you know.
He does seem to be walking that line a little bit.
So Cuddy takes off after a very long interview, and Alex gets down to business.
I'm going to go see the film Matrix.
It's got its new age message, the paper here in Austin, and the entertainment pages said
it's a new religion in America.
Well, it's not new, it's Hindu or slash Buddhism or whatever, but.
So you haven't seen the movie yet, oh my god, but it's Hindu slash Buddhism or whatever.
But also, maybe, it's designed to make people kill.
I've got a London Guardian story about it, Times of London article, US killers blame
Matrix after random shootings, Matrix firms, films blamed for series of murders by obsessed
fans.
There are films that use triggers to go out there, but the government doesn't even have
to brainwash you now in person.
Certain susceptible minds who are programming through the culture with your big TV heads
can be activated.
I'm not saying the Matrix does that.
We know they have these technologies.
We know there's key indicators in it.
We know that some of the things that Chief Moose said, you know, the duck is in the noose
or whatever is a known trigger, and then Malvo and the other guys show up, the Hamid show
up.
It goes on and on, but I don't like to speculate, but I'll tell you what I've seen if I get
a chance to see it tonight.
I don't like to speculate.
Slap!
All I'm doing is-
Slap, sir!
I speculate wildly, but man, I don't like it.
I pull out my white glove.
Don't be like me saying, I don't like to check into things Alex says, but I seem to do it
a lot.
Frankly, I'm honestly a very quiet person.
I think people have recognized that for a long time.
I don't like to be loud.
It's your natural tendencies.
So, on this 19th, this May 19th episode, we have one last clip, and this is literally
the only mention of the Ba'ath Party that I heard at all, and I should say that we are
now past the point where the policy of de-Ba'athification has been openly announced, and there are people
who are coming out and speaking about getting rid of all party members within government
and such, and here's Alex's take on that.
When there's more tyranny than ever, they're putting the Ba'ath Party back into control
while giving speeches that they aren't.
Ooh, nice.
It's an incredible line.
Well done.
So there we go.
Way to sidestep that one.
Just walk outside.
Oh, that train is coming to hit me.
Excuse me.
Step aside.
Don't care.
Whee!
Yeah.
Jesus.
This isn't going to work for long.
I guess it's fine now on the 19th.
Yeah, for like a day.
It buys you some time, but this is not going to be the way that...
This isn't going to pass the smell test for very long.
No.
I think we'll probably get...
As thousands of people are removed from their posts, it's going to be tougher to be like,
ah, they're still in there.
Yeah.
I think we're going to get more in-depth into this stuff in the coming days of 2003, because
I think that Alex is going to have to try and wiggle a bit, and I'm interested to see
how that plays out.
There's actually a couple of really compelling threads that I'm starting to see in 2003 that
I really want to learn more about.
One is the anti-Putin stuff.
Two is the de-bathification.
Three is Alex and Bob Chapman.
Right.
Well, I mean, and you can just expand that out too, like side characters.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What's our legion of doom here?
Well, it's like, I don't know, you're playing a sequel to a video game or a prequel, and
the main character's the same, but maybe they're in a different place, and so you have a different
NPC character.
Sure, sure.
And different side characters.
It's like the cube.
Yeah.
Yeah, and I'm wondering where the old friends are and who these new people are, and so,
you know, I enjoy, I'm enjoying this a bit more, and I want to continue it, and I want
to learn more.
Do you mean you're enjoying learning and discovering new things like you always have, and now that
you're in the present where we are rarely learning anything and often discovering the
same things daily, this is new and exciting for you?
Yeah, kind of.
Oh, that sounds right.
There's at least interesting context and things to discuss, whereas I think in the present
day most episodes that I do end up could just be like, he didn't read this, he doesn't know.
Dumb, dumb.
So we get to the 20th, and Alex, I was hoping, had seen The Matrix, because you know I love
a movie review.
He said he was going to see it on the 19th.
He did not go see The Matrix.
What?
What, did he get busy?
Yeah, probably.
So, but he's going to talk about it a little more.
Okay.
Also, Matrix Maker rejects crime links.
We're not saying crime links, and I'm not saying crime links.
Some have said mind control trigger links.
Duh!
Bunch of idiots.
This is Alex correcting the record.
Call him David Brock, because he is correcting the fucking record.
I'm not going to let people slander me in public.
Right, crime links, pshaw.
How silly, how silly for someone to think that The Matrix has crime links.
I would never.
They control minds.
Duh.
There's a mind control trigger link.
Right.
Jesus.
Now the trigger makes you commit crime.
These plebes, I'm telling you, stay out of my business.
Anyway, Alex has a guest on.
Sure.
And this is a wild guest for Alex to have on for a number of reasons.
This could never have happened in any other period of time.
Okay.
And it doesn't go super well, but this guy named Noah Schackman, who has an article in
Wired that had just come out about a DARPA program, we'll talk about it a little bit
more, but Alex distorts some of the ideas around surveillance and such in order to introduce
Noah.
It's a new level of corruption, we're all prisoners, the kids are thumb scanning to
get school lunches in thousands of school districts, the thumb scanners are going in
the banks, going in the grocery stores, going in everywhere.
It's total.
It's 180 degrees from what America's supposed to be, and they say it's to stop terror while
the borders are wide open and while the feds are starting to accept in 800 plus cities
the fake IDs of illegals from Poland to Mexico.
And Noah Schackman is on the air with us.
Noah, thanks for coming on the show today, sir.
Thanks for having me.
This is, there's no way to really understate this.
This is, or overstate this, I should say, this is, this is scary.
I'm going to guess that if you were to find Noah Schackman today and ask what he thinks
about having been a guest on Alex's show, you might not get an answer, because at this
point in 2003, Schackman worked at Wired, but now in 2021, he's currently the editor
in chief of the Daily Beast, an outlet that Alex screams about quite often for their very
cruel coverage of the stupid things he says and does.
Wow!
Yeah.
That is a career path.
He's on the show because he wrote an article in Wired about early possible plans from DARPA
to create a project called LifeLog, which would seek to compile all available data on
individuals to be able to tell the story of their lives.
It was outrageously fucked up as an idea, and it did not end up coming to pass for a
number of reasons.
One was probably public backlash, but another was probably the unfeasibility of creating
a system that would be able to do this in any meaningful, usable way.
Yeah.
Now the NSA just grabs our metadata.
Duh.
This is beyond that, though, with the conception of what this LifeLog thing would be.
The primary sourcing on the program was a solicitation from DARPA for people to make
proposals on how to create this program that they had the name for and an idea of what
they wanted it to do, but not much else.
This is to say that there wasn't a program they were testing, they were requesting people
to put in bids to create a program to do some pretty overly ambitious and overly fucked
up things.
America, the Pentagon deserves your money.
As I understand it from the way Noah describes it, the way they were hoping to start some
of this research was to have researchers themselves do mock trips, places, and see if this program
that they had created could log their physical movements, their transactions, and stuff like
that.
Sure.
And it did not work out.
Yeah, no, and also that's astonishingly fucked up.
Yeah, no kidding.
Wow.
I can understand how someone might look at, like, boy, that would be really helpful in
criminal investigations, and I don't disagree, probably would be.
Sure, sure.
No, it would make it very easy.
The fact of it existing has a lot of other ramifications that I don't think.
There would be some problems.
I think that they would outweigh it on the seesaw.
I would say that if you're looking at that program as a positive, you are wearing rose-tinted
glasses at the very least.
Yeah.
The point is, government surveillance is a real issue that is taken seriously by serious
people, and it appears that Noah is one of them.
I suspect that he accepted this booking because in 2003, no one really knew how not serious
Alex is, and how Alex will take any opportunity to use Noah's credibility to advance nonsense
exaggerations of his underlying reporting.
And that's all that's going on here.
And I think Noah's polite.
I will say that.
Okay.
And I think Alex is trying to red pill him.
That sounds right.
The National Association of Banks up in Minnesota, they're doing it.
Now even if you have an account, they're going to want you to thumb scan.
Yeah, you know, like I said, I don't know about that particular program, but I know
that there's definitely an overall effort to make that happen.
Well, that makes the cash digital, and basically a part of a digital system.
You know, there's already RFID tags in the money.
I know, I wasn't worried about that.
Yeah, radio frequency identifiers have been in for six years, and the Federal Reserve
says if you don't keep your money in the bank, they're going to devalue it off those tags.
So what I'm telling you is this is maybe a lot further along than you knew, sir.
Yeah, you know, it could be.
So there's just like...
That's more polite than I would have been when he's like, you know, there's already
RFID in the money.
I'd have been like, fuck you.
And they're going to devalue it?
Fuck you.
How does that work?
If you don't put it in the bank.
How?
Wait, but how would that work?
So this hundred dollar bill that I have...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The RFID chip is going to take a zero off of it.
Wait, wait, so I try and use it, and it's only worth like $97 because I've had it for
too long?
You've had it for too long.
There's also a little ticking timer on it.
How does this work?
You're just renting money by the hour.
Is it possible that what the system would be is that if too many people have too many
hundred dollar bills out, then all hundred dollar bills will be devalued?
Oh, almost some sort of inflation.
Like if there's too much of something, it's like it goes and then it dilutes the overall
value.
I don't know how the RFID chips would be necessary for that.
It seems like they would be extraneous.
Anyway, he's very polite, and Alex starts talking about the finger scanning at the grocery
store that you're going to need to do, and it's like, you know, it's the extension of
self-checkout lanes, and of course, as Alex always does when he talks about this, he's
like, then I'm going to have to bag my own groceries.
Now that's not really a problem, but it seems like he's not happy about it.
Oh man.
This leads to a little bit of a disagreement.
Okay.
I mean, the Biometric Consortium and the grocery stores say they want to pull all the check
out lanes out and make you self-serve and thumb scan, and I mean, I don't want to bag
my own groceries.
That's a more low level threat here, and they're going to put in thumb scan and check out lanes
and then pull out the other ones and make you do it.
That's the plan.
We're only a few years away from this.
Well, I think on this point, I'll agree to disagree with you here.
I don't see this as necessarily a job killer, but I do see it as a really invasive intrusion
into our lives.
Well, what I'm saying is, sir, they pull out three checkout lanes of 10, put in biometric
ones, self-checkout, then they pull out all the rest of the lanes and make you check your
own stuff out.
They're saying they're going to do this.
Right.
Well, I haven't seen that, but even assuming that's true, the biometric part is a little
is nerve wracking to me, but bagging my own groceries doesn't bug me that much.
Jesus.
Yeah.
That's so funny.
He's coming here to talk about the plan that DARPA has to try and log every aspect of a
human life and then expand that to every human on the planet.
And Alex comes back with, I'm going to have to bag my own groceries, man.
I'm not positive, actually, even from reading that-
Wired article.
No, the solicitation for bids.
Oh, sure.
I'm not even positive necessarily that the plan was ever to make it for everyone.
Sure, sure.
Because I think that that even, I don't even think that they would think that was possible.
No, of course not.
I think it was something that could be abused.
Yeah, wow.
Were it to exist?
Absolutely.
Yeah.
The article that Noah wrote, Noah Shachman wrote in Wired, is a discussion of this, a
discussion of the moral implications, people even within the sort of technological community
being worried about this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Problem.
And it's an actual article.
And then he goes on Alex's show ostensibly to talk about it.
Right.
And this is what ends up happening.
Hey, I'm going to have to bag my own groceries.
I'm a serious person.
I have to put my thumb on the groceries.
I gotta go.
And then it's going to unlock them, and that's how you have to get groceries now, and I have
to put them in my own bags.
Another thing that is a concern of both serious people and Alex is drones.
And there is also relevant conversations around that that don't involve Infowars stuff.
And Noah brings up drones.
Are the drones going to bring my groceries to me?
That's not the context of this.
Okay.
But this is how the interview ends.
There's some really creepy uses for drones domestically.
Well, it's like They Live where the little drone flies up.
It even looks the same.
I'm sorry.
What'd you say?
You ever seen They Live?
Uh, They Live.
That's what the, uh, the, uh, rowdy, uh, Roddy Piper movie.
Yeah.
That's the John Carpenter film.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's great.
The drones even look the same.
Is that right?
I haven't seen that movie in a long time.
We got one that can see.
Maybe you can see, uh, Noah.
Thanks for joining us.
Okay.
Thanks much.
I just, I just want more.
I want more of that on my regular news.
I want more of like at the end of a very serious interview with a fucking general or some bullshit
that I'm just being like, Hey, you know, real quick, have you seen They Live recently?
That's kind of a pretty good movie.
Yeah.
I think it's a lot of fun and I wish Alex would have swung harder and been like, did
you know that the Matrix is a mind control trigger?
Totally.
Uh, what?
Go for it.
Once you open the can of worms, I want you to get to Matrix mind control.
Yeah.
So Alex has another guest on after this and it's a guy named Rick Adams, uh, who's a talk
show host out of Rhode Island.
I believe Alex has been welcomed on his show.
And so now, uh, the, the, the favor is repaid.
Sure.
Uh, Alex keeps referring to this station W A L E as a, uh, I think it's like a 50 megawatt
blow torch.
Oh no.
He says that like five times.
Yeah.
Somebody, somebody gave him that and he went crazy.
Anyway.
Um, their credibility is up.
Rick.
I remember 10 years ago, you remember back further than that, but a Patriots talking
about everything that's now happening today and that now what's happened is our credibility
has exploded because over the years, people heard us warn them about all this.
Now they've seen it happening.
So our credibility has skyrocketed.
Absolutely.
You know, when I was in college, you know, a lot of people thought I was the nut and
now generations later or decades later, I meet one or two of my friends from college
and they say exactly what you've just said, Rick, I apologize.
I thought you were the nut.
I was the nut.
I didn't believe because I didn't want to believe, but everything you said was going
to happen did in fact happen.
So you're right, Alex.
So yeah, this dude's a conservative talk show host in Rhode Island.
I'm not sure how wide his syndication was, but I don't know.
He just seems like a kind of like a John Birch society dude.
Sounds like it.
I don't know.
I don't, I don't find him all that interesting.
However, what is interesting is that mentality that they're expressing and it's kind of
like a mantra for propagandists and conspiracy theorists.
I've heard Alex say exactly this same sort of thing in the present day.
I've heard him say it five years ago.
He says this all the time.
This like our credibility is through the roof because everything we've said has come true.
The reason this rhetoric is used is because it's not about credibility or track records
or predictions.
None of these concepts are even real in the game that's being played on these shows.
The goal is to tap into the audience's feelings and provide them with psychological comfort.
They all have memory of someone thinking that they were crazy for their conspiracy beliefs
and it makes people feel better to have their supposed expert hero give voice to those feelings.
But importantly to put them in the past.
You were right to believe me all along, we're on the other side of it now.
This supposed story about Rick's friends from college apologizing for doubting him,
that didn't happen.
That story is constructed to give the audience hope that if they hold strong to their fringe-ass
nonsense, eventually they too will have everyone in their lives apologizing to them for being
too afraid to accept the truth.
You see this really consistently in these sorts of communities, like it's rampant
and QAnon conversations that you see of like, you know, fantasizing about the day that everyone
will admit that they were right all along.
It's weird.
And it can't possibly be like, everyone thought we were wrong but we keep being right and
so our credibility is through the roof.
It can't be right in 2003 and 2020.
No.
Like it can't be right at both times.
And then it also can't be right in all those intervening years when I've heard him say
it.
Do people just constantly forget about how credible you are?
I mean it seems like he's creating a like sign wave of credibility that just goes up
and down depending on the year or the day or whatever, you know, like today our credibility
is through the roof and then tomorrow our credibility is way way down, you know, like
what are you talking about?
Yeah, same with like the globalists are winning, oh no they're losing, oh no they're back
to winning!
Oh god, oh that's terrifying.
So Rick, I was wondering about him, and you know, he's very much in line with Alex's beliefs,
two of them are simpatico, and I was wondering, hey does this dude think he's fighting demons?
What type of world from your studies, Rick, do the globalists want to build?
Well I have to go back to a biblical perspective, and I know this turns off some people, but
I have to say it because I'm not a phony and I'm like yourself, I tell it like it is.
We're dealing with, as the scripture says, forces of evil in this world today.
We're not wrestling, as the apostles said, under, you know, delusion that we're fighting
flesh and bones.
We wrestle against powers and principalities of evil, Alex.
Now I want to say Alex does not respond to that comment at all.
So again, he's platforming somebody who has like a sort of fundamentalist belief, a Christian
belief in the war that they're fighting that is presumably political in nature is actually
against principalities of evil.
Demons.
Yeah.
I furrow my brow at you, Dan.
Why?
Because I want Alex to fucking weigh in and I'm sick of this teasing bullshit.
Yeah I know, I'm a little bit frustrated with it too.
But again, it's another interesting thread that exists in this period of time that we
now have the ability to learn more about and unravel.
And I find that really compelling.
So weird.
It's so weird.
When?
Why?
Why was it not acceptable then?
I mean, I guess it must have been a strategy for him then.
And maybe that strategy- That's a conclusion you could jump to and
I'm not entirely sure if it's correct, but it feels like what's going on.
Totally.
It seems like it has to be, something is going on, but it frustrates me because that sounds
like I'm making a conspiracy theory about something going on, but something has to be
going on.
But that's why we need to learn more and gather more information and evidence.
Of course.
The stuff that some of these other folks are saying isn't too far from what Alex says in
the current day.
Of course Alex yells more and talks more grossly and graphically about stuff.
But it's not too far off in terms of the, we're fighting demons.
But Alex stays away from it himself for the most part.
Which that's why it seems like a strategic decision because he's still booking these
people that he knows who Rick Adams is.
He probably knows this element of his belief and he's comfortable with him expressing it.
He's just not talking the way he would in the present day.
He would pray on air in the present day.
No.
And I mean, with those types of people, you've always got a time to Bible reference.
So it's not like he's been talking to this dude off air for, you know, weeks and they
just have never had the Bible come up.
Like these people have, okay, if you are talking to me within a 30 minute stretch, you're gonna
hear about the Bible.
There's a real good chance.
And it doesn't matter what we're talking about.
Sports, it's going to be the Bible.
It doesn't matter.
You know?
So we have a couple clips left from the 20th and they take some calls.
Him and Rick.
And again, this is the other thing too that was really wild.
Like Cuddy is on for almost two hours as a guest.
Rick is on for a really long time.
And I thought like, like this is long for an Alex interview and it's because they're
like just like right on the same page in terms of those new world order basics and the conspiracies.
He can just have them co-host with you while you take phone calls and stuff and it, again,
it's another thing that feels more like, well, this is what this radio show is trying to
be.
Right.
And, oh, also did not get into whether or not demons are what we're fighting with Shachman.
No Shachman.
I'm going to guess he doesn't think that.
I don't know.
That would be a, that would be a twist.
That would be a nice little twist for us.
So like in the Matrix.
Oh, and the third one when they negotiate with the robots.
We still don't remember that.
Yeah.
So Alex takes this call and this is awesome.
I don't even know how to set it up other than that.
Okay.
This is awesome.
Alex, what happened with your deal when you went down to do your license and they asked
you to thumb scan and wasn't there some kind of an uproar?
What ended, what became of all this?
See the video in a Mariner get destroyed by design.
You ever seen that footage?
No, I've, I've, uh, seen Masters of Terror just last week.
We picked that up really enjoy it.
My mom wants to use it at her church in Wisconsin.
Well, I suggest as a primer road to tyranny is the best we've got the production wise,
but I would suggest you get that one.
They're all great.
Were you able to get around the thumb scan?
No, they have a waiver.
Some people have gotten it.
They will not give it to you and will refuse it.
I could sue them, but then I wouldn't have time to be on the radio six, seven hours a
day.
Right.
Like tonight I'm going to be on Jeff.
I'll be filling in for somebody for two hours today or locally.
I mean, I'm just working all the time.
So fucking funny.
This is one of Alex's biggest early publicity stunts, and you could argue that it's the
closing segment, the like the big piece in his documentary, America Destroyed by Design.
Alex brings in a bunch of cameras when he goes to the Austin DMV to go get a new driver's
license knowing that the process requires a fingerprint.
He brings along eight forms of identification and insists he shouldn't have to provide a
fingerprint to which the people at the DMV say you do.
Alex starts yelling about how Bill Clinton wants his blood and urine next and asking
if the DMV workers are going to stick a needle in him.
It's a petulant display and it's a real sign of the sort of publicity stunts that would
come to characterize his career moving forward.
It's so hilarious that at the end of this story, he just went back without the cameras
and gave the fingerprint to get his driver's license because I know he has a driver's license.
He got a DUI a few months back.
Of course he does.
He didn't get a driving without a license charge.
That is so infuriating.
It's exactly like Alex.
It's Alex to a T.
Well, I mean, I need a new ID, so I guess I'll go get it.
I'll give you my thumb.
Right.
I will go and I will take this stand and yell while there's cameras running and get attention
and incite people into a frenzy about these supposed political beliefs and these like,
I am standing up for all the people, you know, and then, you know, I need to drive.
I will die on this hill two days later.
Listen, I'm real sorry about that.
Yeah.
That's my bad.
And then when a caller calls in and asks, he's like, yeah, you can get around it, but
like, I don't know.
It's really hard.
I gotta be on the radio.
I can't sue people.
I work.
I have a job.
What am I going to do?
Hire a lawyer to do it for me while I work?
No, I have to do all of my own lawsuits.
What am I supposed to do?
The hard work of having a principled stand?
Exactly, yes.
No.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hire a principled stand.
Do you have time to have principles?
Because then do it.
I don't care.
What?
What, you don't have a job?
Fine.
Go have principles outside.
Yeah.
Crazy.
What a coward.
So Alex gets a call from an HEB manager, and this has to do with more of his ideas
about waivers and what have you.
Sure.
So this manager is bringing up that at her place of work, they are now talking about
bringing in a scanner, like a fingerprint scanner, for the time clock.
This is different than the idea of a checkout lane that's connected to your credit card
and what have you.
Oh, man.
But Alex says that this is the beginning of bringing in the...
Sure, sure.
Whatever.
Anyway, the manager wants to ask Alex about ways that she can fight back and not use this
system.
And Alex's advice is so Alex that it's almost laughable.
Here's my thing.
I need to know what is my defense, not to give them my fingerprint.
Well, tell them it's a religious reason.
Tell them that you've been a good employee, always clocked in, not had a problem.
Tell them that you're not gonna be part of this, and if they give you problems, I think
you're gonna have a civil rights lawsuit on religious reasons.
We need to do things like that.
Okay.
What about you?
And is there any place you can recommend, like on the web or a certain spot in the library
that I should look to research this stuff and what my rights are and that I can use
as a defense to our...
InfoWars.com.
I can't even think of what I can...
Well, that's a whole section of study, but it's a whole section of study, but the religious
exemption for religious reasons, you're against that, you should be able to do something there.
Find out more, tell me as it progresses, and I appreciate the call.
I really do, Billy.
I've got a ton of calls and I wish you guys ought to call me back tomorrow or tonight
or next week so I can talk to you more.
We're just up against the gun here.
He's not up against the gun.
He has plenty of...
He takes more calls.
But yeah, there's no advice.
There's nothing.
There's no specific reference that he can give her to help her better navigate this
struggle that he wants her to engage in, and his advice is essentially make up a religious
exemption.
Yep.
Use religion as a prop.
There's no part of like, here is what is violated in this religious belief.
Here is the reason.
Like dietary restrictions, you know, make sense as a religious exemption in various
settings.
I keep kosher.
Sure.
Yeah.
Whatever you want.
That makes sense.
And there are other things, sort of opposition to war, being a conscientious objector makes
total sense.
This, I don't know, I mean I guess what he would do is say Mark of the Beast or something
like that.
Sure, sure.
You're going to scream Mark of the Beast.
I guess that would be the direction that it would go, but I don't know if that really
would stand up to scrutiny.
And it's, to me, indicative of how Alex engages with a lot of religious beliefs.
It's a prop.
Yeah.
It's use it to your advantage to do the things that you don't want to do and not have to
do the things you don't want to do.
Or justify the things.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
And no, I will not tell you where to look into this.
I mean, how could you possibly expect somebody to win a religious exemption lawsuit if there's
a clip of you saying, make up a religious exemption for this?
To be fair, I just want to be totally clear, that's my language that I use to make it up.
He's not saying make it up, but that's how it is.
He is saying make it up, you know?
He's saying find something in your religion that you 99% of the time either don't think
about or don't actually believe.
Right.
Convince somebody that it's the most important thing to you now, suddenly, despite, again,
never having thought about it in your entire life.
Have these arguments very loudly on camera and then go back and stay on your fingers.
I'll clock in.
Sorry about that.
My bad.
Yeah.
Man, it takes so much, it must be so exhausting to convince yourself that Alex isn't a giant,
useless piece of shit.
Like you just heard that clip, wouldn't you be like, oh, well then you're useless.
Your entire life is meant to be fighting at the tip of the spear.
And you are giving me advice that is nothing.
You are the person who has more knowledge and more resources than we do as individual
info warriors out there in the field.
And you had a perfect situation where you had a lot of people supporting you.
They had your back.
You could have been the one to do this lawsuit in order to make sure that all of us could
get our waivers and not have to give fingerprints to get a DMV, get our licenses.
Yeah.
Oh, but then you couldn't be on the radio all the time.
So guess, uh, guess it's going to have to be the HEB manager with very little money.
No time.
Yeah.
No support.
No cult of personality around them.
Their responsibility.
Yeah.
It's a little bit, uh, you know, I mean, it's not new, but it is just a gross, uh, denial
of the self appointed role.
This is a grassroots movement where I exploit the grassroots.
Okay.
You can water the grass or you can suck all of the life out of it for every single scent
that you can steal.
Yep.
Man, that was a good show.
Anyway, uh, we come to the end of this and, and, and like, I really feel like there are
threads that I'm fascinated by in 2003.
I think a lot of stuff is, is, is, is coming up that I really, really want to know where
these things go.
And so I hope to, uh, you know, obviously I'm not going to lose track of the present
day or ignore it entirely, but this is, this is, this is getting me, getting my juices.
I think what it is to me, it's just so uncanny, you know, like I recognize this guy and yet
every time I hear him talk, I'm like, who the fuck is this guy?
You know, like it's so close to Alex, but it's just even weirder.
Yeah.
And we're even taking for granted like almost, uh, how like nutty it is, the, the, the position
on Putin is so like night and day, like it's, that's outrageous.
I can't believe how jaded we are that that completely is like almost pass to a certain,
you know, like, oh yeah, yeah, of course he believes this then and doesn't believe that
now.
Like that's just boring at this point, but that's nuts.
That's major.
That's foundational.
Yeah.
There's a lot of major stuff that is, uh, is going to have to give.
Totally.
And then I want to know where, like, where these people are.
Where are the, the, the experts?
Where are the G Edward Griffin?
Where's that dude?
I know some of them are editor in chief of the daily beast now.
Why isn't Alex like he's, obviously he's talking about gold a little bit, but like Midas Resources
is selling gold at this point.
He's not pushing gold as hard as he does in like years after this.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's interesting.
It's confusing.
I'm excited to learn more and we shall in the future, but until then, Jordan, we have
a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yep.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
We're also on Facebook.
We are on Facebook.
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people
doing God's work.
Yep.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
And now here comes the sex robots.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.