N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating.
Knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying we are the bad guys.
Dan and Jordan.
Knowledgefight.
Need money.
Andy and Kansas.
Stop it.
It's time to pray.
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first-time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your room.
Knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledgefight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes.
I'd like to sit around, worship at the Altar of Selene and talk a little bit about Alex
Jones.
Oh, indeed we are, Dan.
Jordan.
Dan!
Quick question for you.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
Why don't you go first?
Well, obviously, there's only one bright spot for me, Dan.
Yeah, I think I actually know what this is going to be.
There's only one possible bright spot for me.
Is it a really long bright spot?
No, it will be fairly short. No. No, I mean the experience of watching it. Uh, it was it was fairly long
Yeah
There have been longer. There have been there have been significantly longer several hours. Perhaps there were
Matches that have gone over two days before each. Uh, yeah, but
no, uh Rafa and Djokovic played the
I did almost say it
I was thinking about him because I was going in my mind through the greatest matches in all of tennis history
Mm-hmm and
Djokovic and Rafa played the greatest clay court match in the history of tennis
Without question the third set lasted an hour and 40 minutes. Mm-hmm
that is the length of most Rafa on clay matches and that was just the third set and it was just
Spectacular shot may get back and forth. It was no no, I mean it wasn't even that it was impossible shots left and right
It was truly incredible and Djokovic won, unfortunately
But I mean, there's no there's no shame there
Three three points go a different way and Rafa wins six three six three six three
Yeah, and even incredible even if you end up losing a match like that
You were still a participant in it totally there's something to be said for like you were able to go that far, right?
Right you were able to go that hard
Yeah, totally and it's not like Rafa hasn't won enough French opens for people to think he's pretty good on clay. Mm-hmm
He's won a few that's what I've heard. Yeah. Yeah
He's been all right on clay for so for so long, but well, it was just it was incredible to watch
Oh, I'm happy for you that you got to watch that if you were a tennis fan. It was a borderline religious experience
I'm not joking. I got that from your text
Intense it's an intense emotional experience. Well, my bright spot is actually kind of a athletic thing as well. Okay
the recently the switch had the Nintendo switch has
Updated it the game so you can now play Mario parties with people in other places. That's awesome
Yeah, and so I've started playing some Mario parties with folks who live in other states
Okay, some friends of mine and I am essentially undefeated. I
Should grant I accept and I understand fully sure game is mostly random sure sure
It's for children. Well, I understand all these things
Um, but yeah, I've been I've been killing it in the the Mario party game
I don't think there's anything wrong with getting confirmation as an adult that you could defeat children at something. Yeah, you know
It's good. Yeah, it's nice. Sometimes you see kids do stuff and you're like, there's no chance I have at competing with that
Yeah, you know and that makes you feel bad because you're an adult
Mm-hmm, but really beating the shit out of kids can sometimes be well
Maybe that's too far but really beating them can feel good
One of the one of the fun things too about this this Mario party this this iteration of the game is that they have these spaces
Where you can get a friend you can get an ally and so you'll just have like I always play as Waluigi
Yeah, you know like of course you do. Of course
I want to get Donkey Kong or Diddy Kong to be my friend and follow me around the board. Naturally. It's so fun
Anyway, Jordan today we have an episode to go over. We're gonna be back into the present today
Ooh, that's a bad place to be. It is. We're gonna be talking about June 10th, 2021, Blackjack. Ahh!
Again, that's my new response to that. Bummer. Missed. Missed again. Maybe maybe that's the new bit
so it's
It's a day. It's a day. It's a monumental day in a lot of ways
Okay, it is also a day of
walking through
Knee deep mud. Yeah
for Alex's content. I imagine it's a day of
Avoiding topics. Uh, yeah, not a lot of topics come up. Yeah, some very important things like whether or not we're all gonna die
That is dealt with quite at length. I mean that seems pretty important
Yes, unless the answer is no in which case it's not very important at all. Is it? You can put that on the back burner
Okay, that's fair
So today we're gonna get down to business on this but before we do let's say hello to some new wonks
Oh, that's a great idea. So first, Dr.
David strange hate or how I signed up for the patreon to get all of the podcast extras and the exclusive audio feed
But I only got two because everything is uploaded as a video. Thank you so much. You're now policy wonk. I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much. To be clear to dr. Strange, David strange hate and everybody else. There's nothing that is behind a paywall
Yeah, we tried very hard to keep things as far away from a paywall as possible and maybe we could do a better job
putting some of those videos as audio, but
Yeah
Next from brother Ben Matt W. Thank you so much. You're now policy wonk. I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much Matt W. That was from his brother Ben. Oh, okay
I freeze that. Yeah, next Emily Finch. Thank you so much. You're now policy wonk. I'm a policy wonk. Thanks Emily
Oh and Blandy and candy. Thank you so much. You're now policy wonk. I'm a policy wonk
Oh, thank you very much Blandy and candy
Thank you and a couple of technocrats out there. I'd like to give a little wave to first Stevie P's most dirty dossier
Thank you so much. You are now policy wonk and brew ha ha Chicago's drinking pot. Thank you so much
You are now a technocrat. I'm a policy wonk crikey mate. That's fantastic. Have yourself a brew. How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right, we got to go full tilt boogie on this Watson. All right, let's just get down to business
We ain't making that money off that heroin. Why you pimps so good. My neck is freakishly large
I declare info war on you. Thank you all so much
Yes, thank you very much. Not to not to correct you but to clarify I believe Stevie P's dirty dossier is also a technocrat
Correct. Yes, you accidentally said policy wonk. Oh, I'm sorry. Yes. I didn't want anybody
You were gonna get so many Twitter messages that were used to been like, oh man. I appreciate you checking me
I told you before we started recording. I barely got any sleep
Totally that's what I'm here for. I'm not judging you. No, I appreciate the the subtle show
So Jordan we have to do a little segment before we get into today's episode
It's a segment that is taking the world by storm seems to be giving someone life is giving someone death
You could say that
Oh life is death you can that's true. Yep, so Renee
Who is the best cat uncle and snail dad who had a birthday on the 6th? Happy birthday. Happy birthday
Also, this is this is a this is a weird one
Mm-hmm. So Sarah sent me a message and said that her friend Joe has a birthday in June June here
Okay, so happy birthday Joe
All right, Joe Sarah also told me that Joe will not say when his birthday is interesting just that it's
I like this. Yeah, I like this a great deal. I am completely Phil Hartman in news radio
I'm conflicted on one level. I enjoy people retaining some mystery in their life, of course
But on the other hand, I'm like just tell your friend when the birthday is
If you're not on Facebook, they might not remember anyway these days most people need that Facebook reminder to get a birthday
I mean, there's only one way to
If somebody doesn't want to tell you their birthday, then you have to surreptitiously discover it in any way pop
You know, like follow them to the DMV one, right? You know just and then be in the corner just with a little
Pair of magnifying glasses or your opera glasses if you will something along those lines, you know, you have to do something
You gotta reach out to a podcast and have the host
Oh, yeah, that's a good idea tell it tell Sarah what day your birth why haven't you texted his parents? They're there
They're ready and waiting to give you their birthday. Yeah. Also, this is not a birthday. This is a congratulations to Camry
This is graduating from the University of Ottawa. Oh
Okay, engineering degree. I realize this is now just spiraling completely out of control
We've lost it completely. This is this is our new show. Basically, I don't even know if we do Alex Jones related content anymore
And we have one more one more birthday message
This this fella Eric actually sent a message. He wanted me to read and be
Jordan just shook his head. No, no. Sorry Eric Eric. Love you. That's a big that's a big shake of the head for me
Happy 22nd birthday, Alexandra
You're the happily ever after in my story, and I hope you have a wonderful day
Remember to work for progress not perfection and keep sight of what's on the other side. There you go. All right
Well, I'm not doing that again. That's a good wedding toast, but I don't think it's ever happened
I'm not doing that again because we are getting dangerously close to territory that I am deeply uncomfortable
No, we're we're borderline morning zoo crew at this. Yeah, but but Alexandra. Hope you have a great birthday. Yes, of course
boy
Being born is a condition that leads to death
You can say that life is a disease that ends in death. Happy life is death day to all of you. Absolutely
So Jordan we got to get this episode June 10th to go over
All right, and here's not a context drop from today's show. My testicles are like, I guess like superstars. Yeah. All right
Alex's testicles are superstars in what like in testicle related fields or or like
As celebrity is it an influencer situation here as testicles average 17
Rebound last season. Okay, so he starts out the show and I would describe it as
Bad weird mood if he were anybody but himself sure since he is himself. It's a regular morning
I would describe it as a pretty normal
Now I've been saying this a lot before the shows just because all I do is tell you how I feel
But I'm having a real trouble doing these products. It's a great way of putting it. That's a really great way because of
how this is really
Starting to set in on me that this is it
And they're really killing people all around us and maybe people all around us and I was already ready today to come on air
And look at the real numbers of the unprecedented amounts of young people
having heart attacks having strokes even dying from the so-called COVID vaccines and
then I
Was sent a big Twitter feed
By a good friend of mine a national talk show host about a 30 minutes for the show
so I ended up reading this Twitter feed of medical documents and CDC numbers and
I
Actually got dizzy and almost passed out Alex almost passed out cuz he read a Twitter thread Wow
Yeah, it's it's a little much it's kind of amazing how
Accidentally self-aware that first bit. All I do is get on the radio and tell you how I feel
Yeah, it's such a great like yeah, man. Yeah, you got it. You have identified the problem
Yes, you nailed it. All you do people tune in to hear you feel things. Yeah, and it's
Terrible, it's somehow weirdly cathartic for people who are really angry. Yes. Yeah. Oh god. No, that's me, isn't it?
Fuck. Yeah, I um, I was interested in what was going on here. What was up with this Twitter thread?
I wasn't so interested in his like I'm so angry. I can't do the show. Sure. It's so we've heard it
Yeah happens all the time. Yeah, the present day is like it's it's it's so boring with something that's so
Interesting. Mm-hmm. Like anybody else doing this would be
good groundbreaking
Anybody who had a boss
Oh my god, they're gonna get fired. Yeah must mean it
This is how TV shows start and then they get worse from there, but the first episode you like
Yeah, it's Alex Alex talks a little bit more about this
You know, you have that effect where quote women would get overwhelmed by something and just pass out
And that's really the point. I've gotten to where I'm just like
Nothing's stopping any of this. It's just rolling forward. I was reading
about hundreds of thousands of people getting sick from the shots that are young how they're targeting our children and it just
Pisses me off. And so my brain says go out and you know, do you know what people are doing this?
I just it's just overwhelming. It's just overwhelming to watch him kill us like this
So
It is overwhelming that's pretty overwhelming
so I looked up the most recent information on the CDC's website and there have been reports of
5208 deaths of people who have gotten one of the kovat 19 vaccines. All right
This is out of 302 million doses administered which represents a point zero zero one seven death rate. Oh, that's too dangerous
So like but that's even if you assume the ridiculous absolute worst-case scenario that all of the deaths are even related or linked to the vaccines
At all, it would be a point zero zero one seven
It's just too dangerous for a vaccine Dan and the truth of the matter is that they are not all connected
No, of course not. So so it's too dangerous to even hear about the vaccine. I guess so
Yeah, it's also there is something that's been happening
Lately there have been some more more reports of younger people having some heart inflammation
Sure, that could be connected to vaccination and it's something that needs more study
Of course, there have been 623 reports of myocarditis or pericarditis in persons aged 30 or under post vaccination
These are primarily males and and through review of medical records. The CDC was able to confirm
268 of these reports none of these cases have resulted in deaths and only 15 ended up hospitalized with 41 of them experiencing ongoing
unspecified symptoms
This is not good obviously and it's something that the CDC is investigating and when they have more information
We'll know a bit more about it
but the way that Alex is dealing with this story is just sensational to the point of
Being dangerous like yeah, it makes me want to do you know what yeah, we do know what yeah
You're talking about killing people. It is it is amazing that he's he's exemplary. You know, he's he's doing part of the trolley
Ethical question where he's like, you know, we can't
Hurt one person with a vaccine to save five other people's lives
What we need to do is
Throw that person in front of the train and then have the train run over the five people after that
And then I live happily ever after and that person I'm gonna throw in front of a train is a doctor. Yes, exactly
Yes, I'm going to get all of these people killed and then I'm going to jump on top of the train and fly
Yeah, so the first hour I would say is meandering
It's it's a bit meandering and it's unfortunate because as we as we learn in this this next clip
Alex has so much news that he's so big like his balls. He's getting chills
20 years ago out of a hundred or articles or so. There might be one really big one. I
Have more than 50 devastating reports that are confirmed that send chills up my spine lightning round
And
It's just it's the real realization of how screwed we are
It'd be like if I walked outside and looked up at the Sun and saw it like explode and I'd go oh my gosh
It feels something kind of like that it's it's like the whoo Wow
because they have set something in motion that is the planned organized total collapse of
Civilization and mass death. So Alex is in a bad mood
We're all dead
It's pretty definite there doesn't seem to be much wiggle room. No, no, this was this would seem serious if here if you're
Think that's the end for all of us
Even if it was the planned explosion into a red giant earth is still gone, man. Yeah
Yeah, and that the way he's speaking about this is obviously meant to be like there's nothing that you can do. We're all fucking dead
Yeah, yeah, and it's um, I mean, it's certainly not inspiring
That's the that's not the up-over-the-hill man charge that you necessarily want, right?
I know that Patton when he was giving some of his sort of famous speeches generally be like we're fucking
We're screwed
We shall fight them on the beaches. It won't matter. You're all fucking dead. I saw the song blow up
So I think that if you see the Sun blow up metaphorically
One of the things that you might want to do is run away to a bunker
You know, I mean if it's the Sun you I would just lay down and be like, let's do this man
There's no hope at this point. That's why I said metaphorically. Okay metaphorically you might want to run away to the hills
Sure, and Alex is certainly feeling that pressure. Okay, it's the end of civilization
Fast and it's not even a selfishness, but my very cells
Say get out of Austin get your family out and go to the most remote area and dig in now go
But if we do that the globalist win boo, and they're gonna accelerate their collapse and finally dig us out of our holes later
Every show is now coming out with dystopic mass death planetary extermination robots killing us
under you in command because they're
Pre-conditioning everyone to accept that and that that is the future that's about to unfold and I mean the video games the movies
All of it. What about movies from like the 60s about robots? No, no
I don't know
Battlestar Galactica never happened every movie is now about the UN having killer robots
That's true I find it so funny that we're also in the past and he's like
I'm pretty sure that Saddam is in the United States or he's in Russia in Australia
And then he's like they're gonna come and dig us up out of our holes and I'm like, ah, you don't even know man
Oh you in the past don't even know
Some people get dug out of holes buddy
Yeah
so Alex is pretty pretty doom heavy here like even actually kind of more so than usual like I think a lot of the
Time he doesn't descend this deeply
Into that abyss. It seems early too. It's it was immediate. Yeah, that's
You gotta you gotta ease me into that. It was immediate and it kept going over commercial breaks
Like you'd go to commercial and he'd come back and he was still doing this. All right. Okay fucking die
All right, so we're in we're in full-on the the guy and watchmen shouting for the end of the world territory
That's what was that's what's going on. Well, here's the situation Jordan when you have been like, let's say I
Don't know convicted of a horrible crime and you're put in front of the the firing squad. Sure. They'll put a little
A blindfold over you. Yeah, I was polite. Yeah, so you don't have to see the bullet coming
You don't want to do that Alex is doing the opposite and in this next clip
He wonders if maybe he shouldn't do the opposite. Maybe he should allow people to just have a blindfold. Okay
This is not a deer in the headlights moment, it's
It's almost obscene
To even tell everybody this it's kind of like they put a blindfold on somebody who's in a firing squad
so they'd have to watch themselves be killed and
They and they give you a cigarette maybe a little bottle of brandy an hour before
also polite
So, you know what
The public's not gonna wake up and stop this anyways, they don't want to they're that we're cursed
We kill our babies they kill our old people. And so I guess I
just guess prepare to have everything collapsed and
Destroyed and and to die. I mean, I guess that's just really it prepare to die seems to be Alex's message
Today, I mean that's a what what day was the 10th was that those Thursday that was Thursday
Yeah, right before the weekend. I get it. No, I get it. You know, it's like Arthur Dent
You know, it's like Arthur Dent. He just never got the hang of Thursdays man that happens. What are you gonna do? It's tough
You know, it's like everybody's working for the weekend. Mm-hmm. It's just rough. Yeah lover boy
Pissed off his hell about Thursdays
So there might be an answer yeah, maybe and from listening to this clip
I don't know if this is exactly the message you're gonna take away from it
But it seems to me like maybe the answer is blindly accepting whatever Alex wants you to do
And not questioning anything and just doing it
Wow seems to be what he thinks will solve all the problems in the world vis-a-vis the globalist. So he's starting a religion
maybe
Because this mad scientist evil
this post-humanist evil
Has figured out all the angles
and the only way you beat it is recognizing the angles and it's full spectrum assault and then do the exact opposite but
Instead the public likes to debate and argue and act silly and and and fight with each other at the low level
And if you do that
We have zero chance if we just woke up and accepted god
And and did what god said to do and stood against the new world order then this evil would just evaporate like
Phantom is it gone?
That everybody can feel it everybody can see it
And
That's just what it comes down to so here's what I'm gonna do
Here's what i'm gonna do i'm gonna make sure we stay on here as long as we can and make sure that that's dealt with
Make sure our own house is in order
And then i'm gonna come back and i'm gonna hit all this finish
As best I can i'm just gonna cover it and then that's gonna be it
What
Alex you're still doing a great job, but maybe next few segments you can't put stuff on screen because
I'm here talking and they just put a screen clip up
Of people in new york saying we want to wear masks forever. We don't want to take them off. We like them. There are blankets
Sure
And that's something I was going to cover later, but see
That's painful to look at
And so i'm right on the edge of just not being able to handle this anymore
Plus it it then just becomes a distraction
From what i'm already covering what i'm doing and i'm not bitching at the crew
I told them to put stuff up on screen. It's just this point. I may have to start doing a show in a radio booth
And the crew can go run other shows or something and i'm just going to go back to reading articles and covering those because
Because I can't look at joe biden. I can't look at the mask cult. I can't look at another animal human clone
Aren't we already dead? What's going on? Okay, so if I understand correctly, here's how the show is going so far
I think also that clip is very indicative of how the show is going. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, please
Yeah, so if I understand correctly, we're all dead. We're all already dead. Yes. We need to prepare to die. Yeah, uh,
My crew put up a picture of joe biden and uh people supporting him
So I am going to throw a hissy fit. I'm gonna go off the air. Uh
The end I don't even think it's i'm gonna go off the air
It's that i'm gonna i'm gonna threaten to just do radio now because i'm too distracted by images. That's bananas
That is unprofessional to a level of like I think pathology. I think I think it's honestly just solving the wrong problem
you know
I'm too distracted by pictures to do my job and therefore get rid of the pictures
I guess I guess it is a solution
But you know if somebody jangles plastic keys in the room, I can no longer function as a human being
So just get rid of all plastic keys everywhere dan. It makes perfect sense. That does make sense unless
Jangling plastic keys are a major component of your job. There is that yeah, that is a problem
Yeah, I do work at a jangling keys factory. So there is there are a lot of disorienting things. You might have to learn
how to
Focus your attention, uh better you could change you that was possible. I'm just tossing that out there. Yeah
yeah, and I and I think I think that that also the idea of like
If you just saw all the angles and all this we would just be able to defeat the new world order
Yeah, like that's that's just your code for like if everybody just thought the exact same way I did. Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah, nonsense if we all just did what god told us to do who's telling me what god is telling me to do
Let me ask you that question because that's a really important question. Spoiler alert. It's alex. Yeah, that sounds right
so, uh the vaccine side effects are something that alex is
Greatly exaggerating and not dealing with seriously. Um, and uh, if you need any more evidence of that
You know, the worst thing is uh, reading all these federal documents
And how they know by design that they're giving the young people shots now that are going to mess up their hearts livers and brains
And lungs for life, which is not going to be very long
And then of course I I knew this a while ago while they're doing it
Not just about killing you
Yeah
It's a sacrifice to the youth and that pleases their god
And also it's going to weigh down and hurt their families and cause great anguish in their families
Because you're supposed to bury your parents not bury your children. Yeah, you see you see
These vaccines the the the side effects that people might experience are a sacrament to satan, right? Yep, right, right
right
I just can't disagree with any of that. Sure
It's just airtight. You're not supposed to bury your parents
Or I mean the other way around i've heard that said yeah parents not supposed to bury their child
Yeah, see there we go
And then if that makes sense, I assume that all the preceding arguments have to make sense as well it all it all tracks
Yeah, so the public is in a trance and that is a problem for alex because his whole thing is about like
Dealing with people who aren't in a trance. Yeah, but it seems like that is the better thing if we're all gonna die
No matter what as he was arguing earlier, maybe just let people stay in the trance put on a blindfold
Yeah, I think that alex is essentially admitting failure here because
His self-appointed role is that guy who yells and wakes people up out of their trance exactly
So if his primary complaint is that people are too much in a trance that means that you are ineffective at the job
You have given yourself. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, so I don't know if I don't know if I would be proud of this next clip
If I were alex, okay, and then I just see the public mesmerized
Into a trance watching their sports and playing their video games
And I can't join the globalist because that
That's evil and I don't want to prey on people and then most of the public he says predator. I'm saying
I guess we're just here to tell the truth and let people make a decision for themselves and it'll all work out in god's plan
but uh
I mean, I feel like i'm being punched in the chest right now
And I I don't know what it is. I'm supposed to do to not feel like that
I don't really feel good about everything i'm doing quit your job and almost always when I feel like this. It means there's some answer
There's something we're supposed to do right now. I'm going to stop this
I guess that's really what it is. I feel extreme guilt
And I'm not someone in my life that feels a lot of guilt
You should I know that you should feel a lot of guilt
That's why I may have to go off here today because I don't want to just sit up here and talk about how I feel
Oh, this isn't some calculated thing before I came in today to say all this I I I
I have stacks of government documents stacks of reports that are all total nightmares all ten on a richter scale of tyranny
Just
Just some person nearby just needs to be like alex. Just do your job
Yeah, just shut up and do your job. Yeah, what are you doing? Don't talk about how well you could do your job. Yes
Don't talk about how it's everybody else's fault. You can't do your job a little annoying just do your job man
Just one time and I would I would argue that it actually is
A calculated thing that alex is doing and not necessarily because he decided to get on air and act like a weirdo
It's that he didn't prepare at all exactly
He chose not to get ready to do his show at all. And so he has to fill time rambling about nothing now
We're all gonna die
You can't just come out and say sorry. Yeah, I have to burn an hour because i've only got two I have
Too much news to get over. I have to talk about all of this
I'm gonna kill a third of the show saying
Complete horseshit, nothing gotta gotta do that. I gotta do that to really get into the news
But you know what else he has to do. What's that predict things? Okay
And we'll be sitting here in a year or two with you know, run 10k to raise money
Because you know all the neurological problems and they'll have movie stars up there. Well, let's get together and
Finally at a certain point 10 years down the road or even sooner they'll say well
Folks are signing on to volunteer to be euthanized
because they know they're too much of a weight on society and
They'll get some extra money and get to party for a few weeks before they are killed
And that's all the plan here. That's the plan
Is this plan f now?
We got a lot of plans on the air a lot of plans up in the air all the time
I don't know. I don't know if I can handle this many plans. They don't seem like complementary plans. No, they sure don't
Yeah, so then two years celebrities will be doing
5k charity things. Yeah, I would assume that's true not necessarily for people who
like were hurt by a vaccine side effect from covid but sure, you know, there are certainly
You know experiences that people have had about long covid, you know, there's totally there are
Things that we will learn moving forward that we're not aware of now or we're starting to become aware of now
I could see celebrities doing fundraising for some sort of charity
Uh in that line. Yeah, 10 years from now
Alex believes there will be so many people who have been hurt by the covid vaccine right that there will be
euthanasia
Uh drives going on where you get to party
Aha a little bit if you agree to let them kill you get a little extra money. Yeah, and you then that's for your family
Yeah, okay
So it's a little bit like looper is that kind of what we're dealing with here?
We're dealing with you sign a contract for about 10 years and then you get killed like I I I guess
It's kind of like suicide bombers, but without the bomb it does seem a little bit like that. Yeah, I don't know
I don't I think this is uh, one of them, uh, predictions that alex is gonna forget he made
Who's gonna run the 5k's 10 years from now when we've got all these euthanasia drives going all the runners will be dead
I assume they're the first to go. Uh-huh
So when you were worried about like who's gonna be uh, interpreting the words of god. Yes
And I told you it was alex. Yeah, I tend to be worried about that, too
I believe that it's alex primarily because he seems to think that churches are all full of betrayers. Well, there's that so this is
in today's stuff
And your church isn't gonna say a word
They just want to party
They just want to have a good time a lot like churches. I know well, I'm not gonna say a word
Have a good time a lot like churches. I know
Hell
You're not gonna find more satanic group of people than the folks that run the churches
Because they're the real betrayers that went there to make sure there wouldn't be a church to fight this when it was needed
So i'm sorry folks i'm real sorry
And i'm not trying to depress you, you know, it means god's plans real and we're being judged but this is gonna be rough
My church wants to party all the time
God there were so many fucking parties at my church when I was young. Oh god all the time
Non-stop partying even the parties that we did have at our church weren't fun. No, we didn't even have communion wine
We run out from so many fucking parties. Dan. We we in our youth group. We had like, uh, every every I think it was every
sunday, uh, we have evening sunday evening, uh, just youth group, uh,
Services or whatever and afterwards they'd get uh papa john's pizza. Yes, right. Yeah, but you had to pay for slice
That's not fun. That's not a party
In the church. Yeah. Oh, man
You realized jesus would have run in there and started throwing pizza all around the place like no commerce in this motherfucking place
Right flipping the pepperoncini box. Of course get the also olives olives. Yeah, it was uh, not fun
I'm jesus and I don't like olives this episode is just a mess
yeah, like the whole first hour is this it is outrageous like and it's
it's even worse once alex starts trying to explain why he's feeling the way he is because
It's just such bullshit
So here's what sent me for a tailspin because I already knew all this but it kind of all crystallized 10 minutes for the show
And then
There's some things I want to tell you and I can't tell you because the sources they told me not to sure
and i've never
michael own a source and i've never given information out sometimes there's information you can't get out because
If you get out any of it
It gives it away from the source before they finish the work they're doing but there's a major counter-strike to all this in the works
right now
But uh, it's been confirmed the documents have been seen that this is a kill plan. So there's a kill plan. Um
Okay
All right
So yeah, alex has a source that he can't give up sure and he can't speak in specifics because the source, you know
Blow their cover still working too hard. Yes still working under under cover
I guess is alex talking to steve again. Is this a double agent situation?
Is this somebody in the government who's viewing the kill plan documents?
Anybody who actually has access to anything would never talk to a dick like this
No one would talk to alex
He gets on air and talks about how we're all gonna die for an hour at the beginning of his show
Yep, i'm gonna be like, oh, hey alex. I've got to get your brain in on this
See, this is why I just can't be allowed to be part of the government because I swear to god
I would crank call alex at least once a week and be like i've got some documents for you
I'd send him pictures of bullshit. It would never not be hilarious to me for them to show up the next day
Yeah, it would just never not be fun. I'm not certain that you have to work in the government to do that
Get yourself a proton mail, uh
sure
You could probably uh plant some stories lieutenant colonel bull s hit
At protonmail.com. Mr. Bull
My grandpa served
Under you and uh, which one did your great grandpa serve in was the north or the south which one was it?
Texas, okay, texas. Okay. Okay. I got you
Um, so yeah
I guess alex was sent into a tailspin at the beginning or right before the show because of some secret information that he got from
a source
Or a twitter thread that he read that almost made him pass out sure not entirely sure which
It is but maybe his secret source is this twitter thread. I don't know
I mean, I understand being thrown off by what would be relatively petty things
like one thing that threw me off during that clip was literally going like
Why don't I remember the theme song to tailspin?
And then I realized that because every time I think about the theme song to tailspin I go did it tailspin we and i'm like
That's ducktails. That's ducktails. I can't do that. Do you remember tailspin?
I think I did the exact same thing that you did in my head just then yeah
I think that it might not have had lyrics. I remember having loud drums
I think the tailspin theme song didn't have lyrics. I think it was just instrumental interesting
I'm, not sure but I did do the ducktail set
Totally totally so we got a kill plan on our hands not entirely sure exactly how this is going to play out. Uh,
Who do you think is way up at the top of this and I i'll tell you sure not a person organization
Okay, so if you're asking me it can't be the un that seems too obvious
Well, actually i'm asking you because we've been listening to this show
for all the time that covet has existed yes, and
You should know
By now who's running all this? Oh, if there's a kill plan sure who's running it. Well the devil, of course
No, no, no, no. Oh china. No biden. No
Stelter. No fauci. No
the cfr
No
the un no
Brazil no, who cares?
I've been talking to folks that have seen the official government plans. Uh-huh cia put out by the
major foundations
oh the uh
carny endowment
That's why the carny endowment is not in full control get bill gates once again. The cia is run by the carny endowment
And it's just a total extermination plan. I mean final solution. We're all dead
It's like wow. Wow, you guys are really evil because I knew they were evil but man
It's bad enough wanting to wipe out third world people
I don't want to kill them, but I know that
They don't have jobs futures any of that. I'm not signed on to kill them. But this plan is to kill everybody
Whoa, that got weird at the end there
Um that is that's just bad writing
That's just bad writing to all of a sudden come up with a brand new villain at the very end to swoop in and cause
That's like if at the end of the scooby-doo episode. They took the mask off and they're like
Terry from three towns down the street. What are you doing here?
And he's like, oh just do this i'm certain that alex has never been like big on the carnegie endowment, but it's true
That was not some
Organization that's come up as one of our even in the mix. No players. No, not tertiary not tangential just gone
John's hopkins is constantly a villain the gates foundation. Of course nation naturally, uh, cfr, obviously
Yeah, the uh, the rockefeller foundation
Yeah, I don't know. I I uh
I mean the rothchilds are always in the mix. You could have just tossed the rothchilds in there. Nope carnegie endowment carnegie endowment, boo
You know, you know what you have to do to destroy the world dan practice practice practice also fuck alex
We're saying uh that stuff about people in the developing world. They have no future. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh fuck yourself. Fuck yourself
Um, so alex has these sources that have told him about the kill plan and he doesn't just believe these sources now
I should tell you he does just believe these well naturally, but he doesn't just believe no
I mean, I see i've just got stuff like that going on
And I don't just believe people that have seen the documents
I can see the documents all in front of me how they're implementing it
Everything I was told by the individual that saw this plan
And held the plan is in event 201. The plan is in lockstep. The plan is in crimson contagion. The plan is all there
But but specifically they've reached the point now of recruiting
Levels deep into government corporations and are have gone operational now
So they're even telling people the plan to get them on board
Hey, like, uh, you know, you and your family are going to live
If you want to be part of that 500 million that live
It's on the georgia guide stones. You better get on board right now and you'll get up space for your family
during the collapse
But of course you read deeper and this is what these individuals were able to see
it's exactly what they've told us that they believe all humans must be gotten rid of and
And above that there's not much knowledge, but everybody including top pentagon four-star generals
They think it's aliens some deal has been made with aliens to kill everybody
and then the people that the small group that does it gets to like
Like the board or whatever join these things. I
Man, all i'm telling you is is that everybody's dead
That's all I can tell you everybody's dead
I mean
If the if true, uh, I I guess there's nothing really we can do right? I mean if you make a deal with aliens
Um, that's out of my that's above my pay grade four-star generals
Think there's a deal with aliens
Then we gotta get new generals. Yeah, that would be good
Um, yeah, there's been a deal with it. Yeah, there's only gonna be 500 billion left. We made a deal with aliens
It's a real bummer. Yeah, I mean on the one hand what if the aliens other deal was like we kill everybody
That's a good deal
Um compared to that. Yeah compared to the human extinction if we live in a scenario where there is kill everyone
Or kill all but a hundred people. Yeah, obviously kill all but a hundred people is the preferable option to everybody dying. Exactly. Um,
Yeah, I mean it's all made up. So sure
Sure. Sure. It's we go back to the trolley problem again. Alex is just feeling bad
What if there are 7.7 billion people in front of a train and we've got a hundred we could save
I think it makes perfect sense
So you got to just get right with god because everybody's gonna die and alex is just he's giving very little hope
Uh at all in this first hour sure get right with god. Do the aliens know god?
It's it's debatable whether they're actually aliens they might be demons they might be demons that's fair
You're right. So you got to get right with god and then alex introduces a guest
He's gonna have and mike down for this because he honestly sounds a little bit pissed that he's gonna be interviewed
Oh no
And the dominoes are falling the the the the the the program has already started the countdown is here
And I I don't know what to do. I just get right with god. That's all I can say
Instead we'll talk to my pillow guy
Which will be fun. I'm sure nice guy really cares. That's a good heart fight the tyranny. Wow
Wow
Get right with god
You can almost hear the silent we're gonna talk to the fucking my pillow. Yes, totally. No. No, I heard it
I heard the fucking that was not spoken so loud
so this is the episode of mike lindell from my pillow comes on for his first appearance on info wars, which is
Baffling that it's his first appearance. That is baffling. Yeah for it says a lot for a guy to go from
Um, limerick soap man to shit talking the my pillow guy
I'm, just saying maybe you're uh getting above your britches there, buddy
Well, I was thinking about like what the dynamics are here and why alex might be like
Not super happy about this and I think why mike wouldn't be super happy about this either
Is is because neither of this is neither of their first choice. No
um alex probably doesn't want to talk to him because he's nuts and he sounds and
He has the potential to drag alex into litigation with uh, you know slanderous claims. Totally. Yeah
Yeah, he's throwing him around like water. Yeah, and I think that he's somebody who
Um, you know, you could you could end up getting uh dragged into court
for having too close of an association with particularly in uh,
This sort of a setting interviewing them and allowing them to broadcast
slanderous claims
about uh
Various things it does people and organizations. It does seem like mike lindell comes along with the same
Producer as like a prank show where after you talk to mike lindell some lawyer just runs up to you real quick
And he's like, okay. I just need to give you a quick interview. You're gonna need to sign this statement
Exactly. Yeah
um, so and I also think that mike can't be super happy about this either because
He's been in the trump orbit in one of these people for a while now
If he wanted to be on info wars, he would have been on there long ago long ago
He would have been on there when roger was on and when the good days were going
Yep, and the reason that he didn't is because obviously no one wants to be on info wars. It's the last resort
Even for these shit head grifters for the my pillow guy
Yes, this is slumming it mike lindell is doing this because he's not allowed on those other channels anymore because he's being sued
by smartmatic and dominion and those claims are all he wants to talk about and those those
Networks just won't let him uh spread that shit. So where can he info wars?
Alex is the last person who will let him the tv networks are better lawyers than mike lindell's lawyers
Because they're the only people who are like no we can't have you talking about your case on air
We're going to learn that mike actually just lost his lawyer
That makes sense a little bit later in this interview. That sounds right
So alex before he gets into the actual interview with mike lindell
He's gonna he's gonna talk a little bit about how the last hour was pretty heavy
And it was yes
I got pretty wound up last hour got into some heavy issues
But i'm just telling you where the globalists want to take us if they succeed they're going to fail
But as we get mike lindell back on and ready
Please remember we're lister supported and I thank you all and you're amazing
Uh, just like they tried to bankrupt and shut down mike lindell. They tried to shut us down
But thanks for your support. We're still on air and still more effective than ever
So we're introducing the brand new mega immune support supplements fun. Jesus. Yep
Oh if you add mega you're you're you've already admitted you're done, you know the moment you're like
You know the moment you're like, this is our mega health supplement. You're making bullshit up very much. So yeah
It's it's interesting to me though the way that alex spends an hour saying we're all dead. Everybody's dead. Fuck it
We're gonna die. It doesn't matter
We're all dead and then he sort of tries to walk it back there with like
I'm, just talking about what the globalists want to do if they win they're gonna lose
Like as if to undo
All that he did in the last hour
Yep, that hour could have been anything else than anything anything else. Yep. It was meaningless
It's a completely meaningless hour of just a guy
Trying to get people scared. Yeah, and and hopeless
I mean
Okay
so
What he did was spend an hour telling us that we're all gonna die
And then his way of apology is like this is only if they win and they're going to lose
Now that first hour would be valuable if you were giving me steps on how to make them lose
Uh, right because you you're giving me the intense fear
Oh, well, maybe yep. You know what? Never mind. You're right
That hour was incredibly important to letting me know why I need to buy those mega supplements
That's the that's the end. That's the destination of the walk that we were on. Oh, I'm so tired
That was a long walk to get there. You think you're tired. I do. Mike Lindell's tired. He works a lot. I believe that
Uh, Mike, great to finally get you on air with us. Thank you so much. Sincere. Oh, thanks for having me on
You're a busy guy working 20 hours a day. Wow
Yeah, I just landed. I'm in Michigan today. I've been going all around this country trying to get
This election pulled down and we will get it pulled down. So we're gonna 20 hour days trying to overturn the election
What are you doing for 20 hours? That's a really good question
I don't know what I don't know what what amount of work there is to be done on this front. I guess writing letters?
It could be
Um, traveling to another place and then writing letters? I guess there's no like time limit on talking shit. That's true
That's probably what he's doing. I mean does does it qualify as work if no one's around to hear you talk shit?
Is that our new like if a tree falls in the forest if Mike Lindell is telling you about the stolen election and no one's around to hear it?
If you're your own boss, you can count that as on the clock Alex. I think so. Yeah
Tax-deductible at least. Mike Lindell's got this argument about overturning the election, right? Sure. And
some arguments
Maybe they're three of a kind. Maybe they're a full house. Uh-huh. Not Mike's argument. No. Royal flush. Okay. All right
It's been a pretty amazing because it's like you're sitting here with a royal flush in a poker game
And we're just waiting to play it. We're gonna probably, you know, we're gonna bring it to the Supreme Court in July
As a full warrant. Oh, that's fast. It's just a matter of getting the word out to every every person in this country
Getting it out there. So the Supreme Court has pressure to accept it. Not a fucking chance
The Supreme Court has pressure to accept this case. Not a fucking chance. No. Yep. No
This seems to be the theme of what he's trying to get to is like we need to get everybody on board with this
So the Supreme Court can't reject it
I think he probably isn't stupid enough to think that that's really how things would work
I think he knows that by the time people realize that the Supreme Court's not going to take this case up
We still will have fleeced them
Tends to be the case. It does seem like you are always moving the date where we're gonna get that royal flush up
Oh, yeah, you got I mean you got to play, you know, you're never you're never pushing it back
You're never like hey we're on the date
You're always like and now next month we'll get there and you know what the the honest-to-god thing is that if he can get this
In front of the Supreme Court
Things are gonna move real fast. That's probably true. Things are going great
I couldn't be happier the way things are going in our country right now really said before our president be back
I said August I could be off by a month or two
This you've been quarterbacking the resistance and I believe in you and I know you've been behind the scenes
I've talked a lot of folks you've been working with. I'll leave it at that but
President Trump our real president in now in his second term with with the Chinese agent
Biden there this weekend as you know
He came out in the video saying oh, we're gonna take back the Senate
We're gonna take back the house and the White House sooner than you think and I've talked
With Trump he is really excited and he believes when the evidence comes out. There's a strategy
So wow, tell us about that
boy
Trump's gonna be president again in August
That is a lot sooner than I was expecting. Yeah, I I that was sooner than I planned for specifically
This is such a goddamn roller coaster. It's like the first hour is we're all gonna die and then Mike Lindell comes in
It's like no Trump will be president again within a few months. Yeah
Yeah, what? Yeah, the globalist plan seems very easy to sidestep how just completely
How are you supposed to feel if you're a listener to this show? It's so it's so untethered. You're dead in a year. Boo
President Trump. Yay
This is just how you go through this broadcast just a constant
Stream of look I'm bipolar and this is fucking with my yeah
If I took any of this seriously as being like it all
Based in reality. I would have a very difficult time
Emotionally surfing these waves. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, no, one of the big things that I try and do to cope is is like lower the amount of intense emotional stimuli that
I receive I believe if I listen to you
One of these broadcast I would be running through the street screaming. That's why the
Delegation of labor is the way it yes, it makes it only way this could work. Yeah, so once the Supreme Court
In July gets a hold of this case. They're gonna rule nine to zero
You understand me
Unanimous I really think the best you're going for is five to four there
I don't think Roberts is gonna side with you guys nine zero
When that when the Supreme Court looks at this it's not subjective evidence
So it's gonna be nine zero not eight to one seven to two
It has to be nine zero because this is not this isn't subjective evidence
So they're gonna pull this down and now and now but everybody needs to know there's a couple other things
One is there were many down tickets to that were flipped especially with you know senators like John James both senators in Georgia
Jason Lewis from Minnesota many congressmen many I mean this wasn't just at the presidential level and and and in our country
I want everybody to know this there's no there's no statute of limitations on this everyone says come on Mike
That's too hard to believe. Well, let me tell you something. Uh, but you believe we've been in this position a year and a half ago. No
So and but I will tell you this every election in the United States is history
if you find out there was a crime committed after the fact or
That the other person won in any way. Let's say it was just a mistake whatever it was
They put the person that won back in office
They put the person that won back in office. And if there was a crime committed by the by anyone else they get arrested
That's right. Let's use the sports analogy that's happened hundreds of times prominently thousands of times in smaller cases where you find out the other team
cheated cheated
So the other team cheated they then forfeited and then it's given to who they actually cheated against
Do you notice how alex used a sports metaphor instead of an example from the world of politics?
It does seem like a sports metaphor has more opportunities
Yeah, like if you're in a boxing match and it later comes out that your opponent was on the juice or something like that
You might you know that you might end up having the other person forfeit. Yes, that's true
I'm hard pressed to come up with examples from
The history of our courts, I mean there have been instances where there were really close races sure and somebody who had won
Uh after a recount, you know, you they had uh flipped the winner sure or something like that
Yeah, I don't know if I can think of any example of what they're talking about now off the top of my head
I I would I would say the thing that's most surprising to me about this whole conversation
Is the idea that mike lindell was talking to somebody about this and was like we've got an open and shut case
It's all done and that person responded with no it's out of the statute of limitations
Right, right. And then mike lindell says there's no statute of limitations and this person goes
What?
Yeah, I can't believe that in that case in that case. I'm gonna relitigate. I think this is the way to do it
So like that's six. Was it 68?
Yeah, yeah, let's go back to the beginning. Yeah, I don't think tj won that election
That's what i'm gonna go out there right now. I think he stole it and you know, it's fucking awesome about that
Too you undo one of those past elections and it throws you all gotta do them all
You gotta start all over it throws everything into chaos because what if it was a two-term president totally then the second term
Yeah, yeah, the whole country has to reset from the beginning
We dig up george washington and we get him back in there. Yeah
I honestly think that that might be a better solution to this fanciful nonsense
Like I mean, this isn't a better solution up george washington. No, not exactly but sort of yeah metaphorically
If mike lindell were to be let me be clear really clear. Sure. None of this is gonna happen
Yeah, of course not if he were to have
Incontrovertible evidence that this election was stolen by foreign powers or whatever sure and he gets it to the supreme court and they vote nine zero
in july
I think the answer isn't put trump back in office. It's right a new constitution
Yeah, if our country has failed no complaints figure something better out
Frankly, we should already be starting the new constitution process as we speak
You know, but let's just take this country like an etch a sketch totally
We'll hold on to some of the good stuff. Sure some of the protections and rights. Yeah. Yeah, but
Anyway, mike lindell is being sued by dominion
I would even go so far as to rewrite that 13th amendment to include prisoners and not uh, you know
Just be like slaves are bad unless they committed a crime one time me
So mike lindell is being sued by dominion and smartmatic, uh over claims, uh about their
Their computers and their technology being used. Uh
Intentionally to rig an election. Yeah. Yeah, that's a bit that's a big one. I think he's being sued for uh, it's in the billions
Yep. Yep. Yep. I think punitive damages would suggest that's a good idea. Now. There's something you may not have heard
What's that? Mike lindell is also suing them. I have not heard that. Yes. What crimes have they committed?
Um, you gotta watch his documentary. Oh, I can't do that. I can't do that. I'm sorry
We'll talk about it here in a minute. I made it. But anyway, um, he's suing them and there's a minor setback and that his lawyer quit
and
apparently
Apparently jordan, this is cancel culture. Oh, okay now last thursday. This is really key. I sued dominion
And smartmatic I threw them in there too because they're all in cahoots together
And for two billion dollars, you didn't hear about that probably in the news, but I even put their lawyers as co-conspirators
I put down their lawyers because their lawyers have served papers either lawsuits or threatening letters to over
200 people in this country and and news outlets including fox and whoever so everybody lives in fear
Of being sued. Well when I did that last thursday, I had to get a local council in minnesota
I got so many lawyers. I don't even know their names, but I got a local council in minnesota to serve them in minneapolis federal court
This law firm said yes, that's great. We'll do it. So we did it they signed up
They were attacked on thursday night by bots and trolls and email and the left and the communism
Who knows who all attacked them? So then on friday they fired the one of their lawyers
And said they did that they blamed it on that lawyer for even taking mike lindale's case
So they could get out there out from under the attack. It's just more cancel culture. It's cancel culture man. Oh boy
it just
Just seems like maybe they the law firm was more like whoops. Uh
I don't think the billable hours is worth this. Yes. Yeah, this is going to really be a drag
Yeah, we should uh, we thought we could go under the radar and just bill mike lindale for money
Oh, we looked at mike lindale's books and granted he's
Bizarrely rich for someone who has a pillow company. Um, but not that rich
We can let him go. Yeah. Yeah. So anyway, he's got this new documentary
He has like these these documentaries have been like absolute proof. Sure absolute collusion
Sure, and now this new one is called absolute nine zero. Oh boy in honor of the supreme court. Yes
Yeah, yeah, this is the cyber evidence. Everybody needs to watch this video. It's absolutely nine zero
This is the cyber proof against dominion against all this it shows it shows china attacking our country
What they did so I like to give everyone a fair chance to be heard sure I went ahead and I watched this film
And I want to tell you this right off the bat. I was not convinced. Oh, no
I I think your standards of evidence are a little bit higher than the supreme courts though, dan
There's nothing persuasive in the film and it's honestly mostly just uh, mike talking into his phone like he's recording on his phone
His ear pods are in
He's talking to an alleged cyber expert whose face and voice is on the screen
He's talking to an alleged cyber expert whose face and voice are distorted. It is an anonymous person
Who knows what the fuck he is got to be anonymous
So what it boils down to is that mike is claiming that he has what's called packet captures or the raw information from these computers
That proves that votes were being changed on election night
He shows these long scrolls of numbers over and over again in the documentary
As if to insist that even though you can't read this code. It's so definitive that trump is going to be president again in no time
Mike does say multiple times that these scrolls of numbers are actually the packet captures that they're working from
That's a problem the washington post among others
Pointed out that the scrolls of numbers are not packet captures and they're not even in the right format that that information would be found
In this sort of data that's transmitted over the internet is generally in binary. Whereas this is all hexadecimal code
So it just doesn't even make sense what the claims that are being made
That's going to be a tough hurdle for him to uh jump at the supreme court
But if he's got this kind of proof, I don't know the post took a look at some of the code and translated it into readable
Uh letters mike lindell is a piece of shit. It appears to be the pennsylvania voter roll, which is publicly available information
Yeah, okay
It might be a safe assumption to believe that this scroll of numbers is a dumb prop and this pixelated cyber expert is someone
Doing some fun role-playing and this is just a bunch of bullshit. That sounds likely. Yep. Oh, man. Mm-hmm
There's an inverse relationship between confidence in a set of numbers that a pillow person cannot read and uh truth
Behind those numbers. Yeah
So alex, I don't know what it was. Like I think mike lindell was a little delayed
And so when he was like, oh we're gonna talk to the my pillow guy
It might have been a situation where it's like he's late sure for the interview and so like maybe that was what was frustrating him
Because alex is saying a number of positive things
He's being he's being pretty polite and positive and putting up with some clearly nonsensical things that might just be a good scene partner
Yeah, and I think what he's doing is he's chasing a contract that's not going to come. Yeah
It's a little too late the cash cow for mike lindell getting some of his money
Is a little bit in the past like a lot of those like oan or right side broadcasting
They could get any money they wanted from him. I'm sure you know
We saw those uh those rallies that were just like the coverage for these networks were entirely sponsored
Yeah, and like I think that alex maybe would want some of that. I mean I would if I were him
It's easy money. Yeah, I think when I think it's too late
He's getting sued for millions or billions of dollars when it comes to principles versus gaining money
I think alex is going to go for gaining money every single time
But that money just won't be there for long. Yeah, I think it's too late. He's uh, he's fishing in a dry well
Um, but he does say some nice things about mike and uh then accidentally a my pillow commercial breaks out
Oh, no, my listeners still love trump, but I love trump. I want to run for president again
He is our president. I want to run for the speaker house, whatever he wants
But from a listener's view on the street people started asking more often. Do you know mike lindell?
Instead of you know trump because it's an example
People want action
They want somebody to stand up and I know trump had to lick his wounds get ready totally cut off a few months to
Exercise lose weight trump's fucking great. He's giving speeches
The threat to arrest his whole family would set up bogus stuff. He doesn't back down
I'm, not criticizing trump when I hold up mike lindell. I'm saying he's the example of putting it all on the line
Uh and and being there so I know you don't want to bring this up i'm bringing up right now. How do people
Support with all the attacks you're under fighting the globalist
How do people support the work you're doing because I know you're separate from my pillow with your your political action
But how do people do that so they can buy the pillows and then finance what you're doing?
Finance what you're doing. Wait, I thought you I thought that my pillow was separate from the political stuff user
But it finances the political stuff
That's suspicious
Well, you know that the best way is because you know dominion attacked my employees soon
We've lost all our retailers. So people have really stepped up but you could you could use the promo code mike today
Just use mike and you can save up to 66 on all our products. That's a lot. This goes on a while, too
This this this ad is not short. Mike has created a new bed that he plugs. Sure. Sure
Oh boy. Yep. I want I need to sue for something for alex
I need to sue for like extreme gaslighting for alex insisting to me that trump licked his wounds by exercising
Yeah, he was doing set ups. I want I there needs to be punitive damages for that
Yeah, something because you can't do that. That's just wrong. Carpe donkdom is gonna put out a uh,
compilation of like uh, uh set to eye of the tiger of trump like boxing
Show me show me one heaven
Meat hanging in a in a in a locker show me an example of him working out one picture. I don't know
I don't know. I just think this is more masculine hero worship nonsense totally. That's so disgusting
So I think that this next clip is one of the weirder things that i've heard happen on the show
Ever. Um, you know, there's there's there's things that are bizarre ideas that are bizarre. Sure
And then there are things that just happen that i'm like how did that happen? That's weird
And this is one of those it's the latter thing. It's not a weird idea. All right. I just don't know how this happened
Okay, we're gonna do what i'm gonna do in I mean now see on your show right now as we speak
Um in july i'm gonna get a place, uh some big location. I don't care
Michael and l stay there. I gotta you know about tv already. I got hard breaks satellites stay there
We'll come right back in a few minutes. I want to hear this big announcement. Alex almost never does that
He runs into the brakes all the time
Whether it's like I will skip this break that used to do that
Yeah, but even multiple times on this episode he's just in the middle of a sentence and it goes to break. That's so great
Why would he interrupt mike lindell in the middle of the big announcement?
That's the best time to interrupt somebody i'm gonna announce people on to on this show
Right now i'm sorry. We gotta go to break shit
You're breaking the flow a little bit. I guess I do understand it, you know from a presentation standpoint
You would want it to be clean. Yeah, you want the full announcement all at once
You don't want to announce the first half and then we'll be back at break and then you announce the second
No, no, that makes sense. Yeah, but not for alex. No, not for alex. No, not for alex
No, and I would uh, I would assume that most professionals would know that a big announcement was about to happen on their show
if you
if you were going to
Also, I mean just from a professional standpoint as an interviewee if you're going to make a big announcement
You should know if it's going to be broken up. Yeah. Yeah. Oh boy. Yeah
So anyway, are you ready here to the announcement? Let's do it
You were you we were going to break you had a big announcement. What is the big announcement?
Yeah, well, this is just part of the plan, but the big announcement is um
If all the cyber evidence I have all this stuff from the day before the election the election the two days after all those packets
They're called packet captures everybody since I went public with that in on an absolutely nine zero
I got all kinds of companies from all over the united states
Cyber companies that are cyber white hat hackers cyber companies said hey, we'd like to look at that and validate that pay us in bitcoin
Sometime in july i'm gonna get either. I don't care if it's us big stadium
I don't care how big it has to be i'm gonna invite all of these white cyber, um experts in
And I want to televise all of them can be there the whole world can watch
The whole world can watch and I don't care if there's a hundred of these companies there here it is
And I want them all to say on on on tb and everywhere. Wow. There it is hundred percent. There it is. There it is
It's like showing a royal flush in a poker game and everyone going does everybody see it?
Hello
That election's coming down. Um, i'm not gonna hold my breath on uh this event happening. Yeah
I would argue it's less like
Showing people a royal flush while you're playing a game of poker and more like instead of having cards
You throw a dead horse on the table and you're like see
I won
Well, technically he would have something to show them. I guess it would be more like he's got a two. Yeah
Um the death card from a tarot deck naturally the instruction card, right?
um
That nolan ryan's, uh, rookie baseball card and a piece of non. Yes, exactly. Yeah
Royal flush, baby. What kind of looks like cards?
uh
Yeah
I don't know. I I would love for this to happen though. I do think it would be chaotic on a level
It would rival the uh, the the landscaping
four seasons
Yeah, yeah, that would be pretty delightful
I was just thinking like I wonder if even if a ransomware company if he would even notice if his
Computers were locked and he can't get into his business software unless he paid 10 million in bitcoin
He'd be like, oh no
And then just record on his phone like he wouldn't even fucking care. Yeah. Yeah, or it would be cancel culture
Yes, it would be cancel culture. So mike's got one last little thing, uh to say here and uh,
This is where I you know, it's kind of getting a little bit worried that maybe mike is a bit of a christian zealot
In the same vein as alex
Everybody needs to pray. That's the number one thing for mike
And and everything he's doing
Yeah, thank you. And I thank everybody for your prayers and I believe I do believe that we're in the greatest revival ever
People aren't looking for hope unless things are bad we get through this
It's going to be once again one one nation under god, but it's the biggest revival for jesus in history
Everybody right now is just they're praying and we are our prayers are answered
They have been answered over and over here. Remember god's got his hand in all of this. This is on god's timing
Can you imagine if this would have been flipped back in uh, december?
You might have had a you know, democrats not believing that they really that it really got stole
Well now when the supreme court pulls this down those nine supreme court justices are going to be heroes
They're protecting our country from china and whether you're a democrat or republican
It's going to be a united and as long as your message gets out we win
So, I don't know. I don't know if you quite grasped what he was saying there at the end
He's saying that like if if trump had been put back in like right after the election or whatever
Yeah, democrats would have been really mad. No, but now democrats all know the election was
Was a scam. Well, we all watched absolutely nine zero. Yes
so and so now the we will
We will carry the supreme court justices out of chambers on our shoulders chanting and cheering. Thank you
Thank you. Thank you three and a half more years of trump three and a half more years. I think he gets time served
I disagree, sir
I have to take that up with mike
I'll take it to the supreme court
So mike lindale takes off and alex has another guest on uh for another the last hour. Uh-huh
And uh, it's a it's a fellow we know uh, he's a rat fucker
Oh boy, he's uh, here we go. Mary prankster. All right. All right this bastard
Uh, roger stone is back and he wants to talk about the good old days
Those were the days that he would like to talk about I assume yeah
There was a time when both parties just had two different governing philosophies a more liberal philosophy a more conservative philosophy
On finances on fiscal matters on foreign policy matters. This is no longer the case you have now we want to overthrow
We want to overthrow democracy america first party under donald trump
And you have the other party that has been completely co-opted by the red chinese. I think this is abundantly clear
Their party will not denounce radical islam. What think about that the party of harry truman?
What?
Why is truman in here truman has nothing to do with radical islam?
I don't connect with you generally. I wasn't like hey, it wasn't like radical islam defeats. Truman is the
Headline he was holding up. You don't know about dewy
Um
yeah, I I think I
um
I don't know. I lose patience for people who make these two arguments together
They like there was a time when both parties loved the country
Sure, and now we have all coalesced around a charismatic leader with a america first slogan and then the other people
Everybody else are co-opted by the comments. Yes, exactly. Yes. It is us against them with no middle ground
Yes, but oh I miss the days when everyone used to be able to do middle ground
We used to be able to do middle ground all the time when I was working for nixon the main thing
That we did in our administration
Reaching out to the other aisle. Yeah, that's what we did. Definitely and when I was working with reagan
We reached out across the aisle to destroy those unions. That was our plan. Yeah, and what?
Jesus christ, so roger has a belief and that is that trump is the greatest president since lincoln
He is the greatest president since abraham lincoln I agree maybe since washington, so let me ask you this
What do we do then? Because we're just sitting here watching the country destroyed and I understand I don't want a civil war
They're trying to start one. Anyways, what do we do then?
But you can go to roger stone's plan to save america.com. That's a long url
That's a little that's not happening buddy. No, you gotta trim that up
Get a bitly or something
Don't have a website that requires an apostrophe. That's what I that's all i'm saying. It's too confusing for people you're trying to target
Especially for those people. Yeah
Please check out my website
Www.rogerstone's got some wonderful ideas that will have very much helped this country get back on track.com
Oh god, I went to this website and it's just one of these
Uh-huh. It's just one of these awesome things that just the people on the right do this all the time
They're so good at this and that is just it's a donation landing page. Yep
And I have a plan that will save america put in your email address and i'll send it to you
Got it. Just try to build up an email list roger's trying to get back on his hustle. Jesus
Yeah, so this is his uh transition back into being able to direct market to people. Yeah
Um, so good good good on him. Yeah, great
Yeah, I bet he could take it. I bet he could get a job working for greenwald at this point
Working on that sub stack. That might be that might be a good way for stone to go greenwald and stone. Yeah
The new well manifold went down
So greenwald's the next obvious choice right get uh get at water in there and you gotta you got a consulting firm
Oh, man
I wonder if greenwald would know how shitty he's become if I
Really told him that he and roger stone are equal now. That'd be bad
So you may have some ideas about greenwald, but roger's got some ideas about fauci
Hitler, okay
All right. Fauci will be remembered
As hitler that sounds strange. I think tony fauci is going to go down with adolf hitler
Joseph stalin and chairman mao is one of the great mass murderers of all time and those who say what are you talking about?
Millions of people have taken this vaccination have had no reaction to which I say. Yeah
Ah
Well, I have been roundly outsmarted roger stone shit I didn't think of that
That's certainly not an argument that
Can't be made about everything. No, no, no, no that one. No, nope
Very dumb, how about uh, how about we just apply that to literally any and all arguments with roger stone from now on just say
Yet. Yeah, not yet. Oh, no, they'll never kill trump. Not yet. Oh now you've been defeated, sir
Oh, yeah, fuck off. So, uh, one of the big things about mike lindell's interview was that trump is going to be president again
Imminently. Yes. He's going to be put right back in that august maybe a little bit later couple months
Maybe couple months max august. Maybe i'm a little bit off couple months
You never know how long the supreme court is going to take with arguments, you know, totally and there's literally no
Uh protocol for reinstating a president. No, I don't think we've ever done that one before so I
I would think that there might be conversations that would last quite a while about that
Um, but yeah a couple months anyway, it would have been funny if after harding they were like listen
I mean, this is too soon. We're just gonna redo it
So that's mike's big thing
Now roger is on right after
No, he's not into it. Okay now I should also tell you just as a way to give a little bit of context for this
this next uh
Uh clip roger his wife apparently has just recently been diagnosed with cancer and that's awful
Yeah, I hope the best for her, uh recovery that sucks. However
Alex takes that information
And tries to turn roger's wife's diagnosis
Into a vaccine talking point. Wow, and if I were roger, I would be furious
Well, first of all, look I have great respect for mike lindell who's doing an extraordinary job and spending his own money putting his
His mouth his money where his mouth is try to undercover the election fraud in all these states parenthesis
I would never do that. Listen, I make the subjective judgment that even then turning over the election will be very difficult
I really hope to be wrong. I hope mike lindell is right
I hope the president's instinct is correct at the moment. I've got to be honest with you
I'm, so distracted with my wife's cancer treatments and the tsunami of contradictory medical advice that we're trying to sort through
And the millions and millions of phds and doctors and professionals as well as holistic and homeopathic healers
Who've contacted us trying to help us? It's heartwarming. It really is but it's also
Overwhelming it is. Hey roger. What do you make of so many people that get the inoculation and get cancer in a few months?
Uh, that's what all these scientists are saying. It's doing i've got a new article out of florida out of palm beach close to where you live
I don't get into your own private life. I don't know if you made this public or not. You didn't take the vaccine
But did anybody else, you know take the vaccine recently? They just got cancer
Well, uh, no, but I can tell you that uh that my uh, a member of my family did take it not my wife
A member of my family did take it not my wife just disgusting
Just absolutely disgusting
No, uh, but I can tell you that you're a disgusting monster
Uh that you have just decided to turn my wife's cancer diagnosis into a prop for your own bullshit
And normally i'm fine with that but this is my fucking wife. We're talking about you asshole
Yeah, I mean he's brought up, uh on this interview a couple times
Like I wouldn't pull clips of it to to discuss because it's you know his private life and you know, sure
That's very difficult. It's not what we do a loved one. Uh have uh have a medical condition like that
And uh, he's brought it up a couple times and it seems like something that is
You know kind of scary and something that is difficult to deal with for even for a slimy fuck like roger
yeah, and I I would rather make fun of his terrible positions than
A legitimate tragedy and pain that he's going through
Yeah, so he's brought it up a number of times and for alex to now do that
Is so insulting it is so exploitative
It's because if alex is listening to him, he has to recognize that like this isn't
Like roger's polonium poisoning right? Right. Right. This is actually real. This is real. Yeah. Yeah
I mean
Here's the thing. Here's the other hand I have for that which is just
Roger and alex have both done this to so many people in the past where they've exploited their personal shit for their propaganda that it's like
Hey, you live by the sword you die by the sword. Of course. This was going to happen
I guess you know you can't roger can't feel insulted
Without wrestling with his own behavior, I guess you know
So I can feel insulted on his behalf because I haven't taken his wife's cancer and used it as a prop
Nor have I taken anybody's cancer and used it as a prop. It's just low, you know, like it's low. It's low
It's a real bummer. It's a it's a it's a it's a real real bummer to be sitting here
I'm, like I hate both of these people but alex is really edging out in terms of who I hate more in this interaction
Yep. Yep. I I can't I can't imagine what it would feel like to do that the way alex is doing that too like
Uh, hey, this this article is from close to where you live
There's all these people who are getting cancer after getting the shot. Did anybody you know who maybe just got cancer?
Yep, like say it was your wife. It's such a leading question kind of thing
It's like please use your use your wife's condition as a as a way
To make my narratives work better for me to make money off of you're around cancer people now
You go to the treatments all the time
So you gotta know a bunch of people with cancer tell me which ones took the vaccine and then let's go turn that pain into
Profit totally totally and my profit not yours, by the way. No, because nobody's gonna get to your dumb url you idiot
Yeah, they're gonna put that apostrophe in and get lost exactly. It's never happening
Yeah, so you have one last clip here and I I really do think that this is so indicative of like
Present-day alex and why it's just this this shit's meaningless. It's just a bad person doing a bad job
Uh, because you know at the beginning of the show, like I said, it's an hour of him
Just talking about how everyone's dead. It just doesn't matter and here's what he says
at the end of the show
Sometimes I start the show the best of moods end up bad moods
Sometimes I start the bad mood in a good mood as rob doodler in the hall was telling me earlier man
You're in a good mood now you're in a bad mood throughout the show
You know, I appreciate listeners that tune into this show because you're not looking for lies
You're looking for truth and the truth hurts sometimes but we got to admit that truth to get through the bad and you know
Make it a better world. So I appreciate you all going through this
just like i'm doing it and
so many days at the end of the show i've got like the most powerful stuff we had I haven't hit yet because
I've already looked at it two or three times and it's already got me pissed
Yeah, man, the news got him pissed so he can't cover the news can't do can't convey the information
That is the information part of the information war but he can
Uh, take his feelings and project them onto the audience and lash out like a little baby in a way that reduce
releases endorphins or gets him feeling better
Remember when he was yelling about how he had a migraine and then he yelled he called the pope this the devil and he felt
Better. Yep. It's just that but with the audience. He's just he just needs to get his emotions out. Yeah. Yeah this like
Yeah, this is I I think any good
Acid therapist or psychologist would be able to correctly diagnose
The relationship alex has with his listeners as incredibly abusive parasitic
Uh, I feel like what he just did and what we listen to of him telling me that everybody's gonna die
And then him feeling better at the end of it and me being left alone with this feeling that is domestic violence
I feel abused this is fucking bullshit. It is but it's it's
You know, obviously it's not that bad because you and I at least know that he's full of shit
Sure, and it doesn't affect us in any way that we're taking what he says seriously, right? But like if you did
You would be
Being taken for a ride. Yeah, alex would be trying to make you feel his emotions and leave you holding the bag
Yes, total of the bad emotions totally and that's just uh, not cool
I am getting my bad out emotions out of me and giving them to you because you deal with them and
That last clip gave me a little bit of a hint that maybe he's a little bit
subconsciously aware that that's what he does could be a little bit which is gross and it could be that rob doo has
Told him specifically and maybe that conversation with rob doo is him trying to be like alex. Yeah, you did it again. Yep
So wow, what a fucked up. Jesus. I listened to this episode and there's something that's kind of like well, that's a
Intense psychodrama. Yeah, that's going on
Yeah, obviously and and it's monumental that michael and elle the my pillow guy is on the show that's not happened before
This is a meeting of the minds
And trump's gonna be president again after a nine zero. No, I still don't think that's happening. I still don't think that's happening
We will see we will see what yet yet. So but you know look
Looking at this in especially in juxtaposition with the 2003 stuff
Like it doesn't feel like alex is taking his moods out in 2003
It does not feel like he's just having a kind of uh lashing out at a microphone. Yeah, no
And that's kind of why it's better
You can't I mean there's just no way to view our time with alex as anything other than watching a man descend into madness, right?
Like we're we're doing a it's apparently lucrative madness. I mean we're doing a
27-year heart of darkness situation
We're watching colonel kurtz, that's what we're doing. Yeah, maybe oh mr. Kurtz he dead
And uh, alex is just a mess. Um, anyway, uh, this has been our adventure on june 10th
Yes, we'll be back
It has been an adventure. It has been an adventure. We'll be back. But until then, uh, we have a website
We do have a website. It's knowledgefight.com. Yep. We're also on twitter. We are on twitter
It's now at knowledge underscore fight and at go to bed. Jordan. We're also facebook. We are facebook
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund near you
Could please find a local charity or bail fund near your area to help out, uh people doing god's work
Yeah, we'll be back. But until then i'm neo i'm leo i'm dzx clark. I'm darryl rondes. I'm gonna go take a nap
Andy and kansas you're on the air. Thanks for holding
Hello alex i'm a first time caller i'm a huge fan. I love your work. I love you