N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Dan and Jordan, I am sweating
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledgefight
knowledgefight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
saying we are the bad guys
knowledgefight
Dan and Jordan, knowledgefight
I need money
A&E In Kansas, A&E in Kansas, A&E in Stop It
A&E in Kansas, A&E in Kansas, A&E in It's time to pray
A&E in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding us
Hello Alex, I'm a first-time caller, I'm a huge fan
I love your room
knowledgefight
knowledgefight.com
I love you.
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes.
I'd like to sit around and worship at the altar of Selene and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are, Dan.
Jordan.
Dan.
I have a quick question for you.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, this is actually a bright spot I'm excited to give or to discuss.
All right.
I was a fan of The Tick growing up.
Oh, hell yeah.
The animated cartoon?
Cartoon.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I loved it.
Deflator Mouse, come on, man.
Chairface Chippendale.
Of course.
It doesn't get better than that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Great.
Loved it.
Fantastic.
The sensibility of it, the humor, everything about it was just fantastic.
I loved it as a kid.
I have always been a little bit hesitant to give other interpretations of The Tick a chance.
I tried watching the newer one.
Which one?
The Patrick Warburton one?
No.
The Peter Serafinowicz one.
Gotcha.
Yeah.
Peter Serafinowicz is great, isn't he?
It's outstanding.
It's so good.
Yes.
I'm a few episodes in and I'm like, this is exactly what I would have wanted from a live
action version of The Tick.
Totally.
Spectacular.
Yeah.
There's so many little subtle things.
I would never have guessed that Serafinowicz would get the character that good.
You know what I'm saying?
And Griffin Newman's fantastic as Arthur.
Totally.
No, no, he's great.
But at least the first episodes are really hinging around him and this sort of backstory
of him as a superhero.
Totally.
And that's exactly the way to tell the story.
It's really good.
I am so pumped.
I'm bummed that I think it's canceled, right?
I'm pretty sure it's canceled, yeah.
Sucks that there's a limited amount of them, but I'm excited to have something to watch
that I really enjoy.
Yeah, that was one of my favorites.
I'll never forget Deflator Mouse, just because I saw the cartoon when I was eight or something.
So young.
And it was like 20 years later that I was like, oh, that's a reference to a fucking
opera?
Shit!
You know?
What kind of eight year old is going to be like, what a great pun?
Was The Mad Bomber Who Bombs at Midnight a pun?
I do like The Mad Bomber Who Bombs at Midnight.
So what's your bright spot?
My bright spot, Dan, is walking.
Not Christopher.
Oh.
Ah, no.
The weather's nice out, and we only live a couple miles away from each other, so I've
started walking to do the show.
It's about a 40 minute walk, which is the perfect length of time to start going back
through old albums and actually listen to the full thing.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I've been going through the Ninja Tunes label here recently, and I just got to Lemon
Jellies 64 through 95, and the final track on that is called Go, and it is so good because
they use William Shatner's sample there, and so it's just like they finally do something
good with William Shatner.
It's been so long, but they finally did something good with William Shatner around 20 years
ago.
What about those talk albums that he did?
That's what they're doing.
They're taking samples from the talk albums.
But I think that even just those raw are great.
Oh, you think so?
Really?
No, I don't know.
I actually haven't listened to them.
I know a lot of people make jokes about it.
Yeah, I mean, it's easy to make jokes about it.
What are you going to say about it?
It's good?
I guess that's as good a joke as I have.
This is good.
Hey, look, we're going to put this on on a date.
We're going to lower the lights a little bit and just listen to some Shatner.
And make out to some Shatner.
Exactly.
Yes.
What are you doing?
Yeah.
So, Jordan.
Yes, sir.
I'm glad you're enjoying these albums.
And today we have an album to discuss.
Oh, yeah.
And that is an episode of Alex's show.
Okay.
I look at those as albums.
Yeah.
All right.
He's prolific.
Very.
Yes.
We're going over May 21st, 2003.
Blackjack.
No.
God damn it.
I bet.
Oh, shit.
We're going back to the past.
Okay.
And part of this is because we had a little bit of sort of a cliffhanger on the last episode.
Alex was complaining a whole bunch about The Matrix.
Yep.
And he was saying he was going to go see it.
Of course.
And he did not.
And he didn't.
So we have to satisfy this.
We have to give some sort of closure to this.
Yeah.
Of course.
And I will say that Alex has seen The Matrix by this point, and we're going to get one
of those rare gems.
Solid movie reviews.
We're going to get a gem of a movie review out of Alex.
Okay.
I'm excited.
Yeah.
As am I. I'm thrilled to walk you through this.
But before we do, we've got to take a moment to say hello to some new wonks out there.
That's a great idea.
So first, Steven T. Thank you so much.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Steven.
Next, Lego from St. Paul.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Lego.
Thank you.
Next, Wren.
W-R-E-N. Wren.
Wren.
on this Watson all right let's just get down to business we ain't making that money off that
heroin why you pimps so good my neck is freakishly large I declare info war on you thank y'all and
unfortunately rest in peace middle-aged mice yes apologies you gotta get you apologies anybody
who's been grandfathered out so to speak is gonna be fine uh-huh if you will yes giving someone
life is giving someone death you could say that life is death I would like to give a happy birthday
shout out to Matt been got in touch with us and on the 17th coming up this okay middle of this week
Thursday it would be Thursday keep track of days also from what I understand you're gonna love this
okay it's uh Matt's hitchhiker's guide to the galaxy birthday oh he's uh what uh 32
was that the answer to the universe and everything uh no it's 42 right yeah isn't it yeah what the
well the 32 first it would just be fun okay if you know I couldn't tell if you were fucking with me
no the the question uh that the universe is trying to answer right is what is six times seven
but if anybody got the question and the answer right at the same time the universe would be
destroyed and be replaced by something even weirder okay yeah well anyway happy birthday
Matt uh uh Alex has uh some kind wishes for you being born is a condition that leads to death
you can say that life is a disease that ends in death so Jordan um today we're going to be
talking about uh Alex on the on may 21st and I this is a rare instance where I decided like
I have not watched these movies in forever it's been a long time and so I decided I might need
to refresh my memory and I actually watched the matrix reloaded as a as a sort of refresher course
because I was like what is he talking about even when it comes to movie reviews Dan's gonna look
into it and research things and take down your opinion well I was curious I was curious because
I remember enjoying uh the movie enough sure and and look I have a lot of things I'm gonna read
some of my my notes uh just sort of raw yeah uh go over some of my thoughts are you doing a live
tweeting of uh I basically did uh on a notebook page um I'm gonna go over a little bit but this
was uh not bad not a bad not a bad film I enjoyed it I would appreciate more movie reviews that were
just very simple a couple words I'm sick of these long like explanations of the plot and the history
of the movie and the shots angle and what that means for interpretation no it's all right it
really picked up after the highway scene yeah that's true I will say that that's true a little
bit of at the beginning was a slog to get through but whatever no everybody wants to watch the
dancing scene for at least another six minutes it had some pacing issues um but I don't begrudge
that too much it wasn't it wasn't insurmountable in terms of enjoying the movie no no no um
like I said I have some thoughts so does Alex last night I went and saw the matrix I'm gonna give
about a five minute review of that and I think a transcript of my review should be made I want to
give a warning about this film if there was any questions about being uh from Illuminati origin
those are now answered put those concerns to bed is it yes oh yeah okay it is a deeply Illuminati
shit just for the listeners I need you to know that when Alex said I'm gonna give you about a
five minute review Dan just went shook his head no it is not gonna be a five minute review nor
should it be transcribed all of that was wrong um yeah so apparently uh Alex had seen the first
Matrix movie sure and he was like is this Illuminati shit I don't know and he saw the second
one he's like yes definitely Illuminati shit I do like that the concerns have been put to bed put
them to bed put the concerns to bed yeah because the answer is yes which is somehow less concerning
well I mean it's it's no longer an open question now you know that this is just evil I mean I
suppose certainty is a comfort in some ways right yeah so I guess at this point I would say that um
if you're convinced that this uh movie has Illuminati origins maybe you shouldn't do that
whole red pill thing like maybe you shouldn't take that metaphor because the Illuminati made
that metaphor so so what you're saying is perhaps these stupid thoughts uh are bullshit that they're
feeling in the moment and then later on they'll be like that's actually a great movie and let's
use the metaphor yes yeah that sounds I get the sense of that yeah that sounds about right um so
there's a lot of people who shouldn't see this movie humans yes but if you're gonna see it you
whatever just don't show it to kids I would not let my children watch the film and uh if you want
to see it yourself to see the face of the new world order go ahead but uh it uh very very dark
and very evil uh is all I can really say about Matrix Reloaded but uh I'm gonna
go over some of it here on the show he does he does go over a little bit of it yeah I will say
that from I listened to Alex's review first got confused and then I watched the movie I'm like
boy there's a lot he doesn't cover
he would not have a very good sense of the movie it's a big movie it's a big movie yeah there might
be too much in it but um you know he he starts off his conversation about uh the Matrix by talking
about the first movie and I don't know if I agree with his premise okay the first Matrix was
obviously new age in its overall presentation that you've got to believe in yourself and then you can
change the parameters that is not no reality no problem within I take issue with that I mean like
maybe there is some new ageiness to it certainly sure sure but I don't think that it's about like
believe in yourself and you can change the parameters of reality I am fairly certain
that most everybody in that movie who also believed in themselves right next to Neo
was immediately murdered within the first 45 minutes yeah Neo didn't have the ability to
change things because he believed in himself he had the ability to change things because he was
created and born inside the Matrix yeah I understand maybe that you're trying to say
that we're all the chosen one but that's not what the movie is trying to say yes yes if you're going
to bring that to the film that's on you yeah I mean and for fuck's sakes in one movie later
after this one Neo is literally in a Christ-like position to show you that he's making the
sacrifice spoilers I'm sorry apologies I have to get to that a couple years from now it's Alex
freaks out about that now you got to go hunting for when Revolutions was released oh god I can't
wait um yeah I think his interpretation of the first movie is a little bit flawed yeah
based on everything about the first movie yes the and the watching of it but he you know he
watched this this the first film and like I said he was confused he's like is this illuminati how
do you get confused well because you don't know if it's illuminati or not maybe the Wachowskis
are putting out something that is heroic sure anti-illuminati sure or maybe it's illuminati
and so I was ambiguous I'm certainly a Christian and didn't follow the new age Hindu or Buddhist
line but I was still overall not sure if the film was a production of the globalist
what well now I am sure that the matrix one and the matrix two matrix reloaded are
in the most pure sense illuminati productions so I was pretty excited to hear about like
why yeah in the most pure sense what sealed the deal what was it about this film that was like
yeah no dead to rights this is this is globalist I need to know I mean did you just watch the
credits and the executive producers were the illuminati sorrow exactly like is that what
we're dealing with I was not prepared for how this review would get going okay I I was like okay
he's gonna misinterpret something sure you know I couldn't have possibly imagined that this was
the start of it look down for this okay it's outrageous the film begins obviously with a
group of trailers and there is a wide screen shot that has been squeezed down and distorted
as an authority figure type man in black sits behind a table with flickering subliminals being
splashed on the screen talking about power aid alex is mad about a power aid commercial I am no
I am no uh you know what it I was I was I was out when he said before we even get to the movie
we got to deal with the trailers yeah no no no no no I don't even why would the illuminati count
trailers this isn't even a trailer this is a commercial power raid yes I thought he was
misinterpreting a fucking uh commercial for men in black 2 or something like rip torn is sitting
behind a desk it's not it's not we'll get into it but he's really mad about okay okay it's a power
talks down to you and says you're not even going to understand what I'm saying to you
you pathetic mindless hive mind of units you are units that power the matrix drink your power aid
do as you are ordered to do
so that's how the film begins it's not it's a commercial
um it's not how the film begins it's really not how the film begins if you watch it like now if
you were to stream it it doesn't start the power a commercial isn't there no so this wasn't an
authority figure in the commercial it was one of the agents from the movie there weren't subliminal
flickering lights the commercial was just set in the entire great interrogation room where they
took neo in the first movie sure some of the stuff that alex is saying is from the commercial but
some is also his own embellishment but it's obviously just a way to like sell power aid
using a character from the movie yeah i spent a lot of time thinking about it and honestly this
is the only way you could do a commercial like this with a tie-in to the matrix like if you use
any of the main characters it's gonna really seem goofy as shit oh no no the agent would be great
they're perfect for this because they don't have a personality except for agent smith so they're
essentially just blank slates yeah one of them selling power aid doesn't negatively affect your
impression of the agents because it can't they aren't individuals right so it's fine that said
i went and watched this commercial uh and there is a canon problem with the commercial okay
i'm gonna play a little clip here uh from that commercial and then we'll discuss uh the issue
i love this show consider this the active human body can generate up to 12 000 btus of body heat
pure precious life-giving energy it is unfortunate your collective puny little minds couldn't figure
out a way to harness this energy put it to good use somehow but that's beside the point the point
is to keep generating all that energy your body needs to be replenished so drink your power aid
we have quotas to meet so that's obviously supposed to be like deadpan comedy yeah yeah
the problem is that this agent is trying to sell power aid to people who are inside the matrix
activities inside the matrix shouldn't affect the amount of energy that gets produced by the
person's physical body outside of the matrix people's actual bodies are in pods they have
no need for power aid there's tubes and stuff going into them i do believe that they are
suspended in goo of some sort you wouldn't even be able to get that power to their mouths power
is it power aid that they're suspended it might be that could be true if so this commercial is
underselling if you don't have power aid you will die yeah given what we know about the machines in
the movies if physical activity in the matrix translated to greater energy production in the
real world then everyone in the matrix would be suspiciously into exercise and fitness if you have
like seven billion batteries and you could boost their productivity by 30 if their avatar of the
matrix works out that's an amount of energy production that would not be ignored by machines
no no no generally they are well known for efficiency they keep humans in pods
anything is on the table that's what i'm saying i do like the idea that there's somebody somewhere
like man nobody is using these gym memberships nobody this is unreal this is unreal anyway
the bottom line here is that uh this commercial is just kind of dumb it's kind of just a fun
powerade commercial that played before the movie it's not part of the film and it's not meant to
shame people for being dumb like there's an ai version of irkot it's like sorry guys nobody's
working out so you can't turn your ac on this this week like come on man yeah i like i like though
that alex is sitting there in the theater watching this powerade commercial and he's like i am
personally insulted by this character talking down to me all you need i i have been shamed by this
powerade commercial wow you just can't find a single moment not to be mad about yeah if you
can get mad about a powerade commercial what why even bother with the movie you're already done
yeah what's it like what's it like what's it like how do you take in any media if you're
shamed by a power so the actual movie starts sure and uh here's where alex is at then it launches
into uh the world of the matrix that is the real physical world of the underground base of xion
yes xion get it and you have the marauding forces that that uh surface to the wrecked cities above
and transmit the minds or the souls in a type of digital astral projection okay into the machine
world or the matrix and you're told that both of these are reality because perception is reality
if there's one thing that i took away from the message of the matrix movies even before i went
and re-watched it it's kind of the opposite of perception is reality yeah basically what you
perceive is not real yes that's the point it felt like the point of the movie is that some things
that feel like reality might not be but there is a definite reality which is worth fighting for
yeah if perception was truly reality then it wouldn't matter if neo ever perceived the matrix
to be the actual world or an illusion if he accepted the matrix as reality then it would
actually be that the movies do actually deal with this quite eloquently perception can shape reality
to an extent like if you're in the matrix and you want that to be a reality it's possible to
live your entire life in that state and not run into any problems joey pants his character in the
first movie he wants to be reinserted into the matrix and not be aware of the fight against the
robots because it's more comfortable to him and it's implied that that's something that can be
done his subjective experience and perception can create his subjective reality but that isn't real
the movie is very clear that there's an entirely different actual reality that exists regardless
of your subjective beliefs about reality nothing you do in the matrix affects that fact as the what
is reality robots have turned humans into batteries and shit in the first movie the first
thing he does is show you the desert of the real the real not not the desert of the we perceive
this to be dark it's really interesting to me that this is this is where alex is at because
he's getting caught up in a pretty elementary philosophical question about perception and
reality that the wachowski's movie actually goes one step beyond in terms of like even just the
starting point is past this i think that's what we're really dealing with here it's like when
you're when you're watching he sounds like he's explaining the movie to my grandma you know of
just like things that aren't really part of the movie but she's gonna like it a lot more than if
you tell her like there's a car chase you know like that's not what's gonna work for her yep
so trinity jumps on a motorcycle yeah right okay wearing black spandex it looks great um so zion
he takes issue with uh-huh he takes issue with like weird things uh specifically about like
naming conventions yeah but when i went back and i watched it i was like it's interesting that he
doesn't take issue with everything yeah everything has a fucking name that means something it's kind
of a reference to everything yeah and so the zion stuck out in his head and then here's another one
and the whole film is basically illuminati characters dark masonic overtones with a dark
occult leader and he says that we are the occult we're the vampires we're the werewolves we're the
demons nope absolutely not him that and of course he's called the merovingian or the merovingian
bloodline this is what the satanist based in france believe that they are descendants of jesus
and he's brothers with satan this is deep occult illuminati stuff so alex takes issue with the
merovingian he's not a good guy nope okay we're we all recognize that he's bad yeah that's why
he's got that name yeah and he's not even like high-end villain he's he's an antagonist he's a
middle manager yeah yeah yeah he is the mini boss of this side quest totally they have to go get
the key maker yes yeah yeah yeah um yeah i guess it's you know zion and merovingian you can take
some issue with those but what about like Nebuchadnezzar was the name of their ship
yeah yeah yeah what about trinity no don't worry about it no don't worry about it no
morpheus absolutely no reference there dan it's it's interesting the selective uh sort of outrage
or selective like pointing this out as sure something that means something without without
incorporating all of the things right into it like it just it's pick and choose yeah i mean
if you name something zion in a piece of popular culture someone's gonna be pissed and it's usually
and it's usually gonna be hard right christians it's gonna be alex in 2003 exactly yes that's
going to happen but if you're mad about that you can't you can't let that get in the way of being
mad about all the other religious references in the movie you know that's the problem here he
needs to be a more holistic hater yeah so the movie it's evil that's that's i mean really the
bottom line and again i'm showing you about small tidbits of this i've got to go back and take notes
which i will do this is a i've never seen a more powerful overtly soul twisting mind control film
there is lesbian and homosexual scenes in the film oh my god oh my god the fucking
illuminati are back at it dan why is that the first thing that he brings up after saying that
it's mind twisting and evil because i urges it's very weird to me it's very strange even for alex
that's weird yeah there's homosexual and lesbian scenes yeah yeah 2003 was uh was different though
like uh you know that was before gay people were even allowed to marry it's true so uh i i think
there was a lot more open and vicious uh uh well i mean now there's so much open and vicious hatred
man the world sucks bummer yep um so look this is all just trying to make implants fashionable
right body mods yeah yeah jacks in the back of your head yeah and living in the future now
that's been born out oh yeah we all have jacks we all have jacks in the back of our head yeah
uh there also is everyone has chip implants and chip plug-ins and this is a good thing
good thing we have a little speech in there where the machines aren't bad we can fight them with all
of all of this so it's making it a new fashion statement probably one of the strongest cultural
movements we've seen in history in modern history is the matrix the video games and the cartoons now
in the a bunch of spin-off uh cartoons for the big screen and dvd there was they again are
conditioning the children the anime that it's normal to have plug-ins into your mind wire heads
as they were called decades ago it is fashionable to have implant points all over your body like
okay so matrix was popular right yeah and alex is trying to make this argument that like they're
trying to condition you to get jacks on the back of your head to plug into computers or something
sure but like if your argument is just that it's popular and there's like spin-off properties like
what about the ninja turtles oh yeah like they were huge yeah yeah what about that were they
try what were what were the globalists trying to mainline uh then were they trying to turn us all
into people who go into goo well i know i know that i had and this i remember specifically i had
a rafael action figure and what you would do is you would push rafael's head down and it would
attach to a spring and then you'd uh click it and the head would pop out like he was headbutting you
right and from that i learned that the illuminati want me to headbutt the shit out of people wait
wait a second yeah i know rafael was a ninja turtle true what weapon does neo grab when he's
fighting the mira vingian's goons in that staircase was it was it size he does he does
yes no shit oh wow neo is rafael this is blowing the whole thing wide open for me oh man perception
is reality wait wait ninja turtles were preparing us for the matrix right preparing us to take
the jacks in the back of our head right i mean wasn't it a point of pride in the movie though
how many people were born naturally who didn't have the jacks and were like happy about it i'm
pretty sure that that was a i believe so yeah yeah um also the scene that alex is talking about like
with uh the machines are good or whatever is it's just that scene where the dude takes neo down to
the engineering level yeah in uh in zion yeah and he's like well you know machines suck but also
we gotta use them yeah we wouldn't be able to breathe down here yeah yeah so it's like a win
some lose some situation it was a little heavy-handed in terms of the uh the dialogue but
you know whatever i guess if alex wants to take that as oh that's right whenever the old guy pulls
him aside and they're standing on the ledge with all the apartments behind him and no one can see
them or whatever yeah yeah it's in the middle of the night the thing i loved about that scene is
like this fucking apartment complex if you want to call it that is gigantic huge that dude the
counselor or whatever had to have been waiting forever on the off chance that neo would walk
out of his little apartment so he could walk up and be like do you need some coke hey you want
to hang out i would have loved for the like a scene of the movie just be like dude he doesn't
even have like a cell phone to like play a game on or something he's just sitting there twiddling
his thumbs he's got he's got the neo futuristic version of angry birds and he's just throwing
plushies off the off the edge shit i hope neo has a bad dream and wakes up he comes out here
just gonna wait gotta make this look like i'm randomly passing by
he's hiding around the corner yeah yeah oh when he opens the door yeah so um you know the big set
piece uh at the end of the movie is uh neo meets with the architect sure who created all the
previous matrix right right and explains to neo that he is a uh like a uh aberration yeah yeah
matrix yeah uh he's supposed to go to the source and then everything will reboot reset all over
again it was built into the code etc etc yeah so alex talks about that a little bit and the
architect this old man sigmund freud obi-wan kenobi archetype no to both sits there and uh
tells neo that they have allowed people to leave the matrix that they discovered
that suppressing an exodus from the matrix
actually causes a shutdown and a degradation of the 99 that remain inside their exoluthal tanks
that's correct as human batteries for the power grid surprised he understood and again you find
out that basically the computers are disembodied spirits are angels are devils and uh have all the
same carnal desires as humans but with an added uh viciousness like greek god so it is an illuminati
film through and they tell you we are the proof god okay i that clip was fascinating to me because
he's kind of getting it but he also doesn't seem to understand that it's a piece of fiction no
and then second he doesn't get that the characters in the matrix that like neo runs into are supposed
to be programmed yeah he doesn't get like the idea that these are their programs in a computer no
no they explicitly say things that are like oh that's what you are yeah you know like uh the
guy who fights neo before he goes to talk to the uh the oracle is like he he's basically like a
password screen yeah yeah whatever to authenticate totally whenever they go through all those doors
like it's the back door in a program like they talk about this pretty explicitly almost constantly
yes to the point where you're like wait and is when is he gonna fight microsoft word yeah they
aren't greek gods yeah or anything yeah he's gonna like clippy yeah exactly what is this gonna show
up agent smith absorbs clippy you're trying to destroy the make matrix would you like some help
with that oh god yeah i don't understand i don't understand how you can like get half of it i guess
and not the the the bigger picture yeah the oracle herself itself is a program and not a person or
an actual oracle at delphi yes yeah so i have now uh my notes from the matrix reloaded they're
getting intense you remember i do appreciate that your handwriting is much larger than mine
um that was just sort of like so i could scribble you know like i see so i could watch it and also
like half ha ha haphazardly take notes gotcha so here i'm just gonna read the notes uh-huh
as they appear on the page michael from lost exclamation point true i forgot that michael
from lost was in this he's one of the main characters he is one of the main characters yes
he's like one of the four people of in abaca and he's great yeah he's really great i love that guy
he's really good in the role too yep i don't want him to get hurt yeah um what oh this is just a
little note one of the fun things about the matrix is how important non-neo characters are that's
true you know what is it is like he's the chosen one and all this but none of it would be possible
like what he's doing if it weren't for other things that like morpheus is doing or niobe is
doing like everyone else has like parts that they need to play in order for him to be able to live
up to his oneness totally or whatever i think that's great it is absolutely no coincidence
either that all of those characters are from a diverse set of backgrounds with a bunch of
different possibilities within that yeah yeah yeah my next note roy jones jr i forgot that
roy jones jr is in this i also forgot that roy jones jr was in that i almost forgot oh man yeah
one of the one of the great albums one of the great uh rap albums uh round one the album uh
roy jones jr weird who want to get knocked out who want to fight roy jones who want to be next
now that i think about it that is weird oh yes oh boy yeah weird yep okay uh there's that scene
where there's two oh this is just a stupid note so there's a scene where there's like agent smith
turns another person into an agent smith yeah each other yeah they made the staring thing i
just wrote two agent smith should kiss totally they had to have at some point right it felt
like they were going they had to have um all right um what would you do if you met you dad
i probably think you'd fall in love i don't think so i'd probably try and beat myself
so i i thought that it was a little bit tacky that the beef between morpheus and the commander
was about niobe was about a woman like i thought that was a little bit uh easy uh yeah especially
when we're dealing with on the other hand there's part of me that thinks it's a good character
choice because despite the fact that we're dealing with such an end of the world level threat of
course people are still going to have those dumb little uh personal beefs you know what i'm saying
i get that it's a little bit convenient and a little simple exactly i fucking love harry lenox
dude who plays the commander he is great he is really really good he is oh what a fucking hard
ass for no reason half the time but also this is my next note he's not wrong to doubt morpheus no
no no agree totally rational morpheus is out of pocket he's doing all kinds of shit he's
ignoring the chain of command yes fully understand yeah um the other the other thing too that i was
thinking about is like you know you you you forget i guess if you haven't seen these movies in a
while you kind of forget that everybody hates neo and and morpheus basically they're not the heroes
to the powers that be in the the human world right of zion like they are not like they are out like
you said they're out of pocket yeah totally and you forget that it's they're they're they're
basically populist leaders alex should love this yeah to a certain to a certain uh interpretation
too you can view that as like it is a positive thing that these people will just completely
ignore orders and completely ignore the the uh current power structure in order to fight what
they believe is is true and correct but also what if they were wrong they've just killed all of
humanity so there's that yeah you know uh next note i love a cave but zion sucks um i do love
a cave uh i just didn't care for the aesthetic of of zion i will tell you about the cave we when i
i watched that movie with uh my best friend and his dad because uh i can't remember how
old we were at the time but it wasn't like cool for us to go because my parents heard
that there was a tit in the dance scene in the cave oh no oh there was a tit my friend really
oh no joke oh could you have spotted it unless somebody told you way in advance there's a lot
of people there's tons of people but that was enough for my family to be like hey there might
be a tit and not being able to see that leads me to my next note and that is this cave is way too
big that was a giant cave everyone's having their their uh their moment the tribal beats and the
rave it's too big the acoustics were great in that cave it's too big it's ridiculously big
uh next note uh fishburn not good i don't think he was carrying his weight i think the first movie
he did so much yeah that in this one he was allowed to just kind of be in the background
yeah you know i was just not uh that i was not that into him um so next note is neo a virgin
look when he and trinity are hooking up sure is that his first time i mean in the real world it
has to be doesn't it i would think so yeah that's interesting what not very but a little bit
interesting what what kind of what kind of dick prowess could you have if you've only done it in
the imaginary world i don't know i mean maybe hey if you come in in the matrix you come in real life
is that true i think so if you die in the matrix then yeah so everybody's goo is gross as shit
next note keanu is not enough of a blank slate like when he was sitting there talking to the
the oracle yeah i was like he's supposed to be like a blank slate that's kind of you know you
have sure he's he has too much agency for the role that he's in i think okay all right i might
be wrong but yeah i think we could i i would need to watch the movie again and then we could really
get into it i got a little bit bored uh there's because it drives a little bit yeah and i i
this note is this movie is just a video game everything is a fetch quest yeah that's a good
point constantly over and over again yeah yeah oh you have to go get the key maker oh the key maker
takes you to a door like you know over and over again like you have to go to a oh and then once
you get there oh no you gotta go to b oh no you gotta go to c it's it's a little bit clunky but
like i said like once they get to the the like highway chase scene things pick up business
business picks up yeah yeah you forget a little bit of like they're just going around doing a
quest right all right you get lost you get absorbed in it a little bit more but at the
beginning it's it was a drag oh uh later on it's borderline a heist film in that way of
like a problem arises we have to go somewhere and get the you know like uh like oceans 11 we got to
go get the uh emp from some other place because ours broke or whatever yeah yeah like that kind
of thing next note hugo weaving is a monster he's killing it he hmm he's good he is good he's good
at acting he's good at uh agent smith i don't know about my uh my boys elrond i have a different
interpretation of the elrond but that's fine that's fine i'm talking about just in this film
he is crushing i get it i get it also i didn't really have as much of a memory of who the bad
guy is like obviously in the first movie the bad guy is the matrix it's the mature sure and i kind
of thought that was true in the second movie too and then agent smith becomes the villain in the
third one i didn't realize that it was really clear early in the second movie and it's agent
oh yeah yeah yeah the matrix and the machines are no longer really like they're an impediment maybe
yeah they're a hassle but the bad guy is clearly agent smith yeah it's a virus yeah yeah um also
this is this is just a little bit of a nitpick thing uh neo stops bullets yes you know yeah
why is he ever punched sometimes you get punched he has telekinesis i don't understand why nobody
threw a bottle of power raid at him that he can also stop with his matrix powers yeah that seems
to make the most sense to me and then while he's stopping the power raid he could scold alex
this will give you power uh i thought the cga fight scenes looked amazing for being made in
2003 totally they hold up they look like sometimes like a little bit of it's a little bit cartoony
you can tell it's digital but like considering that this is 18 years old or yeah yeah it's
amazing there was a point in the agent smith fight where you so clearly see it go from people trying
to actually do a choreography to uh like complete cgi stuff where you're like okay well this might
be uh a little bit on the uncanny valley but but it's not like it wasn't so much that that it took
me out of the experience of watching the fight scene totally no like you get like oh yeah that's
that's digital or whatever but it's not distracting and it's a cool fight scene yeah uh next note
everyone is right all of the humans are right morality is complicated everyone disagrees with
it everyone disagrees and everyone is right
i thought that was a little bit weird i do i like that i like that a lot i like that everybody's
right but everybody is also disagreeing about yeah yeah it's complicated maybe they have across
purposes kind of you know like maybe it's like you have the same goal and the way that you think
we're going to get to that goal is correct right uh but it might be sort of contradictory next note
two exclamation points on this one no you haven't used two exclamation points for three years
correction three oh shit this is unprecedented cornell west
wait cornell west is in there i forgot that he plays one of the members of the tribunal
he does not it's cornell west yes get the fuck out of here i was like that can't be cornell west
it is it's cornell i will be that i feel like i should have remembered yes although probably the
first time i saw it i had no idea who cornell west was why would i know why would i be a 12 year old
that's like a huge cornell west guy yeah it's it's possible that you just had no idea but it's it's
outrageous he's one of the people who's on the board or whatever yeah whenever uh they're talking
about sending two more captains yeah help out with an old guy the old the old guy who talks
yeah and then there's the old lady and then it's cornell west there's a couple other people but
yeah those are the three that have speaking roles bananas yep so this is from the mira
vingian scene okay i forgot that that woman orgasmed from eating the cake that he sent her
that's true that was tacky that was really weird uh because because the only thing that
you can think of while that's going on is somebody right next to her going i'll have what she's
having like that's literally what's happening yeah and the way that the matrix code goes in
between her legs and then there's an explosion i was like this i would i would have taken another
pass at this this is this is totally not in line with the rest of this movie also does the code
in your genitals give you an orgasm it's an explosion right okay all right um so uh
uh the mira vingian's wife monica belucci uh i just thought this was really funny this computer
program really wants to get kissed
i don't know why it does seem like that mm-hmm i i i was watching them go in and out of doors
and it made me think of the adjustment bureau okay i have nothing else to add to that i just
thought of the adjustment bureau all right they wear the hats they do wear the hats i recall um
i i liked the twins i liked the twins the dreadlocked albino twins this is aggressive
i don't know why you're pointing at me because i remember not liking them the first time i saw the
movie oh okay okay i remember thinking it was a little bit uh dumb or whatever but like their
powers are really well defined and well done in the movie yeah they can choose when to have
physical form essentially so they can be in danger from a knife or a gun or whatever like the way
they go in and out of cars yeah yeah it's very fun it's a well imaginative yeah yeah um and that
the only thing i didn't like is that like they apparently die in an explosion they could have
just gone on corporeal at any time yeah um also neo should just have told uh trinity that
he saw her death in the matrix would have really cut down on time it certainly would have been more
i don't know because they have a they have what's presented as a good relationship yes they seem to
really care about each other correct and it does not make sense that he wouldn't trust her with
that kind of information they're in a post uh like apocalyptic hellscape world let's be on the level
with each other yeah yeah yeah honesty is the best policy whenever uh everything is collapsed
three exclamation points again okay steaks so the movie has clear steaks oh okay okay everything is
very clearly like immediately flashback to the joey pants situation oh no no that was the first
movie like wait are there more steak eating scenes no i i i think that the steaks were a lot clearer
than i expected them to be yes yeah it made a lot of sense and then uh the last thing that i i uh
last note was from the architect scene um you know so he says that you can go to the source
and then you choose people to repopulate zion like we've done the last five times sure who was the
last one who did that and created this zion right who was that was that i don't know i know oh oh
okay you're you're telling me i mean was it the exact same neo was it it can't be the same neo
because later on we find out he made a different choice or is it the same neo who's learned from
his previous choices i don't know but it's a turncoat it's it's whoever the last uh one was
is not a good uh character yeah i mean that's that is that kind of like really dangerous choice
of theoretically he could just wind up wiping out the human race and he could just wipe out the
he could just wind up wiping out the human race entirely if that neo and i don't know why we're
using a gender pronoun for this uh could be anybody but uh you know he's the the person
is faced with the choice of like is everybody going to die or am i going to reboot this perhaps
infinitely but if i reboot it at least we got another go right you know so there's that there's
that uh moral quandary there um i hated the architect because uh too freudian no to obi-wan
no i mean you can't replace uh big words for uh actually making sense you know so there's a lot
of that where i'm like you're just using that word because you know people aren't gonna look
up the definition later i feel like it made enough sense yeah to like it's it's serviceable
no contextually you get it but from a fine granular kind of if i'm combing through the
script i'm crossing out five dollar words left and right yeah yeah that might be a good note
but also i did enjoy how like you know the obviously the movie is building towards like a
climax of like something you think is gonna maybe be like action oriented yeah yeah and then neo
walks through the door and it's just an old dude sitting there that is fun yeah it is fun there's
some there's some subversion of tropes there yeah yeah um anyway my review overall not bad okay
all right you know i don't like movies that much but i enjoyed at least half of it like i think
it was really slow starting yeah like when they're in zion and all that it's it was tough to get
through yeah i was like i'm gonna turn this off like 15 minutes in i was like i can't sit here
and watch this but i pushed through and i enjoyed once it got cooking yeah i recall there being a
lot of vitriol towards reloaded and uh and then even more towards uh revolution yeah uh but i
think that also might be because we were coming off the back of uh uh the phantom menace and
attack of the clones at the same time so everybody's just furious at every movie and i
think that the first matrix is almost an impossible challenge to follow up totally like i think that
that was that was something that caught on so huge yeah and and blew minds like i i don't even
know what you would do if you like we were trying to make another one yeah i think they did a fine
job yeah especially with a massive budget that you're expected to show in the film you know like
the original matrix was so well uh written and so tight because of those uh you know budget
challenges at least partially not of course because of them yeah but that that kind of uh
we got to figure out a way to do this that's cheap is a lot of times a really interesting uh and uh
uh font of creativity necessity is the mother of invention there we go i would i could have said it
like other people do uh-huh well i am the architect um so alex gets uh to talking about the
uh how like in 25 years we're all gonna be plugged in that's true we're gonna be plugged
into machines man oh we're counting down it's not just wired magazine silicon weekly and many other
publications including salon today that are warning you of the takeover last year a new army
war college report in 2000 came out and said within 25 years we will all be in a hive mind
that the pentagon will oversee the insertion of the public into a control grid that we will all
be mounted in our homes wired in to a global government mind control computer see that's
kind of fun because alex could take that clip and he could be like look at facebook sure sure you
know like he's like i was right yeah yeah he's not no he's talking about the matrix and talking
about that being real yeah and there's something uh in your in your house that you're plugged into
or whatever like it's not it's not a metaphorical um oh my god social media is gonna take off no
and there were people already at the time going like social media might not be a good idea to have
it take off and they were people who had studied real life technology and real life trends towards
that they weren't like it's gonna be exactly like the matrix dog eyes come on dub dubs the movie's
evil yeah come on that's reality all this is though like this whole movie everything is just
preparing you jordan sure to go into the matrix okay they are preparing you for your journey into
the real matrix now if you're shocked by this i have been warning you long before the matrix came
out this was their plan the elite of course will not be implanted and most of you are going to be
killed after they release mass plagues this is if they get you herded into the larger cities
and yesterday i read from wired news out of the newest darpa document where they say everything
you do will be tracked and traced and you will be plugged in to this system i'm sure you saw all the
you saw all the newscast in the same exact words in the same order uh that wired article in case
you did not listen to our last episode was about a research proposal that darpa had for a program
called life log uh which didn't end up happening and we're not in the matrix we're not so or are
we we wouldn't know uh exhausting yes so um i feel exhausted by those sorts of questions where you're
like well maybe we are what is totally totally great yeah um fun alex finds it painful to watch
movies like the matrix it was painful but he's still gonna buy a copy well of course
this is real truth is stranger than fiction and to have the illuminati shout at me for two hours was
very very painful uh i was nauseated during the first 30 minutes of the film i will have to of
course when it's on dvd get a copy and try to freeze frame it now i'll still give him my money
but you know like i will i just am i i'm just blown away by that statement out of a human
after what he said yeah i mean like he thinks that the illuminati yelled at him for two hours
and part of that was a powerade commercial yeah that he took personally was the powerade
commercial on the original dvd or do you have to get the director's cut i think i played in
theaters you can find it on youtube okay i found it um so anyway this this movie was the most
gripping that's a positive review word right yeah it tends to be it's a gripping instance of mind
control i mean it's hard to keep people entertained for two hours it's difficult uh there were other
subliminals here i'm not sure exactly what the covert subliminals were they're really good then
in the front of the film at higher levels and then saturated in emotional scenes when your
conscious mind is diverted in the primitive combat function mammalian activity structure
so this is what we're facing i recommend that uh you do not see the film i know the
reverse psychology will probably see it though curiosity killed the cat i was i felt like
walking out of the film it was the most gripping but i'm gonna buy it overt mind control i have
ever experienced i don't know if you could do a better commercial for the matrix movie to alex's
audience than that yeah like that is catnip to them they will they're all gonna flock to the
theater to like like oh my god i was able to resist the mind control no it's like one of those
it's like one of those uh marketing strategies where they try and piss off christians because
then they know real people will watch it and be like oh i get it you know this is fun i'm doing
this to make whiny old church ladies angry at me yeah so this next clip just confused me okay
the oldest form of mind control is superstition the witch doctor
knew when the solar or lunar eclipse was coming it's really offensive and he was generally part
of a hereditary guild or kind of your first masonic lodge no and he didn't know why there
was an eclipse but he knew when it was coming and it happened so infrequently that people would
forget about it he could use that knowledge to shock and amaze members of the tribe
and then get special favors the best hut the best women the best food so i guess according to alex
like witch doctors are illuminati i think that's what he's saying man i will tell you this right
now yeah i think the thing that scares him more than the matrix reloaded more than uh oblivion
that's weekend at bernie's too because if you recall i think we all know what happened to uh
bernie in that situation was there an eclipse he was brought back to life and ambulatory by a uh
what we we would have called at the time a witch doctor yeah i i know that i've heard these sorts
of ideas from alex and they they come from like weird colonial era literature totally uh about
the like uh the horrible depictions of yeah uh folks um the i i know that i've heard these
thoughts but i didn't know that his idea of like shamans being part of a guild an ancestral guild
sure i didn't know that part of it which i think is really funny i think that's hilarious to
imagine that he thinks that all of these these shamans or whatever uh yeah they were somehow
linked up back in the day and you know what they got the best huts that's i just that's what the
scam was what a fucking ignorant and racist thing to think without learning anything about it at all
it's interesting to question whether like he got this from some other very misguided source or if
he wrote it himself yeah in his head and i'm not sure um so i feel like alex is kind of
as it relates to the matrix he's really caught up in it being a little gay when you see a society
in decline the empire's always use superstition and gladiatorial diversions to divert and distract
them and that's exactly what i saw in the matrix an overall globalist in your face admitting its
revelation of the method illuminati terms uh homosexual orgies and much much more this is
a corrupting film he brings up way more than once that there's like there are things that are
homosexual in nature right that's a real sticking point for him so what he's saying is that the
elites in the middle of a crumbling empire will do their best to distract you with superstition
and uh gladiatorial type combats a certain sort uh so that is why alex is giving us the christian
point of view of a movie it makes sense yeah fair enough so i thought like man what fun we got a
movie review alex was off base on a lot of stuff he's gonna do for the rest of the show yeah i
feel like there's there's really nowhere else to go after you've dug into the reloading there's
one place to go okay and that's to the phone sure alex takes a call and this guy is uh he's
a disabled person and he wants to know what the globalists are going to do with him oh no oh no
no 50 years old march and uh anyway i i was my left eye was put out with a rock when i was four
so i had to use my right eye uh pretty much all my life and it's getting to where i can hardly read
and uh but i was in a real bad wreck at uh well i had to go on total disability it messed my neck
and my spine up and uh i had to become totally disabled and i was just wondering what's going
to happen to me when all this stuff comes about they're going to just get away with me they are
they are going to uh put you in the compact city and you will live in a small one-room apartment
with arm swat teams all about you cameras everywhere thumb scan to get your food and
the first time you get sick they're not going to treat you they're going to put you on hospice
strap you down and dehydrate you to death it's terrible ain't it well i don't mean to scare you
scary doesn't mean to scare him what the fuck was that they're gonna dehydrate you that is so
fucking cruel that dude is clearly struggling he's super fucked up yeah he's really just man
and then alex just without a fucking thought just makes up some bullshit about how this guy's going
to be tortured to death in a small apartment under watch of the swat teams wow they're gonna tie him
down and uh dehydrate him is that what that guy was calling and looking for i don't think it's
maybe i mean he couldn't possibly have been looking for comfort no no maybe maybe he was
looking for something uh to justify his his belief in alex yeah it's like well this is
the horrors that they're going to inflict upon someone like me and their dystopian future yes
then i must fight and this caller actually does you know i guess he does get what he was looking
for he hopes that he can fight to the death uh against these people who would seek to dehydrate
him well i just hope god gives me the guts to uh fight to die as patrick and you're dead well you
say you have a son yo i got two boys one your job is not to move away and take some jobs and make a
little more money their job is to take care of you right yeah they don't take care of you they're
going to hell what i mean honor thy father and mother of course that is the commandment more
important than all sure uh but also no also no huge no that seemed that seemed a little bit out
of place for what i know of alex like your kids got to take care of you they're going to hell
what a very strange man yeah what a strange man to react like this to a guy who's clearly in pain
yeah and all the time i feel like these are interesting glimpses into things that you know
he would say or support but wouldn't really necessarily come up if it weren't for callers
yeah totally that's why i kind of enjoy that there's a lot more callers uh in the past also
yeah i do like finding out more and more little tiny details of his weird cosmology of like well
obviously if you don't stay with your parents and take care of them until their death you go to hell
yeah yeah satan will uh grab you is that why his dad works there must be must be um so another
caller calls in he wants to he's been he's big into relitigating the civil war um here's a couple
points okay over a hundred thousand soldiers from the union army deserted lincoln ended up with a
general who was a drunk i mean the the odds and the north and later on a president lincoln was
like lincoln was a very spiritual man no yeah his wife was in the adult well his wife is a different
story i hear you listen i appreciate the call i gotta go and they uh have it weird that lincoln
shows up on a episode where he hates homosexuality so much so we get uh alex goes to break and he
comes back and he gets another call and uh this guy is just watched a tv show about hitler sure
and uh he wants to make some comparisons to george bush i do like these calls too yeah uh the wording
uh the phrasing that uh hitler used in his speech before the Reichstag after the Reichstag fire to
get uh passage of the enabling act which gave him uh all-encompassing powers did somebody
take that i'd like somebody to send me that please i didn't but i certainly hope somebody does because
you you will love it alex you're gonna love it so this guy's saying that the phrasing that hitler
used yeah and arguing for the enabling act is the same as the phrasing that george bush is using
yeah he didn't tape this he has no idea alex hasn't seen it it's just a conversation of people
you catch that thing on tv yep okay wild whatever i have a theory i have a theory that i've been
working on for a long time which is that part of why we are where we are now is so many people
have been so obsessed with watching documentaries about hitler and the rise of uh the nazis that
over time it's turned into a sort of admiration for that for a lot of people which is why we see
all of these conversations in comparisons to hitler from the far right about everybody else
despite them adopting those tactics tactics almost whole cloth you know what i'm saying yeah i think
i think they're like it was effective i think you could learn the wrong lessons yes um so alex and
this caller while they're talking about hitler and his speech that is mirroring uh george w bush um
they they get into a little bit of a hey let's recast the bush administration but with their
sort of their analog in the sure sure sure the hitler administration of course of course
the comparison between the bush administration and the hitler administration john ashcroft
homeland security patriot act yeah john ashcroft heinrich heinrich heimler heinrich heinrich
heimler yeah and we've got um i guess ridge is kind of the herman guring and cheney is um well
i guess kind of a behind the scenes guy but it's it's they're not going to get away with it
it's rumsfeld gabbles
it's rumsfeld gerbils gabble's rub spelled gabbles
i need to be in more situations where that question is asked of me yeah so john ashcroft
was the attorney general for bush this is not analogous to himbler who was the reichfuhrer
yeah he was the commander of the ss if you want to be overly generous you could say like he was
metaphorically the head of the joint chiefs maybe something like that maybe he was just colon pal
tom ridge is the secretary of homeland security right herman gering was the head of the luftwaffe
and then he was in control of the reich tag so an equivalent here might be the speaker of the house
or maybe vice presidents and so the president of the senate sure sure cheney's behind the scenes
guy with no parallel so i'm gonna ignore that apparently rumsfeld is gerbils which is fucking
nuts yeah that's carl rove is gerbils yeah anyone who knows how to book a fantasy nazi team knows
that it's a disgrace that alex doesn't like no it's rove yeah it's it's could not have been more
rove ever yeah no there's only rove and gerbils like it's those two it's very very simple so
gabbles um he had some ideas about uh the big lie that is that is so much like how uh how gabbles
he had some ideas about the big lie right you tell a big enough lie and people will believe it
bigger lie harder it is for people to you know whatever the big lie alex has some thoughts about
that well joseph gabbles was hitler's minister of propaganda he's the one who said when you tell a
lie make it big repeat it often and most of the people will believe it and some people say that
that quote is i don't ever bother what our enemies do is tell a big lie and tell it often enough but
that they were still explaining what they did i don't know i seem to remember from sarah's book
uh as the way i quoted it but i may well be wrong but uh but what i'm saying is some people say that
that's taken out of context but no they're explaining how the big lie works regardless
it's a statement of fact so some people think that was taken out of context is there anything
more american than two old white guys talking about nazis that they haven't bothered to read
about so gerbils took the concept of the big lie actually from another source sure from mine comp
yeah hitler's book yep the passage in question had to do with hitler blaming everything that
went wrong in world war one on the jews the jews had committed a big lie about what had gone down
when alex says that gerbils points out that their enemies use a big lie what he's failing to point
out is that the actual context of the quote is nazi propaganda against jews yeah the big lie
was the bit was the lie about jews being the problem that was the big lie yeah the big lie
wasn't the jews lying about their involvement the big lie was telling people that it alex is doing
a great job of putting uh history into context for his this is awesome great hey this is the
guy who said that hitler and stalin were complete badasses he's read so many books about world war
two millions so alex gets another caller and this this is my kind of cat okay he wants to know a
very specific question uh he wants the answer uh from alex and that is what bible do you read man
and this is a loaded question sure because this means something to this caller obviously he thinks
that some uh versions of the bible are not accurate yeah yeah some things like a like a
newer version the king james or the niv or whatever it is you'd like there are some books
that are added yeah yeah yeah maybe he's somebody who's into some non-canonical books maybe who
knows i love this kind of question because it's very specific and there's a specific answer that
you should give okay if you're a religious person uh-huh you should have an opinion even if that
opinion is i think a lot of different translations sure uh are okay sure you should have an answer
alex whiffs uh let's talk to george in colorado thanks for holding george you're on the air
yeah how you doing man i'm a first-time listener and uh i gotta know where you stand on a couple
of things um on sunday morning when you go to church uh just wondering uh what bible you
carried to uh church with you well i don't go to church i don't go to the worship the government
and and learn a masonic religion most of these i can't really find a church here locally i
occasionally go to tex mars church which is good oh no no oh no no so okay so alex doesn't go to
churches but when he does he goes to tex mars noted anti-semite yeah yeah yeah i don't necessarily
even believe that i think alex is just grasping at straws and that was the only thing that could
come into his mind of like oh this is a crazy uh right wing extremist uh church i can you know sort
of signal to yeah um but yeah i mean the caller is just like he wants an answer of like king james
all the way baby yeah and alex instead is like i only go to uh uh uh insane anti-semite church
yeah yeah i don't go to church where you worship the government it couldn't be more of an important
question either because the simple fact is if you want to believe the bible you also have to believe
that it was divinely inspired so if there's a difference between two different versions of the
bible that would suggest that people got involved somewhere along the line uh at least in one of the
versions exactly if there's a discrepancy right so uh this caller is into jesus and that should be
enough for alex it's not it's just on a spiritual level here and uh from my from here in colorado
it's like the mecca where all these bibles are published and everything and uh and we take a lot
of heat and that's what we stand for at our church and uh you know we just believe in the old-time
religion and uh and serving the lord jesus christ you know and going out personal soul winning and
you know confrontational soul winning and stuff well i don't do that the cashless society control
grid of the new world order uh no about uh accepting jesus christ or you know personal
faith i mean so your church doesn't talk about the new world order though well no well yeah i
mean of course what i mean you know that's in sermons and everything great listen i appreciate
the call good to hearing from you george so apparently alex's prerequisite for a church
to actually be a church is they have to have his political inclination yes and preach about the
new world order it's not enough that they are aggressively and confrontationally into saving
souls for jesus yeah that's weird yeah yep yep that's pretty weird yeah you know if there's
anything i've always thought about religion it's that it should be in politics non-stop yep so
alex gets another caller and this guy is kind of into hitler i believe troy in new york you're on
the air go ahead yes uh thank you for allowing me to speak and be heard oh no about the big lie
technique the anti-christ accused uh hitler of inventing and propagating the big lie technique
this accusation is in fact the big lie technique in action well um you know it's not not the devil
who reveals the tricks of the devil it's the anti-devil who reveals the tricks of the devil
oh so i guess he's saying that the jews are the devil so wait so the anti-christ toll said that
hitler no the anti-christ doesn't reveal the anti-christ plans right it's a good thing to
reveal the anti-christ plans in my comp hitler talked about how the jews were to blame right
for everything in world war one and the big lie was uh like pointing the finger at nationalist
leaders right right and so that is hitler revealing the anti-christ plans which was
i mean if you look at it just very clearly saying that the jews are yeah that's basically what he's
saying yes yeah that's why i'm concerned right it's concerning issue yes there is a problem
especially after you know alex has said that he goes to text mars's church yikes like this is
just this is deeply anti-semitic yeah everything that's going on here yeah i don't i but man you
could just get away with a lot of shit oh yes oh man and then it gets even worse because uh
a name gets dropped and alex although he should be denouncing this person will not
because i was hearing that guy forgot his name he's from what was his name is david
david j smith waukesa hatchee texas yes yeah and he was saying you know it's a new world order and
there's not much that we can do about it because you know it's in the bible and i was just
you know uh that's what a lot of people think you know they think well it's in the bible and
certainly bad things happen bad things are going to happen but we have a job to warn people to
wake folks up and we can do something about that and uh at the same time you know people thought
that hitler was the anti-christ you can't fight him at the end of the world some of the christians
thought that they thought scallan was they thought mal was so every thug that comes along
the churches are being paid off not to speak out and fight it i'm not saying david j smith's doing
that he's a good guy i'm talking about the big establishment 501c3s so david j smith is doing
the same thing that all of these evil churches are they've been paid off to do it yeah he's saying
there's no use in fighting the new world order or whatever but alex is like no he's cool yeah well
he's doing it for free um if you don't recall david j smith is the preacher who's super into
british isrealism yeah i i do recall that uh very much a white identity uh proponent and yeah the
true jews are white people yeah yeah so now we have two examples within like 10 minutes of alex's
show of two very anti-semitic preachers uh that alex is a fan of yeah and won't speak ill of uh
he's a good guy that's bad man yeah that's that's really bad yeah yeah and especially because one of
the things that we've thought for so long is that he went under the radar with his anti-semitism by
just renaming it globalism that he's just openly anti-semitic here is kind of mind-boggling like
does he hide it later well i think i think that he probably doesn't experience all of this stuff
as being as anti-semitic that's true that's true well yeah it is it's super anti-semitic so let's
let's take a load off let's get a little bit uh lighter this has been you know some heavy stuff
with these calls a lot of a lot of hatred and uh this is just a good fun it's one of the things
that i think is is one of the treats one of the delights of going back to the past and that is
that there's a running theme that keeps going on through alex's show and that is that people from
the republic of texas keep calling and wanting to like get alex's take on things sovereign citizen
stuff yes yeah yeah they expect alex to be on board because he wants to secede and what have you
but he hates these people uh let's talk to dewayne in texas dewayne you're on the air go ahead
oh alex appreciate your uh time and uh the name is wayne not dewayne but wayne and uh i was just
checking to see if you have gotten my letter and i think you'll recognize it because it had the
texas flag on the envelope and on the letterhead yeah i've got your letter good i need a fax number
from you it's not over the air but you can fax my fax well sir i don't know if i can you know i
barely have time to read these letters i understand let's respond to them i understand what's on your
mind sir i just received a letter from the uh republican national committee wanting my opinions
i answered their questionnaire and then i'm sending them a three-page letter of my opinion
yes and what are your opinions well my opinions are that the only way we're going to beat this
citizen start small and for texas to start the process for succession and then but to do that
we can't have 14 fruitcakes pop up and claim themselves presidents of texas
alex is just so mad at these republic of texas people not a big tent
it's not a big enough tent for 14 presidents oh yes i got your letter that that is the
that is the that's the moment just that deflation of that that i got your letter that familiarity
of like i know exactly who i'm talking to this is happening this is gonna happen is this the
president of texas calling in i have to i have to let you talk a little bit because i know
so many of my listeners are you and there isn't really all that much uh air between us there's not
there's not a real substantive difference between what we believe yeah i just hate you i just hate
you because you won't shut up about it i want to talk about the matrix reloaded yeah for an hour
yeah and take uh aggressively anti-semitic calls yes and now i have to be like oh the government's
a lie so here's how we wrap up uh alex has taken some calls he has a he has a guest uh who talks
to for a bit in the third hour um who's someone who ran a um a a union in new mexico and they
got evicted uh because they had a uh war protest yeah and great yeah great that is something that
you should probably you know you know point out or whatever alex wouldn't do that in the present day
no um but also i don't know if i'm really that interested in this because like obviously
personally i agree that they shouldn't have been evicted yeah but i understand that having a
demonstration could have been a breach of their lease sure so i understand and i don't understand
why alex would be against the landlord's right to evict someone for having a rally yeah yeah yeah
i don't know it's politically bizarre and i i don't know so they talk for a bit in one way i
am like you know part of protest is that there are going to be consequences for it you can't protest
and think that it's not a protest if no one is going to fight back you know that's just uh advice
much like um much like uh the matrix too need to be stakes yes absolutely and then on the other
hand fuck you yeah you for evicting them fair enough yeah uh so here's the last clip and we
posted an article on infowars.com about the mara maraginian bloodline what they talk about matrix
too i don't suggest it's mind control folks i've seen it it's mind control man i control folks i've
seen it someone like me is strong enough to stand up to the mind control you might not be don't go
ahead do you know how strong he is he can't he can't be mind control he's going to buy the movie
just so he can test himself against its mind control or dan it's good practice or dan perhaps
all of the mind control that he was concerned about is not the mind control they were thinking
about maybe they were mind controlling him into buying the dvd yeah he also uh has a fridge full
of powerade and he doesn't know why exactly yes i'm so mad at powerade he's chugging powerade and
saying these mind tricks don't work on me the only way to get rid of powerade is to drink it all
that's true that's what's gonna happen i'm gonna drink the whole business dry powerade is a finite
resource and eventually i'll get to the end of it eventually we're gonna run out of power and i'll
teach them i'll show them i'll give them all my money yeah so i guess in terms of this the the
you know obviously they needed to get to the point where he actually sees the movie yes that's great
yeah and in terms of preparation for an episode this included me watching a movie so right you
know that's a nice little derivation from the norm fun um but yeah we'll be back uh on our
next episode where alex will not be reviewing the matrix hopefully hopefully uh but until then
jordan we have a website we do have a website it's knowledgefight.com yep we're also on twitter we
are on twitter it's at knowledge fight now go to bed jordan on facebook we are facebook like down
the show itunes please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out uh people doing
god's work right now yeah we'll be back but until then i'm neo i'm leo i'm uh dzx clark i'm darryl
rundis i'm the marigigian andy in chansas you're on the air thanks for holding hello alex i'm a
first time caller i'm a huge fan i love your work i love you