I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying we are the bad guys, a knowledge
fight.
Hey everybody!
Welcome back to Knowledge Fight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes.
I'd like to sit around, worship at the altar of Selene, and talk a little bit about Alex
Jones.
Oh indeed we are, Dan.
Jordan.
Dan.
I have a quick question for you.
What's up?
What's your bright spot today?
Unprecedented, Jordan.
My bright spot is the same thing it was last episode.
The tick.
I finished it.
Oh, you finished it?
The whole thing?
Did you start back in the cartoon again?
No, I watched all of the Amazon original series because I just couldn't stop.
It was just too enjoyable and too fun.
Everybody is just great in it.
All the characters are great.
John Hodgman in the second season.
Fantastic.
Ah, it's just great.
Yeah, that was such a fun surprise when Hodgman showed up and you're like, what are you doing
here, John Hodgman?
And it's John Hodgman, so you're like, well, he's going to be a small role or whatever.
Yeah, exactly.
I know that there's a lot of other things we need to complain about Amazon and Bezos
about.
True.
Obviously.
Amazon is going to rank really high in terms of other complaints like, you know, unionization
squashing.
Sure, sure.
There's a lot of problems with Amazon.
It's in the top 50.
Maybe.
Yeah.
Not having a third season of the tick is right up there.
Just barely broke the top 50.
Maybe 48, could be 49.
It's like how Alex complains about the robots at the grocery store.
He's like, and then I have to bag our own groceries.
No, it's not my main complaint.
That's how I feel about the canceling of the tick.
It's the bagging your own groceries of media consumption.
Just a delight.
It makes sense.
Anyway, what about you?
It's fantastic.
I will, I'm going to announce this now.
I'm very excited to make an announcement, Dan, I will be making a return to stand up
post COVID.
Whoa.
That's true.
I was booked for my first stand up gig.
You had some offers during the time that COVID was really sort of iffy, you know, like pre-vaccination
coming around.
Totally.
I didn't want to do it.
Yeah.
I couldn't put people in that situation.
I thought that was a really responsible choice on your part.
Yep.
Now it is in October and it was booked by friend of the show, Matt Drufke.
So apparently there are a lot of people with a higher Q rating than to get through before
my booking, but I'm excited to announce that here.
I feel like there was some open questions about whether or not you even were going to
continue pursuing.
So like I was, that might've led to less people being interested in requesting.
Totally.
No, I had basically stopped before the pandemic, but now that the pandemic's over, I can't
like not see if I want to give it another, you know, maybe give it a shot.
See if you still connect with that kind of expression.
See if I still get the feeling.
It's always fun to do one of the shows, the Drufke books too.
Oh, always.
Although you probably have to go to the burbs then, right?
I will probably have to go to the burbs.
Yeah.
Yep.
I'll come with you.
Back where I started.
I'll make this announcement here.
I will be there as well.
Not performing, but I will be there.
No, no.
That'll be exciting.
Yeah.
It'd be nice to see Druffles.
It'd be nice to take over the entire show and how it just all wonks and then the rest
of the comics are like, I don't understand what's happening right now.
None of these people know.
Let's not take over anything.
No.
Jordan, today we have a present day episode of the Alex Jones show to discuss.
Oh boy.
I am trying to shoot for something a little bit different.
I'm trying to take an analytical perspective of even myself and how I engage with the material
that we're covering.
All right.
And I think that one of the main problems that I have with the present day is sometimes
I try to bite off more than I can chew.
Okay.
And by that, I mean covering more than one day at a time.
I think that's really hard in the present day because Alex's mood is never the same.
No.
Two days in a row.
Yeah.
If you expect him to cover one piece of news that he was really big on a Monday, he probably
is going to forget about it by Tuesday.
Yeah.
We're all going to be dead on Tuesday, Wednesday, we're winning.
It's just incoherent to the point where it's painful for me to try and make it palatable
to an audience.
And it's frustrating to me to try and talk to you about it.
Right.
Well, why is he in a better mood?
I don't know.
No reason.
I don't fucking know.
Could be anything.
He took a nap.
He stubbed his toe.
I don't know.
Yeah.
It could be anything.
It's like he used to do a serialized show and now he's doing a monster of the day kind
of feeling, you know?
Yeah.
Everything's a bottle episode and it's fucking weird.
I think that maybe a better approach to it would be to just look at a day at a time.
Right.
And so today we're looking at June 13th, 2021 Blackjack.
Blackjack!
Oh!
That time I almost didn't say er.
Yeah.
So that was nice.
I didn't trust you to do your bit.
And so I sped into the Blackjack because I knew you were trying to lull me into a false
sense of security.
And that shant happened.
There is a meta game currently going on between us.
So Alex is on one on June 13th as the kids say.
Yes.
Okay.
He's on one.
Yes.
Okay.
He's wiling out.
He is on fleek.
I disagree with your use of fleek, but we shall see.
I'm not, I'm still not 100% sure what it means.
That's kind of my issue.
Yeah.
And we'll get down to business on this, but before we do, let's say hello to some new
wonks.
Oh, that's a great idea.
So first Reverend Dr. Robert E.O.
Speedwagon.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Holy shit.
I just started watching Jojo's Bizarre Adventure.
So there's a character called, uh, uh, uh, Robert E.O. Speedwagon.
Whoa.
Yeah.
So maybe that's a reference to that.
It could be.
All right.
Next, Jim.
No relation to a certain World War II person, Gabbles.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you.
Thanks, Jim.
Thank you for surviving so long with that name.
Next, Chell.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Chell.
Next, Randy C. Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thanks, Randy C.
Thank you.
Uh, I think I've got a couple of technocrats in the mix.
Uh, first, Mr. and Mrs. Makeshift Hamster.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
And Kickfisterscream.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
Crikey, mate.
That's fantastic.
Have yourself a brew.
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right.
We got to go full tilt boogie on this, Watson.
Let's just get down to business.
We ain't making that money off that heroin.
Why are you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large.
I declare info war on you.
Thank y'all.
Yes.
Thank you very much to the all of you.
Mm-hmm.
Now, Jordan, it's time to get deep.
Giving someone life is giving someone death.
You could say that life is death.
You could.
So, today, I'd like to say, uh, uh-
I never don't silently nod with that.
Just like, yeah, man.
That is deep.
So, uh, today, I'd like to say happy birthday and congratulations on the graduation to Madison
F.
Okay.
Also, I should say that this happened in May.
Well, congratulations and happy birthday to you.
I may have missed a message.
No.
I think they just sent it now.
I think they were like, oops, we forgot to give them that birthday shout out.
Mm-hmm.
Let's get on it.
Happy belated birthday.
Right.
And congratulations on the graduation.
And congratulations belated congratulations.
If life, if giving life is giving death, is giving graduation just signing up for school?
Look, I'm gonna, I'm gonna leave you hanging on that one.
It's fair.
That's fair.
It's just fair.
Yeah.
So, one other thing was, uh, Erica sent a message, uh, and wanted a special drop played
and it's something we haven't heard in a while and I thought, why not?
I think the people are itching for this.
So here, this is going out to you, Erica.
You know, they got baby shark, deep, deep, deep, deep, deep, deep.
They got mama shark, deep, deep, deep, deep, deep, daddy shark, we'll be right back.
An oldie but a goodie.
Always good to hear some daddy shark.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
So, uh, we're gonna be talking about June 13th, but here is an out of context drop from
today's show.
You know, I would never say if I got killed, start a civil war.
Good.
Um, well, one, one, you would already be dead, so you wouldn't have the opportunity to say
that.
No, no, you're saying beforehand.
Oh, okay.
On the off, like my death is a dead man switch for a civil war.
Sure, sure.
I think I wouldn't say that.
I know, but I think that's got some Jane Austen, the meaning is the opposite of the meaning
kind of thing.
I would never say nuke the planet when I die.
Why would you need to say, I would never say that?
The only reason you would need to say that is if you want that to be true.
Yeah.
I feel like almost nobody would say that.
Nobody should say that, except for maybe Mandela.
So Alex has got a piece of news here on the 13th, this is Sunday's show.
On the 13th he had gotten some news that this gentleman by the name of Christopher Sein
had passed away.
Sure.
He was a reporter, and he was the person who is credited with breaking the story of former
President Bill Clinton meeting with Loretta Lynch on the tarmac meeting.
Gotcha.
And of course, that means this was an execution.
Yeah, that sounds right.
What is the next thing to come in a season like this?
What is the next move always, and the move they've been carrying out all over the world?
Well it's this right here.
That's what it is.
45-year-old Christopher Sein, the award-winning, Emmy award-winning TV anchorman and reporter
who just had his book published and is doing great and was super happy.
Well he got executed inside of his house yesterday, and his body wasn't even cold.
The blood wasn't even coagulated before they said it was a suicide.
Just like Breitbart.
Hell, they'd say Kennedy was a suicide and whatnot.
You know John F. Kennedy committed suicide, you know that?
Breitbart, no one said that he committed suicide.
That was a heart attack.
Yeah, they said he did a lot of coke.
Yeah.
The situation with this is the reporting on it is that it's being treated as a suspected
suicide.
Suicide, right.
Right, right.
Not that the people are reporting that it definitely is.
Sure.
There aren't signs of foul play.
Yeah.
There aren't signs that generally would lead investigators to initially give a, this looks
like a murder.
Yeah, the doors were locked from the inside, like everything.
I don't know all of the specifics because a lot of it I can't really, you know, can't
find all the details, but you know, this is the same thing that Alex does all the time.
It's like they're saying that it's suicide in order to make sure that there's a cover-up
as opposed to there's reporting that preliminary indications appear to be that this was a case
of suicide.
And you know it's a cover-up because they're reporting that it's not a cover-up.
Right.
See?
Makes sense.
It makes perfect sense.
Yeah, so one of the things to keep a real sharp focus on here is how definitive Alex
is.
He did not...
He's reporting this as an execution in the home.
He really did.
It's kind of funny how that just flies over me now, just that a man can go on his show
and just be like, that guy was executed with no evidence or thought or anything like that.
And I'm like, well, of course he's just going to claim that.
He's decrying that the media is definitively saying that it's suicide when in fact the
articles that I could find about this were saying that it's being handled, the investigation
is a presumed suicide until other information comes along.
And Alex is doing the exact same thing.
Just the opposite.
He's doing what he's claiming the media is doing and that is jumping to the conclusion
of not globalist execution for sure.
Well, because they do it.
It's disrespectful.
It's okay for him to do it.
Yeah.
It's almost as if he forgets that there are real people involved in this story.
Almost positive.
He doesn't care.
So he also is treating this like a real departure from the way things were, let's say yesterday.
And he said, I'll never commit suicide.
And he said, I'm getting massive death threats.
My family, my children is from the Clintons because remember he exposed Loretta Lynch,
the head of the justice department and the FBI, all they have a corrupt meeting on the
tarmac and lying about it on that basically finally brought down the Clintons partially.
Well, they've been waiting for a green light time to go offensive.
I talked about canaries in the coal mine.
His execution is a message to everybody.
And I would expect to see a lot of these killings now.
He was definitely murdered in my view.
So this is, this is pretty definite the way he's reporting this, but also there's a number
of things that he doesn't ever substantiate in any way on the show, which is to me is
a problem.
The first is he doesn't show or give any evidence of him saying, I will never kill myself.
Yeah, I would need that.
That is just something that he says about every case that he tries to make muddy.
Sure.
And then the other thing is he's taking things completely out of context.
There is an interview that he did on Fox news, this Christopher sign, where he was saying
that when he did this reporting, he was getting threats, but he does not say that they are
from the Clintons.
Yeah.
There's a hundred different explanations for where these threats could have come from.
Sure.
Now, I mean, I guess if you want to jump to a conclusion that like Bill got on the phone,
I mean, I guess you could do that the first person I've had killed, I guess if Alex wants
to just make that conclusion jump and take the only evidence that he plays or provides
at all is this Fox news interview.
Okay.
I mean, I think this is proof that the Clintons were threatening him, I guess he can, but
he can't prove that.
When was the Fox news interview?
It was within the last few years.
Okay.
It wasn't recent.
So the interview where he's getting threats is from a few years ago.
But also he's saying that it was when the reporting happened and that was 2016.
Right.
So it's five years ago.
So I'm fairly certain people have let it go.
No, they just let you forget about it.
No, I'm going to go with let it go.
I don't know.
I don't know why Hillary didn't become president.
That's true because she was partially destroyed by this.
Finally partially taken down.
Yes.
Yeah.
So Alex jumps around a little bit.
This is the main story he's going to cover, but he also does just throw a few darts around.
Sure.
Here's one of them.
And yeah, now mainline doctors from Italy to Mexico, to the United States are confirming
that people are seriously magnetic in some cases when they've had the shot.
And then we find the literature that it's designed to grow magnetic prions in the body.
So yeah, apparently Alex is on the magnet tip.
Magnetic prions, huh?
In the body.
Uh huh.
From what?
Uh, iron in the blood.
I would really like to know.
Okay.
So they grow them inside the body.
Do they inject you first and then they like, is it like an embryo that grows with inside
you and then you give birth to a magnet baby?
I don't know.
Cause Alex doesn't explain and I don't really care.
I looked at this a little bit.
It's just like viral videos of people pretending to get their magnet.
Sure.
I gotcha.
So Alex is on that.
He's into it.
Cool.
I wanted him to talk more about this, but he doesn't.
Yeah.
It's just a throwaway thing.
It's like, yeah, everyone's turned into magnets.
I want a magnet, baby.
I need more information on that.
I was like how small his geography is.
Like this is the biggest world in the world from Italy to Mexico.
The biggest amount of like, okay, man.
Sure.
Um, the Clintons, they're killer and this is the beginning of it because they were waiting
for the green light or something to go ahead and take out people who know their dirt.
The Clintons I've noticed do this in waves and people that control the Clintons do.
They'll kill a bunch of people, a couple of hundred here, a couple of hundred there, and
then they'll wait a while.
But when they start killing, you'll see the type of group it is.
People that know about Arkansas savings and loan, people that know about their corruption
and you know, Africa scams and deals.
But this is, I believe the first salvo and I've been predicting this is coming.
What about Larry Nichols?
We don't talk about him.
That's that's past.
Alex doesn't bring up Larry Nichols at all here.
Like he passed away within the last year.
Yeah.
I swear.
I think we're the only people who noticed.
I really, I do kind of feel sad about that.
We talked about it when he died, but it is really a bummer that Alex doesn't even bring
up.
This is if you're doing Clinton conspiracies, you got to bring up the Larry Nichols.
You got to say like, oh, isn't it convenient that now when they start back up their killings,
Larry Nichols is no longer with us.
In waves.
Silenced.
Silenced because he's the Oracle.
Oh man.
Why would they kill in waves?
Doesn't that make less sense?
No, you gotta, you gotta kill in a wave and then let the tide go out, let tension ebb
and then come back.
I don't know.
I feel like a bunch of connected killings in a short period of time and then a long
series of length of quiet time would more suggest that it was a, you know, assassination
instead of like an isolated event.
Hmm.
Well, it's good thing that you're not on their trail.
I did watch mine Hunter.
I think I've got it.
Yeah.
So we got another, uh, stray dart here off of the assassination, uh, uh, narrative.
Very bad developments on that front.
A federal judge has ruled that employers can order you to take a vaccine, any experimental
thing they want to have the job hell, I guess they can mandate you got to inject cyanide
and by free will, you could kill yourself.
And that's really the point they're getting to.
So wait, how would you get a job that lawsuit filed by Houston hospital employees who refuse
COVID-19 vaccine, according to Alex's politics, he should not be opposed to employers having
the right to make these sorts of demands of employees, right?
He swings libertarian.
And based on that belief set, he should think that the employer has the right to make whatever
requirements they want.
And the employee should have the right to accept them as a condition of employment or
find a job elsewhere.
If having the vaccine requirement is something that hurts a business's ability to attract
potential employees, the free market will sort that out.
According to libertarian ideology, come on, it should be unfair for everybody else.
Libertarianism is about fairness for me, fuck all those people.
So apparently 117 employees out of the 26,000 in the Houston Methodist hospital system refused
to get vaccinated and were suspended from their positions.
So they sued and a judge recently dismissed their case.
One of the reasons that their case can't possibly win in court is because they're in Texas.
And in that state, they have very weak protections for employees in cases of wrongful termination.
Oh my God.
Oh, has somebody been hoisted upon their own fucking petard?
In the judge's decision, they spell this out quote, Texas law only protects employees from
being terminated for refusing to commit an act carrying criminal penalties to the worker.
Based on that standard refusing to get a vaccine can't possibly meet the criteria needed to
satisfy that charge, but interestingly, Alex's example of injecting yourself with cyanide
would fit that standard for wrongful termination because that would be a criminal act.
That would be the only example that fits that essentially.
Yeah.
Jesus.
So anyway, this is-
Wow, Texas is just really fucking crazy, huh?
Well, I mean, they have sort of these weak protections in place and employers can make
these sorts of conditions of employment and Alex is thrilled with that until he's not.
Yeah.
It should be unfair for everybody but me.
This fits my policies until, oh no.
Why is this hurting me?
So now back to the main varsity storyline, which is-
Assassination.
We'll put on screen for TV viewers, radio listeners, I suggest you go to Infowars.com
and see the forbidden, verboten information.
Verboten?
That is the headline for today's show.
Sunday emergency broadcast, and I'd say we're in quite the emergency, reporter who exposed
Clinton control of FBI executed inside his home very, very professionally.
The problem here is that Alex can't prove any of this and it feeds into a very dangerous
cycle that we've seen play out over and over again in conspiracy culture.
By Alex reporting this as a definitive execution, it can feel like he's just creating a thriller
plot around a tragic death, but ultimately there's a lot more going on.
Because Alex is so sure that this was a professional execution, he's giving the audience permission
to be just as certain and this leads to problems so they encounter people who don't share
their certainty.
People like victim's family members or government officials or media figures who don't comport
with the conspiracy version of this death are now suspect as being participants or engaged
in the cover up.
These people often get hurt or harassed and hurt badly sometimes in these conspiracy campaigns
and Alex doesn't give a shit about them or their wellbeing.
There's nothing wrong with holding some skepticism or asking questions about events that happen.
The appropriate thing to do then, however, is to explore the questions privately by reading
or interviewing people or doing some other kind of investigative technique and trying
to find some actual information.
This is not what Alex does.
He doesn't ask questions.
He makes decisions about how to write other people's stories so they fit the narrative
that he can make a profit off of and it's to the detriment of the people who are involved.
Yeah.
It's just gross.
The worst part is just like putting that professional in there.
That's okay.
So we do look into it.
We find out that it's absolutely a suicide.
Right.
Well that's how you know it was a professional because only a professional would make it
so clean.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Yeah, definitely.
So there's just no escape.
No evidence is evidence of the conclusion that Alex has already reached.
Exactly.
Yeah.
You can't, you can't.
And overwhelming evidence is even more evidence that the conspiracy is true.
There has to be just a little bit of evidence in that sweet spot, I guess.
And this is bad because, I mean, obviously I think anyone listening to our show can understand
why this is bad.
Sure, sure.
But it's bad even more than we've already discussed and that's because Alex is presenting
this as like a real escalation in things from the globalists.
They're assassinating reporters in order to cover up their dirty business.
In waves.
And there's going to be a lot more.
Exactly.
And this is a crossing of the Rubicon.
To go to that escalation, to start really killing people, passes a whole other Rubicon.
And it's because the globalists are so incredibly desperate.
But if you look at their entire posture and everything they're doing and everything they've
been carrying out, I mean, they're willing to kill hundreds of millions of people with
tainted vaccines, scar billions.
They're willing to do anything.
I just don't understand how anybody could hear this show and not think he's telling
you to kill people.
Yeah, that's the only...
Like they've gone offensive.
They're assassinating the people who are putting their business in the streets and reporting
the truth, quote unquote, about things.
So I don't understand how he can present like, don't do anything violent.
I mean, you literally cannot use the metaphor of crossing the Rubicon because the point
of the metaphor of crossing the Rubicon is that once this happens, it cannot be unhappening.
That is the end.
The line.
Yeah.
The language that he's using and the way he's presenting the story is very specifically
about like, the game has changed and now the rules of engagement are different.
Right.
And I don't understand how he can pretend that that's not what he's doing.
I don't understand how this could be the inciting incident if we're already confirmed that the
people who have the vaccine are going to be killed or are already dead or whatever it
is.
This seems like a de-escalation of if anything, oh, thank God they're only killing individual
people instead of murdering the entire country.
The stakes are weird.
Yeah.
They're not quite as in order as The Matrix related.
I don't like that the Crossing the Rubicon is a single journalist and not the hundreds
of thousands of people or millions of people who have been vaccinated.
Well, it's the way that Alex needs to tell the story.
That's true.
You know?
That's just passive murder.
This is active.
This is when the Cold War goes hot now.
You know?
So this clip is four minutes long and I think it's a ride.
It's a journey.
It starts with Alex intro-ing a clip of Sine, Christopher Sine, talking on Fox News.
Sure.
That clip does not get played.
Okay.
So this will be a ride.
Instead Alex rambles about how big of a threat he's under.
Okay.
He makes this about himself.
Well, that's...
Because of course he does.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's just par.
That's par for the course.
And then it ends in a way that will take your breath away.
Okay.
Here he is from the grave talking about all the death threats and everybody said, boy,
this guy's got courage because the Clintons really come after you.
Yeah.
Believe me.
The Clintons had all these big lawsuits filed against us by DNC party groups.
And a lot of stuff that I agreed to be off record, so I'm not going to say anymore, but
just believe me.
What?
I know some other big national talk show host that did take the threats and basically stopped.
And I know some big networks do the same thing and I understand when somebody starts threatening
to kill you and as you fall around, most folks back off from that.
For me, it's not about being macho or a pissing contest.
For me, it's just about, I got to do what God says and I feel good when I'm fighting
evil and I feel close to God and I feel strong.
Yeah.
I want to pause it right there just to like, I think that is macho in his conception.
I think that is the same endorphin rush or whatever that someone would get from posturing
as a macho person.
It's just put in the context and language of godliness or whatever.
I mean, it's an incredibly fucked up thought to think the only time that I am close to
God is when I am enacting violence.
That's not good.
Nope.
And just to even entertain selling out makes me feel alone and weak and pathetic.
So I'm just addicted to fight these people and fighting evil.
So if they kill me, it's a great honor to die in the service of humanity and I'm just
a very blessed person.
It's not going to be a failure, folks.
You have to realize that's going to be a real success if they're reckless enough to kill
me.
Instead, they're trying to put me in prison.
They got the FBI with a bunch of fake cases they're cooking up and that's fine.
I understand.
You know, they sold out to evil.
They've lost their soul.
Sorry.
That's not me, bro.
So any of the options, you know, I'm going to love lawsuits, fine, whatever.
I don't care.
I'm going to keep getting the word out one way or another.
Even after I'm present, well, that sucks, but whatever.
Or kill me.
That's almost the easier route right there.
But here's how it works.
I'm not backing down, but I will not have them kill me and then say that I killed myself.
So I was thinking how they operate and what they've done to really good men to demonize
them.
And you know what it is?
They come when you're there with your wife and kids.
So I'm just going to be completely honest about this.
I'm a tough guy at certain levels, but I have to really think about everything operates
and the way things really are.
And so I'm going to stay in this fight.
But I do need 24 hour day security for my children and my family.
I'm really I've got it most of the time, but I need to have real security.
I mean, guys on the roof all the time.
And we need to start writing profile stuff on the enemy and doing public reports on that
as well, because, you know, here's the deal.
I'm a canary in the coal mine.
This guy was a big one.
Just a reminder, two and a half minutes ago, Alex was introducing a clip of this guy talking
on Fox News.
Yeah.
From the grave.
Anyways, before I get to that, I'm going to need to build a moat around my house.
I'm going to have to have snipers on the roof, so I'm going to have chain link fences and
razor wire.
I'm going to do the whole thing.
I'm going to need to find more people who used to work for Blackwater.
Because of imaginary enemies.
Right.
So if we start seeing more deaths the next few days, the next few weeks.
It's a message to threaten everybody to shut up.
Or there might be 20 deaths by tomorrow.
Ron Paul's dead.
Alex Jones is dead.
Tucker Carlson.
The car bomb goes off.
I mean, it's a very good chance they're going to turn their little armies loose on us and
then to demonize good men, they'll kill Tucker Carlson, his wife, probably wait till his
kids are in college or over visiting or something.
And that's how they do it.
So I'm calling Tucker to have a show.
I've been telling Tucker, you need to get extra security.
I'm going to leave it at that.
And I'm going to call everybody I know and I'm calling this out on air right now.
We have to go into war mode now, ladies and gentlemen, as these are criminal terrorists
that carried out Oklahoma City.
They burned down Waco with all those tanks and killed those little kids.
They like killing people.
They're child molesters.
Hillary's a child molester.
Bill Clinton's a child molester.
Well guess what?
I'm not going to be a soft target for these people.
And I'm not going to let them tie me up while they blow my wife and children's heads off
in front of me.
Sure.
So I'm going to tell the listeners right now, and I know you're going to come through on
this.
I don't have the budget for the real security I need.
I'm going to leave it at that.
I've got guns.
We've got people around a lot of the time, but what is happening?
I need a serious security detail all the time for my family because again, they won't target
them if they, you know, they want to blame it on me.
I don't know how they operate.
So let them do that.
And then of course, if they do start doing that, if they kill me, ladies and gentlemen,
you know what to do.
You know who did it.
Join me, George Norrie for contact in the desert worldwide virtual UFO conference.
Gotta be thrilled to have your ad playing right after that, George Norrie.
What the fuck just happened to me?
I told you it was a ride.
What just fucking happened to me?
It was a ride.
Is he selling product based on getting people to pay for security for him?
For his family.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Basically he's saying that if you don't buy more of his pills, his family will be murdered
in front of him.
Yeah.
It does seem like that is his point.
Wow.
Yeah.
I just thought, I thought it was pretty shocking that it ran into money at the end.
I mean, I shouldn't be shocked, but the way that was going, it was so intense and like
so off track from where that clip started and what he was ostensibly trying to do, which
was cover this story.
And he started talking about himself like, ah, I don't want him to kill my family.
I need more security.
It just seems like, okay, here's a paranoid spiral.
Yeah.
Whatever.
This doesn't go well.
I get it.
I think that's in the Alex Jones wheelhouse.
But then when it turned into like using that paranoid spiral to be like, I need more money
for this security detail.
That's when I was like, oh, this is crap.
That is.
He saw that they were coming up on the commercial.
He knew that he was about to go to break and he's like, oh my God, ad, perfect.
I can't afford security.
I need you all to pay for my security.
Brutal.
Absolutely brutal.
Mm hmm.
I don't, I, I don't know what world, I don't know what the rest of the world would look
like if one day I woke up and the headline was Tucker Carlson dies in car bomb.
Like what is, the IRA is back.
Like what do we do with the IRA living in New York?
I think if like selected people like Ron and Rand Paul and Alex Jones and Tucker Carlson
all died in a short period of time, I think even I, as somebody who believes in this space
as being full of misinformation and bullshit, I'd be like, there's a problem.
Well fuck.
There is a problem.
This is an issue.
They're probably still wrong.
Yes.
About everything.
True.
But you know, hey, maybe there is some kind of a fringe left wing terrorist group that
we have not been aware of or something.
That would be a shock if we discovered a strange paramount paramilitary leftist organization
right there.
I would, I would start having some questions if there was a convenient series of all of
these people.
I would say that is something that needs to be dealt with regardless of political ideology.
Yeah.
Oh, you know what?
Even if it was just Tucker Carlson in a car bomb, I'd be like, holy shit.
Something's not right.
Yeah.
Um.
What is happening?
What is happening in this world?
Um, so all of this didn't, I mean, all of this prediction didn't happen.
There were not, um, you know, uh, this, this wave didn't, uh, no, that was the 13th.
Right.
Okay.
And we're, we're recording this on the 17th.
That's correct.
Okay.
Tucker is still technically alive from what I understand.
Yeah.
Okay.
So it was Ron Paul.
Oh man.
You just can't kill Ron Paul with a car bomb.
He's too crafty.
He smells it out.
So, but, but again, it seems like Larry Nichols would be exactly who Alex would want to throw
into the mix on this and doesn't bring them up at all.
Nope.
They just forgot about him.
Yep.
So in this next clip, Alex salutes, uh, the, uh, the shorts, Christopher sign, and then
of course makes it a about himself.
All right.
So a real man, somebody's parents and family can be proud of a brave die, but one death.
Oh boy.
The cowards taste of death a thousand times.
Okay.
And I'll tell you again, they are bringing us into that wheelhouse.
You see it in history books.
You read about it.
You talk to grandpa, you tell you about it when they were alive.
People go through this.
People start fights and they don't leave you alone.
They attack you and they start killing people.
And at a certain point you're just like, well, all right, let me just roll my sleeves up
here.
So I don't know what to say at this point.
Nobody should be offensively violent against these people, but everybody should have their
eyes peeled and be ready because they've used, well, I'll talk about it next hour.
I knew this was coming for a long time, folks, but I just, they're going to start the killing
of journalists.
Watch that's next.
I don't understand what offensively violent even means anymore on his show.
Keep your eyes peeled for people to attack.
You're saying that we're in war mode.
Yeah.
Some of these people like to blow up the Waco branch Davidian course.
Okay.
See is their fault.
Not ours.
I don't understand.
I don't understand what these terms even mean and the way he's using them because I have
a definition of offensively violent and I don't think it's the same as the way he's
using the term.
No, it definitely does not seem the same.
Yeah.
Silence talks about karma.
Oh, he should not.
What goes around comes around.
He doesn't want to find out.
There's a large bleep in here.
By the way, you don't just face God after you die.
I'm only explaining to people, people call it karma.
What goes around comes around, you know, report yourself in my life.
I never even wanted to do bad stuff.
And every time I did bad stuff happened right after, I mean, I got a great life knock on
wood because I really am a pretty good person.
And, and I really want, I treat people like I want to be treated and then when I don't
do that, I'm guilty.
Okay.
And I try to make it better.
I run around all these other people, man, they just think that's weak or stupid.
No, what's weak is sh...
And you think you're going to get away with it forever and you're not going to get away
with it.
That caught my attention.
Big old bleep there.
It was a while too.
So here's a, here's what was missing from the broadcast.
I treat people like I want to be treated and then when I don't do that, I'm guilty.
Okay.
And I try to make it better.
I run around all these other people, man, they just think that's weak or stupid.
No, what's weak is shitting all over people.
You fucking pieces of shit, new world order.
And you think you're going to get away with it forever, you're not going to get away with
it.
Yeah.
Man, he's still bad at swearing.
He is.
He's just really bad at using swears.
Yeah.
But you know what else too?
Like I watched the clip of that in the video and there's a look on his face.
That's like, I did it again.
There is like a look of like, I don't think he's that good of a performer to be able to
give that subtle look of like, ugh.
Yeah.
Like he slipped and screamed obscenity again.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's weird.
Very childish.
Bums me out.
I feel like people should learn how to swear.
Yeah.
For someone like myself who has a potty mouth, I accept that.
Telling me to.
I understand that.
Yeah.
It's still, the way Alex swears is a little childish.
It's a little bit.
Yeah.
A little bit dumb.
I'm not saying we should teach children swears, but I am saying as a child, you should learn
them.
Mm-hmm.
So Alex needs to get his family more security.
But he also in the snake slip is talking about them as if they're just like collateral damage.
And by that, I mean, he literally says that they're collateral damage.
Well, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I've already explained this.
I've already, I love my family so much that I know there's no future if we don't meet
these globalists.
So I've taken out of my mind the opposite of a sociopath, but to where just my, my family,
everything's collateral damage because it's, it's a war.
It's not like I asked for this.
I can't let threats against my family govern me and make me stop what I'm doing.
But I will not leave on the chessboard the chance of them having their victory against
me to make me a villain where they kill me and my family and then blame me for it.
So I've got to have people, cause I know, I know how to look at all the angles folks
and it all just like a computer, like it's working, working, working, working.
The answer comes out.
I always know what my answer is, right?
And today I was already saying I need more security.
I was already calling my security people and saying, this needs to be done.
And then I saw this story on info wars and I went and spent two hours reading all about
the angles of it.
It all just went, I've got to have people in my family at all times or anytime I'm with
them.
That really sounds speedy to me.
Yeah.
This is really fucking unacceptable, dangerous shit we're tossing around here.
And the way he's connecting thoughts and the way that it's very scattered.
Yeah.
I'm it's a little worrying.
I assume this is all because of the, the few articles that were like, Alex was coordinating
with Trump for the sixth riot, right?
Maybe.
I mean, he does, he does mention that a little bit and I don't actually, I didn't actually
pull any clips of it cause it was disconnected from these other, this other story and like,
he's totally dismissive of it and he's right to be dismissive of it.
Totally.
But it's, I mean, that's the only thing.
These people saying this clip resurfaced, what the fuck?
Yeah.
Trump said we're going to the Capitol on the stage and it's like, yeah, that is, that is
true.
100%.
Yeah.
I don't, I don't think that it's related.
Right.
But he's just going so hard with personal shit.
And then the fact that he's like the moment you go from like, we need to protect our family
to like acknowledge that your family's already dead is, is when you've turned people into
a holy army and there's just no, I mean that is in some ways crossing the Rubicon if you
will.
When you turn people into a holy army, that's fucked up.
I don't disagree with you, but I also have heard him say stuff like this in the past.
Totally.
When things have gotten like fairly intense for him, he will, he will talk about like,
I've just had to give my family up to God.
No, totally, totally.
I've heard him, I've heard him do it before.
It just seems like in...
It's rare.
And because it's rare, it feels worse.
Yeah, it's, it definitely, well in our current context, it feels portentous more than it
would have in like the late nineties, you know, you didn't get the sense that everybody
was kind of itching for a holy war in the late nineties.
You thought they were itching for a battle over fucking Satanism or whatever it is, you
know?
Yeah.
So Alex has spent, I'd say all of the show rambling about his own need for security and
how this story about this Christopher sign is really a warning to people like him and
you know, really real narcissistic shit.
One quick thing, one quick thought, one quick thought, aren't snipers on the roof more to
keep people in than to keep people out?
I'm not sure, but Alex has many times talked about how he has snipers on the roof of Infowars.
Man, I feel like that's to keep people in.
I don't know.
You shoot people in the back if you're sniping on top of a roof.
You think so?
That's the way I, that's the way I've always seen it.
Interesting.
Um, anyway, Alex has not covered really anything, uh, but he has a lot of news.
I've got all this incredible news to cover tonight.
So much.
I did so much preparation for the show today and I haven't gotten to a lot of that just
because I've been busy on this because they want a message to reporters.
You do not report on Bill Clinton with the attorney general on the tarmac.
What
You do not report on this thing that will literally never happen again.
And was widely reported in every outlet.
All right.
All the New York Times journalists dead, Washington Post dead.
It seems like he's very desperate to excuse him not doing his job.
Yeah.
That's what it feels like.
I mean it's hard.
So I was like, okay, well at least he's getting introspective about it.
He's got more time on the show.
He can, he can get into these stories that he's failed to cover because he got caught
up in this.
Yeah.
So here's where he goes next.
Cause there's the deal.
They are wimps.
So they want domination and conquest and war with us because they, I mean, I'm not against
nerds.
I don't even get into what you call a nerd because I'm a little guy in the computers
being great person, but there's a certain time wants to be an alpha, but they're not.
And then they get into being nerdly and that's like their cover to commit their crimes.
And then anybody that they would call in modern parlance, a Chad or someone is the enemy.
And we'll show in modern Chad's while we'll inject you with poison and sit back and watch
you die.
They're crazy little scientists like Fauci and Gates and all of them are psychos.
I don't, I don't know how I feel about Alex talking about Chad's.
There's nerds bully me with their brains and I'm supposed to bully them with my bronze.
I don't like it.
I don't, I don't, I don't know if this is a useful way to spend time on the show.
I mean, saying that some people have inferiority complexes is something that maybe Alex I mean,
what's that?
Somebody is on the phone?
I think it's the kettle.
It's for you, Mr. Pot.
You know what the problem is that like some of these wimps, you know, they'll like pretend
that they're constantly under attack in order to escalate the things that they're talking
about to make themselves more interesting.
These dorks.
And they'll constantly talk about how they're so tough, even though deep down inside they're
not.
They'd be super into Star Wars, but they'd tell you that they weren't super into Star
Wars.
That way you wouldn't think they're a nerd, right?
So Alex has another clip that he wants to play, it's about this guy Frank Figliosi is
a former FBI agent, guy in the FBI.
That does have, that's a name of an FBI agent if I ever heard one.
And so Alex believes that this guy was saying that he wants Congress arrested.
Not quite.
But Alex also wants Congress arrested.
But he wants them to have trials.
Okay.
That's important.
That's very nice of him.
That is important.
Now they already know the outcome.
He's making this outrageous statement.
I mean, if I was up here saying without trial, let's arrest members of Congress, I would
say I should be off the air.
I don't agree with that.
I want a trial for everybody.
Now to people like Maxine Waters and Diane Feinstein that have been proven to be on the
Chinese payroll and Mitch McConnell, do they deserve to go to prison for what they've done?
Yes.
But I wouldn't want it without a trial because that's something that could happen to my kids
or to me.
I'm not stupid.
That's why we have rules.
So I'm protected.
And so are you.
But see these jerks, they always get rid of the chivalry.
They always get rid of the rules, taking one step ahead, not five steps ahead.
And then they're just in my wheelhouse at that point.
When I say my wheelhouse, people like me, I don't want war.
I don't want death.
I don't want any of it, but I'm like a pig in slop once it starts.
And there's a lot of people like me who've been like asleep, dormant.
And I really feel sorry for the establishment because I've looked at every possible exit
from this and it does not end well for them.
I don't know the difference between this and someone being like, we have cells in every
city.
Yeah, totally.
Totally.
This is basically how a terrorist makes threats.
This is a YouTube video of a terrorist with a fucking mask on going, we will kill you,
we're everywhere.
Also, fuck off with your trial bullshit.
How dare you tell me that you, we want them to have a trial.
We exist on show trials.
Yeah, exactly.
Now, if the outcome was anything other than the one that I've predetermined to be correct,
then the globalists are covering it up.
Of course.
No, no, no.
But the trial is important.
Yeah.
Silly.
Fuck off.
Also, I love the idea that he's like, Mitch McConnell should go to prison, except when
he's acting in line with what Trump wants.
Well, then he's a hero.
Right.
Then he's a hero.
Come on.
As long as he's doing that, I will support him staying in office and I will defend him,
but he also deserves to go to prison.
You know what really shocked me?
They had a Mitch McConnell story out recently.
They had the gall to ask Mitch McConnell if he would see the Supreme Court justice by
Biden in 2024.
Oh yeah, yeah.
I saw that.
I'm going to ask you a question, Dan.
Now, do you think McConnell said yes?
I'm the wrong person to ask because I did see this story and I thought it was like...
What a waste of everyone's time.
This is parody.
Outrageous.
Of course he wasn't going to do that in 2024.
We've already seen him not do it once.
But it's a matter of principle.
No, it is not and it never was.
Duh, you're all stupid if you believed him then.
So Alex plays this clip of Frank Figliozzi and I think his interpretation of it is a
little bit off.
This is such a criminal statement.
Here it is.
Look, Chris Ray testified publicly on the Hill that what happened on January 6 is domestic
terrorism.
What have we learned from our experience with international terrorism?
In order to address that problem, arresting local operatives is merely a speed bump, not
a roadblock.
In order to really tackle terrorism, and this time domestically, you've got to attack and
dismantle the command and control element of a terrorist group.
And unfortunately, and I know this is painful.
Take it back to the beginning.
I know this is painful.
We've got to attack.
That means kill and dismantle.
That means dismember, shut down.
The brain trust that's the Republicans that don't want to turn the guns in or have pedophiles
teach the kids or open the borders and let all you weird lawyers run everything and sell
us out to whoever.
Well, I'm a little scumbag lawyer.
I wear a fancy suit out on to me.
I mean, I'll arrest you.
I'm a lawyer.
I mean, it's just crazy.
I don't know if that's what I would have taken away from this.
Now, I have some problems with what Figliozzi was saying just from a different angle.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't think that certainly the way that we have carried out a war on terror around
the world is a good model for how we would approach domestic terrorism.
I think that's flawed.
I can't think of anybody I want dealing with domestic terrorism less than everyone who
has dealt with every type of terrorism currently.
Yeah, I think the proof of concept has not been good.
I think that there's a lot of dangers when you start trying to apply the way that we
have as a country behaved vis--vis international terrorism, trying to apply that to domestic
issues of terrorism.
I think that you run into a lot of issues and I would hope that we choose a different
way to approach things.
Hey, if there's anything that we know happened, it's that whenever our soldiers trying to
deal with international terrorism went to those places, they viewed everybody as a possible
combatant and that's what I want them to bring back home.
The possibility that everyone you live with is a combatant.
It's not good.
No.
And I would argue with Figliozzi on that tack.
And I would also say that there is something to be said for the other point that he's making,
so, you know, disconnected from that point, and that is that rounding up everybody who
got into the capital on the 6th isn't necessarily going to cause the kind of change that you
would hope to.
Prosecutorially or from a disruption of what caused this, that's not the approach that
you want to take.
There's a broader spectrum of decisions and things that you would want to do.
I do agree with that.
I just don't agree with his comparison between international terrorism and domestic terrorism.
And I also agree with you that what lessons have we learned?
Nothing.
Also, Frank Figliozzi has not been in the FBI since 2012.
There we go.
That's what I wanted to hear.
He does not speak for any organization in any official capacity.
He's a pundit.
That is what I was looking for.
Yeah.
So I just, I think that Alex's interpretation of this is silly.
It's just the same thing that this hypersensitivity that you see in the right.
You know, like when Biden says that the main terror threat in the United States comes in
the form of white supremacist groups, and then Alex and all of his friends report that
Biden said that white people are the biggest threat in the country.
It's just the same game being played here.
And I don't know.
I mean, they're right to act like that, obviously, if there's anything that we've learned from
the way that the right has behaved whenever there's even the slightest threat to their
ability to act with impunity, it's to go apeshit.
And clearly that's the best strategy because nobody's been able to do anything about it.
Yeah.
It is.
It does gum up the works.
It really does.
Yep.
So Alex, like you said, he has a lot of big news to cover.
A lot of big stuff.
Sure.
He's got this clip of Frank Figliozzi.
Yeah.
Whatever.
The Figs?
Here's the next thing he gets to.
You think he gets called Frankie Figs?
Probably.
A hundred percent.
Has to be.
Has to be, right?
Here's the next thing Alex has, and this is just, I have no idea.
I have no idea why this ranks.
He plays a video of someone coming out as a trans man.
Oh boy.
And people clap.
Yeah.
And I don't know why he's mad about this.
So they create all these people that never worked today in their life, never had a job,
and brainwashed by leftist behavior and manipulation.
And then all they can do is just squeal and squawk and scream because this person has
declared themselves something else.
It's the celebration of transhumanism.
And then there's the weird social worker in the pink dress, like approvingly looking on
at what they've done to people.
It just goes on and on.
Here it is.
So these are the lost, helpless people that the system is now in total control of.
I don't understand what Alex is going off of, other than there's a person speaking to
a group who support them and affirm and validate them.
I don't get how he can take this and be like, aha, this person has been tricked into doing
this, or whatever.
The only way he can do that is by complete invalidation of the existence of trans people.
That's really the only way you arrive at that conclusion, is that everybody is being tricked.
Yeah, no, I was kind of blown away by, you know, like I stay away from that world so
much, but my family has told me about some super Christian literature written by pastors
and shit that are like, here's why people think they're boys or girls.
Not like this is even possible.
Just blanket rejection of the possibility and pure society has failed us.
So I mean, I had no idea really how deep that belief was.
I thought they at least were like, oh, they're humans, you know, like it's, it's just mind
boggling.
Yeah.
So these are the sorts of things that Alex is taking his time with, um, and man, he gets
to the end of the, gets towards the end of the show and he realizes, I haven't done my
job.
The great Owen Schroyer is coming in to host two hours of live radio slash TV, and I'm
going to go ahead and cohost with him because I got, I don't want to stay emotional, but
a little preacher in the first hour, it's been most of the time that exposed the whole
FBI being under the control of the deep state, get his head bought off of his house.
Yeah.
I kind of wasted the first hour of the show, so I'm going to do the actual job on another
show.
Maybe, but I probably won't.
Doubtful.
Yeah.
I'm going to, I'm going to be there while Owen does the work that I am supposed to do
and interrupt him and keep him from doing that very same way.
And I'm going to be sauced.
I'm going to be drunk and I'm going to be eating a sandwich the whole time.
I have, I have very little respect for this.
Um, I, I understand that Alex is like, who cares?
I'm, you know, the info wars is still on air.
I can just do it then.
Like, no, this is your show.
Yeah.
This is your two hour block.
You can't just co-opt someone else's show and be like, Oh, that's where we're going
to do the real stuff.
I'm just going to fill time yelling about bullshit here and trying to get you to pay
for my family's Blackwater guards.
It's a, it's outrageous.
It is.
It's just dumb.
It is very out.
I would like to get mad at him when he's doing his job instead of get mad at him when it
seems like he's on his own time.
Yeah.
I, I do prefer, um, it feeling like we're actually responding to something.
Professionalism.
Yeah.
We deserve a mutual professionalism.
It would be nice.
So Alex, uh, has some, uh, racist opinions to get to here at the end of the show.
Can't close without it.
Nope.
So I don't even know how to set this up.
It's just outrageous.
It's just, I, I, within the very group killing black people and dumbing them down and shipping
drugs in their neighborhoods and giving them gangster rap on record to call each other
so they can then be put in prison tells you all day how much they love black people and
how they're just so sweet and you drive down the road, almost all the billboards are black
people for every corporation and all the big TV ads are black people.
The globalist corporations are putting a black face on everything they do because they go
all black people are victims and you got to be nice to them and then the corporations
then you got to be black people.
It's very simple camouflage.
Can't have people saying you got to be black people.
You are going to then sit there and carry out your operations and say black people are
doing this and a subconscious level.
If you hate the government, you hate the corporations, you hate the UN, you hate the chai comms,
you hate all this and then it's got a black face.
What do you do?
Oh God.
Holy shit.
Racism as always is everybody else's fault.
I was blown away by this sort of articulation of how Alex sees the world.
Yeah.
Wow.
BLM gave us NWA 40 years ago.
I would guess that Alex is using some sort of selection bias about all the billboards
are black people.
Maybe.
Could be.
Maybe he's getting mad because he sees some black people there and doesn't notice all
of the white people.
All the billboards used to be white people and now there are some with black people on
it and because that's different to me, I notice it, so now I assume that it has gone 100%
the opposite direction.
Yeah, I'm going to ignore all of the instances of the things that don't make me mad because
seeing black people in ads makes me mad.
I am a child.
I think like a child and I have no higher thinking skills whatsoever.
Yeah.
And this is a bit much.
So again, why does racism happen, Dan?
It's because the government and corporations put a black face on things.
It has nothing to do with, I don't know, several hundred years or fucking, let's be honest,
several thousand years of massive racism.
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
It's because the corporations and the government now.
That's why white people are so racist.
It's commercials.
Everybody knows it.
It's because one time I saw a black person eat McDonald's with a smile on TV and now
I'm racist.
I got to tell you, I'm not loving it.
So this is a bit of a lead in to a story about this recent shooting in Austin.
There was, I believe, a concert and there was a shooting there and Alex has some stuff
to say about it and it's a mess.
We love God or we love Satan or are we a dumb ass that says neither one exists?
That's the three choices.
You're for Satan, you're for God, or you're a dumb ass and of course Satanists are dumb
asses too, but not as dumb as those that say there is no God.
So here's a great example of this.
Most shootings in America that you hear about that are still pretty rare are gang related.
So it's Hispanic on Hispanic.
It's black on black and when it is a gang of whites, sometimes motorcycle gangs, it's
white on white.
Look at the Hell's Angels and the group they were fighting out in California and all over
the country, the Mongols.
So that's how it works.
So when I hear about nightclub shot up in Miami, no one would say what it was about.
So I looked it up.
It was a black nightclub and I go, hmm, I bet black people went and shot that up.
Sure enough, it was two rival gangs.
It's not about what color they were.
It's the reality of it.
If I hear some right wing square dance going on in the middle of Alabama, I had a shooting
at it.
I'll go, well, that must be some white gangs killing each other.
And of course it happens every once in a while, it is.
So here's what I'm getting at ladies and gentlemen.
This story is so huge because it's not about protecting black people.
It's about the media, the controlled corporate media, being able to set the precedent that
whenever they want, they can hide a fact because I can tell you right here in Austin, it started
with R.J.
Savada, who's a big Democrat.
It's gotten way worse now.
There'll be a serious out because I lived down there when I was in a divorce.
I couldn't get a house, had a rental place.
And I mean, there were shootings and killings down there in the most elite part of downtown
Second Street, all that area.
And you'd hear, oh, what happened in East Austin over on Chacon and 12th?
No, it didn't.
It happened on second in Colorado because I saw it.
I heard the gunshots.
So that's why this is so dangerous.
So you've got a hip hop concert going on.
Who do you think is going to be at that?
A lot of people, but a lot of black folks wild.
And here's the news mass shooting in Austin, Texas leaves 13 wounded.
Now can you imagine if it would have been a white person that shot into a crowd of mixed
people?
Yes, I can.
It didn't matter why he did it.
They'd say it was white supremacist.
Well, yeah.
I mean, it's like I guess what he's saying there at the end is like if circumstances
were different, people would cover it differently.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
OK.
Sub argument.
White supremacists never kill anybody.
Wow.
That's Alex's.
Yeah.
That's Alex's main argument that he is burying.
Man.
Yeah.
This is weird.
I don't know how Alex has evidence of crimes that were committed being placed elsewhere
in the city.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I love to imagine Alex just in like, you know, a duster, like a hat, like an old timey detective
from a noir going out there on second in Colorado, like, oh no, they're going to say this was
in East Austin.
I know it.
There's a guy wearing a press badge in his hat, just walking around, sir, did you see
this?
The only thing Alex has in common with like those sort of noir detectives is a penchant
for booze.
That's the only thing he has in common.
Yeah.
I think that this is also a bit scattered in terms of thinking.
There's a lot of stuff going all over the place.
When he was in an apartment, he knew that crimes happened in different places than they
said they were.
Also all of these various shootings.
Yeah.
So what's going on here is that he believes that the media is trying to cover up the notion
that the shooter in this Austin case was a black person.
Yeah.
And so he's going to talk about this here.
And I disagree with his point entirely.
Only Fox carried that press conference.
Every other channel didn't, but the Austin American Statesman went one further.
They said, editors note, police have only released a vague description of the suspect
shooter as of Saturday morning.
The Austin American Statesman is not included in the description as it is too vague.
They still have, by the way.
At this time to be useful and identifying the shooter and such publication could be
harmful in perpetrating stereotypes.
If more detailed information is released, we will update the reporting.
They still have it.
Last time I checked an hour ago.
So why is that so important?
Why is that so over the top?
Because what color somebody is, what they're wearing, what they're driving, what they're
dressed like is evidentiary to stop them and find them.
So this editor's note that Alex is reading from the Statesman, I found it.
And it's in the article about the shooter's arrest.
At the point of the article's publication, the vague description of the shooter is no
longer really that important for the public safety angle that Alex is talking about.
And the newspaper does not have identifying information released to them because the suspect
is a juvenile.
There's just really simple explanations for, you know, all this stuff that Alex is claiming
is so confusing and it comes from the very source material that Alex is going off of.
But it's more important to try and stoke white fear and victimhood and aggrievement.
Yeah, I was going to say, it's very, I don't know if I've ever heard a white dude describe
why what he's doing is not racist without being incredibly racist about it.
That is a phenomenon that Alex falls victim to quite a bit.
Yeah.
And it seems like if you were, you know, like the best a white person can probably do is
be like, hey, listen, I was raised racist in a racist ass country.
I got blind spots.
I'm doing my best.
Please tell me when I'm being racist because I'm sure I will be.
It's my bad.
I'll learn.
Not Alex.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's a slightly different approach to it.
Yeah.
So I don't, I don't know.
I feel like this, this whole display at the end of the show is a real gross and made me
think, Hey, why didn't you get to the news?
That's a good question.
Or was that the big story or what?
So at the end of the show, right?
As he's going out to throwing it to Owen.
Sure.
He's gets to one of the big headlines that he didn't get to.
Oh no.
This is huge news.
If true, which I don't think it is coming up next hour, didn't hit this yet.
The Department of Defense department admits major defector has been there for over a year,
provide evidence that Chinese military orchestrated the creation of the COVID-19 and release the
bio weapon.
And of course that is so huge that you're not wanting to know this.
You don't want people to know it.
How is that possible?
That is theoretically confirmation of everything he's ever said.
It's theoretically the biggest news ever.
Biggest news.
That is essentially saying that China is an act of war.
It's the biggest possible news.
The Chinese military released a bio weapon that has killed millions of people.
Yeah.
Okay.
You had two hours on air and haven't got to this story yet.
That's about everybody else, Dan.
I needed to talk about me.
That's such a bullshit.
I needed to talk about me for the first two hours.
So just the worst.
What an asshole.
That is fucking horrific.
Yep.
So that's how he ends his show on Sunday and I think it's fitting.
I think it all does mesh with who he is as a broadcaster.
Yeah.
You know?
It's about himself.
Totally.
It's intense.
It's trying to incite people towards violence.
100%.
It's transphobic.
It's racist.
It's stupid.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a real murderer's row.
And it's constantly self-critical of, I haven't got to the stuff that I'm supposed to do.
Haven't done any of this.
And pretends that it's about to.
It never does.
No.
It's amazing.
It is like a perpetual child who has not done the book report.
It is a show that is entirely around, what if you just gave that kid three hours to try
and distract himself away from revealing he didn't do the work.
Yeah, it's almost a really interesting bluffing improv exercise.
It is!
In a way, it kind of is.
If it wasn't so destructive and dangerous, it might be the greatest 27 year long herald.
Really?
It's just a non-stop barrage.
I mean, Alex does sing sometimes, it could be a herald.
Bananas.
Anyway, Jordan, we'll be back.
Indeed we will.
But until then, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yes.
We're also on Facebook.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledgefight.net.
Go to betjordan.
Yep.
We're also on Facebook.
Indeed we are.
And if you could, please find a local charity or bail fund within your area to help out
people doing God's work right now.
Yep.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DZX Clark.
I'm Daryl Rundis.
And now, here comes the sex robots.
Andy in Kansas.
You're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.