N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledge Fight
Damn and Jordan, I am sweating
knowledgefight.com, it's time to pray
I have great respect for knowledge fight
knowledge fight
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
saying we are the bad guys
knowledge fight
Damn and Jordan, knowledge fight
Riddle her, riddle her, riddle her
I need, I need money
Andy and Kansas, Andy and, Andy and
Stop it, Andy and, Andy and Kansas
Andy, Andy, it's time to pray
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding
Hello Alex, I'm a victim, calling in my huge fan
I love your work
knowledgefight
N-N-N-N-N-N-Knowledgefight.com
I love you
Hey everybody, welcome back to Knowledge Fight, I'm Dan
I'm Jordan
We're a couple dudes, like to sit around to worship at the altar of Selene and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Oh indeed we are, Dan
I was about to say Psalter of Selene
I heard it, I was gonna let it go
Not good
But you know, now that you've brought it up, I noticed
Yeah, how you doing?
Dan, I have a quick question for you
What is your bright spot for today?
My bright spot today, Jordan, very exciting announcement
Yes sir
So this is something I've been meaning to get to for a while, there have been technical difficulties
Which is code for my printer hasn't worked
Sure
I've been wanting to do this again, we did it like maybe a couple months back, six months back
Gave some buttons to folks, sent them out, and I wanted to do another run of these
We have some new designs themed around the cult of Selene
Excellent
And I would like to announce officially that we're gonna be doing another run of these buttons
for folks, and here's how it's gonna work
Because last time this completely screwed up all of my inboxes
And I am not interested in that
A little bit, yeah
So I've started a new email address that is specifically for this
You do not have to be someone who gives to the show, you do not have to be
anything, just anybody, if you would send your email, your address, I will
You do have to be capable of email
That is the one limitation on this
And you have to send me an address to send a button to
Well true
And then I will take care of everything else and you will have a button sent to you
The email address is kfbusiness at gmail.com
And that's spelled K-F-B-I-Z-N-E-S-S
KF business
Let's KF to business
At gmail.com
If you send an address to that, there's gonna be a little bit of time, you know, obviously
Sure
Gotta make these up so there could be a little bit of a delay
But we will get this in the works, get some envelopes with your addresses on them
And get these buttons sent out to you
I'm very excited
I really, I know that last time we did this, one of the things that I discovered was
I was really, really enjoying the process of making buttons
You loved the meditation of buttons
Yes, there was a thing too, the crafting of it and the sort of, the repetitive
Sure, sure
Zen and the art of button making
Yeah, yeah, and I feel like we're in a safer place now too
There's a lot of precautions that we took the last time around
True
With wearing gloves while making the buttons and everything
And now it feels a little bit, you know, we can chill out a little bit and just send out a nice gift
Just send out some buttons
Yeah, so I'm very excited about that
And if you all want to send in some addresses, we'll get those buttons your way
Yeah, now admittedly this time his gloves will be on and they will be coated with anthrax
So it's a little bit of a different problem
I met an Elvis impersonator and he had some ideas
What about you Jordan, what's your bright spot?
My bright spot is, it's low, it's in the early stages
It's not a super bright spot
But after a year of writing nothing but mean things to Taylor Swift and stories about wizards
I've started a new project
That's great
It's much larger
Hopefully it'll be about the size of the book I put out last year
So that's spectacular
Yeah, and if it's any longer people will definitely not finish it
So I'm fine with that
Here's the inspiration
Yes, I'm very excited
Clink
Yes, absolutely
Well, I wish you the best with that
Yes, me too
So Jordan, today we have an episode to go over and it's a little bit of a challenge
It was a tough challenge for me
And here's what happened
Okay
So Jordan, Alex was out of studio at the beginning of this week
He was in New York
Sure
I mean, I think you're
Is he allowed in New York?
Maybe, yeah
Doesn't Letitia have people on the border?
Well, see, I think that a lot of people probably, that's the first thing their mind would go to
Is that he's probably going to deal with some sort of a legal issue with
the attorney general of New York, Letitia James
Who he has threatened on air multiple times
And of course, he had the cease and desist for some of the products that he was selling
And I think that there is a possibility that that's the case
You know, like, you suspiciously went to Connecticut
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah
Recently, it's like, oh, why'd you go there?
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Maybe something to do with one of your court cases
It's possible, but also he was going there to do a podcast
He went on that Flagrant 2 podcast
Oh, yeah, when he was drunk last time
He said all the weird stuff
Well, yeah, he was so drunk last time that I don't even care to cover it
Yeah, yeah, yeah
And so, like, he went there
You could think that maybe he's going there for some legal issue
But then also maybe he's just doing this podcast
Yeah, sure
And so that was a possibility
Maybe we cover that episode
Sure
Simultaneously, Kill Tony, the podcast, had Alex as a guest
Ugh
Tony Hinchcliffe, noted Asian slur purveyor
Yeah, hasn't anybody taken that towards his career?
Yes, actually
Let's kill Tony's career
Can we do that?
Well, I mean
That's my new podcast
He did get dropped by his agent
Well, that's good, we're on our way
So we've at least maimed Tony's career
Yeah, I mean, I don't think it'll matter
Because the cult of Rogan Enterprises has him ensconced under their umbrella
But yeah, so Tony Hinchcliffe is a writer, guy, and comedian
Who he formerly wrote for the WWE and such
And he's one of Rogan's buddies
And he's one of the ones who decided to go to Austin
Because their bread is buttered in a very specific place
Yeah, yeah, there's no reason to be in LA anymore
People don't like me there
No!
Bye!
Texas is where I'm welcome
My career revolves around Joe Rogan
Joe Rogan's going to Texas
I am too
That's so sad
No, it's not
I think it's people understanding where their cottage industry is
Oh no, totally
I'm talking about the specifics of my career revolves around Joe Rogan
He can do worse
Yeah, that's true
So Kill Tony is a podcast that he does
That grew out of this open mic at the Comedy Store
I believe it was called Potluck Night or something
Something like that, yeah
And so like they just
I guess they just decided like let's find a way to monetize this
And so they monetized an open mic
Not terrible
Yeah
Of the business decisions for an open mic
That one's probably the best I've ever heard
Sure
I've listened to a number of episodes of it
Because there was a morbid curiosity on my part
And like back, you know, a ways back
Not just just recently
But you know the show is basically you've got Tony
You got his producer Brian Redban
And then you got a guest
A celebrity comedian guest
And they just act like hot shit while
Yeah, they just talk shit
A comic does a minute of material
Which is impossible to tell
No, no, no, that's all you need
That's all you need
That's all you need to know if you've got it
Yeah, and then the guests and the hosts will fuck around and act cool
And generally be overly encouraging of some things
And overly mean to anybody who doesn't fit into their like their box
Yeah
And it's just dumb
And I wanted to cover it kind of
Because I felt like, all right, this could be fun
This could be a fun thing to do an episode about
But so much of the episode is like about other people's stand-up sets
Sure
And open mic stand-up sets
And I don't want to cover that
And Alex was the guest
He wasn't due in a minute
Yes
He was the guest judge
Okay
And so like I guess I have this drop
How about some of that Joe Rogan weed?
So there's that
Okay, all right
I guess I have this drop
Once a year?
Yeah, I have this drop
You have a beautiful vagina
Have a nice night
I guess we got that out of it
Great
There's a part where Alex smells some girl's feet who's in the audience
Cool
They call her up on stage because one of the open micers has a foot fetish
And then they get somebody with a foot to smell
And I don't know
Great
Yeah, that's not an episode
Great, great
I'm loving every part of this right up my alley
I'm sure Alex had some insightful criticisms for the comedians
There's one guy who had some dumb jokes
And Alex is like, I'm drunk but that was a very cerebral set
Okay
I enjoyed that
There is some insightful criticisms there
Yeah
I think actually surprisingly at least at the beginning
He was a little bit more thoughtful than Tony
Yeah, well
Or Red Band
Yeah, well, familiarity breeds contempt if you will
It's very difficult for me because, you know, critiquing some of this stuff within the comedy space
Is always going to be walking in molasses
Sure
There's not like
People will just hide behind the like, it's comedy, I'm just joking
Right, right
Whatever stuff
And I don't know, I was listening to the Kill Tony
And I thought like, I have a lot of complaints about this
But who cares
Yeah, I kind of feel like maybe listening and criticizing a podcast
That's about listening and criticizing comedians
Open mic comedians
Is just a waste of everyone's time
Yeah, it felt like challenging, nay, impossible
To make worth listening to
Yeah, yeah, yeah
And so I was like, well, maybe we'll do a little bit about that episode of Flagrant 2
Sure
You know, why not?
This is a little bit longer, this is a conversational piece
Yeah, I want to know what their feet smell like
Alex was so drunk on the first time that I just didn't want to cover it
This time he's a little bit better, but I couldn't handle listening to it
It's so annoying
And look, I think that the hosts actually make a couple of pretty decent jokes
Oh, okay
Like, I can see a little bit of why, if that's what you like, that's fine
Okay
If you like broey, edgy comedy
Sure
Or whatever
Sure, sure, sure
Chat where people are talking about, hey, I had a threesome last week or whatever
Ooh, what a
If you enjoy that, then I can see, you know, this being up your alley
Sure
It was insufferable for my purposes
Hmm
Alex takes his shirt off at one point early
Oh boy
Early
And one of the hosts
What is he, did he see Burt Kreischer on Kill Tony?
Get this
What?
One of the hosts calls him Burt Kreischer
Okay, well there we go
And then the other host makes the joke, did you say Burt crisis actor?
Which is not bad
Boo
See, it's not bad wordplay, it's not bad wordplay
I understand the wordplay
But see, it's funny because Alex ruined a bunch of people's lives
See, these guys are just jokes, they're making jokes to Alex
Right, right, right, right
Not critiquing him about how he ruined a bunch of people's lives by calling them crisis actors
No, it's hilarious
Yeah, it's funny
No, whenever you leave a wake of misery and destruction, what you should do with that is like
make it a funny little bit that you can pun off of
Yeah, it's hilarious
Yeah, everybody will be like, holy shit, I can't believe he pulled it off
Yeah
So I mean like, look, it's obviously only funny because
you're talking about something monstrous that the person next to you did
Right, right, right, right
But that said, fine wordplay
Anyway, I really struggle
More like Iraq bored George W. Bush
All right, let's all have a fun time
See, that's a fun joke to make in a friendly conversation with George W. Bush
Yes, exactly, very funny
Yeah, oh man, that genocide
You are, whoo, let me see, your pictures are dumb, hahaha, all right
So we have a couple things that I'm going to talk about towards the end of the episode
from the Flagrant podcast because I think there were even, you know, like as much as it's just
like, ah, these guys are just bullshitting and having fun and whatever, I don't care
I don't care
Yeah
But there are a couple of salient points that I think could be brought up and, you know,
whatever, we'll talk about that at the end of the episode
Gotcha
Thankfully, something happened that's breaking news and Alex had to weigh in on it
And so that's what we'll be talking about today
A special report that Alex put out last night as we're recording this
Wednesday evening
All right
So this is a last minute
Is it an emergency report on something that was reported roughly a year ago
that we're finally talking about now?
No, no, no, this is actually breaking news
You know what we're going to talk about
Well, yeah, obviously
Anyway, we're going to get to this, but before we do, let's say hello to some new wonks
Oh, that's a good idea
So first, Chavez, why Chavez? Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you, Chavez, why?
Thank you, next, Alex in Blunderland, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you, Alex in Blunderland
Next, Chris, and then there's an alias here
Jordan's Laughter is Sweet Sweet Music, thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks, Chris
Next, Dimer, this is Paul, give Dan some money
Thank you so much, you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
I don't endorse that message
Okay, Dimer, this is Paul
Okay
And then, look, Technocrat, shout out going out to...
I don't know how to say this, maybe Dicobros?
D-I-E-C-O-B-R-O-S
Okay, Andrew Dice Bros
Ooh, yeah
You're now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
Crikey, mate, that's fantastic, have yourself a brew
How's your 401k doing, bro?
All right, we gotta go full tilt boogie on this, Watson, all right?
Let's just get down to business
We ain't making that money off that heroin
Why are you pimps so good?
My neck is freakishly large
I declare info war on you
Thank you so much
Yes, thank you very much
Now, Jordan
Yes, sir
We have to get contemplative
Okay
Giving someone life is giving someone death
You could say that...
Life is death
You could
So first, Fiona got a birthday this week
So happy birthday, Fiona
Happy birthday, Fiona
Laura and Lisa reached out and wanted to wish Ron a happy birthday
So happy birthday, Ronnie
Happy birthday, Ron
Yeah
Cooper got a birthday coming up
Jillian says happy birthday
Happy birthday, Coops
Also would like to wish a happy 21st anniversary to Heather and Phillip
Also known as Captain Awesome
Okay, together they're known as Captain Awesome?
Probably Mizra and Miz Awesome
Okay, all right, well that's good
Also, I checked into this
You know, the Hallmark recommends yearly anniversary gift
Sure, sure
They got the paper anniversary
That's first anniversary
Right, right, right
What do you think the 21st is?
Because I checked into this just to be sure
Is it like brass or something?
Is it one of those?
It's brass, but it's specifically like a tuba
It's like that kind of brass
Hallmark recommends a 21st tuba anniversary
Gotcha
34th anniversary is woodwind
Yes, of course, naturally, yes
No, it's a themed gift surrounding the idea of fire
So that's an interesting
All right, so let's go with
I mean, I have a tattoo of a fire bender's symbol
So we've got that
You can get yourself some fire bending tattoos
Sure
I think that's a great idea
Talk to Zuko, get that out
You know what I'm saying?
Sure
Yeah, fire-based gifts
Light your house on fire
Yep, and finally
Black Dragon Queen Christy
Oh!
Our old friend Christy
Happy birthday coming up
Happy birthday
This weekend
And also end of last month
End of May
Christy and her husband Monty celebrated their 30th anniversary
No shit!
What?
What in God's name?
Do you get like a pair of timpani for that?
What kind of, are we just doing orchestral anniversaries at this point?
30th anniversary is office or desk decor
That's a lie
That's actually the 41st anniversary
The 41st
So you're telling me that I'm somewhere at, I mean, conservatively in my 70s
Uh huh
And you're getting me some office equipment?
So even in Hallmark's world, you work till death
Absolutely
There is no retirement, no social security
No
Office equipment
Yes, office equipment on your 41st anniversary
30th is apparently pearls from what this is saying
I would rather have that one, end your marriage at 30
Why would you make it all the way to 41?
You don't need office equipment, 30 years is long enough
You're gonna love 39th anniversary
What's that one?
Laughter
Well Dan, every day I celebrate my 39th anniversary
Yeah
Weird, this list is weird
That is a weird list
53rd anniversary
That is, that is the list
53rd, what do you think it is?
You've made it a long time, you're 53 years into a marriage
I feel like
Keep in mind, 40th anniversary is ruby, right?
So, okay
So 53, what is it?
So the decades are precious items
Yes, 50th is gold
And then the intervening years is, is, I guess at random
Nick Maxx
It's a bunch of shit pulled out of a hat
Yeah
I suppose
So what's 53?
50th is gold
60th is diamond
40th is ruby, what's 53?
53, I gotta go with marine creature
Plastic
Plastic, plastic
Laughter
So you're telling me that I'm at 90 years old and I'm getting saran wrapped for my anniversary?
If you're lucky
All right
If someone's following the Hallmark recommendations
Thanks Hallmark
Anyway, happy anniversary, Christine
Happy birthday
Also, Alex would like to remind everyone that we were born dead
Yes
Life is death
Or something
So, Jordan, as you know, the big news that was breaking yesterday is that John McAfee is no more
Yes
Or
Is he
He was found deceased in a prison cell in Spain
Sure
He had just gotten word that he would be extradited to the United States
to face some criminal charges
Yeah, I think if I were being extradited from Spanish prison to United States prison,
I'd be like, nah, I'm out
It's, it's hard to say, but it's not if you're Alex
Hmm, John McAfee did not kill himself in public statements and on his own Twitter
As early as just last week, he said, I will never commit suicide if I die in prison
I have been murdered by the US government
I'm going to listen to a man I'm new and respected
Not the lying corporate media that before his body's even cold
You respected?
It's a suicide with no coroner or no inquest
This thing sneaks to high heaven just like Jeffrey Epstein
That's a good, that's a good cold open to his special report that he put out
That's not bad, that's pretty direct
So even if we take as absolute gospel fact that McAfee said he would never kill himself,
he was the definition of an unhinged,
drugged out lunatic who said complete bullshit, essentially for a living
I would never imagine that a man so respected as John McAfee
would perhaps send out a dumb idea very quickly before he thought it through
A couple of my favorite things that he said that were complete nonsense were,
you know, like when he said that he had nothing to do with his neighbor in Belize's murder
No
Or that time that he said that if Bitcoin wasn't trading at $500,000 within three years
from July 17th, 2017, he would quote, eat his own dick on national television
Did he ever do that?
He didn't
Oh, I guess it's too late now
Some of his more recent work includes that time that he tried to create a publicity stunt hoax
where he pretended to have been arrested for refusing to wear a mask,
wearing a lace thong on his face instead
Ah, he's brilliant
McAfee and his wife publicly claimed he'd been arrested in Norway,
but the pictures that they posted as evidence of this were from the Augsburg airport,
which is in Germany
The Augsburg police told the media, quote,
there has never been an arrest, explaining that McAfee tried to enter Germany,
but decided not to when he was told that he would have to quarantine
Then he just created a bunch of bullshit on social media
Right, right, right
And who could forget the ridiculous runs for the libertarian nomination for the presidential race
or the very overt and transparent history of involvement in pump and dump cryptocurrency scams
Sure
In fact, that was one of the cases that McAfee was facing, along with tax evasion,
which is what the US was looking to extradite him back from Spain in order to prosecute him for
Soon before he was found dead,
a court ruled that he could be extradited to the United States, and this actually really matters
McAfee was 75 years old, and he was facing essentially the rest of his life in prison
for his fraud and tax crimes, which he absolutely would be convicted for
Yeah
Since there's video that he released of himself where he confesses,
which might be tough to refute
Let's hear it
I have not paid taxes for eight years, I've made no secret of it
I have not filed returns
Every year I tell the IRS I'm not filing a return, I have no intention of doing so
Come and find me
Yeah, that's gonna be tough
You know what bums me out?
What bums me out so much is that we know for a fact that if you are rich,
you literally can get away with not paying taxes
You know what I'm saying?
Like, we just got a New York Times report
Sure
About how you don't have to pay taxes if you're rich
And the only way that you can fuck up if you're rich is if you're just an asshole like this
It's the only way!
There's one way!
It's... some people are too defiant, I guess
I'll never pay taxes
Well then use any one of a million loopholes we've created for rich people to not have to do that
It's about the principle of the thing
Then fine, you're gonna die in a Spanish prison
I don't know what to tell you!
This is on you!
It's basically like the ceiling, metaphorically which is taxes, is coming down
Yes
And there's an open door
And it's like, do you want to go through that door?
It's open
There's nothing on the other side
Yes
There's no punishments
It's not a trap
You'll just go off your business
This is a loophole for the whole roof thing
The whole thing
I will not
I will be crushed by this roof
Okay
All right, man
I can't say with certainty that McAfee died from suicide
But if that does end up being the determination that experts end up making, I'm not going to be surprised
I wanted to get a sense of how the media was covering this death
So I sampled some of the largest outlets that were covering the story
Mm-hmm
The headline in CNN was
quote, John McAfee found dead in Spanish prison after his extradition to the United States was approved
The article doesn't say that there's a known cause of death at all
quote, McAfee was found dead in his cell in a prison near Barcelona on Wednesday around 1 p.m.
Eastern and a medical examiner is on the scene
A spokeswoman for the Superior Court of Catalonia told CNN
She said the cause of death is under investigation
A statement from the Catalonia Regional Government Justice Department
which manages prisons there
said that prison medical personnel and guards attempted to perform life-saving procedures
after finding McAfee but were unsuccessful
The statement said
quote, everything indicates unquote that McAfee could have died by suicide
That article is eminently responsible and doesn't jump to any conclusions
Wildly so
The BBC headline was
quote, John McAfee anti-virus creator found dead in prison cell
The article also doesn't provide a cause of death but does mention that same press release
quote, the Catalan Justice Department said prison medics tried to resuscitate him but were not successful
It's said in a statement that
quote, everything indicates unquote McAfee took his own life
Right
The New York Times story has a headline
quote, John McAfee software pioneer turned fugitive dies in Spanish prison
They mentioned the primary source statement
quote, the Justice Department for the Catalan region in Spain said that pending an investigation
it was treating his death as a probable suicide
The NPR story doesn't even talk about the Catalonia Justice Department comment
instead just reporting
quote, authorities are investigating the cause of death
This article even goes out of its way to soften McAfee's image
and turn him into some kind of a prankster type outlaw
quote, McAfee took pride in outwitting authorities
He once boasted about eluding police by dressing as a German tourist in a speedo
and another time as an angry homeless man
It's like the NPR version of this is really like
I mean these things are true
McAfee did do
Sure, sure
He did enjoy creating this outlaw
Right, right
On the run image of himself
Yeah
Outsmarting the police
Right
And you know, it's not wrong for NPR to report that
but that seems to be the angle that they're taking more
Yeah, I would have included more of his bombastic psychotic criminal acts
but I suppose if you want to paint him as a modern day world traveling
catch me if you can type con artist
Yeah
Fine
Reuters had this headline
quote, larger than life software mogul John McAfee dies in Spain by suicide, lawyer says
This is because this story isn't about the actual death
It's about McAfee's lawyer making a statement that McAfee died by suicide
quote, McAfee's lawyer Javier Villalba said the anti-virus software pioneer died by hanging
as his nine months in prison brought him to despair
Even so, even though this article is saying this
the article does not say that this in fact was the cause of death
only that McAfee's lawyer had said that it was
None of these outlets are reporting anything definitive
and the information that they have to go on is directly from primary source statements
one from the Catalonia Justice Department and one from McAfee's own lawyer
This is responsible reporting of the facts
I can't find examples of these folks rushing and jumping the gun to call this a suicide
No, I can hear every editor of every major outlet screaming we're not doing an Epstein this time
All right, no fuck-ups, no Epstein conspiracy theories
But here's why this looking at the coverage is important
Alex is trying to rush and jump the gun on the conclusion that his death was not a suicide
and in order to do that he needs to make the circumstances around the coverage
seem as suspicious as possible Alex is reporting a fiction
which is that the media is immediately and without cause declaring McAfee's death a suicide
because they're trying to cover something up
because that kernel of suspicion is necessary for Alex to use this story for his own purposes
Alex is an opportunist by nature and he needs to use everything he can for his largest benefit
Just last week Alex was covering that reporter Christopher Sein's death as a definitive
professional execution and his big prediction was
the globalists are going to start killing people like himself and Tucker
This situation with McAfee isn't a perfect fit
but it's good enough for Alex to use to claim that he was right
so this absolutely cannot be a suicide in Infowars world
Yeah, it's almost like it really doesn't matter how responsible the reporting of mainstream outlets is
Alex is just going to make it up on his own regardless
Yeah, absolutely
There's a real danger to this kind of behavior and it's in how Alex's rhetoric has been shaped
over the course of the past year and even further back honestly
The COVID pandemic has been declared the globalists big move and something that they can't undo
This is the end game coming into reality which means that there's no going back
Alex has said that over and over in so many different constructions
Victory or death, no going back, they've crossed the Rubicon
over and over and over again in different ways saying there's no going home again
Also, I'm very very sorry Hamdi, it's on me, I apologize, I know I said I would die on that hill
but listen, my bad
The rhetoric surrounding how this is like the end game and you know this is the big move
That's dangerous enough on its own
and if Alex is now going to start reporting stuff like people like McAfee dying as the
globalists killing off brave patriot leaders
What's the logical leap he's expecting his audience to make?
He constantly talks about how everyone needs to keep lists of globalists in their town
and be ready to take them out when things jump off
How is killing off patriot leaders
not the most explicit evidence that things have jumped off that you could imagine?
Yeah
Whether he means to do this or not is kind of irrelevant
It's just part of the message that his audience is going to take from that
As far as I can tell all we can really do is hope that the people who get that message
aren't the type of listeners that he has who like to take action
Yeah because the only message you can get is
once they're done with all of these people they're coming for you
Right
So you might as well stop them now before they come for you
Yeah and talking about like Epstein as a murder, a Hillary murder or whatever
is a little bit different even because that's like
all right they're trying to cover up their tracks
Right
Or whatever
It's not a direct assault on the patriot folks
True
These people that Alex respects
Epstein wasn't a patriot that's for sure
He's not like McAfee a libertarian anti-tax weirdo
Right right right
Who actually would go on Infowars
He really would
Is this really gonna move the needle though?
I feel like McAfee is just gonna be a blip and then everybody's gonna be like yeah I'm fine
Alex needed it to justify the previous coverage of his
predictions of patriot leaders being killed
So it's very important for that piece
True he's got to sell it hard
But second I don't think that at this point Alex is aware that
McAfee's Instagram posted a big Q right after he died
Which is gonna complicate
That's gonna make it a little weird
That's gonna make it a little bit dicey
Yeah so Alex talks a little bit about how he got to know McAfee
I got a chance to get to know McAfee back in 2012 right after his escape
from Belize into Guatemala and found to be a larger than life type character
Then a few years later he came and visited us several times in Austin Texas
I had a chance to go to dinner with him
Had a chance to go out shooting with him
And he was even more larger than life in person
The guy was definitely an American success story
He made billions of dollars with his McAfee anti-virus software
So in terms of being an American success story
McAfee was born in England
And he once told the BBC quote I feel as much British as I do American
Well
He founded McAfee Associates but he also sold that in 1994
And since then it's not what I would call a glowing success story
You know more like a cautionary tale
Or just perhaps an evil motherfucker wandering around
Upsetting weirdo
Yeah that's a good way of putting it
I'll take that one
Um so Alex has a comparison
A historical comparison that he makes
That what a shock it has to do with booze
Larger than life
I would compare the guy to like Captain Morgan
He's seen on the side of the rum bottles
I think the pirate
And he certainly tried to go retire down in Belize and live like a pirate
Hmm
Captain Henry Morgan was a big old pile of shit
I don't know if this is the person you'd want to be compared to
In his later career he was employed by Jamaica
To keep privateers and pirates away from the area surrounding the island
They used to call him the Jamoca from Jamaica
Instead
You're gonna compliment the two flagrant two ones?
But what's Jamoca?
Jamoke
Never mind
Okay
Instead what he did is he decided to just demand money from pirates
To allow them to come on to land
Sure
So he just basically was like you got to pay me
Yeah he was running a protection racket
Basically yeah
He was an outrageous drunk and he declared martial law twice in a two-year span
Because of fears of a French invasion
Which it should be pointed out he was accused of collaborating with the French
Well
After all that until his death Morgan owned three slave plantations
And spent a whole bunch of his time trying to enslave more black Jamaicans
He sucked
Yeah yeah but uh you know now we venerate him for his booze I guess
Yeah
That's good
I would imagine that Alex knows him as a pirate on a bottle of rum
Yeah I very much doubt the true story of Captain Morgan is high on anybody's list
Although I would guess that if Alex knew some of these things he'd be like even more into him
That's pretty cool man
I would like to run my own island fortress and collaborate with the French to overthrow my own fucking home
Allegedly
Yes
It's unclear
Okay that's fair
So um Alex
I would hate to tarnish his name
Alex's big piece of evidence that he has really to go on
About McAfee and how this could not possibly this has got to be a murder
It's the one time he tweeted out that I would never commit suicide and if I die in a prison
It's because the United States government murdered me
Yeah yeah it's tweets
Okay
Now he's dead and all we have is his last communications this year and last year
And the year before saying he would never commit suicide
Here's another one from October of last year 2020
I am content here
I have friends the food is good all is well
This is in the Barcelona prison
Know that if I hang myself a la Epstein it will be no fault of mine
So that's a second time he's saying I will not commit suicide and if I die in prison it's a setup
That's the first instance that I heard in this report of Alex having
I don't know why he's saying this is the second time
I think it's probably an editing screw-up
Yeah
I'm not sure
So this tweet is probably the strongest evidence that Alex has that McAfee didn't kill himself
Since he said he wouldn't do that in October
I accept this as something that makes sense on its face but I also don't think it proves anything
John McAfee was one of the most unhinged unstable people in the public eye
And it isn't necessarily wise to take most of the things he says without a giant grain of salt
Okay
I can believe that in October he may have felt that he would never commit suicide
But that was also eight months ago
And a lot can change to a person's mental state over the course of eight months
Particularly if they're in a foreign prison and maybe without the drugs that they generally do
It could change your mindset
McAfee has had a long history of being arrested in foreign countries
Or being wanted in foreign countries and getting away and going on the run
When he was a person of interest in his neighbor's murder and beliefs
He fled the country and he got away with it
More notably in 2019 he was arrested and released when he docked his boat in the Dominican Republic
He was on the run from the United States for that old tax thing
And he'd taken to living on his yacht I guess in international waters
Like some goddamn Andy Daley character
Yeah that sounds fun
Yeah
To kill time on the boat McAfee posted some pictures of himself with a bunch of big old guns
This drew the attention to the Dominican Republic authorities when he tried to dock
So he was arrested and held for four days and then he was released
You know what I think about going on the run?
If I was running from the law I would try also very hard to not be noticed
Hmm See that would be part of my strategy of like
If I had the opportunity to tweet out something I would be like
Maybe people will notice this Yes
And I don't think I should do that
So you're saying that when you're on the run it's kind of like you're in the no flex zone
You know I might even change my name or at the very least get a new Twitter handle
I would try and get rid of that blue check mark
Yeah I think it doesn't serve your interests of being on the run
To like really publicize a bunch of
I'm living out on this boat with these giant guns
No one will ever catch me
This is impressing my Instagram followers
But might be working across purposes of my trying to be on the run
I think that might be why he got caught so many times
Maybe
Yeah
John McAfee has a history of getting in trouble and then the consequences just disappear
So in October just after he'd been arrested in Spain
If you're him there's no way you think you're going to be in jail for the next eight months
Let alone end up extradited to the United States after that
Totally
Him posting that tweet I can see that kind of as shit posting
I mean it might as well be him saying like
I'll probably find a way to escape in a week
Like that's what he's doing
Until some actual evidence can be presented to the contrary
I see no reason to think that the simplest explanation here is impossible
Like John McAfee's luck had run out
He was going to be returned to the United States and he was likely going to be in prison for years
He was a vagabond, a world traveler, a guy who flees countries and lives on boats
The prospect of long-term incarceration seems like exactly the thing that he would find intolerable
Yeah fuck that
There's a lot of questions that do remain to be answered
But making this a hit team murder I think is going to be a really uphill battle for Alex
Especially if the thing he's leading with is a tweet from eight months ago
Yeah
I don't know
I mean, because then you just get back to like
Really? Why? Why would they send a hit team?
Yeah
What's a hit team? You could be, I mean, you know
Also
Like for McAfee?
Also McAfee has very publicly on Twitter in interviews said that he has a dead man switch
Yeah
So like
Okay
Yeah
Okay fine
Yeah that's like okay anybody who would want to kill him presumably because he has some
kind of information that they want covered up
Yeah
Would be like oh wait
They don't want him to go on trial
Oh wait if he if he ends up getting killed then his wife is just going to release all of these
Sure
Docs or whatever
Yeah it's it's nonsense this is all just a spy novel
Yeah yeah
And it's sad because like ultimately the the story is a tragic one I think
Uh I mean you know to a certain extent you could just describe it as the
quick destruction of one man's mind
I don't know if it was that quick
Consequences
I think it's been long
When you give them a lot of money
I don't think it was quick
Well
This has been going on a while
No I mean his mind was destroyed fairly quickly
Perhaps
Yeah
So uh not only did he tweet once he tweeted another time too
Here's another one that was put out in November of 2019
So a year before the one in 2020
And I quote
Kidding
I like fucking whales
From US officials saying in effect we're coming for you McAfee
We're going to kill yourself
It's a nice turn of phrase
We're going to arc inside you
We're going to kill yourself
I got a tattoo today just in case I am suicide myself
I didn't
I was whacked
Check out my right arm
And there is again his tattoo with the money there and the whack saying why he was killed
Those tweets are real but also John McAfee was a delusional paranoid drug addict
Who promised to eat his own dick on tv as a way to promote cryptocurrency
Probably as part of a pump and dump activity
This isn't compelling evidence of anything
Like these tweets and him getting a tattoo that says dollar sign whacked
It's not evidence to me of anything other than McAfee was unwell
Yeah and maybe those weren't turns of phrase so much as typos and poor grammar
Swacked
Yeah could have something
Maybe I might not be so much the well-done authorly talents of McAfee
I would love if Alex did also try to go through McAfee's
Yeah just start reading
Just start going through his twitter follow
I'm trying to explain some of this shit
Yeah yeah go for it go for it
Let's let's all start talking about whale fucking
That's what needs to be in the public eye
So Alex needed to jump in front of this really fast
Right
He needed to get a narrative out and
Can't let the cement dry on this one
No
No no no
Within minutes of him being announced dead we're told it's a suicide
Just like we were told with Breitbart it was a heart attack before his body was even cold
And no coroner's examination
And the coroner that finally looked at him then was poisoned by arsenic and died
Political assassination is a very real thing in America a very real thing around the world
So we already talked about this the the outlets that Alex thinks are in on this
Conspiracy did not report that it was a suicide within minutes
There was dry matter-of-fact coverage of the Catalonian statement and then
Eventually Reuters reported the statement that was made by McAfee's lawyer
I strongly suspect that Alex's claim that within minutes it was called a suicide is
Based on random tweets he saw
That sounds
Which is meaningless
Most likely
We did a whole episode about the day after Andrew Breitbart died and
Nothing Alex is saying is real about that case either
The media didn't immediately call it a heart attack and the initial reporting that
It was suspected to be a heart attack
The place that came from and the direct line that everyone was quoting
Was a press release put out by Breitbart's own website
Yeah
There's no conspiracy there
As for the coroner thing that was just a conspiracy narrative that's based on nothing
This was about the death of Michael Cormier a person who worked at the coroner's office
The problem is that he had nothing to do with Breitbart's autopsy and the amount of arsenic
He had in his system was so large that one of the detectives on the case said
It would be impossible to poison someone without much arsenic without them noticing
And people were pretty confused by that case
Yeah
Alex can't prove that Cormier's death was a poisoning or like an intentional poisoning
Sure sure sure
And he can't prove that Breitbart didn't die from a heart attack
All he can do is pull at strings real or imagined in order to create a sensational storyline that
Fits his purposes
One of the most important aspects of this is the narrative that the media immediately calls
These death suicides or in Breitbart's case a heart attack
Because that implies that there's a cover-up
And if there's a cover-up that means that there's something to cover up
And that means that it's a murder
Yep
In Breitbart's case Alex was just making up that the media immediately called it a heart attack
And in this case he's doing the same thing with McAfee's death
It's a pattern of behavior that exists not because he's responding to real reporting
But because he's operating from a pre-existing script
Regardless of what any media outlet published about McAfee's death
As soon as Alex heard that he was dead he knew the angle was
That the media immediately called it a suicide
Totally
And that's suspicious
Yeah
The rest of this video is is kind of
Bleh
I mean here Alex is just defending himself
This is nonsense
Of course he's talking about himself
I think the evidence is overwhelming that John McAfee was targeted
He told us why and was killed in a Spanish prison
For the cryptocurrency they believe he had or for other secrets
But regardless his work will live on promoting libertarian ideas of basic freedom
What like
For the cryptocurrency they just want his money?
He doesn't have that much money
He might have a bunch of bitcoin or something
I have no idea
Sure
But like
I'm sure he has tons of money but the people we're talking about are like multi-billionaires
McAfee wasn't a multi-billionaire
Right right right
If the globalists were trying to kill him for his money that's silly
Yeah
Second I don't it's not like you can kill someone and then automatically you just get their bitcoin
No you see you don't understand how blockchain works
I don't think Alex understands that
It operates under highlander rules
If you cut off somebody's head the power immediately it's the quickening it's the bitening
It's basically like in Assassin's Creed when you have auto loot
Yes exactly yeah yeah when it picks it up for you
It's perfect
Um yeah so Alex is saying that the evidence is overwhelming and and I I listen to this
I see no evidence
None
I see a couple of tweets
I see the most reasonable course of action being the explanation for events
Yeah
It's the one that makes the most sense to me
I mean if I'm 75 I'm a globe traveling uh rich dude who's escaped over and over and over again
You've gotten
Now I'm
You've gotten outrageously lucky
Totally
You've lived probably one of the most insane lives imaginable
Absolutely
Full of adventure in foreign countries uh ducking and dodging
Totally
Uh boxing above your weight class forever
And what are you gonna what are you gonna get?
You're gonna get another 10 years of life in an American prison?
That's awful you don't want to do that so fucking offer yourself it makes sense
I mean
It does
As tragic as that is and as much as I don't want to minimize
you know people who are struggling with suicidal ideation
There's no way out or anything like that
It is imaginable to put yourself in McAfee's position and be like the indignity of the trial
Yep
The damage that the trial would do to the things that he has made the most important parts of his
life like cryptocurrency
Yep
You could see taking the outdoor
Yeah
I don't know
I think I'm not making any assumptions
I'll let the information guide me to whatever conclusion is there
But based on the statement from the Catalonian Justice Department
Based on the statement from his lawyer that they are saying this is an apparent suicide
Yeah
I don't see a reason to doubt that
The only reasons to doubt that are
Nutty tweets from somebody who tweeted nutty shit all the time
Yeah
I'm not going to take that and that's not going to stand up in any kind of court
Even the court of my mind
Oh this lying liar said something? I guess I must believe it
Yeah
I got nothing here
I think the further and maybe larger problem for me is I just don't care
I just don't care that McAfee
He's just not important
He's like a sideshow
It's like it's like a carnival barker and it's like
I just don't see the power that Alex is thinking that he can wield through this
Do you know what I mean?
Yeah that I get what you're saying and I'm not super interested in the case itself
As much as I am the behavior and what it illustrates
Totally
I think that the important thing to take away from this is really understanding that Alex put
out this report that night because when we talk about that concrete idea the idea that
when concrete is wet a leaf that falls on it could leave a permanent impression
You got it
And the information space is fairly similar and when a story when the details aren't out
when there isn't like solidified information surrounding stuff you can make an indentation
in that concrete
Yeah a lot of people are gonna think that Subway has never used tuna in their sandwiches
Exactly
It's already happened it's too late now
And with this Alex is trying to put into his audience's mind before there's any solid
information that the media immediately reported that it was a suicide and that's suspicious
because McAfee tweeted some crazy shit
That's and that you know that it's a consistent behavior
Yeah it's it's one of the most kind of worrying and disgusting things is that the conservative
media has so insulated their listeners and viewers and the like that they can make claims
about any other media because they know you're not going to go check you didn't listen you
don't read the the papers what what person who is reading Infowars articles is then going
to be like and now I'll switch over to the Reuters article that's not happening so you
can just make any fucking claim that you want about what the media said because they'll
believe anything you say about what the media said you own the mainstream media if you are
in the conservative sphere
It's a puppet that you can wield
Exactly
And even if you are like an Alex Jones listener and you go check the Reuters store you'll
see the headline larger than life software mogul John McAfee dies in Spain by suicide
lawyer says there you go and you'll ignore the part in the headline that says lawyer
says why would you be like oh they are reporting that he died exactly you know and it's yeah
it's it's it's a trap and it's a trap that's used intentionally yeah because the false
version of this story or the presumptive version of this story is useful for Alex
Yeah no it's one of their most powerful weapons controlling the narrative that they're telling
you is the narrative they're selling that's just that's that's complete control over
information yeah you know it's just it's just ironclad you can't escape from that so
it's a real bummer
So I think a lot of people probably were reflecting on some things when McAfee the news broke
certainly I was taking a nap and I woke up and I had a text from a friend telling me
about this news and my immediate response was well I bet Hillary did this
Did Hillary do it?
Um maybe
Okay all right all right so jury's still out on that
Yeah I think some people had some fun remembering that time he said that he was
going to eat his dick on television
That was good times
But for Alex he had a slightly different response
A lot of our interviews with him over the years were on YouTube, Twitter, and Facebook
Dozens of them got banned and knocked off we never re-uploaded them to ban.video
This reminded us to so we're going to create a John McAfee archive page and we'll post
all the interviews we've done with him and any other interviews that are out there that
have been censored and so we're going to put a few of the interviews on the tail end of
this right now when we're shooting with him my first interview with him in 2012 and then
we'll endeavor to post some of the other archives in a John McAfee section again at ban.video
We're gonna juice this thing
Oh man guys I just gotta let you know the iron's hot and we better be striking
Yeah
Jeez
No one has told me that his Instagram posted a queue
Quick! Quick! Exploit this! Quick!
Shit
We need a new page we need to get traffic to that page and we need to fill it with ads
Uh somebody call Steve Pachanik and tell him to pretend he was on the yacht
Yes exactly
Uh all right
I'm waiting to find out that Stevie P's is the one who orchestrated the assassination
of McAfee
He's been getting out of pocket
Now my people in Catalonia
Yeah exactly
All right man
So like you already sort of uh
suspected and uh I think anyone would uh Alex does have to make this about himself
Sure
And you know it makes sense he's in a big season right now about how he's under threat
Yes
And the globalists are gonna come for him and they're gonna like kill his family and set him up for it or
Of course, of course
Whatever we heard this like a week ago on his show
Makes sense
And so he can't not take this opportunity to restress that theme
Now just when in closing I want to say to listeners
We've been getting a lot of threats a lot of attacks by the globalists as well
They are making their move worldwide they are killing so many reporters so many journalists
So it'll be a thousand percent a trillion percent clear to infinity
I will never commit suicide I will never kill myself
And if I'm found dead in a jail cell or if I'm found dead in a hotel room with a needle in my arm
Or anything like that it is the deep state that did it and I want them held accountable
If anything happens to me look at Bill Gates, Hillary Clinton, the deep state of the new world order
They are the enemies of America the enemies of humanity and they're the ones that have long histories of serious criminal activity
And never being held accountable
So if anything happens to me the thunderbolt should strike me
And what the godfather says, blame those people
So you know, maybe it is Hillary?
Could be, could be
I would prefer if every time he was like
If they find me with a needle in my arm if he just got really specific into what kind of drugs and alcohol he's doing
If they find me in a hotel surrounded by three empty bottles of Jack Daniels
You know they killed me
That is their fault one hundred percent
Because I'm a Jameson man
Everyone knows it
So this is the only actual content and analysis that Alex put out
And it's as boilerplate as you can get
There's more information that's yet to come out
And Alex knows that once that information is available
His job of rewriting this narrative is going to be next to impossible
The only time to act is immediately
So you get this, a rushed formulaic meaningless insistence that McAfee didn't kill himself based on a couple of years old tweets
It just doesn't matter, and this episode I think is still salient
And I think it's important to do because it's important to recognize these tricks
This is a key trick that Alex uses
And the one thing that I find fucking exciting
And I haven't, you know, we're recording this during the day on Thursday
So we haven't had time to listen to the end of the week shows
Of his, I want to know how he incorporates that cue on Instagram
Because that's going to be tough
Alex has already said that QAnon is a globalist intelligence operation
Which seems like this is going to be something he has to either ignore
Or maybe it's the globalists taunting people on McAfee's Instagram
Could be, could be
It could be that they put it on there to claim responsibility for his murder
That way they put the cue on there so Alex knows that it's the globalists who are doing it
Could be
That could be an option for him
It's going to be an interesting needle to see him thread
And I'm excited to, I'm not really all that excited, but I think it'll be interesting
Maybe actually we're just finally figuring out the real spelling of John McAfee
It's M-Q-A-F-E-E
And he had to change it for the software
Maybe it's him admitting that he's Q
It could be, I don't think so
Probably not
So that's it for the McAfee coverage
Sort of exactly what you'd expect
A little underwhelming
Yeah
Whatever
Yeah, it would be nice if there was one
You know, when the cement is this soft
And you can really just pull off whatever you want
I want one big swing
You gotta give us at least one big swing
Of like a perpetrator, or a group of people, or something other than just like the globalists and Bill Gates
And they want it as crypto
Yeah, yeah, there needs to be a good story behind it that you've got
You know, you can't just be like, oh well the media's lying
You have to give me a better story
Especially when you're lying about what the media's saying
Yeah, when you're not even doing the bare bones of your job
You're making up media coverage in order to justify your made up shit
Right, right, right
It's just stupid
Give me something, give me like, oh, did you know that Brian Stelter was in Spain last month
And then we're like, aha, now I've got it
Give me something like that
Somebody was in Spain around that time
Is what you've got to give me
Yeah, that would be good
But no one was in Spain, however Alex was in New York
Okay
So we went down to do this Flagrant 2 podcast
And, you know, I don't know, Flagrant 2 is a giant podcast
But at the same time it's still like Joe Rogan Jr. Varsity
Sure, sure, sure
For Alex
He can't get on Rogan at least not regularly
Not yet, yeah
Or not enough
Right
And so, you know, he can get on Kill Tony
Sure, sure
That's not going to move the needle enough
No, no it won't
So, you know, you get this publicity tour
He goes all the way to New York presumably either to do this podcast or to do this podcast
And
And something else
Maybe have a deposition or something, who knows
But, yeah, I just, I don't know
It's really hard for me to cover these sorts of appearances that Alex does
Because it's like, alright, I get that this is an attempt at a joke
Right
And I don't think it's funny
And I think the subject matter sucks
Yeah
It's probably somewhere on the bigoted spectrum
And whatever
Sure
You know, like
Yeah
I oppose, I oppose this joke
I oppose the message that's underlying this joke
But, I don't know, like where is the line of free speech?
It's objectionable speech to me
But, you know, YouTube should be able to decide whether they want it on the platform or not
But in terms of
Yeah
In terms of our conversation it becomes, it becomes a total mess when you're trying to
Criticize failed or iffy attempts at humor
Yeah, I mean, it's, it's what, we don't cover shows that are just bros talkin' all too often
Yeah
You know, like, bros riffin' doesn't sound interesting or really that, that like, newsworthy I suppose
The exception is like when Alex is on Rogan
And that's just kind of like because it's a vent
Yeah
Level of
And, and because Alex really goes for it
He does
And, and, and so like, I was listening to this and I was like, well, okay, we do cover Alex when he's on Rogan
And so like, maybe this is something that we should, you know, like, he, he is a guest on this show
Yeah, I mean if he makes, if he, if he's got something to say then I want to hear it
If he doesn't have anything to say then
He doesn't have much to say
Well
Um, I want to play like the beginning, this is how it starts
Uh, Alex, uh, spoiler alert, comes out wearing tinfoil around his arms like bracers
That is not funny
What's up everybody and welcome to Flavor 2
I am incredibly excited, we have a major, major guest
Huge guest
Huge guest, uh, probably one of the biggest actresses on the planet
Icon
We figured, a real icon, we figured because it is, uh, Women's Empowerment Month, I believe it's Women's Empower Month
We bring on maybe the most powerful woman in the galaxy
Some might say I'm incredibly excited, everybody right now give it up
I wonder who it is
For Gal Gadot, everybody, Wonder Woman is here, Flavor 2
We got Wonder Woman in Wonder Woman
We have Wonder Woman
Yeah
So Alex comes out with a bunch of tinfoil on him and it just turns into a protracted transphobic joke
Uh, it's, it's a load of nonsense, but it's, I get this thing where it's, imagine right before they started recording
Alex is like, here's what I'm gonna do, I'm gonna put on a wig and some tinfoil, I'm gonna pretend to be Wonder Woman
Like, that's an idea he had, and then these guys were like, that'll be great
We gotta do that
That'll be great
And you know what, we're gonna sell it
Yes
Oh boy
And Alex taking his shirt off
It's disconcerting
You can take that, you can take that shirt off if you want, Alex
Yo, just go dog
You can go for it if you want
I see you sweating, just go, just go
There's the one
Take it off, take it off, take it off
You guys wanna see this woman's beautiful body?
Yeah
Yeah, show them fucking heavies
Heavies, heavies, heavies, heavies, heavies, heavies
Hey
Let's go, brother
So it's moments like this that just like really highlight to me how much of like a duplicitous game everyone is playing
Yeah
Like, Alex is there to try to launder his extremist beliefs to a gullible audience
And he's also trying to bring more customers into his revenue stream
Of course
Simultaneously, these dudes know that if you get Alex to do sensational things it leads to increased attention and traffic
If you get him to run around without his shirt on you might end up going viral on Twitter
You're like, that could be a meme, that could turn into something that is a long-lasting reaction gif meme or whatever
That's better advertising than you could ever pay for
Totally, totally
So there's this whole game that both of them are playing that is promotional in nature
And it's just like, okay, I guess you're trading the possibility of having these moments for willingly or unknowingly
platforming a monster
Pulling your audience to Alex
Yeah, yeah
It's like, okay, cool
I just can't believe that people would want to listen to the same social dynamic that one would see at a fucking elementary school
Alex might as well be eating worms
A drunk elementary school
Yeah, just like, eat the worms, eat the worms, eat the worms
It's the same fucking thing
Alex is there to be humiliated for them to exploit and then they laugh at him and he acts, I mean it's so, it's so degrading
No, no
I'm degraded
Well, you're gonna eat even more degraded
Oh no
Because Alex was about to talk about his dick
Oh god
Bro, you got a nice little bulge, yo
Dude, you got a nice pecker, bro
I have the largest micropenis in North America
Now, women get blown away by it
It looks like a grub worm with ear muscles
You've seen like, seriously, those little balloons you buy at the store get really big
That's me
So you're a grower
Man, women go, they go, this is a trick dick
And then like, this hurts
I got a trick dick
So it starts out small and then surprises them later on
It's like a turtle head, it goes in
Yeah, yeah
It actually goes in
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So then it comes out
Aha
This is not good riffing and it's unbecoming of someone in Alex's position to act like this
Yeah, yeah
It's just, imagine this juxtaposed with him fucking praying on air
I
I got a trick dick
I mean, it's so much like, I immediately get flashbacks to like, early on doing standup
Working with an established, clean comic headliner
And it's me and a young female comic
She and I are at about the same level of talent
And then we're at the bar afterwards
And he starts telling creepy ass fucking jokes right to her face
Sure
That is so fucked up and inappropriate
Yeah
And you're like, this is not okay
That is what I'm hearing Alex do right now
That creepy ass shit where he presents himself one place as being a pious, god fearing man
And then when there's a social situation where he can fucking take advantage of his goddamn position in the hierarchy
To fuck around with people and I hate it
Yeah
It really lights me up
I think that there's some of that
And then there's some of it too that is just wanting to have people think that you're interesting by kind of like oversharing
Yeah
And I think that early on in my time doing standup I kind of was susceptible to that
And I certainly would say more stuff on stage than I would be comfortable with now
Sure
You know like, there's sort of an extra version of like, let it all out there man
Yeah, I'm a truth teller
And I think that that was partially because a youth idiocy
And not taking myself seriously enough to know that this wasn't appropriate
Yeah
Alex is 47 years old
Wow
He's been doing this as a, he's been an investigative truth teller reporter for 27 years
Yes
He thinks he's fighting the literal devil
Yeah
He thinks that governments want to kill him
Yep
And he's still like, acts like I did
Hey, you gotta laugh
When I was an early doing comedy guy
Look Dan, you know what, when you're so stressed out you need an outlet
And that outlet is telling two weird bros while they mock you to your face that you've got a weird penis
That makes perfect sense
I guess
I mean it should, I guess if people want to look at him as an
Yeah
I don't know
The thing that I kept flashing to was these people like these hosts of Flagrant
And I would say even Rogan probably is this way
Or Tony Hinchcliffe
They have an image of Alex as this
Yeah
The drunk guy who talks about his dick or yells about aliens
Or like tells them some weird subsection they've never heard of
And he's like, I'm gonna blow your mind, I'm gonna blow your mind, let me tell you
I'm gonna tell you, I talked to the weather weapon guy
Yeah, yeah
That's the image that they have of him
And that's what they think his show is
They haven't listened to his actual show
Probably not, no
They don't know
And when Alex comes on these types of shows, he's not crying about fighting the devil
Right
He's not like yelling all his racist shit
He's not doing what he does on his show
If these people actually listened to Alex's show, they would either be bored out of their mind
Or they'd be like, wait a second, this is what Alex does?
I'm not sure I want to be associated with this
You know, I don't know
Alex's years-long Trojan horse quest to get people to give their life to Jesus
Do you think that people like these hosts would be like, oh, I want to be a part of this
Bringing people to God
I mean, I could see this
I could see them all in their mind
Because they are all these
I mean, the names of the people that we're dealing with are all traffickers in toxic masculinity by trade
So I could definitely see them being like, oh, you know, we just play it up on our show
Alex just plays it up on his show
And in real life, he's this guy
So it's okay for us to be cool with him
Despite not realizing all of the fucking destruction that his show does
Just because he's a character on the show means it's okay for them to be like
Eh, you know what, we'll have him on our show
Where he's the real guy
See, that's great
And I applaud that, except the reverse
Yeah, I was gonna say, please do not applaud that
No, I think it's worse
That's fucked up
Yeah, if someone were to make that argument, I think that
That's what I'm saying
I'm saying these people are worse than you give them credit for
Yes, because if the argument is that it's a character and this is the real Alex
That we're hanging out with, broing down with about our dicks
Like, okay, then that person that you're broing down with is a psychopath
Yes, yes
And they are too
I mean, you could absolutely see them saying something like
The crisis actor joke is funny because it's not Alex's fault
It's people taking Alex too seriously
Who went too far with all that Sandy Hook stuff
Alex is an entertainer, man
If people take it too seriously, it's not Alex's fault
Just like when people take our stuff too seriously
And it's like, no, we're making a joke
Sure, I made a quote unquote joke about raping a woman
But that was a joke, I don't know why people are taking it too fucking seriously
It's that type of shit
They even do, you know, touch on that a little bit
Everybody takes me out of context
I find that to be a pretty boring argument
Because I've listened to hundreds and hundreds of hours of Alex's show
I think I got a pretty good sense of what's an actual position and what's him fucking around
And I don't take things that he's fucking around about all that seriously
I think that argument is thin
No, I would say it's a self-serving and delusional argument
That helps you go to sleep at night
Because what you're actually doing is exposing people to a fucking monster
And you're helping make it easier for people to accept the bad arguments
And the awful things that Alex does believe
By presenting him in a way that's positive, that's sociable
That is like, hey, we're having fun
And allowing him to perpetuate things that just explicitly aren't true
It's like if Renfield had a fucking podcast
Like, he's putting Dracula on, man
He's gonna push Dracula on you
Well, I mean, if you want to use Alex's own language
But there's just things that you allow him to perpetuate that aren't true
So they're talking about Colbert and why Colbert isn't funny anymore
And here's what Alex says
They admit Charles Schumer, the Senator of New York calls him and says what should be in his bits
No
That's in the news
Same thing with
That's almost unbelievable
Some of the funnier late night guys, you should be really funny
You wonder, why aren't they funny now?
They admit in the news that they get calls from Democrat spokespersons
And Senator Schumer goes, I'd like you to talk to this guy
He's my cousin, he's a funny guy
And those guys know that corporately, their job and their contract is
Pursuant to a weird New York Senator
Can you imagine like a Senator calls up
Oh, Andrew, I'd kind of like to see this in your piece
You say, fuck you, man
Yeah
Can you imagine like, I'm out here like, okay, Senator Schumer says I'm supposed to say this now
Here's Schumer's joke
So this old man can sit there and watch and go, I control that young man
This is entirely about Jimmy Kimmel discussing on air how he'd spoken with Chuck Schumer about the Affordable Care Act
Which you might recall was a super important thing to Jimmy because his son lives with a congenital heart defect
So he was discussing on air, this piece that he did
About how the coverage of pre-existing conditions really matters in a very concrete way
Yes
Kimmel was taking issue with the Graham-Cassidy bill
Which sought to get rid of some of the provisions of the ACA
And in preparation he got some assistance from Chuck Schumer's office about the bill's details
Alex has taken that kernel from 2017 and embellished it now
To the point where he's telling these dudes that Schumer is basically the booker and head writer for all late night shows
This isn't joking around and it's not even in the territory of embellishment for effect
This is just a lie that Alex is specifically deploying to convince these people's audience
That all non-crazy entertainment is just secret globalist programming
And they're reacting to it with like, no way, that's almost unbelievable
And you're like, why wouldn't you stop for one second and go, that is unbelievable
No
I mean Alex even gave you an example for you to be like, I know people in comedy
Of course they too would say, fuck you Chuck Schumer, you're not funny
And the hosts of this show, the two dudes who are the main hosts of it
One of them used to be on MTV's Guy Code and the other one was on Wild and Out
So it's like, they're comedians, people who have worked, they have done stuff
You know people in the industry
All of whom would do, regardless of whatever political affiliation you have
Comedians are very very aggressive about you shutting the fuck up
And they probably have some exposure to some of the things that Alex is being completely duplicitous about
And it's just not worth it to have an actual conversation about it, I don't think
If you've been on the Guy Code or Wild and Out or that kind of stuff
There's no way you haven't interacted with people who literally work at SNL or Colbert or the like
Like, that's, they're there, they're everywhere, yeah, I mean, that's bananas
And that means you know Chuck Schumer
Yeah, well, that means they're taking orders from Chuck Schumer
Yeah, so I found largely listening to this to be, like I have already said, intolerable
I found it so boring, just ha ha ha
That's the kind of noise, just put that for two and a half hours
Look at us being bros
Yeah, so I turned it off after about an hour
But there was one really important thing that came up a couple times in the first hour
And this is Alex trying to formulate a way to justify some of his bigotries
And I found this really really interesting
Here we go
Because all the Renaissance is, it's not a utopia, it's saying all the old fucking weird shit, we throw it out
All the old weird shit's like, oh rainbow flags, oh look, black people
It's all exploiting gay people and black people
There's nothing to do with rainbow flags and gay people
They're just literally sitting there putting that out
We need a total Renaissance to overthrow the entire thing and empower everybody
Well you're saying, you're not saying let's get rid of rainbow flags and black people
That's what it sounded like
You're saying they're mascotting the rainbow flags and the black people
No, yeah, get rid of the front
Imagine if I walked in here and I said, I really like black people
Do what I say, I like black people
You're a fucking opportunist
I see what you're saying, I see what you're saying
But this is interesting
No, no, I'm saying don't get rid of rainbow flags and black people
No, get rid of the people that are using rainbow flags and black people
I'm just saying stop listening to them
Like when some defense contractor has a rainbow flag you're like, dude, that's not you
You're killing people but you're using this rainbow flag so we think you're
That's protection
I've listened to countless hours of Alex's show and I honestly don't think that that's an idea that I've ever heard him articulate like that
I really haven't either
I think it's intentional
This is a very attractive point and honestly I don't actually disagree that much with how he's framing it
No, I think he's, well, I mean you see Nancy Pelosi and the like in a fucking, yeah, yeah
I see, you know, businesses do pay lip service to communities in meaningless ways in order to garner goodwill
While their actions might not be as supportive as those words may imply
Rainbow flags and donations to Trump do not go together and yet somehow
I think that happens a lot and it's a part of the shallowness of the nature of corporations
We treat corporations like people and all of a sudden they have a brand and a persona to cultivate
And part of that is trite social media gestures
And I think a lot of people see through that
By framing Alex's opposition to things like black people and rainbow flags this way
Alex is trying to hook the audience by appealing to something that they could easily believe
This could possibly be the belief that Alex has that everyone says is racist
You know all those times Alex gets called a racist?
It's gotta be because people are misrepresenting his stance against corporate use of Black Lives Matter and rainbow flags
That's gotta be it, he's not actually a racist
That's what Alex wants the audience to think because the reality is that Alex is a gigantic racist
And if the audience knows that going in, they won't ever make it to the Infowars store
Trust me, the difference in how Alex responds to a murder when the victim is black or when the victim is white
Has nothing to do with corporate signaling
His behavior is explicitly racist, it's homophobic, it's transphobic
He is those things and he's being allowed to launder this in a way that's appealing to not only the hosts but the audience
And gives them a way to be like, oh yeah everyone says Alex is racist
He doesn't like this corporate thing where you put a rainbow flag up during Pride Month when you're a bigot
Or you're doing horrible things
It's a valid criticism that's trying to be used as a shield for bigotry
Right, but I mean that's the feedback loop
That's the feedback loop of conspiracy theorists and shitty politicians
Is that when the system is so corrupt and so transparent bullshit
It is easy for you to take a pot shot like this and get people towards more conspiratory laden bullshit
Because obviously Nancy Pelosi is fucking lying to you
That's not hard to jump to
It's a miniature version of how Alex's opposition to the Iraq war can trick you into thinking that he is an ally
Or ideologically on the same page
Right, and then corrupt and shallow assholes use that conspiracy theory to get elected
When they corrupt the government and make it less functional than it was before
Then your conspiracy theories get even stronger because the government is so obviously corrupt
And it creates that feedback loop of destruction
If it were possible, I mean I've said this so many times
But the greatest weapon that the Democrats have against the Republican party
Is just the governing effectively and they cannot do that
They simply cannot
True
And that's why we get into these situations
I think that even if the Democrats wanted to or had a unified will to govern well
I don't think it's possible
No, that's probably true
It's probably too late now
It's probably way too late now
Everyone can just do their best
Man, they really had a shot
They really had a shot 2008 to 2010
If they had just got their shit together
Man, we would have avoided so much
We would have had a right wing terrorism problem
Yeah, that's true
We would have had an extreme much faster
Yeah, it wasn't going to stop
Yeah, so I just, I grow weary of these laundering attempts of Alex
And I just, I don't think people don't have the right to do it
Sure
I don't think people are, you know, should be banned
I don't know, I mean it's the platform's choice
They can do whatever the fuck they want
Sure
I don't think that, you know, I don't think they should be arrested or anything for this
But I wish people would consider a little bit more what they're doing
I wish that, like, if these guys want to have Alex Jones on their show
I would like them to ask about the devil
I would like them to ask about, like, valid criticisms about him
As opposed to allowing him to present his very, very clear racism as opposition to corporate signaling
Right
I would like it if they allow, you know, this is a rare opportunity
Where you have Alex there, you could ask him digging questions
And instead just allow him to poach your audience
I mean, there's really only, at this point the bar is so low
So there's only two things that happen if you have Alex Jones on
It's obviously you're right
You have either the option to fucking eviscerate him
And then you will not be on his level, you will be over the bar
Or you do this, in which case you are under the bar right next to Alex
I have no sympathy for people
You've turned flagrant 2 into Infowars in my mind
More or less
The end
Like, I have no interest in you as people
You should fucking stop
And if you don't get that and if you don't make a change towards that
Then fuck off forever
You're just Infowars
Yeah, I think we have probably a very unique perspective
And I don't mean unique in, like, necessarily an overly positive way
But a perspective that other people don't have because we focus so much on Alex Jones
Sure
And that is that, like, I think that we have enough of an awareness of what this dude does
And what he's up to, his history, the way he lies, the positions that he actually has
That people who would choose to associate with him
It's your right to
Sure
But we know that you are him
Yeah, yeah
I don't give a fuck about Joe Rogan or Tim Dillon or these fucks or any of these people
You are next to Alex Jones forever
You're at the rally, if you're at a rally surrounded by Nazis
I get maybe you feel like you're not
But if you stay at that rally, guess who's a Nazi now
You have Alex on a second time
Exactly
I mean, I guess it probably boosts numbers
It probably helps with traffic
And these guys have a bunch of ads on their show
Hey
Hope their sponsors don't dislike Alex being on
It's okay if you destroy the world if your listeners go up
It's fine
It's the trade-off
I just don't understand being this irresponsible with presentation
Yeah
That's really what it comes down to
It really comes down to like a part of you just breaks down and you just go like
Do you guys just not care?
Like is that really it? You just don't give a shit?
I mean it feels like that's got to be the most simple explanation
Yeah, you don't care about your show
You don't care about the people who listen
And you don't care about what happens because of it
That's what you're telling me when you have Alex Jones on
Right, I mean like because here we have a completely dissonant presentation
A week ago on his show, Alex is talking about how we're all dead
Yes he was
He's talking about how the globalists are going to kill everybody
Yeah
And you know like I gotta stand and fight against these
I promise you I will take everything in my ability and fake crying and shit
And within the week he's in New York wearing a wig
Hey my penis is like a turtle
It's great, great
What are you doing?
What are any of us doing?
Yeah
Brutal
And then Alex comes back and tries to present McAfee's death as a murder
Which can only serve to incite his audience
Yeah just unreal
This is just nonsensical
It's just so fucked up
It's so fucked up how easy it is to jangle the keys of like
Hey I'm a fucking performer in front of these idiots
And then they'll just be like hey let's talk about dicks for two hours
Fuck off
And again maybe I don't know I watched most of the first one
And it was not in depth or interesting
Yeah
I watched the first hour of this one before I turned it off
And the only thing I found interesting really was this presentation of Alex's racism
As being opposed to corporate artifice
Yeah
And I don't know I guess I could have listened to the rest of it
Meh
Yeah I mean again if it weren't so reasonable to assume that they are corrupt lying pieces of shit
I think it would be harder to launder your racism behind
See look at those corrupt lying pieces of shit
I would like it if this was actually a long game which it's not
But they were trying to lull Alex into a false sense of security
Yeah you missed the last half hour where they just fucking nailed him
Nailed him to a wall
I doubt it
Anyway
I'm somewhat excited to see how Alex tries to incorporate that cue from John McAfee's Instagram
So we'll check in on that on Monday I believe
Yeah
But yeah until then Jordan we have a website
We do have a website it's knowledgefight.com
Yep we're also on Twitter
We are on Twitter it's at knowledgefight.com go to bed Jordan
Yep we're also on Facebook
We are on Facebook if you're not on the show
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund in your area to help out people do God's work
Yep we'll be back but until then I'm Neo I'm Leo I'm DZXClark I'm Daryl Rundis
And now here comes the sex robots
Andy in Kansas you're on the air thanks for holding
Hello Alex I'm a first time caller I'm a huge fan I love your work
I love you