I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys, saying, we are the bad guys, knowledge
fight.
Dan and Jordan, knowledge fight.
Riddle her, riddle her, riddle her.
I need, I need money.
Andy and Kansas.
Stop it.
It's time to pray.
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding us.
Hello, Alex.
I'm a first-time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your room.
Knowledge fight.
Knowledgefight.com I love you.
Hey, everybody.
Welcome back to Knowledge Fight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple dudes.
We like to sit around, drink novelty beverages, and talk a little bit about Alex Jones and
also worship at the altar of Selene.
Damn it.
Autopilot, baby.
Hey, hey, it's okay.
It's okay.
We got a sneaky steak episode.
You don't have to nail it perfectly.
I didn't even realize that until after it had come out of my mouth that I had, yeah.
No, I didn't hear it at all.
Wow.
I heard you say worship at the altar of Selene and then just let it, yeah.
I think I've been making so many buttons with Selene on them that it's just like-
It's in your brain all the time.
That's where that lives.
It's an unspoken situation.
Yes.
Yes, Dan.
But I do have a question for you.
Sure.
What's your bright spot today?
My bright spot today, Jordan, is a lot of nice messages that people have sent with the
requests for buttons.
As I make these buttons, unfortunately, there's so many that I cannot possibly respond to
most of these.
Yeah.
So please just know that I have read these messages and I very much appreciate them,
and their buttons will be sent as they're received.
Also-
Here's your response to the message, some fucking buttons.
That's right.
I'm taking a weirdly aggressive tone.
Yes.
That is how I'm feeling.
Also, something that has come up a number of times is people wanting to pay for postage,
particularly international wonks, thinking like, I'll pay something for postage.
That's a really nice thing, but I want this to be a gift for folks.
I appreciate that, but I don't want to accept that, but I also don't want to be disrespectful
to that generosity.
Of course not.
So if anybody feels the desire to, here's what I would say, this is my blanket response.
Feel free to give a little donation to a charity that you support, or you think that Selene
would support, and do it in the name of my cat.
Yes.
We will all worship at the altar of Selene eventually, because that is the name that
will be donating to every cause from now on.
Right, donate to a charity in my cat's name, and that'll be good for the postage.
That'll be good for everybody.
Yeah.
So my bright spot was thinking about that.
Imagine if we were as wealthy as Bill Gates, and you were just like, ah, our foundation
is named the Cult of Selene.
Let's move on.
Yeah, that wouldn't start any conspiracies at all.
No problem at all there.
We're donating $3 billion in the name of the Cult of Selene.
Uh-oh.
Yeah.
What's your bright spot, Jordan?
Dan, my bright spot is Wimbledon!
Goddammit, what a tennis.
Another tennis one.
No, this year, because of the, I don't know if you noticed, but the past year has been
rough.
Yeah.
So this year, the French Open and Wimbledon were only a month apart, and I will tell you
this, inspiring shit, Dan.
Whoa.
Andy Murray.
The Andy Murray?
The Andy Murray.
Former member of the Big Four, back when there was a Big Four and Andy was not kicked out
of it.
Former world number one, destroyed by injuries.
He's old as shit now.
Back in Wimbledon, for the first time in years, won his first match.
So did Federer, coming back after his injuries at Wimbledon, my friend.
Whoa.
This is a big deal.
So anyway, that's my bright spot.
Oh.
I've got a lot of energy.
Andy Murray is an amazing person.
I understand that, but that was like Charlie Brown's teacher to me.
That was just, wah wah, wah wah wah wah wah.
I could not understand a word you were saying.
This is why I keep my love to myself.
Yeah.
I want to care, and I want to join you in the things that make you excited, but I could
not, like my eyes glazed over.
I'd listen to you talk about Christian Ska on a podcast on my own time, too.
Well, that's because I have interesting thoughts about it, unlike you.
Unlike me and tennis?
No, I understand.
I understand completely.
I have some more thoughts about Survivor, if you're interested.
So Jordan, instead of some wonk shout-outs today, one of the things I wanted to do since
we're doing a Sneaky Snake Wednesday episode here, I wanted to get into the mailbag, because
it's been a little while.
It has been a while.
We have a little bit of catching up to do.
So Steve and London, I want to give you a thanks for the Department of Truth graphic
novel.
Yes, thank you very much.
Appreciate that.
Also Jase sent some cool shirts, those Q shirts, those Q Meme shirts kind of thing, from Infidel
Meme Wear, and I went over to their website and checked out some of the designs.
They're pretty cool.
I think there's one I may end up getting a hoodie.
This is not sponsored.
This isn't spawn-con, but thank you for the shirt and cool stuff.
Thank you very much.
Also, Keith and Laurel sent a care package a while back, and I have been horrible about
giving a thank you, and I really appreciate it.
Thank you, folks.
Giving that horrible into lore-able, and thank you very much, Keith and Laurel.
You're a basket of lore-ables.
So thank you so much.
Also this is something that we forgot to do, and I felt a little bit guilty about it, and
that was when we were giving a thank you to Bex.
Bex sent that ukulele, the pink ukulele that we were very confused about, and it turns
out it was for you, because of Steven Universe.
Steven Universe, pink lion!
And then I got a green ukulele from Bex because of plants, but what I forgot to do was Bex
requested that I give a shout-out to Quicksilver on the Discord, and I forgot to do that, and
I would like to write that wrong by saying, what's up, Quicksilver?
Hey, Quicksilver on the Discord.
I have no idea what any of this means.
This is also Charlie Brown's teachers.
So Jordan, let's get heavy.
Giving someone life is giving someone death.
You could say that life is death.
You could.
Happy birthday, J.G.
Gunner!
Hope you had a good one.
Also, Dexter reached out and wanted us to wish a happy birthday to Zoe.
Oh, okay.
Zoe, happy birthday.
Wow, you can't be named Dexter and wish a happy birthday after opening with, giving
someone life is giving someone death.
I have never watched that show.
I don't think you need to.
I think you get the reference.
I do.
He kills serial killers.
He kills people.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Cool.
I heard the ending was bad.
Probably.
I never watched the show either.
Also, Renee checked in and wanted to wish Rosemary a happy birthday, and this is fun
because Rosemary recently reached out and wanted to wish Renee a happy birthday.
Yeah, of course.
Of course.
So turn about is fair play.
Also, Renee says, she's the best friend I could have, and thanks for putting up with
me.
Happy birthday, Rosemary.
Unfortunately, life is death.
Life is death.
According to Alex Jones.
Uh, unfortunately.
Yeah.
So, Jordan, today we're in the past.
Ooh.
I like the past.
We're digging into the past, and we're going to be talking about May 22nd through 27th,
2003.
Yeah.
No blackjack.
No.
Dealer got blackjacked.
Yes.
Um, and, oof, not great.
Not a great stretch of time.
If I'm going to be perfectly honest with you, there's some funny things that happen, but
in terms of, like, if you're looking for anything in-depth, I am afraid you're not going to
find it here.
Not going to happen?
No.
May 22nd, not the best day of the year.
22nd and 23rd, a lot of it is talking about Bilderberg.
A lot of it is talking about the same sort of Bilderberg conspiracies that we've discussed
over and over again, and it's very boilerplate, fairly boring, and that's Thursday and Friday.
Alex doesn't have a Sunday show at this point.
Right.
Monday is a repeat of a show from the past week.
Wow.
Because I think it's Memorial Day.
Oh, okay.
That makes sense.
And then, so Tuesday, he comes back on the 27th, and there's a little bit of interesting
callers maybe, but, like, there is nothing going on.
Oh, man.
It is a wasteland.
I like how we've gotten so far into this show that a Bilderberg conspiracy, we're like,
Jesus, that's quaint.
Back in the day.
It kind of is.
Oh, Bilderberg, yeah.
They were scary back then.
Oh, man.
Bill Gates is killing everyone now!
Bill Gates-ter-berg.
There's one thing about the people that he has to talk about Bilderberg that I think
is worth pointing out, but in terms of the actual conspiracies, they're all just exactly
the same stuff, as always.
Yeah.
So...
I feel like a pertinent question every opening of the show is just going to be like, hey,
are we going to be getting into Blood Libel today, Dan?
Yep.
That's what I thought.
Do you say Bilderberg in 2003?
I'm guessing anti-Semitism might come quicker than you think.
So we start here on the 22nd, and not much is going on until Alex takes some calls.
He takes some calls fairly early in the episode, and Alex, I think he's trying, he's Mr. Brightside.
He's talking to this caller.
Okay.
Yeah, I just wanted to tell you, like, what I do, so, like, if other people are listening,
they'll do the same.
Like, I make, like, books with news stories, and I pass them all out, and I pass out your
movies, and 9-1-1 is the best one.
That's amazing.
Well, we're getting 90% wake up with Road to Tyranny of People.
Yeah, I get a lot of people who, yeah, they wake up and stuff, but, like, some of my friends,
like, if they even start talking to me about it, like, they're girlfriends or wives, you
know, like, give them a look, you know, they're not allowed to talk to me.
Most of my friends don't even talk to me anymore.
Man.
Don't blame the girlfriends.
Yeah, everyone's waking up, but now they won't talk to me anymore because their girlfriends
won't let them.
That's very sad.
That, that, uh, that is unfortunate.
That is, that is bad.
I need, I need corroborating evidence on we're getting 90% wake up.
Well, actually-
I need a survey response.
I need, uh, something.
I need something.
A Rasmussen poll.
You can't, look, I remember back when I first started out my job, one of the ways that we
marketed was with direct mail campaigns and you get like a 0.5% response.
That was the industry average.
If you're telling me, if you're telling me you're getting 90% wake up out of this, I
got to know what you're doing.
Yeah.
It's like, if you're getting 90% response, uh, to something, it's gotta be like heroin.
Yeah, totally.
Totally.
Or, or, or sophisticated brainwashing.
Um, so I actually do have a little bit of insight into this because Alex was talking
to another caller and he gives out DVDs to people and he's like, I'm getting a hundred
percent response from people, a hundred percent wake up and they talk about it.
And the way that this guy's defining that is that everybody who takes the DVD seems
happy about it.
But still there's a lot of people who are not taking the DVDs.
Which also means, um, they didn't necessarily watch it.
Yeah.
I don't know if there's follow up with these people about the content of it.
I don't know.
Uh, but this caller in particular, this first one is just really bumming me out because
you know, you can really see what this looks like in real life.
You know what this looks like in real life.
Yep.
They're telling you weird shit and then their girlfriend's like, look, we can't have him
at parties anymore.
He really freaks out my normal friends.
Totally.
Yep.
He said something incredibly rude because somebody challenged him on this and he freaked
out because you're not awake.
We can't live that way.
That's not how we live.
If that guy wants to be over there by himself listening to Alex, fine.
Yeah.
Um, so this behavior also apparently extends to digital stuff with this caller.
Sure.
Now every seed sprouts the first year and they're dormant.
I email stories like when people send me them stupid emails with like, you know, it's forwarded
a thousand times.
I still all them emails.
I email like Post Gazette and Trib stories and uh, and there's links with your movie
on there.
I emailed that to people.
I probably emailed like thousands and I probably got back like, like 20 responses.
I got like five thank yous and most people, you know, tell me I'm crazy or where'd you
get my email from?
You know, that's about a half a percent.
All right sir, I appreciate the call.
Yeah.
He's one of those weirdos that thinks the world is round.
He's definitely a weirdo.
He's getting chain emails, saving people's email addresses, spamming them, and then when
they respond, how did you get my email?
He keeps sending them Info Wars stuff.
That's, that's, that's harassment.
I would say, uh, that's an interesting, look, I will give them this.
That is an innovation towards chain emails that I had not even considered that you could
essentially turn those into your own mailing list and just bother people for the rest of
their lives.
Yeah.
I mean, you could do that.
You'd also have to recognize if you do that, you're a piece of shit.
Yes, there is that.
They're not all innovations are good.
No, I will agree with that.
So Alex gets another call and this guy has got a bad question and Alex has a worse answer.
Alex, can I ask you a real quick question before the break there?
Sure.
Someone told me that, uh, there, uh, the 9-11 attack, that, uh, there are 7,000 Jews that
are employed in the World Trade Center.
They were not employed at work that day.
You ever hear anything about that?
That is true.
MSNBC checked into it and said the urban legend was true.
Also the Jewish newspapers have reported they were told not to go to work.
That is a confirmed fact.
That's so fucked up.
I don't think it needs to be said that Alex is completely wrong and lending credibility
to an explicitly anti-Semitic conspiracy theory about 9-11 here.
This is lazy, sloppy behavior that only serves to validate the complete bullshit that this
caller has heard from his bigot friends.
And Alex is just using his platform as a voice of authority or certainty on the subject in
a way that is abhorrent.
You can very easily find the names of many Jewish victims of the 9-11 attack.
Some were on planes, some were firefighters who died trying to save their fellow person's
lives and many worked at the World Trade Center or at the Pentagon.
I could name specific names because I can.
I can find them.
And I've read biographic sketches of these people, little mini, mini obituaries, but
I'm not going to get into specifics out of respect for those people's memories.
And it wouldn't change anybody's mind anyways.
This narrative was a baseless claim that was made to demonize the Jewish population of
the United States and to imply some kind of complicity in the attack.
Alex should be deeply ashamed of this response.
I can't believe we got to the very first time in 2003 that the Jews were blamed for something
that they had nothing to do with.
I don't think this is the first time even in Alex's show in 2003 that we've gotten there,
but it was, I thought that that was bad on Alex's part.
I just think that they're, like this caller, they're going out to break.
He's saying, hey, is it true that all the Jewish people were told to stay home?
Yes, that is true.
It costs you nothing to just be like, no.
No.
Actually, that is nonsense.
Yeah, there's no other, I mean, there's just no interpretation of that that doesn't wind
up with the Jews were involved in the planning and the attack.
And it's specifically the, capital V, capital J, the Jews, not like these people, not a
group of them, the entirety of Judaism.
Yeah, so we're fucked.
Yep.
So Alex gets to a first guest here on the 22nd and it's a Bilderberg expert.
I remember five, six, seven, eight years ago on the radio, I'd talk about the Bilderberg
group and get calls from listeners.
I heard that's a code word for terrorism.
It doesn't exist.
You're insane.
I heard on the news, insane people believe this exists.
It didn't exist.
Well, it does exist and now it's public thanks to the work of folks out there like Tony Gosling
of Bilderberg.org is about to join us.
So I'd never heard of this dude.
Tony Gosling?
Yeah.
I wanted to learn a little bit more about him because he's not the Bilderberg expert
that I'm used to Alex having on.
Wasn't he in the notebook?
It's his brother.
Oh, okay.
When later time Alex Jones is trying to look into a Bilderberg story, he pretty much always
talks to big Jim Tucker.
And then in second place, if Jim's not available or had died by then, Alex would talk to Daniel
Estelen.
Tony Gosling's not a super relevant name in the periods that I've listened to of Alex's
show.
Tony runs a website called Bilderberg.org and I will say that this site pretty quickly
deteriorates from being about the Bilderberg group at all.
If you scroll down his homepage, you'll soon find a picture of Jesus as Che Guevara, which
is on a shirt that he sells.
Not good.
And then a reprinting of the Ten Commandments and the Lord's Prayer.
Okay.
It's weirdly religiously centered for what appears to be a site about the Bilderberg
group, which if I'm not mistaken and based on this interview that I'm hearing on Alex's
show is supposed to be a political conspiracy.
Things really fall apart when you get to the section titled, quote, My Spiritual Beliefs.
No.
This passage.
That should be on everybody's wall.
Things really fall apart when I say, here are my personal beliefs.
This passage stood out as not sounding great.
Quote, Many problems have been caused by some of the Jewish people's refusal to acknowledge
Jesus as the Messiah.
That does sound like the root cause of many problems.
Many Jews, for example, live in Old Testament Torah times, believing they're still God's
chosen people.
It seems clear to me that God cut off the Jewish hierarchy from his favor after they
pleaded successfully for the unjust death of his only son.
Why?
Where?
When?
Why?
In the Bible?
Do you mean the Bible where they wrote letters, the rest of the New Testament is writing letters
to Jews about Jesus being great?
There's a lot of conversation about who is or is not real Jews also on that site.
There we are.
It's a little convoluted and not good.
Okay.
The website's also just weird.
If you scroll down a little bit further, you find a list of Tony's 30 top movies.
The Life of Brian.
What did you just say to me?
The Life of Brian weirdly came in at number 24.
How can the Life of Brian be on there?
He likes to have fun.
You know this satire of every...
My personal beliefs, my 24th favorite movie eviscerates how stupid they are.
Great.
So after that, there's a section about how great Bill Hicks was as a comedian.
I'm not kidding.
I don't...
There's a big section about Bill Hicks.
No!
What is wrong with the humanity?
It's a really poorly laid out and confusing website.
And I don't know if it would even be helpful, even if you did assume that he had evidence
of something.
Listen, religion is the center of all of our problems in this life.
This guy is my favorite comedian.
Anyways, here are my personal beliefs.
Number four or five on his list was They Live.
Oh boy.
Well that one actually tracks.
I didn't recognize a lot of the names of the movies and I'm guessing some of them were
not good.
It'd be funny if they were all...
It was like They Live, The Life of Brian, and then a bunch of weird 70s art.
Like Harold and Maude is up there.
They shoot horses, don't they?
Everything Lee Remick has ever been in.
Right.
Like all of that stuff.
Or like Lenny Riefenstahl.
Sure, sure.
This was...
I don't know.
I didn't read over everything, but it seems like this guy's a little bit unwell and he's
a bit defensive about his positions vis-à-vis Judaism.
He's defensive about his movies.
So welcome to Bilderberg.org Top 30 Movies.
Today... a lot of the stuff that he has to say about Bilderberg is all kind of the same
stuff you hear from just about any of these folks.
You know, just stray talk, powerful people are there, let's imagine what they're talking
about.
Sure.
Although this guy did have a little bit of a fun twist on it, and that he seemed to be
kind of like a bird watcher for Bilderberg members, because he seemed to get really excited
when he was talking about how one day, one day...
He saw one in the wild.
No.
One day during the Bilderberg conference, all the people, all the richies who were attending
the conference decided that they were going to go to the Palace of Versailles, and they
were going to just go tour around, and so he was like gawking at rich, powerful people.
He was really excited that David Rockefeller actually answered a couple questions from
people, and it didn't seem standoffish or mad.
It was like, I think you just enjoy this.
There's a really...
I don't see a conspiracy here, I think you like following around a powerful group of
people or something.
No, I feel like we're in a situation where the continuum is there's something, there's
a very thin line between avid hater and fanboy.
There's a very thin line between oh, I hate the Bilderberg group, and I'm going to follow
them everywhere they go and hope to catch a glimpse of them.
He seemed like he was on that line.
Yeah.
He seemed to be doing it a little bit more than a lot of the other folks, like the Tuckers
or Estillans, that seemed just to be either insane or full of hate.
Yeah.
But yeah, this guy, I don't know, here's just a clip of...
In his own words, let's hear what he has to say.
An interesting character, Bernhard, because he's both before and after he started the
Bilderberg, had some really disastrous things happen to him, which throw a lot of doubt
over his integrity.
First of all, his membership before the US entered World War II of the SS, the German
SS.
He then left Germany afterwards and married into the Dutch royal family, but he was in
Hitler's feared SS during the war.
This is the guy that started the group off, and the irony is, of course, that they will
tell us that one of the reasons for the group is to stop the next or to stop any other possible
Hitler surfacing in the future.
Now I would have thought one of the worst people to start an organization dedicated
to that task was someone who'd been in Hitler's SS.
It is true that for a brief time before the war, Prince Bernhard was a member of the Reiter
SS, the mounted division of the SS.
This is definitely not cool, and I'm not making any kind of an excuse for it, but it's usually
a good idea when you're looking at a historical figure like this to judge them based on the
measure of a person's actions as opposed to a tiny, not a tiny detail, but a specific
individual detail.
Bernhard clearly did not support the Nazis in World War II, and he actively fought against
them when Hitler invaded the Netherlands in 1940.
His track record is fairly clear, and he was fighting Hitler's forces before the US even
was.
This is an instance of something that's a true enough fact that's being used to create
a dishonest image in the listener's head.
The goal is to portray that Bernhard is somebody who fought alongside the Nazis in the war,
and is someone who's a part of this elite division of Hitler's organization, and that's
just not true.
There's more complexity to this than that.
Yeah, that's got Soros's dad written all over it in that, like, fine!
I get what, yes, your fundamental basic fact is correct, and by leaving out literally everything
else you can support your narrative, but that's not the only fact.
Yeah, and probably Prince Bernhard's a little bit less of a sympathetic figure than 14-year-old
George Soros, inasmuch as he was older, and he was a member of the writing SS, but still,
the totality of his actions during the war speak to somebody who was not on the side
of Hitler.
He's not on the side of the Nazis, and I think that at that point you can say, alright, this
was a blip on your, it's a stain on your history, but it's not something that should be deterministic
of your character.
And that's what this guy wants to present Bernhard as, because, you know, he hates the
Bilderberg group, and if one of the people who co-founded it can be just portrayed as,
you know, one of Hitler's higher-ups, then there you go.
Right.
No, it's one of the most annoying things, because you don't, like, I don't need help
being prejudiced against a prince.
Like I'm fine with that, I don't like royalty.
But you can't make me hate him based on bullshit, that's not fair.
Also I'd like to correct myself.
That's not fair.
His name is Bernhard, I kept saying Barnard.
I did hear Barnard, and I was like, ehhh.
I don't know why.
Yeah, no, I mean, I don't need help, I don't need help there, and you lying about him makes
me then have to defend him, which I don't want to do.
No.
I don't want to defend a prince, fuck royalty.
No, it makes you need to, like, be like, well hold on a second, and then secondarily it
makes me very wary of whatever information you're putting out.
Whatever information you have about the Bilderberg group seems kind of sketchy, if this is the
level of accusation you're making.
If you can't get a basic detail contextually right, then why would I believe the rest of
what you have to say?
Yeah.
Anyway, the rest of this is just, you know, standard Bilderberg conspiracy nonsense.
Sure.
Gossip.
And bird watching of rich people.
You know, can't argue with a good bird watching.
So Alex gets back to calls, and this caller is sort of relevant to my interests, and that
is of course whether or not Alex was fighting the literal devil in 2003.
This gives us a little hint, maybe?
Wyatt Maryland.
Wyatt, you're on the air.
Go ahead, sir.
Good afternoon, Alex.
How you doing?
Good, good.
Boy, there's so much to talk about, and there's so little time, but all I can say is the demons
are loose, and they're out, and they're doing the work.
I mean, Alex doesn't have a direct response to that, but they're loose.
Demons are loose.
I don't know what happened, but demons got loose.
Who let the demons out?
We had, listen, we had them in a corral in northwestern Montana.
We had kept all the demons there.
That's how we had developed this great nation of ours, and somebody tripped, ruined the
summoning circle, and now the demons are loose.
There's just nothing to do.
Someone's gotta get a lasso.
We gotta drive in these here demons.
I think we need the regulators.
I think Nate Dogg and Warren G need to mount up R.I.P.
I think that this is an indication of some of the conversation that is clearly just pretty
organic and natural on Alex's show at this time, talking about demons being loose and
what have you, but it's still kind of a nebulous picture for me.
I'm leaning more towards there being a real literalist religious vibe going on.
I'm leaning closer to that, but I also don't have merely the amount of information that
we do from the present that Alex legit thinks the shoot devil is there and he's pulling
the strings of the enemies.
This guy sounds like he definitely believes that the literal demons are loose.
This dude.
Yeah.
They're doing work.
You could still see that as a metaphor, or if you're Alex and you're responding to that,
you could see that as a metaphor for the demonic impulses of the elite are given free reign
now, no longer having to be corralled or moderated.
Yeah, who knows?
So Alex gets a lot of mileage out of people pretending that he's been right about so many
things, about so many things.
For 27 years.
He's righter than he is wrong, and he's not.
But one of the things that I thought was really fun about this next clip is he makes a bunch
of predictions about gun grabbing and stuff and everything he says is wrong.
Okay.
They're going to reauthorize Clinton's gun ban and they're going to expand it radically.
So they're going to add a semiautomatic shotgun ban.
That's the NRA telling you that they're going to sign S 22, which is Patriot act two in
the Senate, full of gun registration, shutting down the gun shows, national ballistics databases,
the most gun control, the most hardcore draconian stuff we've ever seen.
And the average conservative out there has no idea because the neo cons like rush Limbaugh,
Neil boards, Michael Savage, Sean Hannity will not tell them.
Wow.
He likes a lot of those people.
Now.
Yeah.
Loves them.
All those predictions are wrong.
I was, I was trying to keep track of him.
I wrote, Nope, Nope, Nope.
And also Nope.
Nope.
None of those happened.
Yes, that is true.
Um, so yeah, I mean, he's right.
Most of the time.
Sure.
Anyway, this next clip, Alex goes back to calls and this dude, I tried to trace this
down.
I got very little on this, but this, this was, I enjoyed this is going to be a big swing.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Sure.
Okay.
Tom and Texas.
You're on the air.
Go ahead, sir.
Yeah.
You're on the air.
Go ahead.
Yes, sir.
I, I first informed, uh, Tex Mars in, uh, 1988 about the, uh, the church, the hidden
church over there on highway six, uh, about, uh, as an area and as a moment, I was in work
with you all movies world, sir, I really don't understand what you're saying or have to give
us some background.
I do not understand this and I want to know, tell me about the hidden church on route six.
Well, thankfully Alex does ask for clarification and here it comes.
Okay, the background is, uh, I went to this church that we moved pews out of and the old
man walked out cussing like a sailor cause we got there late.
He said, you realize who's church this is?
I said, no.
He said, this is George Bush's church, but we walked in and had a big swatch to go hanging
down and up above the pulpit and I said, well, okay, well tell me all about, he has the Christian
symbol up there, you said, and it's, and he showed me all the pictures in the offices
of the Bush family.
So about, I guess two weeks later, I went and told Tex Mars about it at a convention
at the hobby airport.
So first of all, this dude worked for a moving company and he was called to show up at a
backwards hidden church to remove pews, but somehow the only person there hadn't called
them to move the furniture and was confused that they were there.
Correct.
This is a little fishy.
No.
My second issue is that this was in 1988.
So at this point, George H.W. Bush was coming to the end of his second term as vice president
and was about to win the 1988 election for president.
He still flew back to Texas every Sunday to go to the hidden church on Route 6, everybody
knows that.
George W. Bush hadn't even become Texas governor yet and honestly, he hadn't even bought the
Texas Rangers at this point.
I don't see how the either, it would be in either of their interests to be running a
secret Nazi church in the middle of Texas when they were spending most of their time
at this point in DC and campaigning.
I am the vice president of the United States.
And have been for years.
One of the most looked at, observed, and known where a person is at all times.
People you can be.
Almost like there's a schedule that's public.
That's public.
Every day.
But on Sundays, flies back to Texas, heads to the hidden Nazi church.
No one knows about it.
Except for this guy, the U-Haul mover who accidentally showed up there or something.
And there are hidden pictures of the, okay, okay.
So you're telling me, you're telling me that this moving company shows up, the guy is cussing
like a sailor, says, do you know whose church this is?
This is the Bush's church.
And then that aggressive attitude wipes away and he's like, come on back into the office.
Let me show you George Bush and the Nazis.
And no one will ever find these pictures despite the fact that this guy seems willing to show
them to literally anybody who walks in.
Yeah, yeah.
He seems, seems to be real neighborly.
Hey, hey, this is the hidden church on route six.
Come on in.
Let me show you the vice president's Nazi memorabilia.
Well, you know, I work for George H.W. Bush and he specifically told me when he left that
while I was watching over the place, I was to tell everybody.
Let everybody know.
Be sure you show the pictures of me and my family.
Yes, I want this information getting out.
That's why I go to this hidden church.
Ridiculous.
Also, Tex Mars is a extreme anti-Semite.
So yeah, it's not good that this guy felt like, hey, first person I got to get this
information to.
Yeah.
Not good.
No.
So Alex wants to know where this church is.
Yes.
Because that is an important question.
Now, where is this church, sir?
That was the problem.
Now, when I told Tex Mars, he wrote about me in his book, Hidden Days of the Rainbow.
I'm the one that informed him about it.
He didn't know nothing about it.
And he found it to be true.
Where is this church, sir?
Okay.
It was on Highway 6.
Best I can remember.
This is in 88.
I'll have to do some more investigation.
Outside where?
Right outside.
It's close to, I'd say going out past Sugar Land.
Outside Houston.
Right.
It's on the east side of Houston.
I mean, the west side of Houston.
Look, man, if you find the vice president's Nazi church, you will forget.
Just know where the vice president's Nazi church is.
You will drive people by.
It's pretty big.
Yeah.
It's a pretty big thing.
No, I would find ways.
I would be like, hey, look, the main highway has been torn down.
We're going to have to take the long way through Highway 6.
Oh, by the way, I met George Bush's Nazi pastor and he's got pictures of George Bush with
the Nazi bullshit.
I find it difficult to believe that if you did find something like this, you wouldn't
go back yourself.
All the time.
Not all the time.
But at least you'd go back and be like, did I really see what I thought I saw?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, this is Brigadoon.
It's outrageous.
Yeah.
So anyway, this church, I want to ask you how you're picturing this.
How big is it?
What are you imagining?
Give me some physical attributes that you're-
All right, I see it seating maybe 60 to 80 people.
There are about-
So it's kind of a smaller congregation.
Kind of a smaller congregation.
There's two rows of pews on either side with a walkway there.
There's a pulpit and directly behind it hanging is a, let's call it 20 foot tall Nazi flag
based on his description.
Do you think that it's a place that's in good repair?
Do you think it's something that's dilapidated?
What are your feelings on this?
I think it has to have that feel of being absurdly clean for the area that it's in.
Like the walls are painted absurdly white, almost as if they're immune to the nature
around them.
So it's like an OR, like an operating room in the middle of a swamp.
Yes, absolutely.
Okay.
That is an interesting picture and I think that's probably about what I thought.
We're both wrong.
Okay.
How many people would you say the church would see?
7,000.
Probably at least 800 at the least.
That's a lot.
It's real organized.
That's a lot of people who know George Bush is a Nazi.
I mean, the whole family was in there, they had the Bushes, the kids, the whole nine yards
in there.
He says, I said, well, I can't believe this is Bushes.
He said, man, this is the God, God, this is the true church of God here.
And he said it was a branch from the Abyscapelian.
I do remember him saying that, a branch away from the Abyscapelian.
Sir, I appreciate your call, Tom, appreciate it.
But look, that is not how I know the global is to operate.
It's an armored fortress at the Skull and Bones tomb and that kind of stuff is in there.
That's confirmed.
It's guarded at Bohemian Grove and there is that type of stuff.
I don't know that story, sir.
I really, I don't like to speculate on, so, you know, I'm not saying you're a liar.
It just, it just doesn't, doesn't fit.
It fits with some stuff but not in other areas.
I'm so proud of Alex.
That's one of the few points that I've ever heard him be like, I can't accept this.
Yeah, that is, that is intense.
Yeah.
How great would it be to be like, I'm on the phone with the person who found George W. Bush's
Nazi church.
And he's like, I can't make this fit.
This is no good.
No, sir.
Look, this just doesn't match.
Yeah.
Sorry.
I'm not calling you a liar, but I don't know about this.
Yeah.
That's, that's a, that is a level of pushback I rarely see from him.
That's true.
But I mean, at the same time, his pushback is not based around like, that's ridiculous
so much as it is like, okay, I get you think there's a Nazi base on the moon, but it's
on Mars.
Duh.
I can't accept this Nazi base on the moon.
Whatever my Nazi base is on Mars, man.
I have to actually push back on what you're saying because I think that that's not fair.
I think that what Alex is saying, the reason that he's, he's pushing back on this guy is
because he's saying there are little Nazi enclaves and, and, and like worship centers
or whatever.
Yeah, of course.
But they're heavily armed.
Yes.
That's like, you, you can't get into the skull and bones area where there's the big Nazi
flag.
Right.
There's not going to be one out in the middle of like at this church that you get welcomed
into.
And it's not, it's not that it's like, okay, it's on the moon or on Mars.
It's the context surrounding this doesn't make sense.
I understand.
This would not be that easy to accidentally stumble into.
I broke into Bohemian Grove.
That's how I know their things.
You didn't break into this church.
No, you were welcomed in by a, and that would never happen, a surprisingly neighborly Nazi.
Right.
Because his narratives require that it's hard to find these secrets.
True.
And so that's why he's pushing back.
But I still think that it's at least, I mean, functionally, it serves the same purpose as
saying that this is ridiculous.
Sure.
No, that's, that's definitely true.
That's definitely true.
And he, I mean, I assume it would feel like a bit of a personal attack on his manhood
if you just got to get secrets by walking into places.
And then potentially bigger scoop than Bohemian Grove.
Exactly.
Just by accidentally showing up with a U-Haul truck.
I think it would just be so much easier to be like, really seats 800, huh?
Wow.
So there's, there's a, what, 768 people who know that the entire Bush family is Nazis?
No, no, no.
Here's what you don't know.
There's 800 Bush family members.
Now that might as well be your, your angle on it.
Sure.
It's the only Bush church there's ever been.
Yeah.
So here's, here's our last clip from the 22nd.
Alex is talking about the situation in Iraq, and he's saying that, about to confiscate
weapons from people.
Allies to begin seizing weapons from most Iraqis.
Iraqi citizens will be required to turn over automatic weapons and heavy weapons under
a proclamation that allied authorities plan to issue this week.
Allied officials of the day, the aim of the proclamation is to help stabilize Iraq by
confiscating a huge supply of AK-47 machine guns, buck repelled grenades, and other weapons
that are used by criminal gangs, paramilitary groups, and remnants of the Saddam Hussein's
government.
Well, the remnants of Saddam Hussein's government, we've got the names, the Ba'ath Party's being
put back into control.
So Alex still thinks on the 22nd of May that the Ba'ath Party is being put back into power
and it's all a CIA operation.
Isn't he reading about how they're confiscating the Ba'ath Party's weapons?
Well, I mean, I think that, I have to assume that he just thinks that that's window dressing
or cover or something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That way people won't suspect that the Ba'ath Party is still running things.
Right, right.
Yeah, yeah.
So I still think that we have not reached a point where this is interesting.
It's still sort of rising, it's crescendoing reality, and Alex just...
They're on a collision course.
Head on.
Head on collision.
Two trains traveling directly at each other.
And I'm very interested to see how that, how Alex tries to veer around that, that looming
accident.
It does have the feel of two trains riding straight towards each other and one train
is like, ooh, I can't hit reality, so I'm going to turn off, and then it hits a bus.
You're like, way to go.
So a large portion of this episode on the 23rd is Alex talking to this Belgian doctor,
Dr. Van Martyr.
Okay.
Mortyr?
Martyr?
I'm not entirely sure.
That's a good name.
He's a dude who witnessed crimes being committed by our military against Iraqi civilians, and
there's talk of bringing charges against military leaders in foreign courts.
Yeah.
That would be nice.
I have little problem with this interview as a whole.
I think that this guy is bringing up some fine points, but also it's not a very good
interview.
I think I don't think that Alex really gets to too many of the more important issues.
It seems like he's doing a bit of grandstanding and what have you, and I just think that this
subject matter is covered better by almost anybody else.
Even in 2003, there were much better commentators that you could find discussing human rights
abuses on the part of our military in Iraq, but at the same time, I'm not going to sit
and nitpick, because it's mostly this dude talking, and his perspective is like, he saw
some US soldiers shooting at an ambulance, and like, yeah, that sucks.
Yeah, that's a war crime.
So would you say that this interview is Alex letting somebody give legitimate criticisms
of the US military in order for him to be like, see, the military and the government
is all evil, despite not actually giving a shit about the war crimes, and just kind of
exploiting that the government is evil?
Somewhat, and then also using it to translate into, like, they're going to start a police
state here.
Sure, sure.
And so I don't think that his use of this stuff is great, but I also think, like...
Yeah, the US commits war crimes.
We got it.
Yeah, it's...
We should do something about it now, soon.
It's hard to lose...
In 2003.
It's really weird to me.
It's really weird to remember 2003 and hear that Alex was having a Belgian doctor on to
reveal US war crimes and was not...
Like, because I remember how bloodthirsty everybody was.
Everybody was so fucking bloodthirsty.
If you went on TV and said like, hey, the American government is committing war crimes,
there would be another talking head being like, that's the cost of war, you know?
And people would agree, yes, sometimes you have to commit war crimes.
To fucking have to live in a world where unfortunately, despite his exploitative nature, Alex was
one of the few people putting on an agreement fest about the US committing war crimes is
wild.
Yeah, yeah.
It is.
Yeah, it is.
Sorry, I just needed to observe that.
That just feels like really strange to live in both the present and the past at the same
time.
And it's worth pointing out, I don't think it's worth discussing this interview like
actual clips of it, but it is worth bringing up that that is a reality.
And again, I think you can say hooray to an extent to him for that.
But there's still other voices that exist that were talking about these things, and
they weren't doing things like the other things that Alex is doing.
And one of those things is hanging out with fucking shitheads and talking about Bilderberg.
Yeah.
I mean, just in the context of that, it is kind of something that I think about a lot
just because that's part of how Alex got to where he got to, is that there were shit tons
of war crimes going on, and because this is correct, you are sucked into the rest of his
bullshit until he just gets rid of even any pretense of giving a shit about war crimes,
and then you're trapped in this place of, neither do I, you know?
It's weird.
Yeah, it is weird.
And the things that he cares about more aren't those things.
They aren't...
Exactly.
They aren't issues that he cares about for the sake of them.
He cares about them as a means.
Yeah.
And it's an important thing to point out that one of the big reasons that we are here where
propagandists can destroy everything is that cyclical nature between a corrupt war crime
committing government and a propaganda outlet who's creating that like, yeah, you can't
trust these war crime committing people for good reasons until it spirals out of control,
and now you can't trust anybody or anything.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I got lost on a tangent there.
Apologies.
No worries.
So one of the things that Alex does care more about, one of the things that's really consistent,
like I said, is that Bilderberg shit.
And so he had that guy, Tony Gosling, on the 22nd talk about Bilderberg, and if you go
check out his website, he has some iffy opinions.
I would like Alex to put his top 30 movies on the Info Wars website.
I don't.
Okay.
I think it would all just be...
Oblivion 1 through 30.
Yeah.
Yeah, Life's a Movie, man.
So he has another expert on the 23rd, and that's big Jim Tucker, baby.
Well, I spent 20 years with the establishment press, with Washington Daily News, Akron,
Beacon, Journal, Richmond Times, This Statch, other newspapers, until 1975 when I was being
interviewed by Willis Carter at Liberty Lobby for the position of editor of a newspaper
he was getting ready to create called The Spotlight.
He asked me what I thought about Bilderberg, and I said, who are they, and he gave me a
brief description.
I said, that's impossible.
I've been with newspapers all my life.
Such a group could not exist without me knowing.
Willis Cardo is a Nazi and white supremacist.
The Spectator was a paper whose editorial position was anti-Semitism and Holocaust denial.
Jim Tucker was the editor of that paper.
In case you've forgotten since we talked about him in our Endgame coverage, here's one of
Willis Cardo's famous quotes.
Quote, if Satan himself, with all of his superhuman genius and diabolical ingenuity at his command,
had tried to create a permanent disintegration and force for the destruction of the nations,
he could have done no better than invent the Jews.
Describing his motivation to start The Spotlight, the ADL says in a bio of Cardo, quote, Cardo's
chief aim was always to mobilize opinion against Jews.
Liberty Lobby was his chief instrument to bridge right-wing constituencies.
Hard-right or paramilitary libertarians, conspiratorial anti-communists, racists by inflaming their
anti-government and nativist fears and identifying Jews as the country's chief threat.
Willis Cardo is a bigot who wanted to sway public opinion against Jews with his media
entities.
And Jim Tucker worked for his big media entity from its beginning in 1975 until they folded
in 2001.
Fuck him and fuck whatever he has to say about Bilderberg.
It's even more insulting that he didn't know about them until Willis Cardo told him about
them.
God damn.
Yeah.
One of the worst.
Fuck Jim Tucker.
Yeah, it makes you want to invent a bow and arrow that can shoot arrows into the past.
One of the things that's really funny to me though is like, Alex is like, oh yeah, Jim
Tucker, you know, you climb fences and get in there.
He's a real intrepid journalist.
And then like you look at the videos of Jim Tucker and he's always drunk and smoking at
cigarettes.
I was going to say, yeah, this is not a man, he's the guy who was wearing the hat all the
time too.
I was like, that is not a man who can jump a fence without severely injuring himself.
He seems like he's exhausted reading a paper.
Or at the very least continuing to breathe.
Yeah.
So anyway, Alex talks to Jim Tucker and it's all just the same shit except without the
excitement at seeing David Rockefeller, the Tony Gosling guy.
We don't have the fanboy moment.
But one of the things that I think is worth pointing out about both of these interviews
is that Jim Tucker is somebody who I don't know and I don't care what his personal positions
are.
He was the editor of a fucking white supremacist Holocaust denial paper for 25 years.
And Tony Gosling has a lot of questions about who is or is not Jewish and thinks a lot of
the problems in the world come from Jews not accepting Jesus as the Messiah.
Seems like it.
You wouldn't know that from listening to their interviews.
You wouldn't know that.
You would think that these guys are concerned about politics and really powerful people
getting together and talking behind closed doors.
You would think that, hey, these are just guys who have a political position that maybe
is anathema with what the media wants to report.
You wouldn't know that maybe a lot of antisemitism is what drives.
Yeah.
You know, a lot of people don't sympathize with Nazis as much.
But what you got to understand is you used to be able to just tell people that you hated
the Jews all the time.
And now you have to hide behind all of these things, you know, like that's hard.
Let's just think about the Nazis for a second.
Now they can't even say openly on the radio that everyone should kill the Jews because
it's their fault.
It's brutal.
Poor Willis.
Anyway, we go to the 27th because most of this show is just that interview with Jim
Tucker and then the interview with the Belgian doctor.
And like I said, the discussion of mistreatment of Iraqis and all that is fine and it's good.
It's something that there was probably, I don't even know if probably is the right word,
I would say definitely, there should have been more space for in public conversation.
But one of the reasons that I find it kind of not that interesting or not that relevant
to give Alex too much of a pat on the head about it is he takes these stories and he
discusses or reads headlines about mistreatment of people in Iraq, the civilians, and then
he just makes it about himself and the United States.
Naturally.
This is so horrible and it's only going to get worse.
And MSNBC reported before the war plans for reeducation centers.
Marine centers, movie screens, blaring propaganda, machine gun nests, everything.
This is so embarrassing.
But again, Europe controls America, is using us as the bad cop right now, they own our
full reserve, they've ordered the dollar to be imploded.
So again, none of that came to pass here as he's suggesting.
He's covering here, this is on the 27th now, we've jumped to that Tuesday, and he's covering
conversation about Guantanamo, about the possibility of military tribunals taking place there.
And now he's saying that they had plans before the war for here in America to have these
detention centers and machine gun nests.
It's all the conversation about the wrongs of the war exist in order to facilitate his
narratives about his fears about what's going to happen here.
It's not on its own merits.
The people there, their pain and what's being done isn't wrong because it's wrong.
And I have a difficulty with that.
Yeah.
I mean, you know, it's tough.
The good thing is that, if I recall correctly, in 2008, Obama fulfilled his campaign promise
to close Guantanamo Bay, right?
That was like one of the first things he did.
But Dan, I'm...
So Alex goes to calls, and one of the things that he's been pretty upset about is seat
belt checks.
I really, really don't know.
He's not a fan of click it or tick it.
The devil with all of his might is arrayed against us, and I can't stand a $70 ticket.
So he's talking here, another instance of him being totally right about his predictions
of what would...
So the seat belt checks.
Yes.
It's going to get out of control.
Okay.
It was, we then learned the name of it.
It was the National Seat Belt Use Initiative funded by Clinton to the tune of over $4 billion
a year.
Started at 2.4, and then it phased in over to $4 billion a year.
Bush is funding it.
It's going to build internal checkpoints that will also serve as toll booths to fund it.
It will be the equivalent of airport screening.
You'll be harassed.
You'll be searched.
That's why they don't care if you refuse to fly.
You're going to go through it at the checkpoints, and it says, citizens will wear gray uniforms,
part three of the four-part plan.
Citizens will wear gray uniforms.
That will be a national draft, compulsory draft.
You will have to serve in Homeland Security.
It will be high school students to be able to graduate.
They will be searching you at checkpoints.
The Philadelphia Inquirer reported last year that the kids are training with M-16s.
They're training in warrant service, checkpoints, fugitive apprehension, building clearing.
It is going to be throngs of power-tripping citizens with submachine guns.
It's a nightmare world, sir.
How does it sound to you?
I don't know.
I don't think this happened.
But, you know, one of the things that's wild is, like, you go back to 2003, and the world
was so, like, topsy-turvy because of the aftermath of 9-11 and the Iraq war that I think a lot
of people probably could hear something like that and be like, fuck, I don't know.
Maybe.
I don't know, I mean, the only thing that, like, the main argument I would have against
that is just, like, that seems like biting off more than the government can chew, you
know?
Like, there's not the infrastructure in place to get everybody to wear gray uniforms.
That's going to take a monumental effort of manufacturing.
I think he was talking about the conscripted youths wearing gray uniforms.
All right.
Well, still, you've got to outfit all these kids with submachine guns.
That's going to be noticed.
Yeah.
The gun manufacturers and the gun sellers are all used to exploiting fears about the
people having too many, you know, like, I don't think it's going to happen.
No.
But, I mean, the kernels of some of this stuff is stuff that I remember, like, not sounding
that crazy.
The national draft, you could totally, yeah, the national draft, you totally, I was scared.
I remember not insane people having that conversation about, like, is there a possibility that a
draft may come back because of the world circumstances?
Totally.
And so I think you can take that level of, like, okay, that's not that nuts, and then
attach all this nuts stuff on it and get someone to, I don't know, accept the nuts stuff because
of the...
Yeah, if I can buy something that is ostensibly nuts, which is the reinstatement of the draft,
then it's not that much bigger of a step to assume that there will be gray-clad children
with submachine guns patrolling my neighborhood.
Yeah.
All of this because of seat belts?
Sure.
Okay.
So another thing that Alex talks about a bit is there's a mad cow situation in Canada,
and the Canadian beef market is taking a hit because of, there's at least a few cases of
mad cow have been discovered and there's a fear of an outbreak.
Yes.
And Alex is complaining a bunch about how you need to, you can't be feeding animals
other animals, dead animals, especially sick animals.
You can't be feeding herbivores animal products and stuff like that.
And fine, I agree.
But I don't know what the answer is other than regulation.
Well, we can't do regulation.
It's nuts.
He just complains about how people can't be allowed to do these things.
How do you deal with this from a functional standpoint?
He never brings up a solution other than people shouldn't do it.
It's the free market system.
If everybody wakes up, if he's got a 90% wake up rate, then the free market will, I assume,
account for the fact that people know that these businesses shouldn't be doing that.
So all of these people won't patronize these businesses.
Well, it'll be too late because they'll have mad cow.
They will have mad cow by then.
That is unfortunate.
Yeah.
I think regulation might be the only way to really...
Boy, it could work.
Yeah.
Anyway, I thought that was really stupid.
Very.
Alex has a call from a guy and he says Jesus a couple times.
Like just like, oh, Jesus Christ, you know, like...
Oh, as an epithet.
No.
Well, sort of as an exclamation.
Gotcha.
Alex ends the call.
And this is...
Because he's taken to the Lord's name in vain?
Well, not because of that, but it's definitely what's on his mind.
John, great to hear from you.
I appreciate the call, sir.
Great points from the United Kingdom.
Please, though, I'm a Christian and we're on a many Christian stations.
I know we have a worldly audience.
Be very careful about using the Lord's name in vain because I don't want repercussions
of that, not from stations, but from God.
So I'm not mad at you, John, but be careful about, you know, being like the rest of the
world.
I'm not trying to chastise you.
I just...
Please, folks.
We have a lot of homeschoolers listening as well.
No!
And...
What?
And not...
What did you just say?
And not use the Lord's name in vain.
I don't want to divert people off, but that's an important point.
That is an important point.
Wow.
Cut to 2021.
And Jesus says, you gotta buy my products!
I gotta trick Dick.
Yep.
Oh, boy.
What a fucking ridiculous thing to say.
I worry about God's vengeance when a caller says Jesus Christ on my show.
Yeah, I think that's performative.
Maybe.
Just a ten.
Yeah, I think that's a little bit.
Just a hair.
So Alex thanks the audience here for putting his content out into the world, making copies
of his videos and stuff, because those things aren't going to spread themselves, and 90%
success rate.
90% wake up.
Pretty impressive.
We've got to research that, because whatever he's doing...
I can only commend you, thank you so much for what you've done.
In fact, I never thanked the listeners enough, the people that have gotten my films, the
people that have made copies and are still making copies.
Those that have aired them on local community TV stations.
Those that have rented out the movie theaters and shown it.
Those that have rented out the local gym or ample theater and shown it on a big screen
TV.
I want to commend everybody.
God bless you.
It's really having an effect, because we could back the globalist off.
I have no doubt that if we wouldn't have been fighting them on 9-1-1 and exposing their
involvement, the globalist would have already carried out more chairs.
Fuck you.
Yup.
Wow.
I'm a fan of that kind of framing of things, you know?
That's always really fun.
Like, if we hadn't been doing this...
You know, actually, your supporting my show and spreading my materials has actually made
it so the globalists can't pull off another 9-11.
Yup.
It's so great.
That's why Mark Wahlberg flies on every flight he can, all day every day, because he's trying
to make sure that no more 9-11s will happen, and the only way to stop it is to put a Mark
Wahlberg on your plane and have an Alex tell you how to stop it, I guess.
Right.
There we go.
We did it.
I think we've just fixed terrorism.
Can you imagine what kind of a shithead you'd have to be to act like this?
We could be like, okay, hey, thanks everyone for supporting our podcast, and actually,
I'm certain that there would have been another Oklahoma City bombing, there would have been
another Patriot federal building bombing if you hadn't been supporting our show.
What the fuck?
Listen, your support for our show made it so January 6th was not as bad as it could
have been.
Could have been worse, but we did it.
Here's the problem.
That is something that did happen.
Alex is making up imaginary things that didn't happen because his show is finished.
So what you're saying is, we successfully stopped the attack on January 7th.
That would be how you'd have to frame it.
Okay.
Then we did it.
So there's some people who are saying that the war is kind of like a holy war.
Yeah, that's not good.
No.
And Alex thinks that's bullshit.
Good.
However...
Oh, no.
And they said, this is a holy war and you're with the devil if you're against it.
That was a fraud.
But when they said that God has taken his protection away from America and allowed these
attacks to take place because we have become a corrupt and decadent nation on average,
that was true.
It's a scientific fact.
You read what's shown.
Okay.
All right.
It is a scientific fact that God removed his protection over the United States.
That's why 9-11 happened.
In order to allow 9-11 to happen.
Yep.
And that is why it's not a holy war.
No.
Because it's divine retribution.
Also, Alex does say now that people who are against him are with the devil.
Yes, 100%.
So I guess it's a holy war now.
Well, now it's a holy war.
Right.
But back then it wasn't.
I'd like him to scientifically prove that God's protection was removed and that's what
made 9-11 happen.
Yeah, what exactly is God's protection doing around the United States prior to that area?
Did we never have any terrorist attacks prior to that?
None.
Okay, good.
So Alex takes another call from a guy and he brings up scripture in a kind of clunky
way.
I just found this to be amusing.
Bill in New Jersey, you're up next.
Howard, go ahead.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Alex Jones.
I have recently been reading in 2 Chronicles 23-11 and, you know, they anointed a son of
a king, you know, they said God saved the king, you know.
23-11 wasn't long.
So I don't know if you're familiar with 2 Chronicles 23-11.
Okay.
All right.
Got a weird vibe going on.
Yep.
Don't know what's happening.
Are you guys talking about kings?
Well.
Something?
The Chronicles are about the, I mean, they're literal chronicles of all the cool shit that
the kings did.
Sure.
So, easy caller, easy.
What do you want to talk about?
Let's hear it.
But the idea of this, I've got a book here that says the true story of the seventh in
line to the British crown, and of course in that book is pictures of the mother and the
queen's mother, and they all kind of look like the Bush family, you know.
And of course I know that the Constitution was...
You're talking about British Israelism.
Well that's possible.
No he's not.
But that's interesting, because that implies...
That Alex knows very clearly what British Israelism is.
Well at least he knows of it.
Yes.
It doesn't imply that.
It proves that Alex is aware of it as a concept, he knows it's a thing.
It's not something that he can feign complete ignorance about, which is a problem.
Yeah.
So the true caller, what he's talking about is a book that is about Prince Charles' brother,
his younger brother, the seventh in line for the...
It's not Andrew, it's the other, I think Edward is the other brother.
Sure.
Nah, whatever.
I don't like royals.
Yeah, it's just some biography about him.
Sure.
I don't think it has anything to do with British Israelism.
It sounds like where he's going is that the Bushes are related to the British royal family.
Well, I don't know where he's going exactly.
Well, that's fair.
And I've listened to this.
That's fair.
That is fair.
So the caller brought up the scripture, and he's talking about anointing of kings is in
the Bible.
Right.
And he's saying he read this book about the royals, and they look like Bushes or whatever.
And so I miked down for this, because I want you to help me out here.
Okay.
And I can't tell if what this caller is bringing up is a satirical suggestion, or if it's sincere.
I'm not sure.
All right.
You know, in the Bible, it talks about how they anointed the king and gave him the testimonies.
And they were the Constitution, you know how they're tearing up the Constitution and manipulating
it.
Maybe we should forsake the Constitution and go with the king in this country.
And we should say, God save George W. Bush, you know, King George, you know.
So will we say that if Hitler was in Germany, let's go ahead, the Bible says follow Hitler?
A lot of people like Hitler, you know.
In Germany, they did.
I don't know why.
He was a complete badass.
I tell you what, I think that's another story about, I think Deuteronomy 23, 2, about, you
know, how illegitimate children were allowed into the congregation of God for ten generations.
It was a Jewish law, you know, Deuteronomy 23, 2.
But that's the Old Testament.
We have the New Testament.
That's right.
And I don't know what's going on here.
I can't tell, like, I think this is a sincere suggestion that the caller is making.
I agree.
But I can also see a way that he's really poorly expressing sort of a point of satire,
like, hey, you know, it's in the Bible that we have kings, why shouldn't we have King
George?
Like being, like presenting that as like an over-the-top argument.
But then again, I don't know what the point of that would be.
Like what would be underneath that satire?
Is he satirizing the Bible?
Uh, no.
I don't know.
No, I view this as him being 100% sincere.
It kind of feels that way.
And I think the main reason for that is he's been reading about how great kings have been
and how a philosopher king is perhaps the best type of government that there possibly
could be and has decided that democracy has failed us, the Constitution is meaningless,
and we should have a king.
Also...
And Alex, after a little while, is going to agree with him.
True.
Yeah.
Yes, I do think that Alex has come around on the idea of monarchy, at least a specific
sort of monarchy.
Seems like it.
Um, yeah, weird, weird that this guy's rebuttal to Alex being like, should we all just...
A lot of people liked Hitler.
Ooh.
A lot of people didn't.
I would say probably a significantly larger number.
So this is something that kind of is a problem for Alex.
Much like the Republic of Texas callers, this is something that sticks in Alex's craw.
And so he goes to another call, and he's got to bring it up.
He's got to bring up this idea of making Bush king.
Hey, what do you think of these people that say it's Christian to worship your leader
and not criticize your leader?
Yeah, yeah, that's another important thing.
You know, don't put down a king just because he's king.
What?
He's a good king, he's a bad king.
And my family, I have two lines of royal blood dating back, I don't know how long.
I'm sorry, what now?
The one, I'm not going to say the name, but he was elected by the people.
The people held him up, and they said, we want him king.
Sir, sir, sir, this whole thing of getting rid of the Constitution and making Bush king.
George Washington fought in the backyard of the house I grew up in.
This didn't go the way Alex wanted it to.
Yeah, this is spiraled out of control pretty quickly.
This is spiraled out of control real quick.
Hey buddy, I kind of got the sense that maybe you'd back me up on this whole making kings
thing is bad.
Hey, some kings are good, actually I have two royal blood lines.
Yeah, yeah, that's definitely not what you would be expecting.
I mean, if you're Alex, with your Alex audience, I can't imagine you would get two pro-monarchy
people in a row.
That would be a surprise to me as well.
Yeah, I mean, at a certain point it's just like, wow, this is bad luck, it's full moon
or something, I don't know.
I mean, his fucking description of kings is literally, don't hate the player, hate the
game.
Some kings are good.
Some kings are good, like the two blood lines I come from.
I won't say which.
No, no, no, no.
But George Washington fought in my backyard, just throwing that out there.
I wouldn't want to dox my blood.
I'd hate it if the Tudors heard I was bad mouthing them behind their backs.
Alex has said that he's related to the Tudors.
Yes.
Maybe they're related.
Could be.
So we're coming into the end of this here, and on the 27th Alex gets into talking a little
bit about some new news stories about some SSRI issues that are becoming conversations.
One of them is about dangers of withdrawal for some SSRI medications, and that is a real
thing, although Alex is trying to portray it as just being on these drugs will make
you kill people and what have you.
I thought this was bizarre, because Alex hasn't updated any of these talking points for 18
years.
These are all the same things that he says just word for word.
By the way, when they did these studies in the early 80s of Prozac, they found a large
percentage, around 14%, had suicidal tendencies.
You see, it puts you into a dream state.
So you're happily bumbling around kind of in a mesmerized, mind-controlled state, literally.
Then you have a bad day or a bad trip.
These drugs are more associated with hallucinogens than they are with other type drug families.
And some people just have a snap.
I've talked to psychologists and people that know what's happening, and they say that they've
had patients who were on it, and they're dancing around naked with butcher knives on top of
their houses, they kill their kids.
Most of these women who killed their kids were on multiple drugs, almost all the shooters.
In fact, we haven't found one yet who wasn't on these drugs.
Yes, we have.
It also makes you very open to suggestion.
It puts you into a subconscious state, folks.
These people are sleepwalking.
This is just exactly the same sort of stuff that he says all the time.
And the thing that I think is really interesting is that story about the butcher knife on top
of a roof is also the specific example that he uses for years and years.
This one image that he has of a case of somebody with a butcher knife on a roof, I think this
is just deeply irresponsible.
I think this is the definition of an unnuanced take on psychiatric meds.
Yeah, I mean, there's not much to say whenever it's like, man, in 2003, I was unmedicated
just coming into my own as a type one bipolar person.
But you could see reality, man.
And just reading about it back then, it was legitimately in the literature of bipolar
type one was just straight up like one fifth of you don't make it for whatever reason.
And it's related to your mental illness.
And like that idea of somebody being like, well, you know what?
That's better than SSRIs and feeling good is just like, I just don't know how you can
talk to somebody who's aware of the death toll that just being alive gives them.
Yeah.
It's real shitty.
In a way you could say that giving someone life is in fact giving someone death.
Yeah, there's a lot of factors and variables that Alex isn't taking into account here.
And obviously any medication that people take isn't without risk.
Living without medications for some people is also a great risk.
And it's unfair to attack medication because of the risk while not accepting that there
is a great risk to not taking medication.
And the fucked up part of it, the fucked up part of it is what one of the biggest contributors
to that is.
Let's say you were on an SSRI and then you listen to a fucking radio show and suddenly
decided to stop taking your medication.
And then your withdrawals fucking light you up and you become part of the statistics that
Alex is going to use the next year to say that people who are on SSRI should immediately
stop them as part of his evidence for what's just so fucking-
I have to correct you because it is that Alex does bring up that just stopping taking meds
is dangerous.
Well that's good.
Yeah.
I don't know if it's enough to dissuade his listeners who hear him say that taking meds
make you have a bad trip or you're just brainwashed and sleepwalking through life.
But he does actually say that you need to take a decreasing dose and it's dangerous
just to stop.
That's very good.
Yeah.
I mean credit where credit's due.
Oh totally.
At the very least he's doing the absolute bare minimum while fear mongering about the
meds.
I just couldn't let that not be said because he does actually-
It's good to say, it's good to point out, yes.
Now unfortunately he also says things like this.
And that says, last year more than 22 million prescriptions for antidepressants were written
out by British patients.
Most of them for SSRIs.
These drugs work by allowing the hormone serotonin to act properly in the brain controlling mood
swings.
Oh to act properly.
How about you go for a jog?
How about you splash some cold water on your face?
How about you get on your knees and ask God to heal you?
Because believe me folks, their vaccines, their drugs are a bunch of trash.
Yeah.
And apparently you should just pray.
Well, you know, I feel like I'm worthless and like I'm a drain on every single human
being around me and that every part of life would be improved if I were no longer here
for it.
But actually you know what I should have just done?
Jog.
Gone for a run.
Yeah.
My bad, my bad.
Just jog.
While I was running I definitely wouldn't fixate on those very same repetitive thoughts
that I can't get out of my way.
No, you should just pray that God heals you.
She's gotta pray.
Man, that advice really worked for me when I was growing up.
Oh me too.
I got that one a lot.
Yeah.
Fixed everything.
Yeah, it solved a lot of problems.
I mean, look, I don't want to like give any credence to what Alex is saying, but you know,
exercise can help people feel better.
Exercise and meditation are great ways to cope.
They absolutely are.
Yeah.
But that is not a full health regimen necessarily.
And I think that this is just kind of dangerous, kind of bad, and I think, you know, obviously
it's not what I'm looking for in terms of figuring out if Alex believes he's fighting
the literal devil.
There's a corollary here that Alex does seem to think that health can be achieved by God
giving it to you.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So there is at least some kind of weird religiosity here.
Yeah, I mean, there's definitely an escalation from metaphorical to Jesus and God having
a literal effect on curing you, which suggests that they are real, literally, and if they
are real literally, then his cosmology suggests that the devil is real literally.
I'm not positive that that is an assumption that you can make, because I think that a
lot of people can believe in literalness of God's existence without believing literally
in an antagonist Satan.
Sure, sure.
That's, I agree with you, that's true.
I think the evidence presented so far in 2003 of Alex, though, is such that you can't be
like, I'm guessing his belief in the Bible does not include Satan.
But I also think that you can believe in the literalness of God and not necessarily believe
in the literalness of prayer is a health care plan.
True.
You know, like, I think that there is a difference between those kinds of engagement with religion.
Yeah, absolutely.
And I think you're seeing that Alex is at least clearly in the God is better than single
payer.
Yes.
In 2003, but I still haven't found...
Single payer?
More like single prayer.
Boom.
That's what we do.
I still haven't found enough evidence of literal Satan, so we will keep looking.
Although this episode was just bizarre.
I mean, beyond just the boringness of it, it's very boring.
Just standard ass Bilderberg shit.
Yeah.
But behind that, you have two guys who are, have a lot of appearances of anti-Semitism,
who are the experts that Alex has on to talk about the Bilderberg stuff, which I think
is a problem, and it definitely merits attention.
Yeah.
Next, the other thing that I'm seeing here, bizarrely, 22nd to 27th of May, 2003, Alex
isn't talking about Putin.
No.
It was conspicuous in its absence.
I don't think it means anything, but it's like he would talk about the fucking apartments
and Putin constantly, and on these episodes, it doesn't come up.
It might just be that he had other things to talk about, but.
I mean, I would get distracted too if my guests were notorious anti-Semites and my callers
were oddly pro-monarchy.
I would get tossed out of my regular.
And one guy found an 800 seat Nazi church in the middle of nowhere.
That would toss me from my regular Putin stuff.
Yeah.
Got other fish to fry.
Or at the very least, I'm distracted by those jangling keys.
Sure.
Yeah.
We have a website on Friday, but until then, we have a website and we have a show on Thursday.
Yes we do.
Thursday, July 1st, it's at 9 p.m. at the Lincoln Lodge, there are still some tickets
available.
I will have buttons there.
Ooh.
Probably not the new buttons, but I have some holdover buttons.
Nice.
And if anybody wants to come out, I'll throw a button at you.
We'll get buttons.
Yeah.
You will get, I guarantee, buttons will be tossed at you.
There will be some buttons there.
Yeah, it'll be a good time.
So if you're in Chicago, obviously it's not going to be a live show of our show.
Right.
But it is something that, I think that we will have a feeling of, is there an interest
for a show based on, like if no one comes to this, then I think we'll continue recording
in my apartment.
It does seem like that might be the way to go.
I don't want that to be a threat, but.
No that was a very good, that was a very good plug.
Well done.
Thanks, we're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter, it's that knowledge, go to bed Jordan.
We're on Facebook.
We are on Facebook.
If you would like to download a show, go to, apologies, iTunes, iTunes, I lost my mind
there for a second, iTunes and then find a local charity or bail fund in your area.
We'll be back, but until then, I'm Neo, I'm Leo, I'm DZX Clark, I'm Daryl Rundis, I actually
found Barack Obama's secret Baha'i church in Evanston.
It's actually just the Baha'i temple in Evanston.
It's not secret.
I don't think Obama ever went there.
I just found this really cool building.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan, I love your work.
I love you.