Not.
Knowledge fights.
Dan and Jordan.
I am sweating knowledgebuddy.com.
It's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledge.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're good guys.
Shang.
We are the bad guys.
Knowledgefight.com.
I love you, everybody.
Welcome back, knowledge fight.
I'm Dan.
I'm George.
We're a couple of dudes like to sit around worship at the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are.
Dan, Jordan, quick question for you.
What's your bright spot today? My bright spot today is uh oh, what am I doing? I don't know.
Is it a morning showing? That is what this has become.
Delightful week of celebration.
I don't know.
Celebrations.
Yeah, you can't celebrate a sneak, can you? So we have the interview with reliable sources.
Brian Stelton.
Monday, we have the world exclusive interview with the lawyers, wife Bankston and Bill Ogden.
So funny that we do.
Then Becca Lewis on Tuesday.
But in order for Sneak Week to really be sneaky, sure, there has to be a day where nothing happens.
There has to be a day where nothing to surprise you expect shows the whole week.
Absolutely.
No, we sneaked, we snuck, and we didn't have something on Wednesday.
And do you know what else? When people think we zagged, that's when we're going to Zog, baby.
See, I know that that is a quote from News radio, but I worry because Zog means Zionist occupied government.
Okay, well, yes, that Jimmy James has been ruined.
Yes, there is a different issue.
Yeah, that's true.
So have to put an embargo on that.
Yes.
So Thursday.
Here we are.
Today we're beginning a two parter about the trial time and getting up to speed on a lot of that stuff.
Right.
And then Friday, we cap off Sneak Week with an appearance on the Majority report.
Oh, my God.
What do we say on Cedar? We're so silly.
Yeah.
Long time coming, I think maybe.
I don't know.
I've been looking forward to that.
I have been a big fan of Sam and his work, and so, yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
I'm really excited about each week.
Absolutely.
What a week.
I'm going to sing septopus to Sam the entire time.
You've already told me that.
You're going to have a tough time not doing home movies.
Movies, impressions.
I'm even going to go into Lucy, daughter of the devil.
I'm going to be like, holy shit.
Do you remember when you played the vampire guy and you were like, I forget everything you know about vampire.
You remember that? Yeah.
It's going to be great.
So he's going to like me.
I have thoughts about various interviews.
He's done with academics, authors, debates.
He's done with libertarian.
Right.
He's fucked with Stephen crowder.
You just have voice acting.
I have Brendan Small, and that's it.
Yeah.
There we go.
What's your bright spot? My bright spot is I put it up.
I finished it.
I compiled all of the annoying tweets that I made and I got rid of all the insults and all of the personal tax and all of the anything that isn't at the trial because I wanted to share a disorienting experience with people.
There's going to be way better books written about it that make more sense and that will be enjoyable to read, but you won't get the real experience of being there, which was disorienting and unenjoyable.
I think a lot of people are going to resent the lack of insult.
I think people are going to want those insults.
Yeah.
Well, that's the problem you've cultivated through the live tweeting, where people are like, I know I don't like it.
Here's the problem.
The final draft, 50,000 words.
Dan, I don't know if you recall what I said.
The initial amount of total words I'd written over this time period.
No.
70,000.
Yeah.
20,000.
Cut out.
I know how to take care of things.
$20,000.
Quite a ratio.
Yeah, but it's done.
You can go to my website.
The quiet part loud.
It's the front.
Did you include that whole thing where everyone was saying grapejob to Barn? No, I did not.
Again, no personal tax.
I didn't even mention that grape job barns existed.
All it is, you can go to my website and you can download it as PDF.
Don't pay anything for it.
Don't give anybody anything for it.
Donate, buddy.
Or just read it.
Well, what fun.
Yeah.
For everyone who is wondering, where are those where are those tweets? I'm so sensitive.
Well, in front of me for writing good Twitter, but you had a good tenure at your new job, as you refer to it.
I say I got a gig one time and it is death for me.
It's a funny way to describe eating.
Yes.
For a short period of time.
Yes, I get it.
Because it's hilarious.
It does.
And it is.
And it's sad.
So, Jordan, today, like I said, we're starting to part one of the trial coverage and sort of the surrounding aura.
Indeed.
In some sense, I think the surrounding stuff will be a little bit more in the next episode.
Got you.
But today what we're going to be doing is going over the testimony that Alex gave at the trial, which I didn't expect we were going to cover, because I thought all that stuff was like, you can't make copies of this, but then it's all law and crime.
I guess they just put it out there.
So, yeah.
I mean, it's ours now.
Yeah.
Nothing you can do about it.
Hundreds of thousands of people are watching those videos, so I'm going to go ahead and take it.
Fair use.
Now, that audio.
So we're going to cover Alex's direct questioning from Raynal.
Sure.
And then the cross examination, and then we're going to get into the aftermath of the compensatory damages.
And that's where we're going to leave off.
Okay.
Alex's response to the compensatory damages, waiting for the next day when he will end up in the punitive fix.
Got you.
Okay, so that is what part one will cover and then part two will pick up and sprawl from there.
So this one is far from home.
And then the next one is endgame.
I forgot how these movies are titled.
I haven't seen any of them.
Okay, so yes, good call.
100% perfectly accurate.
Marvel metaphor.
So before we do that, though, Jordan, let's get back to something we haven't done in a while.
Say hello to some new walk.
Yay.
So first objection, non responsive.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Next afternoon podcast.
You inspired me to fact check my local Birch right weirdo in podcast form.
Thank you.
You are now a policywalk.
I'm a policy walk.
Thank you very much.
Next.
Hearing the old technocrat drop makes me feel three years younger.
Thank you so much.
You are now policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Next.
Justin and Tony.
You're going Zimbabwe.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy walk.
I'm apology walk.
I forgot that one.
How much have we forgotten? I thought it was baby, but I still like it.
That was good.
Thank you very much.
Next, it may be easier to just say it's pronounced Mikayla.
My mom was a creative speller.
Thank you so much.
You are now policywalk.
I'm a PolicyWonk.
Thank you very much.
Mikayla.
And angering Alex by being tall at the mall.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Finally, Jordan, we have a technician in the mix.
I have to make that other person feel three years younger.
We use the old draw.
Alright.
But my husband knows the term is policy wonk but still calls it poly wonk.
He's going to be so happy.
He's now a technocrat.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk four star.
Someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop.
Daddy sharp bomb.
Jar Jar Binks has a Caribbean black accent.
He's a loser little kiddy baby.
I don't want to hate black people.
I renounce.
Jesus Christ.
Thank you so much.
Yes, thank you very much.
So now, Jordan, we begin with Alex being sworn in.
And I do think that this isn't going to be a complete play by play of everything that happened.
There's a lot of stuff that I think, honestly, anyone who listens to our show would be like, this is boring, this is that was a lot of the experience of us being in the room for especially his first day of just being like, are you doing an ad read right now? Well, we might include that.
Well, maybe, but Alex is sworn in and he tries to take a piece of paper up to the stand with him, which causes a little problem.
Mr.
Reynolds.
The defense would call Alex E.
Jones.
All right, Mr.
Jones, come stand in front of me, please.
Raise your right hand.
Do you solemnly square or affirm under penalty of perjury, that the testimony you are about to give shall be the truth, the whole truth, and nothing but the truth? I do.
Thank you.
Come have a seat in the witness chair.
There is water and glasses.
You have pretty good volume.
I don't think you'll need to lean into the microphone.
I see that you have a document with you.
I don't know if you were here when I explained to a prior witness who brought documents with them that you can't look at any document for any reason while you're testifying and go on unless one of the lawyers or myself instructs you to do so.
So I'm going to ask you to actually just give it back to Mr.
Reynald until he may think you need it.
Okay.
Did you understand all that? I did, yes.
One of the things that's fun about that is that Alex is so invested in this.
Like, we're teleprompter free, and then he's trying to bring handwritten notes to the stand.
So he remembers his talking points.
I mean, it's the fact that they were handwritten, too.
Come on.
Really? Yeah.
On some level, I get it.
I get the impulse.
Yeah.
I would rather have talking points.
Sure.
No, that's fair.
Instead of just being adrift at sea and having to answer whatever question is asked of me.
Fair.
But yeah, you don't get to do that.
Yeah.
I mean, this wasn't day one of the trials.
No.
Day five.
Yeah.
We've already experienced this Tuesday.
No, this would have been day seven.
Day six.
Yes.
Day six of the trial proper.
Yeah.
Because if you don't count but we had seen for a week everyone come unprepared and then they had a weekend.
Because what we have not discussed is up until this point, you already had Owen Troyer, you already had you already had Becca, you already had Wills zip.
Yeah.
Mr.
Crouch.
Yeah.
And so you'd already had a real contrast in the infowars people and the witnesses that were being called by the plaintiffs in terms of their ability to answer basic questions.
Sure.
Yeah.
And so Alex comes up.
I also didn't include the part where he was scolded for chewing gum and then tried oh, my God.
There were some things that were just kind of like, what do we do? We have some things to talk about.
Let's not get bogged down.
Yes.
We're going to be here a while.
So Reynold comes in with his first question, and one of the things that I think becomes abundantly clear really fast is that Alex does not appreciate the notion of not just being able to ramble.
Right.
Yes.
He was not a fan.
It's one of the things that he has.
It's the most sacred to him and he does not respond well to being told you have to answer questions.
Alex, would you please introduce yourself to the ladies and gentlemen of the jury? I'm Alex Jones.
How are you feeling today, Alex? I actually feel good because I got a chance to, for the first time, say what's really going on.
Instead of the corporate media and high powered law firms manipulating what I actually did.
I want to start by kind of letting the jury know a little bit about your use and where you grew up so they can get to know you better.
Is that okay? Okay.
Before we do that, I just do want to say this on my head.
As I said it many times, I apologize to both the same.
So, Mr.
Jones, one of the instructions I just gave you is that this is not a conversation question.
And the answer so she got the monologue, but not me.
I got it.
And so you have to only answer questions that are asked to you.
So you can see here that in the first question Alex has asked, he's already off track.
He's trying to monologue and control the entirety of the conversation because why wouldn't he think he should be able to? I find it hard to imagine that Renault has had any success ever trying to keep Alex on point, like off the stand.
So why should this be any different? Right at the end, Alex says that it's not fair that he doesn't get to talk, but she got to monologue.
This is in reference to Scarlett Lewis's testimony from just prior to him taking the stand.
And there's a reason why she got to monologue.
As Alex put it, it's because Reynald knew damn well that he wasn't going to object and interrupt her for as much of a shithead as he seems to be.
I don't think Raynall is so detached from his humanity as to deprive Ms.
Lewis of her chance to speak her piece to Alex after all this time and him dodging the moment of having to look her in the face and hear her words.
Truth be told, Lewis probably was a bit off subject at a few points in her testimony.
And if Reynold had objected, there's a really good chance that the judge would have no choice but to refocus the question asked.
But he didn't do that.
And that's what Alex is mad about.
You're not mad that she got to monologue and you don't that your lawyer didn't stop it, right? Yeah.
I mean, it does seem like what is really causing Alex ire is that his lawyer did not badger Scarlett Lewis with questions or interrupt her answers of questions that the plaintiff's attorneys you understand why we're here? Yeah, I think that it would have taken a really cold, cold lawyer objection.
Not responsive to her talking about her son died.
Yes.
That would have been a dark day.
Yeah.
So Alex does want to stress, as he was trying to this sidebar that he was going down, that he apologized and he's sorry and all this, so he attempts an apology here.
Mr.
Jones, have you been wanting to apologize to the plaintiffs in this case for a long time? Yes.
And what would you like to say to them? That I never intentionally tried to hurt you.
I never even said your name until this case came to court.
I didn't even really know you were until a couple of years ago.
When all this started up, the Internet had a lot of questions.
I had questions.
And over that six, seven year period before I got sued or six year period, it's clear you can see the whole progression of us, the few times we covered it, trying to actually find out what happened.
And that's really been my big frustration, is that people have said that I'm personally trying to hurt them, are coming after them when I question every big event.
And a lot of times it turns out that we've not been told the truth.
And a perfect example is today, where they play a 30 or a 1 minute clip.
And I had just done that this morning, and I knew that.
I said, I believe that Scarlett Lewis is real, and she's a really nice person, and she's really a sweet person.
And then I went through and talked about her ex husband, too, and then I said, I believe they're being fed and manipulated.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
I always just wants to power through.
So the clip he's talking about is something we went over on our 711 episode.
Episode 711.
It wasn't an episode about it.
It wasn't in 711 either.
That was the clip of Alex talking about how hesleyn appeared slow and all this.
He's trying to argue that they selectively edited everything.
Right, whatever.
Yeah.
His argument was essentially you didn't play the whole clip.
See, what happened is the first thing I said was, I'm sorry, and then I said that he was slow and that I think he's on the spectrum.
So this is not an apology.
Alex attempting to defend himself by saying that he didn't mean to hurt anyone and he didn't actually even say things that would hurt them to begin with, because people just take things he says out of context and attack him.
This is pathetic, but this is Alex's understanding of an apology.
It's not about recognizing and respecting the pain that other people experience due to your actions.
It's about pretending that you care they were hurt and that it was someone else's fault.
It's cowardly, but it's to be expected.
Yeah.
I mean, if you follow his words, he's essentially saying, basically, you're not smart enough to understand why what I did was actually okay, here are my excuses that you just don't understand.
Like, you're mad at me, but really it's your fault, right? I didn't hurt you.
It's the media lying about the things that I said.
I don't even know who you are.
I never said your name.
Yeah.
A very respectful thing to say in your defamation trial is honestly, I didn't even know who you were.
It doesn't matter to me who might hurt.
Right.
It's almost like he's embassy in the Street Fighter movie a little bit like, wow, you are a real villain here.
The day that I came to your village is the most important day of your life.
For me.
It was Tuesday.
Nothing.
Jesus, man.
That's how you're going to go? Good.
Not great.
So Renault wants to humanize Alex, obviously, and so a part of this is walking through some of his earlier life.
And I didn't cut clips from all of it, but there's some stuff that just seemed like, wow, this doesn't match up at all, right.
The way you guys usually talk.
Yeah, we were in there.
So here's the first of that.
Can you let us know where are you from in Texas originally? First was born in Dallas, then I grew up in a suburb of Dallas called Rockwall.
And how old were you when you moved to Austin? 16.
And can you tell the members of the jury why your family relocated Dallas? My dad sold his general practice and there was too much crime in Dallas.
In Austin safer city.
There's too much crime in Dallas.
Oh, boy.
You lived in Rockwall.
Too much crime in Dallas.
Wealthy suburb.
Apparently, if you watch Alex documentary, it's one of the richest suburbs in the country and everybody's rolling around in Rolls Royces and doing his problem is there is too much wage theft going on.
There was a lot of crime going on in that neighborhood.
Service employees were paid too little.
That's what his main issue was, is that the people he was around were not paying their employees well.
You know what? I respect that.
I wish it was.
Yeah.
I think that he knew better than to do the I grew up in a town where Satanists were trying to recruit me to worshiping the devil because they knew that through psychic powers the devil gave them, I would be important to God's mission in the future.
And I uncovered a drug ring within the Rock Wall police department and they threatened to murder me if I didn't leave town.
I think that maybe he knew that the jury wouldn't take kindly to that.
Or maybe it would paint him in a bad light because it's clearly ridiculous.
Yeah, it would be a little bit like the jury's punitive damages at that point would have to come back with like and he has to wear a straight jacket forever.
If you say that on the stand, punitive damages stop being money.
I think Alex is pretty lucky that this is not one of those performative, judge exactly situations.
Section eight.
Yeah.
So Alex talks about some of his early influences, and this was one of the points where I almost had to leave the courtroom.
How old were you when you first felt that you wanted to be on the air, that you wanted to work in media? When I was about 17, I really liked listening to talk radio.
And I'd grown up with my dad on road trips listening to, like, Larry King when he was still on radio.
And I really liked Larry King on radio and then also on CNN.
And I also liked Howard Stearn.
Thought he was funny.
And I really wanted to be a talk show of you, like CNN, you liked the Clinton News Network.
Please.
This is a strategic answer on Alex's part because he doesn't want to say to the jury that he was brought up listening to and admiring extreme far right demagogues and Christian Identity radio preachers.
He doesn't want to say to the jury that he was a devoted fan of the British Israelite preacher David J.
Smith or how he was a regular listener to the Holocaust denying preacher Tex Mars, whose church Alex has said repeatedly that he attends.
Yeah, he doesn't want to even tell the version of the story that he relayed in his documentary Alex's War, because even that would sound bad to a jury.
Larry King and Howard Stern are largely mainstream touchstones, and they do the sort of shows that Alex wants the jury to think he does.
It's total bullshit.
But it's also very clear why he's presenting his inspiration to get into media this way so the jury doesn't get an accurate sense of what his career has actually been about.
Also kind of makes Alex Lee Moyer's editing choices look even more embarrassing.
The use of swelling music over Alex, telling the tale of how he discovered people bringing the fight to the New World Order on public access and how that was the moment he realized he wanted to get into this field seems particularly dumb now.
Just imagine the same music that she played over Alex saying, I really like Larry King's radio show.
They wanted to host a chat program like his doesn't have the same flair.
Maybe you got played or maybe you wanted to be played.
It is so very funny to me, the idea of having made a documentary and then only days later, here your subject almost completely disavow every single thing in that documentary under oath.
I don't know.
I'm getting Reset Wars vibes in terms of, like I think there was a lot of ramping up to it, and it seems like no one cared.
No one cares at all about that fucking documentary.
I don't know.
I mean, I feel almost like I'm dumb for doing as much work in advance because I kind of thought it would be a little bit more widely discussed and maybe viewed than it was preemptive.
They had some big names pre marketing.
It like the interview with Greenwald.
It feels like that should move the needle somewhat.
Right? And there were ostensibly 2 million followers.
There were a lot of pre orders online which take however you want, I guess.
I don't know.
Anyway, Alex's early show that he did at the beginning of his career, apparently quite different than the current one.
Way different.
And what was the format of your early shows on Austin Public Access TV? It wasn't as conspiratorial or political.
There was some of that because there was some people doing those shows, and I already knew about that information, but it was just all over the map.
It was just really calling shows different topics, different variety shows like card pumpkins on TV on Halloween and have a guy come in with his pet monkey and dances around.
Just fun stuff because I also like Johnny Carson growing up.
Okay, that's complete bullshit.
Maybe Alex did do a bit of goofing off on his show, but it was also straight up conspiracy content.
He and his early public access co host, Jeff Davis, made a documentary together titled Are You Practicing Communism? If that gives you some sense of the vibe he was working with back then.
It's really hard to get your hands on the shows from back then, but the ones I've seen are complete bullshit and conspiracy laden nonsense, and it's super easy to find accounts from people who worked at the station with him back then.
He was a raven conspiracy lunatic.
Even back then, he was an asshole, and no one liked working with him.
That's a big part of why his career took the trajectory he did.
Right.
It would have been more fun if that was like a PSA where it's like, are you practicing your piano lessons? Like, are you practicing your communism? Are you working on your absolutely, yeah.
Practice makes perfect.
Are you going to Communist in Carnegie Hall? Is the question that you should be asking yourself.
Yeah, I tried to watch that documentary.
And how did it go? Well, it's not a documentary.
It's like them sitting at a table complaining about communism.
It's between Two Ferns, sort of, but there's a table.
Sure.
No ferns, right? Yeah.
It just was like, I'm not going to do this.
There was no flair, nothing.
Anti communism is terrible.
But look, man, Alex loved Larry King.
Of course.
Tell us you've told us already about Larry King and about Howard Stern.
Who would you say influenced you artistically in the format and how you did your show then and became the man you are today? I mean, really? I listened to Larry King a lot because my dad listened to him on the radio a lot when I was, like, six, seven.
I'm really sorry.
Larry King.
And then I watch him a lot of nights at home in junior high school.
So I would say more than anybody, larry King.
If Alex's dad listened to Larry King, he was yelling at him.
It was like listening to Larry King and being this fucking communist.
You know what? Honestly, I would almost believe that.
And here's why the Alex's need to interrupt over the TV had to have come from somewhere.
I think it's entirely possible that he did watch his dad just interrupt.
Larry King screaming at the TV all the time.
It's an interesting theory.
I think that could just be a style he developed.
Totally.
I understand.
Low attention span, highly knee jerk reactive, but yeah, you do what you see.
I'm just saying that I'm aging and now I'm recognizing my father's actions in my own and this is entirely about me.
I have no idea what we're talking about.
I can't relate to that at all.
alex touches on his first documentary, and this is a real fun claim.
Did you also start making in order to support Infowars, did you also start making documentaries? I did start making documentaries in 1997.
I made my first documentary, american Destroyed by Design, about the great reset.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
And the different UN documents that were in it.
And I made more than 25 more films after that.
See, this is, like, so indicative of Alex's shit pretending that his first documentary was about the great reset.
Something that didn't become a hot topic in conspiracy circles until 2021, basically.
So this is what he's about.
He's about RET conning.
He takes these things that he yelled about in the past and then applies modern labels and contexts to them in order to make it look like hashtag alex Jones was always right.
Yeah, it's just such bullshit.
You weren't yelling about the great reset.
You were yelling about, like, Agenda 21 and the road in Texas.
The road through what was it? Highway.
Yeah, the north transatlantic North American highway corridor.
Yeah, something like that.
You're yelling about national parks having a sign up in them.
Get off.
It is like, we talked about it with Market Bill just a little bit.
But it is like, you can't really have a jury of Alex's peers out of anybody that doesn't like, how can you say, oh, you can't lie under oath to that? Like, you and I both know that that's a complete lie, but who's going to say it? I don't know if that's a substantive lie to the case.
Totally.
So maybe it's kind of fine for the proceedings of this.
Right, but you're under oath.
I know all that stuff.
I know it's legally all that it is.
But there is a certain part of me that's, like, you have to be able to know that Alex is lying even about that.
Sure.
Yeah.
I agree with that.
I think that this runs into the issue of the separate realities because there's a part.
Of Alex that probably believes absolutely that I was talking about the great reset.
When I was three years old, I had a dream about the great reset.
The Lord spoke it to me.
How does Narcissism work and its effects on whether or not you think you're being truthful? And that's something that would be difficult to unpack.
But I would say that, oath or no oath, you're a fool if you think Alex is ever going to actually give you truthful answers, tricks and direct answers.
Yes.
So we get back to talking about the time of Sandy Hook on Alex's show, right? And what was his show like? What was the environment at Infowars? I believe I recall.
Can you tell us what the sort of different segments are that would appear on a given day at Infowars circuit 2012? There was my four hour radio show that in 2012 was just a webcam on me for people that wanted to watch it online.
And then it was just me on a desk or camera.
That was it.
Basically, the primary goal of Alex's answer here is to downplay his own relevance and the size of his operation in 2012.
He wants the jury to think that though he's a big famous boy now, back then he was really just mom and pop talk show.
Unfortunately, he's lying.
He didn't just have a webcam on a desk at that point.
He had two studios, each with multiple camera angles available at any point.
He also had more than just his show being broadcast daily, since the Infowars Nightly News was in existence at that point.
The Nightly News started in 2011, and it contained a bunch of content that's relevant to this very lawsuit, like instances of Rob Do covering Sandy Hook.
Alex knows all this, but the goal is to create the perception that he really wasn't that big back then.
So it couldn't have been him that was so influential in getting the Sandy Hook conspiracies rolling and causing the harm that was done to Neal and Scarlett.
It's a fraud.
And one of the telltale signs is that pretending a show he produced all the way to 2017 doesn't exist.
It's nonsense.
Never heard of it before.
What's this? I've never heard of it before.
I was thinking about this.
I can't think of any testimony, real or fictional, I have ever seen that may be more chuck filled with absolute non truths.
Like, you were saying that's because in this world, I don't think we're ever dealing with a truth or a lie that doesn't exist.
We're dealing with both and neither simultaneously.
Yeah.
What's convenient and useful to me is the truth is the truth, and I believe it under a lie detector.
And I think that it's bizarre because Narcissism for Alex works in this way of, like, all right, when I need to inflate my self.
Right.
In 2012, I had the biggest show in the world.
I had 100 million every world leader on the planet to my show.
Ron Paul loved me, and he was the rightful president.
Oh, something I owned the tea party.
He did run the tea party.
He did explicitly say that.
And then the narcissism here is that he needs to not be very big because it's important for him to not have the grand title of the thing that is negative.
Right.
What is that hallmark thing of psychopaths? Is that the manipulating based on what people think want to hear in any situation? Is that one of those things like that? Yeah, that sounds right.
So this next clip is where Alex gets to talking about how talk show hosts are judged.
And this is bizarre.
At the time 2012, how did you all source or how did you source the stories that you wanted to cover during that segment of your talk radio? 95% of what we were covering was mainstream news going, look, they're saying this.
Do you believe it or what do you make of this? It's that kind of thing is that we would simply do what talk radio does.
That's what talk radio does.
That's what Larry King did, is stack the news articles, talk about what's going on, what people are saying.
Ask callers, what do you think of that? Do you buy that? What do you think is going to happen next? Are there really WMDs in Iraq? Are they lying about it? And then the talk show hosts make their predictions about what they think.
And then the talk radio listeners basically keep note and see who's the most accurate.
And it becomes a big game to see who has made the best predictions and things like that.
And so that kind of lends itself to the very nature of a soapbox, is people speculating that's the nature of people going to a park and standing up at Speaker's Corner in London for 600 years and giving their opinion.
That's what free speech is.
Okay, that is one of the most absurd descriptions of, like, five different things I've ever heard.
I mean, it got into, like, town criers.
Exactly.
Yeah.
He thinks that his audience is sitting there with a pen and a pad.
His prediction? No, it's like they have baseball scorecards.
They're like, oh, okay, Alex hit a single on this one.
Draw one line.
Holy shit, Rush Limbaugh hits one out of the park.
I mean, look, from the time that we've been doing this show and the predictions that we've seen from him, if anyone was doing this and talk show hosts were judged by this, he would be out of business.
He would be an outlier.
Yeah.
That's true.
He's fortunate that no one is keeping a pen and paper.
Yeah.
If that is true, god damn.
The world would have to have been destroyed multiple times over by now in order for his predictions to have any decent track record absolutely.
Cities in America would be constantly getting nuked.
Right.
The globalists would be starving everyone.
We would all be dead of a plague of locusts years ago.
Right.
And this is how Alex always kind of gets into your head.
It's like, that is so insane that you almost forget he said that free speech is really just a dude standing on a box in the corner in London screaming for 6 hours.
But back then, the town crier that you listen to, you judge by their predictions.
Yes.
But then you judge their predictions by how long they stayed in the stocks.
I think that might actually be a better situation for us.
Man, you have enough bad predictions, you go in the stocks for a week.
Yeah, I think that is you're, right.
That is one of the tools of Alex's absurdity.
Yeah.
There's constant heightening.
There's so many layers of absurdity.
Yeah.
So you're like, wait, I can't deal with part A.
Part B is part C is hilarious.
Part D what are you talking about? What is happening? So in the conversation about sources, Alex says this now most of the time though, I say, I want this person, I want that person.
I'm more in control of the guests that I have.
But in the past, we let more things driven by the Internet and by Fortune and HM.
But in every case I've had problems has been a curse.
I'm not thanking everybody that's on there, but I told my producers, do not touch it when it's on there because it's just a death and it causes nothing but problems.
It's bullshit that Alex is saying there's a moratorium on this kind of sourcing, like some things on Fort Chan.
But if you want to take this seriously at all, then what Alex needs to do is take a real hard look in the mirror, take an inventory of the things that he said based on Fortune posts, and retract all of it.
He needs to go back and look at the Soros antifa contract.
He needs to go back and find all of these things and really wrestle with like, okay, if you now know this to be a completely unreliable source, you need to figure out what parts of your mythology, what parts of your worldview are solely informed by that and work to get those out.
Make sure that people don't still believe them because otherwise you're still using Fortune as a source.
Essentially he doesn't do that because those things that are based on Fortune nonsense are too important to you.
Right? Yeah.
No.
If you find out a single cop used to be a drug dealer for ten years, every single case that that cop worked on needs to be reevaluated and thrown out or whatever.
So it's the same thing.
It's the same fundamental principle.
Yeah.
It's hard work.
It is very hard.
The reason Alex isn't going to do it justice is you don't do it you don't like what the result is going to be, it's not going to be good for him.
No, because then you have to find another way to try and prove that Soros has antifa contracts to burn down cities, which is a real big part of your whole bullshit opposition to the Black Lives Matter protest, while you're at least one of the ways that you pretended it wasn't based on any flagrant racism.
Right, but, hey, don't go ahead and do that because it's too complicated.
It would take a while.
Daria didn't even like finding the things that she was asked about for two years.
Well, Wikipedia.
Well, she did like finding that.
So Alex doesn't like the news anymore.
It's not surprising.
And more and more I don't really follow the news model of covering the news.
In the past.
I did.
We still do it a lot.
But now, I mean, I just talk about philosophy and the big picture and then have some guests on the show has gotten more Christian because I'm a Christian, but as things progress while things happening in the world, I'm moving more towards doing a self help life experience than the political show.
Like, I've been trying to segue out of this just because I think we have to change individuals, kind of like Scarlet was saying earlier, more than we're going to change the world, we can't change ourselves, that we're ever able to change the world.
And I've made a lot of mistakes, and I've learned a lot in that process.
And I've also learned how the corporate media is able to completely manipulate a story once you're caught in it and then manipulate other people.
And if anything, I want to teach people about how that process works because they say I'm the mastermind to figure it out, manipulate people.
And I didn't have any understanding of it coming.
And then now I've seen it from the inside, the way this stuff goes on.
And again, I think only getting the individual awake and aware and not under his control is the way to beat it.
And you can't just cover a bunch of news and get somebody to understand that.
You can't be told about the matrix.
You got to see it.
He's on the stand.
Yeah.
This is Rambling.
Look, on the one hand, I guess he's just saying what you kind of could tell if you watch his show.
Sure.
And that is that he's kind of pivoting into something that is less grounded in reality.
Televangeli.
Yeah, stuff like that.
You don't have to pretend you have proof for things.
You can lie about the Bible all day and people really don't care.
Yeah, sure.
I think that getting into philosophy in the big picture is a generous way to say yelling about the devil.
There's one way, but yeah, I think this is true.
Alex is giving up the pretense of being about news and documents and all this because it never was real to begin with.
Exactly.
I think what's interesting about that is that this is something that I noticed throughout Alex's testimony, is that Alex was clearly the best coached, because I really don't even know if Dario and we're given instructions on what questions Raynall was going to ask me.
Right.
But Reynold was clearly giving Alex prompts for these answers that they had talked about because they don't look as terrible as the real ones do.
Right? Yeah.
And then Alex just can't not be Alex.
So he gives his prepared remarks, and then you can see him kind of scramble and then start rambling off and on.
All of a sudden, he's like and so that's why the Democrats are and you're like, no, you are doing so good.
Yes, but that's like, what Alex wants.
It's what he wants to get out on the stand.
He's just got to do it.
He can't stop himself.
So part of the reason that he can't stop himself is because he's just over prepared.
How many hours a day are you on the air? I'm on the air about 4 hours a day.
And since when have you been on the air? About 4 hours a day.
I've been on the air 4 hours a day.
And in order to prepare for those 4 hours that you're going to be on the air every day well, let me ask you this.
How many days a week? I'm on the air six days a week.
So in order to prepare for 4 hours a day six days a week, how many hours per day do you spend on prep for your show? I spend about 2 hours at night and about 2 hours in the morning, and then I do some research in the afternoon.
This is a far cry from the 16 hours a day you're studying.
The Globalist really did seem like he was overplaying his hand, and now it seems like he's downplaying it, huh? Yeah, it seems like on air, I do literally nothing but read Globalist white papers and documents.
All of their dirty laundry breathing that are filthy.
Filthy dossiers, not even dirty.
I'm dreaming reading these documents.
Exactly.
Yeah.
I do about 2 hours of the morning, maybe 2 hours at night.
It's busy.
But also, I think that this is a lie.
I really don't even know what this is also being used for, because here's why I can explain it.
Well, go for it.
Like, him saying what he says on his show would be laughable.
The jury would never believe that.
It would be something like yeah, right, sure.
What are you doing for 16 hours? Right? You're high.
That's fair.
But the two to 4 hours is believable.
Right.
That is a believable amount of work.
You do 4 hours of a show, you do an eight hour work day.
Call it a day.
It's kind of what you would expect for somebody who's doing a job.
Sure.
More or less.
Right.
And you don't want him to look like I just shoot from the hip entirely.
Sure.
Because then there's an approach that is structurally irresponsible to what ended up happening.
Right.
But at the same time, you don't want to make it look like he does nothing but do the show.
Because first of all, it's unbelievable.
Right.
Second of all, if so, then you should have vetted Wolfgang Halbeck.
You would think, if you're working hours a day at the time.
Yeah, I mean, I meant more for like the defenses case, because part of what they're arguing is clearly Alex spent so much time on air, what, he spent like five minutes telling these people all of this stuff, that kind of thing.
There's one 10th of 1%.
Right.
But it could also be that, look, he works so hard, these things are going to fall through the cracks.
He says, 95% of my time is I'm not doing anything like this, that kind of thing.
But either way, the problem is he's already been found guilty of doing the thing.
Sure.
So it can't really reduce the damages, can it? Or is it just like, see, he's a down home country guy.
I think that's a large part of it.
You think that means more like humanizing him? That kind of thing.
Okay.
And the mom and pop aspect of it.
Sure.
Because it's just a small propaganda outlet.
That's true.
He just puts his payoff no nightly News at this point.
There's a limited amount of employees that he has and the perception is kind of making it more normal as opposed to the absurdity that is.
And that continues even into this next clip, which actually just made me really sad.
2015.
I don't have the exact days.
Alex knows damn well that The Nightly News started in 2011, but that would make his operation look much more professional if he were to be aware of that.
So it's pretty important that it started well after the period of Sandy Hook.
Even worse is that Alex has completely forgotten about his original companion show, the Infowarrior, featuring Jason Burmese.
That show was on in like 2009 and really, Burmis did so much for Infowars in those early days, in that era.
This omission is insulting.
In fact, in court I poked you and said he forgot about Burma.
You sure did.
Again, though, it's definitely not in Alex's best interest to present the image that he was producing other shows on Infowars at this point in his career.
Like I said, this is a mom and pop propaganda outlet.
Absolutely.
And it can't possibly have been the big bogeyman that led to so much pain.
No, he wasn't the CEO of maybe what Owen would have to eventually describe as a mainstream media TV studio.
No, I mean, it goes all directions.
We're a small thing.
No other shows.
I put in an honest nine to five day at work.
But then, of course, there was actually another question about the working on admin stuff.
Sure.
And he was like, yeah, I do extra hours on that.
Right.
So of course he does extra hours on that.
He does nine to five.
But still, folksy, and also the money.
Let's talk a little bit about where you get your funding.
I had some corporate sponsors when I was against George W.
Bush and the war.
Sorry, what? We lost a lot when we ran to war, but we still had some big ones.
We had like, car companies, clothing lines, everything.
We were making a lot of money to expand the operation going back to about 2005, up to when Obama got in.
And then being anti war was not allowed anymore for whatever reason.
I wasn't anti Obama.
I was antiwar.
So I continue with being antiwar.
We lost all our sponsors.
I guess Alex is just forgetting about his decades long business relationship with Midas Resources and his couple of attempts to branch out into selling his audience to multilevel marketing scams.
That one was fun.
How he took a bunch of money from Mike Lindell and my pillow pretty recently.
Sure.
And his affiliate links with my Patriot Supply.
Wow.
Sure, these aren't respectable sponsors like a car company, but it's pretty important to pretend that Alex had no institutional support around the time of Sandy Hook.
There was nothing.
It was just him in the wilderness.
See this? And he's lies.
So much for having his principles.
This is why you have to tell people you took one.
And you go with Diamond Gusset and you say, we took one sponsor and they couldn't even get anybody's.
Jeans.
Right.
Diamond Gusset jeans.
And then we were done self funded from there on out.
I think it would be really difficult to pretend that Diamond Gusset decided not to sponsor Alex's show because he was against Obama.
Yeah, that one might be tough.
Anti NAFTA commercial.
I do like his bullshit on this one.
I was too anti war like a thing that people would believe him saying, where to hide your gun? We don't want to be involved.
Sure.
Anyway, Alex decides that maybe a good idea would be to try and red pill the jury.
Yeah, he did do that.
This is one of a couple of them.
Here we go.
Well, take that clip earlier.
There they are.
At the beginning of the clip, I say, I believe Charlotte Lewis is real.
I believe her son died.
I'm very sorry.
And they cut that off the front, and then they cut me saying I'm sorry off the end.
And they brought a real clip, but it's synthetic to try to see what and I hope you get to see the real clip and then you'll figure out everything else that's been going on.
You'll see all the bullshit, man? Yeah.
That was a moment where I was like, holy shit, this can't be allowed to stand.
There were so many times where it was like he was trying to argue that, listen, you and I both know what this is really about to the jury.
Like he's saying to the jury like, hey, listen, I know you know that all this glitz and court is nonsense.
Watch the clips in this.
Absolutely.
You'll see that I'm right to convince them, like, listen, you're going to be one of us at the end of this trial.
He believes that? Yeah.
It's crazy.
This is a tough way to become an info warrior.
Trial by fire in the crucible you have accidentally enlisted.
Oh boy.
Yup.
So another moment that I found particularly distasteful is when he started talking about his products.
Do you sell vitamins? Yes.
Are your vitamins? FDA certified.
No, they're not.
Why not? The FDA has no trouble working over any nutraceuticals.
Not the ones at Whole Foods, not the ones at GMC, and not ours.
And ours are privately labeled top brands that are sold at Whole Foods GNC.
We have a made by the top lab recognized in the United States.
All we use put our label on it so we know it's triple tested the highest quality.
And that's why people love it because it is the best out there.
And I'll give it to Whole Foods and I'll give it to GMC and others.
They got molly pirates.
There's all sorts of crap you can buy at a gas station out there.
That's not what ours is.
under oath.
I'd like to tell you that the 4 July special is still going.
I am so mad that I wasn't allowed to laugh at the moment.
He was like, we buy our PQQ from the Japanese.
Holy.
Everybody in the courtroom is going to blow what? The Japanese, everyone, everyone knows that the Japanese do not sell their PQQ to just anybody.
What are you talking about? What is happening right now? And the way you said it, the way he delivered it too, like holy shit, I'm going to blow their minds.
Yeah.
God damn, what an insane person.
Yeah, that really threw me for a loop.
Wild.
And you know that he had to have given Reynald that question to prompt him to sell.
Well, no, I don't think so.
Maybe in Alex's head.
Okay.
I would imagine that Raynall believed that the set up of the question was to facilitate exploring Alex's revenue sources in as much as he sells vitamins.
And people look down on him because of it, but they're actually good.
I bet that is the thrust of the question in the attorneys mind.
Right? Not that Alex is going to talk about getting PQQ from Japanese.
Right.
See, this is where I feel like trying to apply the rules of normal logic to what's going on is because it's clear that Raynall thinks something is true and Alex thinks something is true.
And despite the fact that they're supposed to be on the same team, it is not the same thing.
I think that's probably a fair assessment, but then again, we're kind of trajection speculation.
We're on the outside.
I get it.
Sustained.
Yeah.
So here Alex Blies.
Let's discuss, for example, email.
I know when we look to comply with the discovery, which we comply with, it was over 10 million that they had a search that was still in the inbox unopened.
So it was 10 million unopened and a few hundred thousand opened.
So Alex has said that he complied with discovery, which is going to be a problem later.
Oh, yeah, I'll do it immediately later.
Because he says something else.
going back to.
I want to ask you a question.
that really depends on you, Mr.
Vincent, whether you think I need to hear them now or later.
I'm worried.
we're going to take a break.
So Mark has stood up and said that we need to make a contemporaneous motion.
Yeah.
It's because Alex cannot say that he or his company are bankrupt in this part of the trial that they're in at this stage.
That's a claim that he could make in the portion about net worth, which is separated from the compensatory damages phase of the proceedings.
But it would also probably be inappropriate at that point since it's not true.
This is why Mark asked to make these motions.
Alex has now said that he's bankrupt and that he complied with discovery in front of the jury, which are both deeply inappropriate things for him to do.
Can't do it.
He raises this concern, mark does.
And that leads to Judge Gamble dismissing the jury and then saying this.
I remember today watching part of Hesley's testimony when I was coming here and him talking about the bankruptcy.
So I thought that was totally fine.
Mr.
Jones, stop making okay, just stop.
Yes, he is confused.
Oh, yeah.
And then this is the last clip from day one.
And I think that this was something that was pretty cathartic for a lot of folks.
Mr.
Jones, you may not say to this jury that you comply with discovery that is not true.
You may not say it again.
You may not tell this jury that you are bankrupt.
That is also not true.
You may have filed for bankruptcy.
I don't know that.
But I've heard that it doesn't make a person or a company bankrupt.
You're already under oath to tell the truth.
You've already violated that oath twice today.
Just those two examples.
It seems absurd to instruct you again that you must tell the truth while you testify.
Yet here I am.
You must tell the truth while you testify.
This is not your show.
You need to slow down and not take what you see as opportunities to further the message you're wanting to further and instead only answer the specific and exact question you have been asked.
No.
Asides the comments about discovery, the comments about the larynx or whatever it was, the comments about bankruptcy, none of those were responsive to questions.
They were just you abusing my tolerance and making a side for the to read improperly and in these two cases, untruthfully.
Do you understand what I have said? Yes or no? Do you understand what I have said? Yes.
I believe what I said was true.
Yes, you believe everything you say is true, but it isn't.
Your beliefs do not make something true.
That is what we're doing here.
Just because you claim to think something is true does not make it true.
It does not protect you.
It is not allowed.
You are under oath.
That means things must actually be true when you say them.
Don't talk.
You understand what I have said? I do understand.
The don't talk there is so intense.
Yeah.
I believe what I said was true.
And the response to that is at the crux of why debate with someone like Alex is pointless.
There is a complete disconnect from any objectivity, any belief in a reality that exists outside of what you want to be true.
Right.
And that is hard in a courtroom setting.
Yeah.
I mean, we've said before that any communication begins with the definition of terms kind of thing, but that cannot be possible.
If somebody is speaking bird while you're trying to speak English, you can't be like, oh, okay, cheap.
Cheap means no, it's just not going to happen.
Yeah, you can't do it.
I can.
I can talk to birds matter.
I mean, it is satisfying to hear somebody have to be like, listen, objective reality is real.
I don't know how to like she's flabbergasted by the idea that that needs to be introduced into court.
I have to introduce to you bedrock concepts of object permanence.
Is this a desk? Tell me what is and is not for you so we can continue.
Don't speak.
Exactly.
I was subject to this as well, the notion of Alex being under oath in the first deposition that came out.
There's a lot of people who are excited about the idea that Alex is finally going to not be able to lie.
Right.
And I myself was intrigued by the possibility.
Maybe.
And I think through.
Watching them and engaging with the trial as it proceeded, I was not expecting the same things that a lot of people might have out of this trial.
Right.
And I feel for the judge, for sure, having to preside over this is an impossible task.
And the notion that I think a lot of people are entering this with or the perception is that this trial doesn't exist in the context of the case that preceded it.
You see her being kind of annoyed, and it's because Alex has pulled this shit over and over and over and over again.
I think in one interview that I did, I can't remember who it was with, but I made a point that she looks like she's pissed off, but she's being so patient.
The context of this is missing.
If you only watch the trial.
Yeah.
And if you only watch the trial, I could understand coming away from it with the perception that she's not giving Alex an inch or whatever, but there's a reason, and that's unfortunate that there's not a previously on before the trial, and it is such a thing where she is doing such a great job because she is giving so much preferential treatment to the defense.
And let me try to explain that better.
That sounds like you.
Right.
So if Alex was a normal person, the fourth time you tell them they can't lie on the stand, there has to be some consequences.
That's when you bring out the stocks.
Exactly.
Do you know what I'm saying? But a normal person would never let it get that far.
So we don't even know how to deal with this, because if you do that, that's what he wants.
He wants you to say, oh, I have to go to jail for lying.
They're locking me up for telling the truth.
Right.
That's what you're going for.
Like, hey, Alex, why don't you put that bumper sticker on your mouth? For real? Absolutely.
Just talk.
So there's just this constant push and pull between her being like, I have to treat you like a screaming, whiny baby, and at the same time, I have to treat this like we're in an actual courtroom.
Yeah, you have to be treated like a screaming, whiny baby because that's what your behavior is.
Exactly.
And at the same time, you have to be treated like an adult because you're facing adult consequences for your adult actions.
And yes, it's a difficult position to be in.
I'm not jealous of that.
There's a lot that she wouldn't have ever allowed the plaintiffs to get away with legally simply because she's like, you're adult.
I have to hold you to a standard that I'm not holding these fourth graders to and that she did give them that preferential treatment is both, like, starkly unfair and yet at the same time, the only way to have this trial.
Well, to be totally fair, I don't know if it's appropriate to call it preferential treatment, but gave a lot of patients a lot of wide birth.
Sure.
All right.
I'm not going to hold you in contempt for clearly lying under oath, for doing the thing that we hold people in contempt for.
Right.
There was a lot of generous approach to punishing Alex.
And he still couldn't operate within that space.
He couldn't do it.
So we go to the second day now, because this is where they took the break for the day.
It was about 05:00.
Right.
And so Alex returns under oath, and there's still the direct questioning.
Raynal is still giving him questions.
And unfortunately, the law and crime video of this is missing the first ten minutes or so.
And so the beginning of this is establishing that Alex kind of, like, had less connection with those weirdos than maybe he actually did.
Right.
This is the part where he's trying to say that he didn't know Steve or Wolfgang, especially not the Kraken.
Steve under the bus pretty hard.
Real quick.
I would not be happy if I was steve reached out for comment.
Steve on the subject, which is funny, because in the first week of the trial, steve patentic was one of the names that Raynall brought up to Becca being like, whenever he was on his array of, do you think this person's a racist? Do you think this person's a racist? Do you think CVP's name come up as, like, a defendable name along with Stefan Molyneux? It was absurd.
Is Stefan Molyneux racist? Yes.
He said so real loud.
It's, Steve.
Pichenic a racist.
Weird feelings about Jewish people.
Hate them.
So the beginning portion of this is really trying to downplay the connections and Alex's associations with the major players, and some of them, I think, are kind of like, you could actually get away with this.
I don't think him and James Tracy had that much connection.
Sure.
I can see that.
And I think Alex should be hanging his hat far more on the fact that Paul Joseph Watson's interview with James Tracy, the initial one was a little bit adversarial.
Yeah.
Maybe not as much as an actual responsible journalist would.
Sure.
Paul did push back on the idea that there were actors.
Right.
In the same way the court grades on a curve for the fifth graders, paul has proven himself to be in 7th grade strong.
So Steve does come up here, and Alex has an interesting perception on what he did during that time.
You interviewed Steve Pachanic about the story.
Why did you pick him? Did you reach out to him? Did he reach out to you? How did that I reviewed the video, but it was a few weeks ago.
I believe he was on other subjects, and I believe it came up, and then I think I argued with him about it being totally staged.
Sound hard to believe.
This isn't really accurate.
Alex didn't argue with Steve but it would be a mischaracterization to say that he gave Steve a full backing in his claims.
Right.
Alex was interested in the theories and was like, oh, we got a top expert saying it's fake.
But he didn't really commit to it in that interview.
And Steve was on for something else.
He was pretending to be Alex's on the scene reporter in the Demilitarized Zone because Alex was trying to drum up panic about how North Korea was going to start a nuclear war.
Oh, God.
I remember that.
He said he was in Korea.
He said he was inside hanging out with soldiers from both sides of the country of Korea, from Florida.
He claimed that.
I have no evidence.
He might have no, I think that there is a really decent chance that he was on a vacation to South Korea, because I have seen some pictures that he posted of him in various all right.
Touristy places.
Well done.
I'll give you that one.
That's possible.
And then he just pretended he was at the DMZ.
All right.
I'm not doing DMZ, but I'll give him vacation.
Yeah, I think that's possible.
Okay.
So in this course of questioning, I think that Alex the goal that he had was to present this image that his life was really in trouble around the time that Sandy Hook happened.
Poor me.
Yeah.
Can you tell us what led you to have Wolf Bang How Big on in 2014? He was on a lot of shows, and he had a group of bullet points, and my producer set him up all the shows, so I had him on at the time.
What, if anything, else, was going on in your life? My family was falling apart.
I was so weird.
Attempt to paint a picture of, like, if you weren't getting divorced, you wouldn't have booked Wolfgang How Big on your show? Yeah, that's weird.
This got weird.
Yeah.
This whole section where his whole Woe is me thing was I know that they wanted it to come off as though he was, like, a person who was also suffering, but it really just came off more like, are you going to do this here? Yeah, it was strange.
And he also tries to blame Steve more, which, if I were Steve, I would not appreciate.
And I would probably attack Alex because you're a crazy old man, and you got nothing to lose.
Why not? We've had a video received in evidence of you stating your belief at that time that no one died at Sandy Hook, that the whole thing was fake.
Do you understand, as you sit here today, how crazy that is? I have said before that there have been so many lies and so many things in the past, and I was under a lot of pressure.
And I truly when I said those statements, when I say something, I mean it, except for what my wife totally stays at that point, and I was basing that off of, really, Steve Hochinic, who has been a very prestigious person.
You understand now that it was absolutely irresponsible to do that.
It was.
Especially since I met the parents.
And it's just 100% real.
As I said on the radio yesterday, and as I said here yesterday, it's 100% real.
And the media still ran with lies that I was saying it wasn't real on air yesterday.
It's incredible.
They won't let me take it back.
They just want to keep me in the position of being with Sandy Hookman.
My son got confronted yesterday.
Objection.
Speculation is what the media wants.
Mr.
Jones is just a test being on the show in a game.
What is me? Alex is the real victim here.
Although I think Steve needs to get on YouTube and cut a video about Alex.
Something throwing him under the bus.
Yeah, he wants to be the one the media claims the Sandy Hook man.
Yeah.
Come on.
Come on, Steve.
Wow.
Start a public battle.
That would be great for both of them.
Yeah, but mostly for me.
But then who's David Nike going to side with? Boy, I feel like it's all old dudes against Alex.
Okay.
Old dudes against Alex's.
Young guards.
Shirts versus skin.
I would like to see David Knight and Steve Bochanic reach Dayton.
That would be nice.
Desire to spill the tea on Alex.
A final team up of grumpy old men.
Three also kind of thing.
By the way, is this the first time that Daytone and spill the tea have been used at the same time? I don't know.
I don't know.
The French had a lot of things to say, correct? What? No, that's going off the rail.
This is a testimony worthy of this trial.
So Alex says something about his realization that Sandy Hook was real in this next clip, and I found this deeply troubling at the end or at the middle of 2015.
In July 2015, you stopped info were stopped covering Sandy Hook.
Yes.
Why did you stop? Because Halbig was saying that I was involved in Sandy Hook because I wouldn't have him on.
And I started finding out that some of the things that the anomalies they had put forward weren't true.
And I had just ended my divorce and just kind of got my head cleaned up and stopped drinking for a while and realized that it probably did happen and there was a good chance I was wrong.
So I started basically trying to walk it back long before I got sued because I wasn't sure that I was right anymore.
Not everything's a false flag.
Not everything is staged.
So this is disturbing because there does seem to be a pattern of Alex discussing his drinking as it relates to his actions involving Sandy Hook.
We've seen it in an interview and now under oath, and honestly, it's indicative of a very serious substance abuse problem.
Drunk or sober.
Alex is an asshole and deserves the consequences of his actions, but I want to draw sharp focus to the difference in how Alex talks about the issue depending on his surroundings.
Here in court, Alex is discussing his realization that Sandy Hook actually happened about some time in 2015.
There's absolutely no prompt for him to bring up that he'd stopped drinking for a while as an explanation for his supposed period of clarity, but he does, which leads me to believe that it means something to him.
I don't think that it's true, but I do believe that he probably was going through a lot and stopped drinking for a while around the end of 2015.
This is all being said in service of humanizing Alex and minimizing the things that he did.
He was going through a lot and was drinking a ton, but once he got sober, he realized that he was wrong and changed his behaviors.
Except in reality, he didn't.
He was still doing his show wasted years past this point, and he didn't change his behavior in any meaningful way.
He still just ran with bullshit stories from bullshit sources and defame people regularly.
But he wants the perception to be that this was just a bad pocket in his life when all these negative influences led him to drink and his judgment was weakened.
He doesn't want the jury to know that he got right back to the heavy drinking and bullshitting with Steve Patanick basically the next week, because that kind of cheapens whatever fake display of penitents he's trying to put on here.
But the other time Alex discussed his drinking in relation to Sandy Hook was a lot different.
In the Glen Greenwald Q and A, alex was joking about how he defamed grieving parents and caused immeasurable pain in their lives by saying that he didn't know what he was doing and drank a bottle of vodka that day.
It wasn't a person expressing this as a negative thing.
It was Alex trying to appear cool because he wanted to impress the cool kids like Greenwald who can give them access to a new audience.
I find this dynamic deeply upsetting, and the only conclusion I can come to is that Alex was drinking on air a lot during this stretch and that he probably has a way bigger problem than even I think, and I have been chastised for begging people in his life to get him help a bunch in the past.
That's true.
Anyway, a lot of this falls on deaf ears to me in a courtroom setting.
I would take him more seriously if he took the tone that he did in the Q and A while on the stand, but that's not going to happen because there's no cool kids to impress there.
Yeah, but if he was on the stand, he's like, I drank a bottle of vodka.
I would be like, all right, this is interesting.
Being an asshole consistent how do you say that in a courtroom? How do you do that? Because to me, what you just said is, nah, come on, it wasn't that bad.
Whenever I hit him, I was drunk driving.
Right.
I don't know how you say that in a courtroom in a situation that is ostensibly you also say that you believe it's 100% real, but you are only drunk driving because you're in an ugly divorce.
Exactly.
But even then, you're saying it's really his ex wife's fault.
You're saying that you said that when you were drunk, and now you're saying that it's 100% real.
Are you drunk or are you sober? And does it matter? If that's your reasoning here, then it doesn't matter.
When they reported it was 100% true.
There's a part of me that's like, well, was he drunk? Because that doesn't mean yeah, right.
Then what? It means the same amount either way.
Right.
It's just a way for him to contextualize his actions by looking at his past self as the drunk self.
Exactly.
And that's not me.
No, that can be definitely true for people who get help.
Sure.
I'm not saying that who you are when you're in your addiction is necessarily who you have to for the rest of your life.
Sure, recovery is possible and all that, right.
But Alex has not done any of that stuff.
And so him trying to pretend like this past self is somebody that I own up to being but it is not characteristic of me.
It's a false perception.
It's an abuse of people's understanding of absolute abuse problems.
Yes.
Mike Tyson on his fucking show a month ago or whatever.
No, I mean, part of listen, you do have to own up to consequences for your behavior regardless of whether you are an addict or not.
That's part of recovery.
That's part of what it is.
And he's not even owning up to his behavior in a fucking courtroom.
Right.
Yeah.
Because all this is ingenuine and just an attempt to feel less bad about himself.
Absolutely.
This whole situation is not about the parents for him.
It is entirely about him trying to feel good about him.
Yeah.
And trying to make rationalizations for things.
So the crack in comes up.
Dan Bodandy.
Alex definitely does not want to be associated with him, which makes sense.
Yeah.
During that time, there was a reporter working there's, a gentleman who at least we've had yeah, you shouldn't have said reporter.
Remember at some point for info wars named Dan Vedandi? Are you familiar with that name? Yes.
Can you tell us who he is? He was a part time reporter.
We're supposed to say that it was a really nice guy, but we were being more comedy based part of the show then.
And so Rob's, like, this guy is like a Howard Stern character, and so we hired him to do some funny stuff that he wanted to do, serious stuff.
Oh, man, he's like your whack pack.
So the comedy that Dan Vidanti was doing was things like going to that foyer hearing with Wolfgang Halbig.
Hilarious.
Hilarious, hilarious.
Or like when he interrupted the Boston bombing, the press conference police were giving while the Zarnett brothers were still on the loose and unidentified.
Right.
But at least he didn't say that he was specifically harassing people.
He said he was being a hilarious jokester.
Right.
I mean, look, this is such bullshit for every reason.
Oh, man, so many reasons.
And Alex saying that he didn't approve of this stuff.
Go back and listen to those Boston bombing episodes where he's like, over the moon and just, like, celebrating Dan Bodandi interrupting this press conference and yelling infowars.com.
Yes, you approved of all of it.
You're making a joke of serious things.
That's what you were doing with him, and you just don't want to own up to the pain it caused.
Yeah.
So this whole defense has largely circled around the idea that you have to watch the full clips.
So at this point, Raynal puts on a very long video of Alex's.
Now, the things that are a problem here, some of them we're going to get into, but also the video includes Alex repeating the claim that Wolfgang Halbig correct.
Said so.
This is supposed to be his big apology.
At the same time, he's like, why did the school have no traffic online? Yeah, okay.
You know all this isn't true.
Yeah, it was wild for them to insist on playing the full clip.
The full clip of which was more damning than the shorter clip.
Yeah, I would argue so outside of just the repetition of Wolfgang's points and the conspiracies around Sandy Hook, which I don't think helped their case.
No.
There were some other things that I thought would be interesting to point out.
Here's the first one.
So let's look at these stories here.
I do Benjarras and cartoon based, of course, on my original term, dinosaur media.
You've got ISIS working with Ms.
Mcnn.
You've got NBC.
They got it in the water hole getting their money.
And here comes Stefan Molyneux.
Here comes Paul Watson.
Here comes Cernovich.
Here comes the infowars.
Here comes Drudge.
Here comes my part.
Yeah, back then, Molyneux was completely, totally fine.
I am a white nationalist.
Paul Joseph Watson.
You had a real different climate in the time that Alex made this video.
So different.
Yeah, all those players are so different.
Well, I mean, they didn't have to snub Molyneux because he spoke a little bit too openly.
Shouldn't have spoken like a Molyneux.
I'd be pissed.
I know all you assholes.
All of you guys are open white nationalists now.
Why don't I get to be coming back? Did you ever see that video of Owen Benjamin after the intellectual dark web started not liking him? There's a video of him drinking beer and complaining about all the intellectual dark web people who don't like him anymore because he got kicked off Twitter.
Right.
It's just the same thing.
I understand that.
Yes.
You should be pissed off at your friends who don't like you anymore because you spoke too openly about the things that you all believe.
You all believe the same shit.
Yes, absolutely.
You just said some slurs, and all of a sudden, you're too toxic to be a part of.
I feel like Stefan Molyneux should definitely feel that way.
Like, the content that he was putting out when everybody was buddy buddy with him is just as offensive as the stuff that he puts out later is a little bit clearer later.
I think the way that I would describe the feeling that they must have is like they're all over the line.
Like, these are all people who are Wiley Coyote, who have already jumped off the edge of the cliff.
And if you say the slur, that's like you telling everybody else, oh, look, we're floating.
And then you fall, and they're like, Good thing we're not floating.
We're just standing on solid ground.
Honestly, I was never running with that guy to be yeah.
I've never even seen look at how far down he is.
It's crazy how far down he is.
Yeah.
So Alex discusses in this clip that they're playing in court this coverage of him.
That is actually pretty good.
There's one person who's done a great job.
This is an excellent article from Zero Hedge, alice Jones implores NBC not to air interview with liar Meghan Kelly.
This article, better than anyone I've seen.
I want to post on impuls.com exactly how I feel.
What's actually happened is from Ibankcoin.com originally.
It's from Zero point now as he posted it.
This article, I need to get this person to write for Info Wars journalists.
They actually reported on what I said.
They showed my quotes going back over years saying, I don't know what happened, but it's got more holes out of Swiss cheese, and I believe kids die, but it needs to be investigated, and there's definitely a cover up.
Zero Point Now is the person who wrote the article that Owen was relying on when he defamed Tesla.
Yes.
Owen is zero point Now's puppet.
Yeah.
Literally zero point.
I bank coin according to under oath.
Owen under oath.
He's his puppet.
Yeah.
So it's just interesting to see this pop up here, because this is also in a very close time frame with when Owen made that video, because Alex is talking about how he doesn't want the Megyn Kelly interview to air.
Right.
So it's after he shot it, but before it airs it's in that pocket.
And then Owen shoots that video pretty much closely after the Megan Kelly interview errors as a response to it.
So what you have here is Alex wanting to hire the person who wrote the article that Owen relied on to create defamatory content.
Yeah.
Fun.
It is amazing to me that, one, the defense only used the plaintiff's evidence, which is usually a bad sign, and two, that in so doing, they have made the plaintiff's case really well.
I would think so, yeah.
So Reynold comes back, and he wants to have Alex say that Sandy Hook is real and not a conspiracy.
He wants that so bad.
So here's the first attempt.
Here we go.
As you sit here today, what are your beliefs around the San Diego School street? I certainly studied it now, and I should have a better job studying it.
That's an apology, right? There was an initial cover up of what happened, in my view, because I'm sorry, wait, are you questioning Sandy Hook in the stance they're going to Uvaldi? Both children really died, and they had a cover up there.
It submitted there's now state investigations of the cover up.
Texas Rangers are on it, and the governor said it's an outrageous cover up and it's incompetence is what it was.
And I thought it was incompetent.
What's the question? Alex Rambles gets caught off into talking about Uvaldi because he latches onto the idea of a cover up, and he feels the need to defend this cover up idea.
So he jumps to Uvaldi, gets an objection.
So now here's the second attempt.
Let's go for it again.
My question was, as you sit here today, what is your position, your view on what happened, the murders at Sandy Hook Elementary School in 2012, a young man on psychotropic drugs, and the inserts on those sessions can make you do mass shootings, mass murders, as he says on the insert.
I think we're coming really close to Kentucky.
Okay.
So Alex now says his pharmaceuticals talking point and feels the need to defend the pharmaceuticals talking.
And so he goes down that road, hits another objection, and so at this point, Raymond just gives up.
Yeah, he said, I'm going to move on.
And then Alex, of his own volition, decides to try a third time, and he whips it.
Here we go.
I think Sandy Hook happened.
I think it's a terrible event, and I think we need to protect our children from mentally ill psychopaths.
And I think there was a cover up because they had warnings.
The FBI knew about it.
They knew he was planning to attack the school that's been in even The New York Times.
And I think, well, right now there's actually no question.
And it's not a show.
It's a question answer to the question after you got it.
So that objection is sustained.
And we need another question.
Yeah.
So Alex had three tries there to say something very simple.
So simple, and could not help himself in creating conspiracy yarns.
So we have one last question from Raynall.
I just hope in my entire life that I never hear Mark say something with the amount of smile in his voice.
I don't ever want to hear that.
That's a bad sound.
Getting close to contempt.
That makes me feel like some danger is around the corner.
Yeah, and it should, because it was.
So, like I said, Renault is one last question yes, that we're going to look at, and it's a doozy.
When you look back on your 20 plus years in the media, what are you most proud of? I'm most proud of 911 early on exposing that the WMDs weren't in Iraq and it was a fraud and it was a lie.
Close.
And I'm very proud of being the first to expose Jeffrey Epstein and his child trafficking ranks.
We're on record be the first to expose that a decade before anybody else, by name even exposing the island and the rest of it from our sources.
So Alex definitely wasn't the first to report on WMDs in Iraq and the questionable intelligence surrounding the story, even though he was correct to be skeptical of that story.
His skepticism was childish and it was just a knee jerk response.
It wasn't based on anything other than his own Whim, so I guess he can brag that he got that one right, but he can't really take any credit for doing any work on the subject or even covering it competently.
As we've seen, his Iraq war coverage in 2003 is embarrassing stuff.
From the insistence that the Bath Party were being reinstalled to rule the country while debacification was taking place, to his unsupported weeks long assertion that Saddam's kids weren't killed and were in Belarus with their father they still are to his really shitty coverage of David Kelly's suicide.
The larger picture that you get from that time is of a person who's not really worth accepting as a source.
It's not worth it.
He wasn't the only person saying that WMD intelligence was sketchy, and the other people who were expressing that opinion didn't overwhelm that accurate opinion with an avalanche of embarrassing bullshit.
As for Epstein, I really want to challenge this because I don't believe this at all.
I've listened to Alex from a lot of periods of his career and I've never heard him bring up Epstein except after larger media covered the story.
I don't believe at all that Alex was covering Epstein, let alone covering him by name ten years before the mainstream.
I believe that Alex has convinced himself of his own bullshit.
Like we talked about earlier, from as far back as I can find, alex basically believes the Satanic panic type stuff was real.
Things like the McMarton school case were actually real, and he based a lot of that off that insane shit that Ted Gunderson apparently had told him.
I do accept that Alex has talked about his fantasies of satanic groups kidnapping and abusing children for a long time, and I think what he's done is retroactively connect Epstein to that coverage so he can claim he was on the.
Story all along, like how his first documentary was about the great recess.
Right.
I'm open to anyone providing me with evidence that Alex was talking about Epstein by name, about his island and the sex crimes ten years before everyone else.
And if they do, I will reevaluate my position.
But I've looked, and I can find no evidence that this claim that Alex is making is true at all.
I've even looked through the Alex Jones predictions section on his website where he posts all the videos of him ostensibly being right about all these things way back in the past.
I can't find any video of him being way ahead of the curve on Epstein.
And thus, this answer Alex is giving feels accurate.
He's asked to say what he's most proud of in his career, and what he comes up with is one story that half the country got right and the other is something that is almost certainly not true.
There's nothing in his career to be proud of.
He spouted meaningless bullshit for two decades, and I'll definitely applaud him for dragging it out that long.
But beyond that, his career has meant nothing but other people's pain and in profiting from it.
Yeah, if that was me, I would have said nothing.
I would've been like, you know what? I don't really want to answer this question.
We've launched so many media stars, like Reset Wars.
Oh, no, that's not good.
What else do we got? I've made a lot of money.
Jakari Jackson published a children's book.
I think that was pretty cool.
That was after evil wars.
Anyway, cross examination starts.
Oh, boy, this is fun.
Fireworks happens a little bit down the road.
Yeah.
But first, Mark's initial strategy in the beginning of this is to impeach Alex as a credible witness.
And so to do that, he sets a couple of traps.
Before I talk to you about the details of the history of this case, I want to know you're taking this job seriously.
You're approaching it in good faith? Absolutely.
Okay.
The truth is, you and your company wants the world to believe that this judge is reading this court proceeding to make sure that a script, a literal script, is being followed.
That's what you want the world to believe, right? Aren't I barred from talking about this? I'm asking you a question, Mr.
Jones.
The way court works as you answer a question until there's an objection, again, Mr.
Jones, make sure you understand it very clearly.
You and your company want the world to believe that this judge is rigging this court proceeding so that a script, and I mean a literal script, is being followed.
That's what you want the world to live.
That's what Info was.
I believe when you're given a court order that you cannot say you're innocent, that that's not America.
And the court orders right at their own table.
I've been told I can't say I'm innocent.
So you need to answer the question that is asked.
I asked you this question.
Yes or no? That's what you want the world to believe? No, I believe the jury's real, and I believe that I'm innocent till proven guilty.
And I believe the jury should decide my guilt.
Your Honor, at this time we'd like to offer a clip from Infowars on Friday for the purposes of peacement in which those exact words were said.
So that happens, and then it immediately leads into another trap.
One of the things you've been talking about a lot recently on your show, even within the past couple of months, is your allegation that government officials are aiding in pedophilia, child trafficking, and the grooming of children, right? Well, you mean like what Jeffrey Epstein did with the Clintons? Sure, if that's a yes.
Is that a yes? Yes.
Okay.
And on Thursday, you and Infowars started connecting those allegations to our judge, didn't you? No.
In fact, Mr.
Jones, you're telling the world not to believe what happens in this courtroom because the judge worked with Child Protective Services, who you say is involved with pedophilia and child trafficking, correct? Not all of it, but the Texas Youth Commission got caught doing it.
There's a lot of that here.
I'm not asking you that, Mr.
Johnson.
I'm asking you you're telling the world not to believe what's happened in this trial because this judge is involved with CPS who is working with child traffickers in Mediterranean, correct? No, that's not what I'm saying.
Okay.
Your Honor, at this time, we would like to show a clip for Mr.
Duncan on Thursday where those words are said and there's, of course, a third rate.
Why wouldn't they tell the jury? You're taking the show seriously.
You're telling the world that someone inside Travis County government rigged the jury summits and picked these jurors specifically who don't know what planet they are on, correct? That's what you're telling the world I'm saying that could potentially be a danger if they don't know what's going on.
Potentially is what you're saying.
Potentially? You didn't go on your phone and say those words is what you're going to tell me.
Can you show me? I would be happy to forgive.
We would like to now offer a video for Mrs.
Jones show on Friday saying those words.
This reminds me so much of the deposition where it's like, okay, we're on.
Try number three.
How do you not realize that when he says, did you say those words, he's going to play the clip? Right, but answering yes is a chaotic option.
That is true.
But you have to answer yes.
It's a show like you have to answer with and then something you can't say no because he's just going to go, yeah, that is let's go to the clip.
That is an option.
Yeah, but no matter what, what you end up with is like, okay, we've demonstrated that Alex is an untrustworthy person.
This is all bullshit.
It's not a witness that you should take seriously.
Trust, right? No.
He's got no winning position.
No, that's true.
No.
So Mark tries to bring up the video that Raynall played and the whole thing about how you just repeated all the claims about the school not it being real.
And you realize that if you do that, then you are once again denying Sandy Hook.
Yeah.
And I think this is about two minutes and it is a really good encapsulation of why it is useless to try to get Alex to recognize points that he doesn't want to recognize.
Yes.
Do you remember them talking about the FBI crime stats saying no one killed in Sandy Hook that you read in that 2017? That was the headlines, yes.
What headline? But that's what it said.
No, it didn't.
Mr.
John, did you admit that now the FBI did not have a crime status? I mean, I met we later learned that in the full report.
They don't report those in that state.
They do, I think, everywhere else.
Mr.
Jones, we've heard a lot of testimony about the FBI crime stat and how that got wrong.
We heard that Mr.
Salazar, were you in the report room for that? I think I was in different part of it.
Okay, so you probably heard Mr.
Salazar how he messed that up, right? I think we admit we messed that up.
Right, but you were still saying it in 2017 at a time where you want this jury to believe you were saying it really happened.
You, in 2017, were saying the FBI says nobody there.
I said it on the video.
I thought it happened like five times.
Yeah, just like Meghan Kelly said in your interview.
You want to have all way extension, Mr.
Pennsylvania.
No, I think Sandy Hook happened.
Yeah, but if Sandy Hook happened and that means there's not an FBI crime stat where nobody died.
It means that there was web site traffic.
It means that nobody ate their food inside the school.
All these things you're saying are false, right? I'd have to review all of it again.
Ten minutes ago, we saw a video of you saying no EMTs entered the building.
Do you remember that? You remember saying that? I never see the timeline of what you're speaking about.
I'm asking you, when we broke from your break, when your attorney put up a video that he really wanted this jury to see how far you were being about Sandy voter, you said no paramedics interfered, right, at a certain time frame.
What do you mean by that? I'd have to see the time frame you're talking about.
What do you mean timeframe? You said they never entered the building.
Never entered it.
That's what you said, and you said that for years.
I think you're taking out the contest, right? Because they had to keep them out of the building because otherwise you have to pay off all the MPs because they get in the building and they'd see there's no bodies.
That's what you told your audience.
You've told them that many times.
I don't remember what you're talking about.
See, this is the next stage of the you have to watch the full clip.
Never going to win because they watched the full clip.
And now it had some stuff that Alex probably didn't realize or forgotten was in it, didn't want that.
Now these are questions that are coming up.
We have watched the full clip.
It's out of context.
I need to see the timeline or whatever.
There's always going to be an excuse for why there isn't complete information in front of you that is exculpatory in some way for Alex and it's bullshit.
It's fascinating to me to listen to this and to realize, like, this is also confirmation bias.
They watched the clip and saw what they wanted to see, and then we're like, well, obviously this is a great clip.
It didn't even occur to them that the other stuff inside the clip could also be used to question Alex.
Well, I think maybe they approach it from maybe a perspective that I had when we were going over the Sandy Hook immediate aftermath, and that is that I had a singular focus on trying to figure out, like, the actual literal claim of actors.
Sure.
And so when I was going over the time frame in 2012 and 2013, there was a like, Alex isn't quite there yet, or whatever.
Yeah, we did have that conversation and through the case and understanding a little bit more about what was going on and all that, my perspective has changed in terms of like, oh yeah, you said it was a false flag immediately, basically, and had different incarnations of what his theories were and stuff.
But when I was approaching it with the most generous possible approach and reading of things, I might have heard him say something like, why didn't the paramedics arrive? Or whatever and not be like, okay, this is him denying Hook.
And I think that probably when looking at the clip, there's, like, he didn't say actors anymore.
Right.
And I think that might be just part of how they are oblivious of what is being said to them.
I also feel like you just brought up a really good point in the way that you view that is, like, when we talk about denying Sandy Hook or Alex denying Sandy Hook, I think a lot of people are talking about him saying this didn't happen.
Right.
What it is, is an amorphous blob.
All of what he has to say is denying that Sandy Hook didn't happen in a sense like, okay, so he's saying, I 100% believe it's real, but I question the official narrative that is just part of the amorphous blob of denying Sandy Hook.
So when he says that what he's really doing is signaling that he's still denying Sandy Hook on whatever level he can cling to.
So there will not be a resolution where he says it's 100% real.
If he also says, But I question the official story.
Right.
You know what I'm saying? You can't say it's 100% real and then rattle off all of Wolfgang how? Big's reasons why.
Exactly.
Yeah.
And if you're even saying that there are things to question, then you're saying that you were right to question them, and you are saying that there are questions, which there weren't, about Sandy Hook.
I actually have to take issue with that because I think that, first of all, what Alex was doing wasn't questioning.
And so you're falling into the framing there.
Totally.
Fair enough.
Because I think that it is okay to question things like, what is a journalist doing other than asking the who, what, where, why, when, how? I meant when he was in court that day when he said, but I questioned the official narrative in court.
I mean, that outside of that official narrative is okay until you get an answer.
And he had answers.
Yes, that is what I'm saying.
In 2022.
If he's saying, I had questions.
If he still says, I have questions about the official narrative in 2022.
Exactly.
But I think that was in December.
That was last year.
Yeah.
I'm so unspecific.
That's my problem.
So, Mark, the big moment in the cross examination, of course, is the revelation of these text messages.
Beautiful moment.
We all loved it.
But I think a lot of the coverage surrounding this is missing the point of these text messages.
Obviously, there is the juicy idea of what could be in there.
Of course, I think a lot of people are setting themselves up for real disappointment.
No, Geraldo found everything in that safe.
This isn't based on any kind of, like, inside information that I have or anything, so don't take this as me being like, I know X, Y, or Z.
Sure.
But I see stories about the notion that Trump's raid was about Alex's text or January 6 is going to be blown wide open.
And I think that there is a desire to expand things and, like, take the what ifs and give more credence to them.
Yeah.
And I think people are falling into that, whether it's through headline writing or tweets.
And I would advise caution just to like, hey, we'll see what happens.
We'll see what's there.
Sure.
But let's not write a story in advance.
Right.
I mean, you get that, though.
You hear we have this how can we not say it? Tranche of text messages.
And your mind immediately goes to, like, oh, what could be? And you can't not think to yourself, it is entirely possible because we live in the weird world we live in that Alex, Roger Trump and Mike Pompeo might have had a group text where they're like, let's overthrow the country.
On the 6th.
Like, you can't not think in your brain.
Like, that kind of ridiculous thing is possible.
The world has gone cuckoo.
Right.
But then you also have to remember, no, that is not how it works.
And these are Alex's text messages.
This is not a big player in the game.
Yeah.
There may be pieces of information that are relevant to things, and we'll know when we know.
Exactly.
But for now, don't get ahead of yourself, because if you do, you end up backing yourself into a position where you've basically created a storyline.
And if reality doesn't live up to that, it's disappointing.
Yeah.
I think that if we've learned anything in the past couple of attempts at impeachment, we maybe should be a little careful about setting expectations in a reasonable place.
But the reason why I started with this sure.
I think that the media is absolutely missing the concrete reality of the text messages use in this case.
Right.
And why they came up in the cross examination in the way that they did.
And so Mark begins to get into this, and this is really where the Paul text is most important.
Were you here for, Mr.
Short? Yes.
Okay.
You remember what Owen said? The company has learned from its mistakes about San Jose.
You remember that? I didn't hear you say that.
You agreed that.
Yeah, we've certainly learned from our mistakes a lot better.
Mr.
Jones, I'd like to show you what's been marked as planes.
You've got it upside down, isn't it? And they mentioned Sandy hooks, don't they? Yes.
Plants move 130 into evidence.
So the lead into this question is about Owens testimony that they had learned from Sandy Hook and their behavior had become better.
And so that's why it's important how this is revealed.
Right.
Mr.
Watson has sent you a screenshot from Infowars.com, correct? Appears to be, yeah.
And it has an article here, right? Yeah.
And it says, stays video, shows hospital using Dummies in Er for coronavirus footage.
I believe so.
Read along with me, Mr.
Jones.
He says this is a video.
No problem.
Take your time.
Give me a second.
All right, go ahead.
Mr.
Watson says this is a video of a medical student training to intubate.
Makes us look ridiculous, suggesting this means Covet is fake Sandy Hook all over again.
I read that correctly, yes.
Go to the next message.
I get it.
Mr.
Jones, it's true that this article is right now live on Info.com.
I can pull it up.
Right? I've never seen this text message.
I guess you guys got calls.
My phone didn't save them.
So that's a sad response because Alex has already said that this is his phone, and these are text between him and Paul.
And so the notion here is the set up of the question is you learn from Sandy Hook.
You agree with that? That's what Owen said.
Yes.
Here's a text during Covet that Paul was telling you, this is Sandy Hook all over again with you doing this bullshit about fake patients in hospitals to pretend that there's covet patients in the hospitals.
And you said, I get it.
I understand that this is Sandy Hook all over again.
And the article is still live today as we are in this courtroom.
This is a damning picture that is basically no, you have not learned from Sandy Hook.
Not only have you not learned from it, when reminded this is Sandy Hook all over again.
When you're in the middle of a lawsuit about this sort of behavior as it relates to Sandy Hook, you say, I understand.
I get it, and I don't care.
Right.
And not just that it is not a message from your son or just some stranger email.
It's a message from your literal head editor for most of your career.
Yeah.
You should pay attention.
Right? Yeah.
And the person who, like, throughout the course of this case has had maybe the only moment of someone having clarity in his deposition, there's a reason that Paul's not getting right? Absolutely.
There is documented evidence of him back then saying, cut this out.
This is bullshit.
No, he's literally the guy who is like he's the person if you had listened to him, you wouldn't be in this situation.
If we were in a movie that's different from the one that this trial turned into, which was astonishing, but Paul would be the guy who gets roped back in for one last job.
But in this movie, Paul's like, no, this is a terrible one last job.
I'm not going to do this one last job.
You guys go do the one last job.
And then he's watching them all die.
That's what's happening.
He sucks, obviously, but in the lowest of low bars, he has cleared it in terms of he has not stolen $100 million from a bank.
Congratulations.
You are not being prosecuted for stealing $100 million from a bank.
It's wild that you have this situation where Paul is if you listen to him, you wouldn't be getting sued.
You wouldn't be in the situation.
Crazy.
And then you have this text from fairly recently of you should have listened to him, and you should not have had this text exchange because it illustrates how little you give a shit, and that doesn't play well.
No, I love that.
Here's the movie, because this is the Perry Mason moment.
The Perry Mason moment.
Well, the Perry Mason moment is coming up, right? But Mark dramatically revealing we have all your texts, right? The parody is whenever he goes, you're reading it upside down.
That's the encapsulation to me of this moment in testimony is that combination of high drama, like, I have revealed fucking Tom Cruise's text messages to you right now.
And then the fucking hilarity of, like, it's upside down.
Alex.
So anyway, Alex tries to spin this, and he's trying really hard to figure out.
Like, what the fuck can I do here? I've never seen this text message.
He can choke.
I guess you guys got Paul's.
My phone didn't save them.
That's fine.
Your phone didn't save the second.
Here we go.
I gave it to the lawyers, said they drained the phone.
They found that stuff, gave it to lawyers.
They were supposed to find that Tesla is no, I searched as well.
You guys have all this stuff that you say, we didn't give anything.
You know how an iPhone works, right? You've had iPhone text messaging for several years now.
Yeah.
I turn the phone over, take stuff off.
Can I have you look in the very bottom below the very bottom left corner? Is that your phone number? Yes.
So you did get my text messages, and it said, you did.
Nice trick.
So this is the beginning of the Perry Mason moment.
And this is what all of the John Oliver Show and all the clip shows, they run this moment.
And I understand why, because it is I mean, it's made for TV.
I mean, it's literally made for TV.
It's evocative like Bill said in our interview, it's like the biggest legal moment.
It is.
Yeah.
I mean, it doesn't get bigger, does it? And I understand that.
But because of the way our show works and stuff, I'm so much more interested in the reasoning and the context to it.
So you have that Paul reveal, and then the reveal of the text messages and the nature of them comes.
And so that's here.
Let's all enjoy that.
Okay, so you did get my text messages and it said you did.
Nice trick.
Yes, Mr.
Johnson.
Indeed.
You didn't get the text message to me.
You don't know where this came from? Do you know where I got this? No.
Mr.
Jones, did you know that twelve days ago twelve days ago, your attorneys messed up and sent me an entire digital copy of your entire cell phone with every text message you've sent for the past two years, and when informed, did not take any steps to identify it as privileged or protected in any way.
And as of two days ago, it fell free and clear into my possession.
And that is how I know you lied to me when you said you didn't have text message about Samuel.
Did you know that? I told you the truth.
This is your Perry Mason moment.
I gave them my phone.
Mr.
Jones, you need to answer the question.
No, I don't know what happened, but, I mean, I told you I gave him the phone over.
You said in your deposition you searched your phone.
You said you pulled down the text.
Did the search function for Sandy Hook? That's what you said, Mr.
Jones.
Correct.
And I had several different phones with this number, but I did.
Yeah, I mean, that's why you got it.
No, Mr.
Jones, that's not why my lawyer sent it to you.
But I'm hiding it.
Okay.
Mr.
Jones.
That's mr.
Oh, I love it.
Yeah, I mean, like, all of these attempts to wiggle out of this, I just feel like have backfired for him and made it worse.
Do you know what the craziest thing, the craziest moment? Because whenever I went back through all of the stuff that I've written, there were so many moments that you do just lose because it's absolute, nonstop insanity.
But the craziest one was on Tuesday or day one of the trial proper, the day after jury selection, the opening statement day.
Yeah.
In the middle of one of the breaks, alex is talking to the HBO documentarian on stream, and at one point, he does say, they don't have my texts.
How crazy is that? How fucking wild is that? That was the wildest thing, like, going back to irony.
I was like, that can't be real.
And I checked, and it's crazy.
Well, again, we have to make the point that could have been talking about other text.
No.
Your tweets may or may not depict reality.
They absolutely do not.
Yeah, who knows if that conversation even happened or you imagined it.
Fair enough.
So Alex has now said that he searched his phones, of course, and didn't find these things.
Right.
And so Mark has to inform him that, hey, buddy, you may have just committed perjury.
That's not good.
Mr.
Jones, in discovery, you were asked, do you have Sandy Hook text messages on your phone? And you said no.
Correct.
You said that under oath, if I was mistaken.
But you got the messages right there.
You know, I just want to make sure, you know, before we go any further.
You know what it is.
Yes, I do.
I'm not a tech guy.
I told you, I gave in my testimony the phone to the lawyers before, whatever.
And so you got my phone, but we didn't give it to you.
No.
Mr.
Jones, one more time, please remember, if you need to assert them in, you can I need to know that you can do that.
When you testified under oath previously that you personally searched your phone for the phrase Sandy boat and there were no messages, you said that under oath.
Yes.
No, I did not lie.
Ouch.
When you say something that is then later found out to be not true, and you knew that it was not true, right? Because it was you who said you did it and you didn't.
What is that called? Not good.
Yeah.
And it turns out also applies to his emails.
I quit opening email and using it for sanity.
Go.
Okay.
In other words, if somebody was to tell me, oh, I have emails from Mr.
Jones that he wrote about this case in the past couple of years, that person be lying.
You're telling the truth.
Somebody else has got my Info works email because I haven't been using it's not qualified.
Mr.
James, you know, in this case you were asked to produce your emails, any emails you had about San Jose.
You knew you were asked to do that, right? Yeah.
And you said he didn't have it.
I told my It.
People go, you got all that stuff now, mr.
Johnson, I'm saying in deposition, under oath, sworn to God, you said you don't have any emails for saying hook because you don't use email.
Right? I have been using Infowars email and it's got to be a decade or longer in my memory.
We're with infowars.com email, he keeps trying to bring it back to Infowars email as opposed to another email thing.
And what Mark is doing is very clearly trying to establish like, you lied again because I have an email.
But the attempt to wiggle out of it is just the constantly bringing up Infowars emails and it's just not going to help.
Earlier in the trial, Raynall had been talking to Daria as the corporate representative that he objected to and then talked to her as the corporate representative.
He had said like, Alex doesn't have an email address, right.
And she's like, oh, when he did, he'd get 100 million emails a day.
So he got rid of it as though that would be later the excuse for what now happens.
Yeah.
How did it go? Not well.
Not the best.
So we go back to the text messages.
Now, we have already illustrated that Paul had texted with Alex and told him, this is Sandy Hook all over again.
I get it is the response.
And now there's some other texts here from Tim Fruge, who's the business manager of Infowars.
And so here's how this goes.
This has been marked as planned, exhibit 132.
Do you see that? Yes.
Those are text messages of Tim Fruge, the operations manager of Infowars, right? Yes.
And we requested information about your revenues in this case, you remember that? Yes.
You didn't give us this, did you? There's a lot of stuff yeah.
You didn't even look through your text message.
And this is going to hit them, right? Correct? No.
Okay.
I gave it to the lawyers.
That's why you have it.
This is ridiculous.
Yes.
132 is submitted.
Before we put that up, Mr.
Jones, I just want to make sure you understand something about these emails.
You understand that when your attorney sent me your hold on, he didn't mean to do that injection.
Your honor, I just want to make sure this is not discovery.
Well, I do think it's important that since we're discussing all of this, that the jury understands discovery is a process that occurs and concludes well before trial what the lawyers say is of evidence.
So we don't.
Know whether it was on accident or on purpose.
Yeah, we don't have evidence about that, but what we do know is that it wasn't properly turned over when it should have been.
There's no question.
Mr.
Downstairs.
Okay, so there is a fair objection there.
Yes.
Because you're asserting that he did this accidentally.
True.
You can't prove that.
Can't do that.
Well, I mean, kind of.
But what you have is text about finances that are like, here's the numbers for this day, and then Alex just didn't turn those over.
Right.
That's real bad.
It does appear that I do think there's an argument to be made that you can say that he didn't mean to do it because the Reynold did email back, like, please disregard, which isn't legally it doesn't mean anything.
But Mark hasn't introduced that.
That's true.
Sorry, he can't do that now.
Right.
Then Reynald would object to privilege.
Yeah, it would be a mess.
The court is unaware of that email response.
Right.
So one of the things that's critical about the revelation of these texts is that they illustrate financial information that was demanded and ordered from Alex right.
That was not turned over, but more for my purposes.
They also reveal that Alex is full of shit.
Mr.
Fruge.
How do I say his name? Mr.
Jones.
All right, so Mr.
Fruge, you would agree with me that pretty much every day he sends you an update on how much the store has sold and sometimes he lets you know how much profit you make.
Right? Yes.
Okay.
And in this message, he says 110 gross sales in food equates to almost 70K pure profit.
That's what he told you? That's what that says.
That's not what it does.
So, look, this makes total sense.
Alex has said that there's a 20% to 40% profit margin on the food, and you just let that go and you're like, oh, yeah, okay, I guess that makes sense.
He's not paying anything for the food.
It's not like he buys it from My Patriot Supply and then sends it to people.
Yeah, he's not a resale.
No, he's essentially getting a cut of what the business that they do.
There is no overhead.
No.
It is all pure profit.
So that also illustrates that the thing that Alex testified to earlier, which is that the 20% to 40% profit margin is a load of shit.
Yeah.
100%.
It has no risk, no exposure on the food.
Maybe things are different with the private labeling.
Maybe with his supplements and stuff.
Sure.
He has to buy a bunch and then resell.
It possible, but yeah, for the food, that's not the case at all.
I mean, they even did, like, drop shipping from the My Patriot supply facilities.
Got you.
So only 110 units is 70,000 in pure profit.
Right.
I think that's crazy.
I think that probably is an unreliable statistic to, like, universalize.
Oh, no, I wouldn't.
They have different sized buckets and things that they sell.
So it's not a uniform commission, I'm sure, but yeah, even percentage of the total.
That still is pretty sweet.
Not a bad gig.
Pretty sweet.
All you have to do is say stuff and then they give you money.
All you have to do is convince everyone that they won't get food tomorrow.
You're going to die anyway.
So here is Mark's Dismount.
And then I think we saw your revenues from 20.
So we saw a few months of 2015 on the beginning of that document.
Right.
Do you remember that document you relied on and testified about planning to exist? I saw it, yes.
Okay.
I had a couple of months from 2015 on it.
But not a whole lot of sales on that, right? I believe so.
Okay, so we're mainly just talking about 20 16.
20 18, right.
You remember that? 165,000,000.
You remember testifying? Yes.
Okay.
And I know you testified about your profit margins, but I think we've seen that now.
You were saying that that's gross, so that maybe doesn't we have to calculate what your profit is, right? I need a yes or no.
this is what you should pay for the damages that your company admits under oath through your corporate representative costs? Were you aware of that? One dollars.
Were you aware? Yes.
Not that we were do you agree? Do.
I agree with it.
One dollars.
I'll pay it for you.
Are we done? What does the New York Times do for why? About WMDs? I don't think there's any point in asking you any more questions.
Okay.
Slamming the door.
Yes.
I don't think there's any reason to ask you any more questions.
What a great way to just call it so good.
Again, a little theatrical in as much as you pull out a dollar and be like, this is it.
Is this what we're doing? Come on, give the man his moment.
No, I'm fine with it in this context, but yes, Alex can't answer that question.
Absolutely not.
And then Rayna all one question on redirect.
Yeah, very funny.
Is so funny.
You've trusted your lawyers to produce the relevant documents.
Yes.
You've cooperated with us in every way.
And you trusted us to do a good job and turn over what we need to turn over.
Yes.
When we're supposed to turn it over.
No further questions.
Yes.
And this is the end.
That is one situation where Alex did not realize that his lawyer was no longer working for him.
His lawyer was working for Reynald.
Yeah.
Cover your ass.
Maybe Alex should have said no to all of those questions.
Yeah.
So this testimony took place over the course of Tuesday and Wednesday? Yeah.
Tuesday afternoon, Wednesday morning.
And there's closing statements and then we get the revelation on Thursday that Alex is hit with the compensatory damages of 4.1 million.
And as this news breaks, it is past the point that Alex is on air.
And so Owen is hosting the War Room at this point, complaining about, I don't know, the Chinese.
Sure, probably that sounds right.
And so here's him discussing that.
The judgment has come in.
A lot of people are tuned in right now because the news is broke about the first verdict in the Sandy Hook case.
And they got a $4 million judgment.
Never had a trial by jury.
Judge just decided guilt.
And now they got a $4 million verdict, which is they were shooting for 150,000,000 because they got to line their pockets, I guess.
Whoever is getting that money, I don't know where that money goes.
That would absolve any emotional distress, but okay, so there might be a statement from Alex Jones soon.
He might go live.
He might pop in.
I don't know.
We're on a Titanic right now playing the violin.
Okay, well, that's good news.
I've got all the news to cover.
And that's what's so sad about it, is nobody else is going to cover this news.
It's only info where it's going to cover it.
And now we won't even be able to cover it.
So just stay tuned.
There will be a statement from Alex shortly.
Can't cover the news.
Too busy playing violence.
That is such a funny Whiny way of, oh, look, now I can't even cover the news.
See, now who's the victim? Look what the Sandy Hook parents have done.
They may be unable to cover the news.
Is that what he's saying? In his many words, look at what these people have done to me.
And who knows where that money is going? What an hour.
Really trying to make suspicious the idea of a lawsuit.
And so he's right.
Alex does pop in later.
So that's one thing Owens right about.
He's second winning in the talk show predictions.
Second thing he's right about, alex was filming a statement before he came on.
And so here is that we're going to go to that right away.
The Democratic Party, the entire corporate media lined up against Infowars and the American people's free speech.
The judge, more than 20 times in the last week and a half in Austin, Texas, told the jury while I was there in the courtroom and it was on national TV that Alex Jones is guilty.
The lawyers for the plaintiffs asked for between 150,000,000 and $3 billion.
When the jury came in this evening with $4.2 million, I admitted I was wrong.
I admitted I made a mistake.
I admitted that I followed this information, but not on purpose.
I apologize to families, and the jury understood that what I did to those families was wrong.
But I didn't do it on purpose.
I didn't lie about WMDs in Iraq.
My God, is the people on purpose? I questioned the public event because I saw anomalies and others saw anomalies, and the jury understood that and awarded $4.2 million.
Now, that's more money than my company and I personally have, but we are going to work on trying to make restitution there.
Oh, what a great guy.
Wow.
So I think the 3 billion number is meant to make the judgment look even smaller.
Sure.
I was trying to figure out where that came from, and I think it's the sales figures that Mark showed from the text messages that Fruge was sending over okay.
During CPAC, it was like, what, $800,000 a day? Yeah.
And so this extrapolated out to, like, 300 million in a year over 20 years.
Over ten years.
Sandy Hook.
Sure.
I think that that's what I don't even remember if Mark made any statement of 3 billion.
Right.
But it's like, okay, you made $300 million a year.
Ten years since you've made, in theory, $3 billion since then.
I think that's where Alex may be taking that number from, but I never heard that as, like, what, he should be penalized.
Yeah.
I really wish that the way that amount of money was reported was based on why it was chosen.
I understand that the 24% of Americans is 75 million Americans, so the idea is one dollars for each American.
Right.
There's a symbolism.
Yeah.
But it kept going back to, like, oh, they want money, or they want money, or it was about how huge the sum was.
If they really just like, listen, the Sandy Hook families believe that because of Alex, alex owes them $1 for person that believes that they're a liar.
That makes sense to me.
And it also makes it feel like the judgment isn't that high, because if you had said that they owe $10 per person, I wouldn't think that that's a huge judgment, and that's $1.5 billion.
True.
So there's that.
And the other aspect of it, too, is, like, you don't start a negotiation low.
Oh, of course.
Absolutely not.
It's a number that you don't necessarily expect you're going to get.
And then the misunderstanding of the symbolism I agree with you.
That could have been the symbolism was what was really important about the money and not the money.
Yeah.
And that's what was so frustrating.
Yes.
Alex's statement goes on.
Now, here's the next phase of this.
When the judge realized that when I was on the stand, I woke that jury up and laid out the facts, she ruled today.
Of course you did.
Putative damage phase that starts tomorrow.
I cannot testify, and my lawyer cannot put on evidence.
So she already found me guilty and told the jury I was guilty.
And now she's saying we can't defend ourselves in the punitive damages face.
I trust in God.
I trust in the truth coming out.
So this just isn't true.
Raynal gave a defense in the punitive phase of the trial.
Just as west did for the plaintiffs.
The defense wasn't able to call any witnesses because the purpose of that phase of the trial was to determine net worth of both Alex and free speech systems.
And after repeatedly failing to provide ordered documents and repeatedly sending in incompetent corporate representatives, the judge sanctioned Alex's defense by disallowing him from being able to participate in the net worth discussion.
At this point, essentially, this is not a silencing or an instance of Alex being jammed up.
It's just another case of him not doing the bare minimum he was required to do in the discovery phase of the case, and now it's too late for him to pretend he wants to be involved.
Plus, Alex violated the rules on multiple occasions the prior day, including lying to the jury by saying he was bankrupt.
So on that count alone, he should not be able to be a witness in this part of the case he lied on under oath.
Nothing that he said can really be accepted as credible.
So his evidentiary value is zero unless he were to have produced the documents backing up what he says.
Which brings us to the next problem.
One of the primary things that was brought up as it relates to his text being disclosed was the messages from Tim Fruge, which discussed detailed breakdowns of sales numbers.
These numbers did not match the revenue numbers that Alex has claimed.
And even more importantly, the existence of these texts, which were not turned over in discovery, reveal an attempt to hide information relevant to the determination of net worth and the company's value.
There are three major reasons that Alex is not being allowed to be a part of this phase of the trial, and it has nothing to do with the Democratic Party or conspiracy against him.
It's the simple consequences of his stupid actions.
You can probably get the basic tone of this announcement already.
It's Alex taking this $4 million judgment quite in stride because it's much lower than he was probably fearing.
His tone is essentially no different than when he's gotten other bad news in the past, where he's using it as an opportunity to fundraise off of it, more or less trying to get the audience to flip the bill for him so he can remain insulated from the consequences of his actions.
It's pathetic, but it's what you'd expect because he's always been able to do this before, whether it's his dad paying for the medical bills that Kitty almost killed, or his dad buying advertising on his show so a radio station would air him early on, or the audience donating to his suspiciously timed money bombs, or his suspiciously timed $8 million bitcoin donation.
Alex has always had people to bail him out of the trouble of his stupid actions.
And he probably thinks, based on his $4 million figure, this is just going to be another in that series.
Yeah, and there's very little reason for him not to think that.
Yeah.
I mean, if it were me in Alex's shoes, I would have received that judgment as a massive victory.
But that's only because if it's me and Alex's shoes, i, much like Alex, have forgotten that there are more trials coming.
I have completely forgotten that.
That means more judgments are coming as well.
True.
So I'm overjoyed.
I am announcing my victory over the Democratic Party.
It's a thrill up until the midterm.
Could have been worse.
Yeah, it could have been worse.
Yes.
The plaintiff lawyers, though, they were not happy about this.
They don't like that Alex won.
At the end of the day, I don't have all these millions of dollars they claim I have, so I'm at peace.
But this is still a major victory for truth.
And the plaintiff's lawyers got upset in the courtroom and according to multiple witnesses, were screaming and yelling at my lawyers, Joe, andandino when they were in the hall, they thought they would get hundreds of millions of dollars we don't have.
They thought they would shut us down.
But that jury understood the truth and resisted the propaganda.
This does not at all match my experience with the Plant displayers.
I mean, I don't know who these two sources Alex has, but I think they're Lieutenant Colonels, probably.
It is this exact video that should be played further in the other trials just because this was after the judgment.
If you think that damages are going to make him stop and he can still be in business, that is not how this works.
He's in there and he is doing his shit or he's out.
There is no getting him to moderate.
Yeah, but I think that's difficult to I think you and I can say that saying that in a legal setting, I think is well, presupposes that, you know, 100% the future, which you can't do in a courtroom, I assume.
Right.
But it also presupposes that it is appropriate to be like, I want to bankrupt him as a punishment.
And I don't know if that is necessarily healthy.
I feel like this is so important.
It is not that well, I understand bankruptcy.
I mean, this way, if the point of the trial, if the point of the damages is to punish someone to get them to stop their behavior right.
And this is what they do after that judgment, then it's not about money at that point.
It has to be, how do we make this behavior stop? So I don't care if the judgment is ten jillion dollars or it's literally just a guy going like, hey, listen, you got to turn the lights off.
That's just what's got to happen.
It's not about the money kind of thing.
You know what, I just think it's difficult to translate that from what I think you're saying.
That makes total sense in this conversation to a courtroom.
I think that's a challenge impossible and it's also incredibly difficult, because when you have something like this happens, it's just an opportunity for Alex to trick his audience into being more money.
Listen, we're in bankruptcy right now.
Listen, we're maxed out.
Listen, we are fighting hard for your First Amendment, your Second Amendment, your 10th Amendment, your sovereignty, not your choice if you want to keep us in the fight.
We have a plan to stay on air through this bankruptcy.
We have a reorganization plan, but if you don't fund us, if you don't buy products at Info Worthstore.com, we will shut down.
It's your decision.
Just like that jury had a decision right now on whether Infowars is going to stay on the air.
We are so broke that I'm not even worried about that $4.2 million.
I'm worried about our bankruptcy to emergency stabilized Info or we have a plan, but to do that, we need support.
So get a T shirt, get a book, get a film, or get some of my supplements that under oath have been proven to be great.
Wild.
Just wild shape.
What do you expect? It's exactly what you'd expect.
Yes.
Now, what I didn't expect with that is for this announcement that Alex makes to go the direction it does, because when there's a direction to go from there yes.
Oh, God.
He starts talking about Neil and Scarlett.
No.
What? No.
Mike down.
Get them all at Info werestore.com and keep us on the air.
That is so critical because they use these families as ponds.
The families come over and shook my hand and hug me and really woke up the fact that they'd been manipulated and their own lawyers went like they were dogs.
Get over here and stop talking to him on video.
I was wrong.
Sandy Hook happened.
I admit it happened.
I'm proud to admit it happened, because when I'm wrong, I admit it.
I don't make mistakes on purpose.
We're tomorrow's news today.
We're 95% accurate.
But these people tried to misrepresent what I said to these families.
They showed them edited videos.
They showed the jury edited videos, and it backfired in their face big time.
Yeah.
So he's creating this perception that Neil and Scarlett are Info warriors.
Now.
They woke up to the fact that their lawyers were manipulating this case.
Yeah.
I realized that my comments about the previous clips have come too soon, and I would like to reiterate them about that clip, but, like, twice as much.
Yeah, it's bad.
Yeah, that's fucked up.
No, it can't get worse.
It does.
Oh, God.
I told and my lawyer told that jury, I said, listen, we want to pay for their psychological stuff.
We want to take care of problems.
We didn't cause all of it, but we want to step up and prove that and do that.
And Scarlett Lewis has a beautiful organization called Choose Love that isn't about gun control, isn't about liberal conservative.
It's about teaching children love and compassion so they're not hateful, so they're not satanic, so they don't kill people.
And I have invited Scarlett Lewis on my show.
We're going to email organization.
If I see her tomorrow during the punitive face, I'm going to shake her hand and give her my number, and I am going to gladly have her on my show next week.
And I'm going to raise money for her organization on top of the big judgment because she's a real lady.
She lost her child.
And I'm not going to let these people misrepresent what I said and did anymore and claim that I'm a Sandy hook man.
This is a beautiful time.
It's a great time.
And the trial lawyers, the ambulance chasers lost America, and the first amendment won.
And the poor parents that went through so much, neil hesley and Scarlett Lewis, they have won as well.
So this is a big victory.
An answer to prayer.
Thank you so much to viewers and listeners who are continuing on as long as you support us.
We were so close to being shut down, so please support us so we can have Scarlett Lewis and Ilhaslin on.
I'm going to take them out to dinner.
Their lawyers are going to try to stop them.
I mean, I literally yesterday saw them.
Neil tried to follow me out and shook my hand.
He goes, hey, buddy, I want to talk to you.
I said, yes, sir, please come out.
Their lawyer said, get over here to him.
I'll never talk to them like a dog.
I'll see you tomorrow on the Friday show.
So it's strange to hear Alex say that he and his lawyers said they wanted to pay Neil and Scarlett's medical expenses and such because I was in the courtroom during raynall's opening statement where he asked the jury to return a judgment of $1 in damages.
I do recall he held a dollar up.
It was a callback.
Yeah.
Closing statement in the cross examination of Alex.
Alex is such a disgusting liar, and this is just an attempt on his part to exploit his audience's obvious lack of awareness of what's actually happening in the trial.
Scarlett wanted to hug Alex and realize he was being used by the lawyers.
He told the jury he wanted to pay their expenses.
All this is complete shit.
And more importantly, Alex knows fully well that he's just lying to his audience, so they keep giving him money.
And then also, like the scarlett has a great organization.
His corporate representative, daria, under oath, testified that she suspects that it's a front.
Yes.
Also, this is Alex's attempt to portray himself as the good guy, which is all based in bullshit.
Further, he's putting Neil and Scarlett into a trap where he's casting them as characters and his personal image rehabilitation.
As far as the audience is concerned, they either get to play along and act how Alex is setting them up to which they aren't going to do, or they'll be seen suspiciously by the audience all over again.
Why aren't they speaking out in support of Alex after they realize that they were being used by the lawyers to attack the First Amendment? Maybe the evil lawyers won't let them.
Or maybe they just said that to Alex to pacify him during the trial and they actually are in league with the deep state Democrat lawyers after all.
Come to think of it, that would mean that they would have to put on a pretty good performance to trick Alex, of all people.
What if these people are actors after all? Maybe that's not the direction it would necessarily go.
But Alex is forcing Neil and Scarlett to exist in terms of his bullshit show into the future, because creating these fictitious pictures of them is helpful in terms of making Alex feel better about himself.
What he really should be doing is leaving them the fuck alone, which they've wanted all along.
But Alex is kind of like a child who's broken something and then is trying to clean it up, but he doesn't know how to clean.
So in the process, he ends up breaking more stuff.
You just want them to stop trying to help because they're not helping and they're just making things worse.
But they're a dumb kid and they don't get that.
He's kind of like that kid, except he broke that original thing on purpose.
He claims that he didn't, and then he's breaking other stuff to distract from the mess he initially made.
It's like a sociopathic version of that kid who broke something.
Yeah, he's a fucking asshole.
Yeah, that's so fucked.
But that's another part of the amorphous blob of denying Sandy Hook.
Now I get it.
I say Sandy Hook is 100% real because I've changed the goalpost to now the lawyers are manipulating these people.
That is just the same thing.
It's all one big thing.
It's not that he denied Sandy Hook happened.
It's that Sandy Hook is part of whatever it is he wants.
You understand that that is exactly the model.
You have to play the full clip.
Absolutely.
The full clip.
Oh, I need a timeline.
Give him a timeline.
There's going to be another excuse.
And even think about it in terms of world events.
Like you have this lead up to the 2016 election.
It's like we need to get Trump in.
Because if you have a Democrat in it's so bad, Trump gets in.
Oh, no, there's enemies within the deep state.
Is that's why everything sucks? Yeah, it's always something else.
The conspiracy in the narrative has to shift because that is where the money is.
That is where the ability to keep his audience interested is.
Without that, like, oh, we won, or, oh, I was actually wrong, let's move on, doesn't play.
There isn't an angle.
He's just a coward.
Well, yeah, that too.
So he does have the balls to show up on the War Room.
Oh, boy.
Hard hitting interview with time.
He had an adversarial conversation with the press.
He might have an adversarial conversation with Owen once the paychecks stopped clearing, but it would be a good time to for now, it's friendly.
So Alex has recorded this announcement and statement and he comes on with Owen, and a lot of it is kind of rehashing some of the same stuff, but he has some other things that he says that I think are really shitty.
Well, I might be going down with a Titanic, but I get the first exclusive interview with Alex Jones.
Play that violin, baby.
Person on earth right now.
No, not very good news about Kobi being made in the lab.
No, not because he covered Jeffrey Epstein while everyone else was covering it up.
No, not because he told you about the globalist corporate world government with carbon taxes, but no, because they think they've destroyed him now and the lies get to permeate on Twitter.
But Alex, you're not allowed on there to defend yourself.
That's right.
Here we are.
The jury came in on the big verdict.
Tens of millions spent by the Democratic Party law firms.
And the jury came in at 4.2 million when they asked for 150,000,002 days ago.
3 billion yesterday.
I don't have $2 million in the bank or anywhere.
Seems like a bland version of triumph for him.
There's a victory to it, but it's also blah.
Right.
They didn't spend tens of millions on that case.
But you need to think that, cause then you win.
They're down ten, I'm down 4 million.
Sure.
But they're down so much more trying to get me right.
And yeah, that's the perception that Alex wants and I don't think that has any bearing on reality.
Yes, Alex can't be like, listen, the law firm that they're specifically went through, the lead plaintiff's attorney said that he only eats what he kills.
So obviously they spent.
Yeah.
So it's a low verdict according to Alex on War Room.
The good news is it's a very low verdict for what they're asking for.
The bad news is we don't have the money to pay for it.
We can get a bond and appeal it.
We're going to move forward.
That's why I explained to listeners, you want to see the War Room or you want to see Alex Jones or you want to see Harry Smith or you want to see did everybody else.
If you want to see what we're doing here, we need your support@infoworkartstore.com.
And I was going to testify tomorrow, which under Texas law impede damages.
You're supposed to have the person under attack testify.
The judge ruled after the ruling today when they got that low ruling.
Sounds like a lot for the average person.
It is a lot, but for what they were asking for, it's small.
That I cannot speak tomorrow and my lawyer cannot put on.
Evidence because we're defaulted.
So she gets more and more desperate as she rigged this whole thing.
So it's rigged, but no matter what the judgment was, he would not be allowed to participate.
There's no bearing on any of that.
I mean, you just can't commit perjury one day and then still come back the next day.
Particularly about financial stuff.
But even so, the sanctions in terms of the default judgment, a big part of it is not cooperating with this stuff.
There was a time to provide that evidence and he very much didn't and was given multiple opportunities to clear that up and fix that.
He didn't.
You don't just get to swoop in and be like, AHA, now I will reveal everything.
It's not others works.
Yeah.
It's that example of you're never going to win with Alex.
He lives in a reality where he always wins.
So you're never going to get him to be like, oh, you're right, I fucked up in a way that means anything.
That's too threatening.
Exactly.
So he just switches into a different world.
And if he's guilty in this world, he's going to switch into a different one.
Yeah.
It's crazy.
The MCU.
But it's obviously this is all just trying to get money.
And Alex thought he'd be making more money, honestly, and he's a little disappointed.
But I'll tell you, I don't say this mainly to the crew.
We're in bankruptcy right now.
And I thought in bankruptcy, we could bring in the money we needed.
Right now we're not.
So it's a pirate victory if you don't fund info or worstore.com, order a book, order a film, get Bodies Ultimate Tumor formula, get vitamin fusion, get all the great products and infowars.
You've invested so much in us.
We've invested in you are in this together over the last 28 years on air.
Now is the critical juncture in the fight.
Now is the last few minutes of the basketball game or the football game where everybody is in a tie in a dead heat.
Now is the big boy pants time.
Now is the time to decide where you're at.
You've got my commitment.
I'll never back down.
I'll never surrender.
I'll never go away.
But I could give out.
Please support us@inforestore.com.
It is, once again, Big Boy pants time.
It's big boy pants time.
I regret to inform you it is Big Boy Pants time.
I wish it was Burger Boy pants time.
Nick Weger.
Yeah, sure.
Oh, boy.
That meme.
Someone made I struggled with that a little bit.
It's a little unfair.
But then also think about it like you're the Nick in the doughboy's comparison.
Our picture of us on Bible sources.
Right.
You're married, Nick's? Married.
Okay.
I am Mitch.
I have a cat.
Mitch has cats.
Okay.
Squinty eyes.
Both of us have squinty eyes.
I grew up in Boston for a while.
He's from Quincy.
I did not know there were this many similarities.
There are more than I'm comfortable with it.
I didn't realize none of this even occurred to me.
Do you like hot salad? Honestly, I have no doughboy's references whatsoever.
Whenever that meat thing came out, I was like, I really don't know who Nick and Mitch are.
I was like, wait, I love doughboys.
I would, honestly, if they want me to.
Come on.
Hey, you're available.
But yeah.
The only thing that obviously there's some nuances here and there, but I do not think that cakes are pies.
I haven't shaved in a while.
That was my reaction to that picture.
I'm sorry.
Cupcakes.
Cupcakes are pies.
That is not a pie.
No.
Until the day I die, that is not a pie.
That threw me for one.
Anyway, big boy pants time.
Big boy pants.
So in this interview that Alex is doing on the War Room, he frames why people are mad about him, about Sandy Hook in a particular way.
Let's correct the record on a couple of things here, Alex.
The media today says Alex Jones concede Sandy Hook happened.
I believe he did that six years ago.
We barely covered Sandy Hook less than one 10th to 1% of the time.
But when Hillary ran against Trump, she dredged up things.
Take a question.
And there was some anomalies, but it turned out I believe it happened.
So the whole thing about why people are mad about Sandy Hook is just because Hillary needed to attack Trump about something and Alex was easy.
You may remember this as the entire framing device of how Sandy Hook is covered in Alex's War, the shitty documentary made by Alex Lee Moyer.
And I think that you see how patently absurd this is and how easily tricked she was as a filmmaker.
Yeah, that's a moment where you either got to go, I'm going to be 100% complicit in this average, or you have to go, I might be shitty at my job.
Yes.
So let's not dwell too much on this because we already did that episode and I was blocked and then unblocked by their let's not worry about it without doing anything.
I didn't respond to him at all.
I have no idea what happened.
Anyway, yeah, there's something really terrible about the way Alex proceeds to the end of this episode.
In that Special Report announcement thing he did, there's a characterization of Scarlett Neil, and it's unfair.
Yeah, it's inappropriate.
But what Alex does now is worse.
I am very thankful to God, very thankful to listeners.
And I want to invite Scarlett Lewis, who doesn't have a gun control group.
She has a group about children learning love and empathy and helping children that are beat up and helping people that are being bullied so they don't become this.
I totally support her grip.
Choose love.
She came over, shook my hand, gave me a hug repeatedly, and I told her, regardless of this ruling, I want her on air.
So tomorrow I'm barred from speaking at the trial, but I'm going to go with a letter I'm going to write tonight, and I'm going to hand it to her and Neil Hesleyn, who are very sweet people.
I didn't question them on purpose.
I didn't try to hurt them.
Once I met them, I saw, God, these are totally real people.
I was brought in to stuff.
It's good to question things.
But you never even said their name.
I said, Hesley's name one time covering the Meghan Kelly interview, but that was it.
But still, I do believe that they have some pains.
This is harassment.
Like that Alex is planning out on air.
Yes.
Like Dan Pedandi.
Their lawyers don't want me to talk to them, so I'm going to write a letter and slip it to them so I can invade their space.
I'm going to go to their house when their lawyers aren't there, and I'm going to slide this letter underneath their doorstep.
You know, like a sane person who's not harassing people would do, right? Wow.
So, anyway scarlett jesus Christ.
In particular, alex seems to be wanting to paint as his new best friend.
And this is just awful.
Tuesday, I did the morning show for an hour.
You came in and took over, and I said, I believe she's a real person.
I believe he's real.
I believe they're manipulating them.
And I'm sorry, it was a ten minute rant.
They cut it down to a minute with me saying it didn't happen.
That's why the video was so blurry.
It was all blurry.
You couldn't even see me, really.
It was this audio.
Oh, my God.
And I got on the stand and I said, Scarlett, go to the fourth segment.
Go to 33 after in my show today on stand.
I said, watch it.
I said, you're real.
I said, your son's real.
Whoever gave that to use a liar.
She got up and left, came back an hour later crying, and was like, oh.
And she said, well, you're right.
So we broke through that.
They're being handled and manipulated.
Is that the lawyers then giving them edited video? She said, on stand, I was given it by my supporters.
So the point is, they gave her a minute edited video.
Imagine the sickos.
I'm on everything.
I believe you're real.
I believe your son died.
I'm so sorry.
I want to work with you.
And I believe that your ex husband's son died.
And he's a great guy.
I think they manipulated him.
I think he's kind of simple, not dumb, smart, but very trusting.
He's a rodeo guy.
He's a cowboy, which are not dumb.
They're just really trusting, nice people.
I have family like that.
So she apparently went and watched the full video that Alex was referring her to.
She wept and then told Alex that she gets it and she's being used by these lawyers.
This is fucked.
Up.
I genuinely think she should sue for defamation.
I don't know what else to say about that.
I would take that as defaming a character.
I really would.
Yeah, I really would take the idea of you claiming that she a person who I fucking don't deserve to be anywhere near her.
She's so strong and powerful and amazing.
To claim that she is your friend Alex Jones is so fucked up.
I think that one of the central things about what makes this the experience so painful is that you're being like as the parents of this child who was killed, you're being deprived of your ability to experience your life on your own terms.
Someone else is creating a caricature of you, and it's deeply painful.
And Alex is doing it again.
Here's what happened.
Alex created a diorama and then dropped it around them and trapped it in there for years, and they finally fucking got out of it.
So Alex is just building a different diorama that he's trying to trap them with.
Yeah.
And here's our last clip for our episode for today.
And I don't know, I have no words for this.
This is so unacceptable.
I mean, they are desperate.
And then a later break, hesley said, hey, buddy, I appreciate you.
Thanks for admitting my son down.
I said, yes, sir.
I tried to reach out and his lawyer went, Get over here.
Here's the clip right here.
Talk to him like that's one of the clips.
Talk to him like a dog.
So we're reaching out to them.
We're going to Connecticut.
We're meeting with them.
We're supporting what they did.
We're not going to be kept away from these families, and we're not going to be caught in the CIA New World Order propaganda operations.
Not Sandy Hook, but the media control.
Oh, and great job.
And we're going to stop school shootings too, with the Second Amendment.
That's right.
God bless you.
So obviously when he says we're going to Connecticut, that's about his other trial.
Yeah.
The Lafferty case.
I think that saying we won't be kept from these families is something that is so wrong.
Obviously, the way he's trying to portray it is like, me and the families are on the same side and these evil lawyers are trying to keep us apart because of the power that we could have together in this unity and love and all this, which is nonsense.
But the place where the real world intersects with this bullshit is exactly the same kind of harassing behaviors encouraging those from the audience.
Because let's say that Scarlet or Neil or some of these other families don't behave in the way that you would expect based on Alex's rhetoric.
Well, you should go talk to them.
Why aren't they if you're not allowed to, while these lawyers are keeping them from you? It lends itself towards encouraging harassment.
And beyond anything that we talk about in terms of the lawsuit this response is.
I mean, I agree with you.
As someone who has no legal background at all, I think this should be a cause for another action.
Yeah.
Honestly, absolutely.
I think because for God creating a mountain so big he couldn't move it, leave them the fuck alone on it and then dropping it on Alex's head.
Yeah.
Look, I don't want to use the kids terms, but you got to take the L on this one.
Alex, I got you.
Just walk away.
Just leave them alone.
Yes.
I don't know what kind of bullshit game he's doing to try and save face or create the enemy is these lawyers and not the families.
And now I'm best friends with them, but this is exploitative, it's abusive, it's disgusting, and it's the kind of behavior that lends itself towards his audience.
Not behaving in ways that you'd want.
I believe exactly that what he did was what he did.
I believe it wholeheartedly.
You knew it was going to happen.
That's exactly how it was going to go.
It wasn't going to be a, hey, listen, I'm sorry.
We're never going to talk about Sandy Hook again.
It wouldn't even have been just a quick one like, hey, listen, judgment.
Turns out it was better than we hoped for.
Frankly, I was fucking up.
Let's not talk about Sandy Hook ever again.
Honestly.
I'm putting the words on the board verboten now.
I am going to actually instead that's a great idea, but instead, what I'm going to do what are you going to do? I am going to go for the challenge mode of life, and I'm going to try and pill the family.
That is for experienced players only.
I've been doing this 28 years.
All right.
I guess if you want to go with the challenging mode.
I don't know.
Yeah.
I haven't played Dark Souls in a long time, but it's pretty hard.
I found this deeply upsetting and offensive, and that is why this is where we break for this episode.
Because I don't know, I don't know how else to really put a button in stress like that is what Alex did after the compensatory damages were right after.
And it sucks.
He'll never learn any lessons.
No.
He's a piece of shit.
We'll be back.
Indeed we will tomorrow with another episode, part two, wrapping this baby up.
And also tomorrow, you can find us on the majority report.
Oh, that's true.
That will be noon central.
01:00 PM.
Eastern.
Yes, I can't do time math.
Yeah, I can.
I don't know why I said I couldn't anyway.
What are you? Doctor who? Come on, man.
Tired.
So we're back, but tell them we have a website.
We do.
It's Knowledgebite.com.
And we're on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledge underscore fight.
We'll be back, Jordan.
But until then, I'm neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm dzx Clark.
Dreamy, creamy summer is happening, man.
Eat some ice cream.
And now here comes the sex robot.
Andy and Janzis, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.