Not knowledge fights.
Damn, Jordan.
I am sweating knowledgebitecom.
It's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledge.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're good guys.
Shang.
We are the bad guys.
Hey, everybody, welcome back.
Knowledge, right? I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple of dudes like to sit around worship at the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are.
Dan Jordan.
Dan Jordan, quick question for you.
Bright Spot today.
My bright spot today? Jordan we are recording this late due to some logistics, and so I can say that my bright spot is that we just got done recording the Majority Report.
I guess it was live.
Well, yeah, but yeah, I didn't get a chance to say some gushy things that I might have wanted to.
Sure.
But that show was very important.
I think, early on doing the show, a lot of people ask me, like, how do you stay sane listening to all this? Alex and one of the things that was really critical for me was there is a groundedness to reality in a lot of the interviews that Sam and the Cohosts do with people surrounding, like, some political things and policy issues.
And I found that to be very comforting in the same way that I don't know, my parents listening to and watching, like, the McNeil lair hours when I was a kid.
Well, it's granular.
Yes.
That's what you like.
And it's granular and it's real.
Yes.
Talking about real stuff as opposed to so much of what infowars is right, and then the entertainment value of just like, Sam and Andy Kendler breaking down Dennis Miller shit, it doesn't get better.
Isn't that? And so when we started the show, that was something that was really helpful in terms of keeping me on the level and the notion of being able to be on the show just crazy.
Yeah.
I think that this sneak week has been really bizarre.
And no disrespect to CNN or Brian Stelter, but that doesn't compare now.
Being on the Sam and the Majority Report was like, yeah, something not bucket list, but it's something that I'm thrilled about.
Absolutely.
It's big.
Anyway, what's your bright spot? My bright spot is first off, obviously that, too.
But second, my mother's in law were great also.
Shout out DJ Danucky.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Shout out to DJ Danarchy by a million.
Jesus Christ.
I just wanted to interrupt you.
I feel like we say nice things about him all the time and never enough.
Yeah, no, they invited their daughter to go to Ireland with him, and then I married her, so they have to take me now, too.
So I am going to Ireland tomorrow.
You'll be here.
Nice.
Yeah, I know.
That the Lucky charms there is.
It tastes better like a Guinness.
It's a lot like wine in Paris.
The Lucky Charms in Ireland, you just don't get them anywhere else.
I was trying to think of something that I would like you to bring me back, and I don't know, I just think of, like, racist things.
No, I was thinking about what I would want.
I would want to go someplace that has, like, the Pete moth.
Oh, yeah.
And I don't think you can really bring that back, nor would it be worth it.
I think it's illegal for me to bring that back.
It might be.
You have to declare it.
Yeah.
Which would be an odd thing to declare.
I don't drink that much these days.
So like Guinness or whiskey would not really I'll come up with something.
I'll text you.
I'll come up with something.
Okay.
And then I'll text you something.
Probably.
Very thoughtful.
I hope you have a great trip.
And that leads us to I haven't really fully decided exactly how we're going to play it yet, exactly.
But you're going to be gone for the next week.
And so our ability to record any episodes is going to be gone, basically reduced to nothing.
Right.
And so I guess if there's a giant emergency, we could, like, Skype in the middle of always.
That is a possibility.
And I don't like taking time off, so there's a decent chance I'll come up with something to do.
But temper your expectations.
After sneak week, there may be a creeping away.
Well, I mean, the truth is you need at least some break, and the only way to enforce that is to leave the country.
That doesn't work.
Doesn't work.
But maybe you take a day or two.
But, yeah, there may be one episode next week.
There might actually be none, but we're not entirely sure.
We will see what happens.
Yeah.
I mean, there's no way that we put out, like, 12 hours of content in the past seven days that people need time to catch up on.
You picked a good time to go.
Like there's nothing happening.
Yes.
So today we're going to be finishing up the trial recap coverage.
And so what that's going to be is talking about Alex's show on Friday, which is the day when later in the day, the punitive damages would be announced.
Right.
And then a bit of the afternoon and a special report Alex put out on Saturday discussing the punitive damages.
Got you.
And because you're going to be gone, I mean, it might be might have to wait a week to find out what he said about the rate on Mar Alko, how under attack we are and how the FBI has got to go.
Don't attack the FBI guys.
I didn't say that.
It wasn't me.
Anyway, we'll get down to business on this.
But before we do, Jordan, let's say hello to some new wonk.
Oh, that's a great idea.
So first, Steve, thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Next I like my mind with lettuce and tomato, heinz 57 and French fried potatoes.
Thank you so much.
Boo.
You're now a policy walk.
I'm a policy walker, not a buffet fan.
Thank you very much.
Next drink every time Jordan says right, right.
And diamond alcohol poisoning.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Take it.
Next.
Fuck the horse that gave me a little breaky in my arm.
Thank you so much.
You're now policy walk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Check out next the other Patty.
Not the Patty, the other one.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Pick out next mike.
Knowledge Fight is cathartic for depression, but not as much as UT nuclear reactor aren't.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Next.
Johnny, this is your dad.
You got to start listening to Knowledge Fight now.
Walk the dog and do your schoolwork.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy walk.
I'm a policy walk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
And we have something very exciting this weekend.
And we wanted to wish a very heartfelt congratulations to a couple who are getting married and Mr.
Impe getting tie in the old knot.
And we want to wish you nothing but years and years, as many as you've got left of happiness.
I'm not good at these things.
May all your summers be as dreamy and creamy as the dreamy, creamy summer.
You're practicing for Ireland.
That's what I'm doing.
That's what I'm doing, man.
Well done.
From what I understand, MP is a mod on one of the discords.
Okay? And there may be some Wonks at the wedding.
So that is very exciting.
That is exciting.
In honor of that, we would like to declare your wedding a raptor princess.
I'm a policy Wonk.
Four star.
Go home to your mother.
Tell her you're brilliant.
I'll barbecue your ass.
It's over for humanity.
You're a beautiful soul.
They're coming for your balls.
Well, I piss all over your god.
Very few people crap in the pool unless they're babies.
I piss all over the state.
You make it a practice of calling people pieces of garbage when they are.
Comment as you see fit.
Congratulations.
So, Jordan, like I said, we're going to get into this in part one of the series, which you put out earlier, we looked at Alex's testimony from the Sandy Hook trial and reviewed his response to the announcement of the compensatory damages which ended up being a little over $4 million.
That took us to Thursday afternoon.
And the next day, the trial entered the punitive phase which ended before we entered the weekend.
On this episode, we're going to pick up where we left off and tune into Alex's show the morning of that Friday august 5 and track the response as the reality of the punitive damages sets in.
And he has to wrestle with a very large weight that he is now carrying, both in terms of financial consequences as well as the potential fallout from his texts being accidentally turned over to opposing counsel and what that could mean for his future.
Yeah, not good.
Well, I mean, his future if you're approaching it from, like a reality.
Yeah.
But if you're approaching it from Alexand.
Here is how we start the show.
No.
It's Friday, August 5, 2022.
I'm Alex Jones, live in studio.
Strap yourselves in.
your allegation that government officials that's your dunk are aiding in petrol child trafficking grew Upstein did with her.
Wait, we're doing it twice? Same one.
Love the great meme makers out there.
Great job.
Love you all.
Love it.
So this clip that Alex is playing has cut to make it seem like Alex is dropping a truth bomb on the court.
But if you listen to the larger clip or really just Mark's response, it doesn't actually feel that way.
In reality is your allegation that government officials are aiding in pedophile records, child trafficking and the grooming of children.
Right.
You mean like what Jeffrey Epstein did with the Clintons? Sure, if that's a yes.
Is that a yes? Oh, Jeff.
No one cared that Alex brought up Epstein.
It wasn't a mic drop moment, and honestly, it wasn't even meaningful in the context of the question.
Mark just says, yeah, sure.
That was a question about Alex making accusations about the judge in this case being involved in pedophilia and child trafficking, which is conveniently not included in the memes that Alex is playing because it wouldn't support the fun truth telling thing that they were hoping to convey with the memes in the real world.
This question was part of a setup for a trap that Alex walked himself into, which helped impeach him as a credible witness in the trial.
Alex is a painfully unserious person, and this should be a great example of that.
What he said isn't threatening to anyone.
It evoked more rolled eyes than anything else in the courtroom and it was part of a line of questioning.
It was pretty effective in demonstrating that Alex was not at all a good faith participant in the trial and that his testimony was not something the jury should be taking at face value.
But it has the appearance of being something that owns the libs or something.
So people made memes and Alex decides to start his show with it because that's great.
Yeah, that's sad.
I would want at least more than one clip of a different there wasn't much to go for.
Yeah, exactly.
If you've only got the one clip, that's more sad than if you well, how are you going to make memes out of Alex? Like coughing a bunch and like, oh, you got my phone.
That would be more fun.
I would like that.
Oh, you got my text, didn't you? How about that? Well, it's harder to play that boxing commentary after that because then the messages that Alex is the one who got knocked out, you don't want to convey that it is difficult.
Now, one thing I will say is that this episode involved a bit more news than I expected.
Interesting.
I mean, there's plenty of navel gazing to go around, naturally, but there are some headlines that Alex covers, and some of them are a little bit fun.
Okay, we have the official announcements happening everywhere of shutting off the economy and the cannibalism will now be good.
New York Times, Washington Post.
There's Fegel.
All of it.
They are officially saying what I told you two years ago.
They would start saying the cannibalism is good.
Cannibalism is good.
All right, it's about time.
I have been waiting for someone to say cannibalism is good.
So this is just Alex playing fun games with headlines to create the perception that we're on the path to eating each other, which doesn't really make sense.
I thought Claus Schwab wanted us to eat bugs, but now we're supposed to eat each other.
This is dumb.
In the past, we've discussed why cannibalism is inefficient as a diet in all but the most extreme circumstances.
The calories expended to kill a person and eat them would likely not be worth what you'd get from it.
And so there's a whole other bunch of issues.
Even leaving, like, societal taboos aside, it's not a good plan.
I mean, it's not called the most delicious game.
We're called the Most Dangerous Game.
Right? And that means it's chalice.
What's going on is that the show Yellow Jackets is really popular, and that's a show that involves a girl's soccer team who are on a plane that crashes into the wilderness in Canada.
They have to survive for a long time, and apparently Cannibalism is involved in the pilot episode.
It's a really good show.
I watched it.
It's kind of like a live, but not really like it at all.
Yeah, the crash in the show happens in 1996, and the show includes tracking the girls who survived in their current lives in 2021.
And it's very heavily implied that their resorting to cannibalism wasn't entirely based on a need to eat human flesh to survive.
Oh, no, there's weird stuff going on.
You've watched it? I'll admit that I haven't, but from the reviews and breakdowns I've read, it seems like it has a little bit of supernatural nonsense and the Lord of the Flies kind of vibe in it.
I would try to discuss the plot more, but that would involve spoilers.
And honestly, from reading it explained, I have no idea what's going on with that show, and I bet you don't either.
It's one of those shows where it's like, what if we imply everything and then we'll get a second season and we'll fuck it up then, right? I think it seems like one of those shows that if I hadn't gone along for the entire ride of Lost and then also flash forward many other shows, maybe I would jump in.
Totally.
But I'll wait.
See, I didn't see Lost, I didn't see all these things, so I'm fine with it for now.
You haven't been burned.
Next season is going to be garbage and they're going to be like, we're going to explain things and there'll be midichlorians involved.
So maybe not.
You never know.
Anyway, in the wake of that show's massive success, it was released on DVD in mid July, so there is renewed conversation about it, including discussion of the coming second season and the cannibalism scene in the first episode that apparently wasn't even explained by the season finale.
People are talking about this show that they're enjoying.
So the New York Times published an oped about a couple of pieces of cannibalism related creative works that have come out recently, seemingly building on the premise that cannibalism is a hot topic in fiction these days.
Naturally, the right wing went bad shit over this and created an entire news cycle based on the nonsense idea that the Times was trying to tell people that cannibalism is actually really cool and maybe that you should eat people.
Alex is a shallow thinker and a shallower reader, so he's not read this op ed, and I wouldn't be surprised if he didn't even read the full text of the breathlessly, outraged response articles that were written about it.
But if he had read the original thing, he would have read this part towards the end.
Quote.
According to Miss Summers, cannibalism is always symbolic.
For her novel's protagonist, eating human flesh can be seen as a way of holding onto a relationship.
That ended for Miss Summers herself.
The plot of a certain hunger can't be uncoupled from, quote, my own personal experiences with disordered eating, with the tamping down of feminine appetites, the way the media chews up and spits out writers, bougie consumption and bougie lady consumption, she said.
More generally, Miss Summers thinks that the recent spate of cannibalistic plots could be commentaries on capitalism.
Quote Cannibalism is about consumption, and it's about burning up from the inside in order to exist.
Burnout is essentially over consuming yourself, your own energies, your own will to survive your sleep.
Schedule your eating, schedule your body.
The article is a thoughtful examination of some of these social commentaries that are possibly being made by themes of cannibalism that are being expressed in a very limited set of pieces of media, including a very popular recent series.
But of course, for people like Alex, it's secretly the Times telling everyone that eating people is trendy.
Now, this is idiotic kid shit, but it's fun.
At least it's something.
Here's the thing for me, I'm trying to imagine what the real world would look like if a positive Cannibalism article was released beyond right wing freak out.
We all live in a world where suddenly the New York Times is like, hey, guess what? We talked to this scientist and he's like, actually, we're super nutritious and when we die, you should eat your grandparents in front of them.
What would that look like? A conversation surrounding, hey, a lot of the world does eat insects, and that's not something that is weird to everybody.
It's a cultural thing.
Right.
There are a very efficient source of nutrition and protein.
They can be rebred a million times.
Right? Yeah, I understand that conversation.
That conversation would never happen as it relates to human flight.
I couldn't you would put a name on it.
You would be like, oh, yeah, so yesterday we ate Grandpa Joe.
And then everybody would have to stop for a second, think about themselves.
The only way it would exist in any kind of publication would be in some kind of a swifty and satire kind of yeah, it would have to be.
But yeah, it is funny too.
I do appreciate that because it does feel more normal for Alex.
Yeah, that does feel natural.
Yeah.
Having been on such a long like I'm a victim.
Right.
It is kind of nice to have a little bit of something else, even if it is entirely stupid.
I will accept that.
That was a breath of fresh air.
In a certain sense, it's still rancid, but it was fresher than previous.
Yeah.
So there's some other news down in Florida.
Things are going up, but this is before the rate on Marlowe.
Don't get too excited, okay? We're going to hit that rate.
The huge developments with DeSantis leading the charge, firing, and then having the police go to the offices of soros operatives inside the government so they can't destroy any evidence of them criminally taking orders from the big guy.
This is before Mara Lago got rated.
So this kind of idea is pretty good, right? This is a good thing.
Yeah.
So government figures being rated, it's pretty cool.
I want them to do that because they're corrupt.
So this is about DeSantis firing the Hillsborough State Attorney, Andrew Warren, because he refused to prosecute cases regarding trans people and reproductive health care cases.
Right.
The reason this is a big deal and a clear abuse of power is that the state attorney is an elected office can't do it.
And there are processes to remove the person from office, but the governor just sort of dismissing a person.
It's a little bit dicey.
Yeah.
I mean, it's probably bad if a governor is willing to just risk being a fascist and see if it pays off.
That's a bad sign, is when the governor is like, you know what, fuck it.
I bet there's a 50 50 shot.
This one works because I think that he really does this person that people voted in.
Yeah, maybe it doesn't.
And if it works, guess what? I'm dictator now.
I own Florida.
If it works, it opens up a lot of doors.
It opens up a lot of doors.
Yeah.
So Alex is not going to be hosting the show the whole time today.
And then Mike Adams in studio, always amazing.
Wow.
Coming up in the second hour, and he's going to also have some big guests on with him because I've got to go back down to this kangaroo court.
The rest of it, I'll be here for about an hour in 15 minutes and I'll be back this evening as I did last night, shooting special reports and going on the War Room with Owen Schroueer.
Three to 06:00 p.m..
I should be in there during the last hour today.
Yeah.
So Mike Adams is going to come fill in and I'll tell you what, I skipped it.
Not listen to the health ranger.
No, don't care.
His throat sounds a lot better.
I'm glad he's feeling better.
He's got 18.
It does feel like his throat sounds so much better.
He says he has a cough button and all that.
And I know that he does, but still come on.
Actually, we're going to get to it.
Yeah.
We have an excuse for why it was so bad.
Okay.
And it's great because there was some bad acting.
His excuse is pretty awesome.
Okay.
All right, listen.
So like I said, there is still some naval gazing.
There's still some talking about his own victimhood.
Sure.
And it involves Alex actually accusing the judge of criminal behavior.
And you're not going to believe what the judge is doing publicly.
She's not even hiding it.
And I believe it's criminal.
I believe it's criminal.
But again, this county is run by sorrow, so they're allowed to commit crimes.
We can't even be good people.
Will be right back.
Stay with us.
Yeah.
So the judge is committing crimes in a larger sense.
He did speak a real truth, which is that we can't even be good people.
Can is you got to parse that he is unable to be a good person.
So I said, but what he's arguing is he's not being allowed to be a person, but if you remove the parts where he's lying, then he's telling the truth.
That's a fair point.
Yes.
So Alex really wants to get into this DeSantis, kicking out this state attorney story, so he even needs to bring in a buddy to ride side car with him.
The great work that Santa is doing, literally firing these deep state soros operatives that violate their oath of office and having the state police go to their offices, make sure they don't destroy any evidence of what they've been up to.
He's got them under investigation.
Santa just gets better and better because he's actually going after the deep state.
Trump never really did that, but the Santa is doing it.
Trump fought the deep state.
Trump did a lot of things executively, but never actually took sorrow sean head on.
So we got a special guest, pastor Rodney Howard Brown, popping in at the bottom of the hour.
This prosecutor is the one that had him arrested.
Now he's been fired by the governor.
So Rodney Howard Brown is going to pop in for a segment or so.
Yes.
In March 2020, Rodney Howard Brown defied public health guidance and held church services when large public gatherings were restricted.
He was charged with some things like unlawful assembly, but ultimately those charges were dropped and he didn't really face any consequences.
Very oppressed, this guy.
Have fun.
He's going to come in and talk shit without nightmare, nightmare.
You know, Trump has given them a taste of fascism, and based on Alex's current comments about an elected official, absolutely wrecking any and all power structures.
I think they want more fascism.
Yeah, you could get some of those indications.
I think there's clues.
Yeah, I think that's what that's what I'm picking up on here.
So Alex has lost in the cumulative compensatory phase of the trial a little over $4 million.
He touches on that a little bit.
Let me do this now, because a lot of people are tuning in to the show, wanting to get my response to the $4.1 million judgment by an Austin jury yesterday.
I shot a video last night.
It's a band out video where I lay out in about five minutes my stance on it and where I stand, but I'll do that again.
Bribe is tuned in live.
I know a lot of you are tuning in, their new viewers wanting to get my view, but there's last night's announcement breaking exclusive alex Jones response to 4.2 million Sandy Hook verdict.
628,000 views.
You want to go see it? It's a very important video.
So important.
But let me just briefly chronicle what's been happening in the last week and a half now, almost two weeks as of today in this kangaroo court and how it's the model for the rest of the country and the world, and then how George Soros and the operatives are literally coordinating and running this.
Oh, man, that's quite a scoop.
I would not have said that.
I wouldn't have said that.
Why not? That's just me.
And here's why I wouldn't have said it.
Because you're not fun.
Right.
It's not so much the jury now or the judge.
It's more the sanctions that are coming.
Sure.
But also.
You're really casting your bet on the other trials aren't going to happen if you're Alex.
Because some of this post trial behavior.
I could easily see it being introduced as like.
Look.
How do you not in the way that he behaves.
How do you not I mean.
In another punitive hearing.
How do you not go.
Okay.
We did one punitive hearing.
And this was supposed to get him to stop doing this.
So here's what he said.
Hours later, he decided that he was going to imply that he will not be kept away from the Sandy Hook family.
Please.
And then accused the judge of criminal behavior.
Punitive damages doesn't even begin to describe what needs happening.
So the media in on it? The judge in on it, of course.
Soros operatives unnamed, right.
But definitely in on it.
Of course.
The corporate media that's in the courtroom are all coordinating.
The judge is coordinating with the media.
The judge is altering the record of the trial, in my view, and I'll explain that in a moment by recording it.
She didn't just say I'm guilty until the jury more than 20 times, I'm guilty, and that they had to find me guilty.
You're not allowed to find him innocent.
I found him guilty.
she barred us from being able to respond in the punitive damages phase to our net worth.
Now we turned over to them an accurate net worth at machine defaulted us.
I spent days up here with lawyers.
They got all the numbers, looked at my personal money, everything, gave them a complete list under court order.
Did they? And I knew it was all rigged, but I wanted to show the world this.
And then instead, they barred us from argument or calling any witnesses.
We could only cross examine their expert, who literally is some dandruff covered guy that looks like he has a gray wig on, stumbles around.
He has a name, like first and Howell the 7th or something.
I'm not joking.
He has like five names.
He was great.
I got to find his name in the news.
Yeah, that is my new alias.
Yeah, Wilford Snipel.
Can't argue with that.
That's a good one.
His name is Bernard Pettigil.
Yeah, it's the Pettigiel part that makes you just think of it.
Snapper people.
It sounds like that name is missing an Esquire after it, though.
Yeah.
You know what I'm saying? You can hear it.
Yeah, you can hear it.
But isn't esquire for lawyers.
Something like that.
Shouldn't be rain all esquire.
Yeah, but he wouldn't be an Esquire of the great Grimm Pivot family.
Oh, do you mean the Brooklyn Grivel pivbles? I am Dead snivel Sample God damn, that's good.
Oh, man.
Good stuff.
It's? No.
Stratford upon Avon.
And it also distracts you from the nonsense that he was saying earlier in that clip where he's talking about the judge falsifying the record or whatever.
And so I was kind of interested to hear what that meant.
And here's what he was talking about.
I was here yesterday, running around the office trying to watch the verdict, and she was killing the stream every five minutes or so because she said she would live stream it.
But we kicked their butts so bad, even though we had our hands tied behind our backs, that she killed the stream.
During most of my testimony, So that Law and Crime can only put out edited clips of me where I go, oh, that's a Perry Mason moment.
Except it's not.
Those text messages all come from me on my phone.
I gave it to all the lawyers as I testified, and now you have it proving I told you the damn truth and you guys just act like you didn't have it all.
We've got his phone.
We got his phone.
Let's give it to him.
The most generous explanation for this is that Alex is an idiot and doesn't understand that Long Crimes YouTube channel posted the long form videos of the trial and also published shorter snippets of particularly exciting moments, like when his text messages were revealed.
Alex doesn't deserve a generous interpretation, and the reality here is that he's just lying to make his audience think that the judge in this case shut down the feed and only allowed these shorter clips to go out, which is nonsense.
It's likely too late for it to matter, but I have to assume that this could constitute some kind of contempt of court type thing.
He's literally accusing the judge of crimes.
Yeah, I mean, they still have to work out the exact sanctions for both Renault and Alex.
That is still in the air.
It's not like they wrote down a number and they handed it to Alex and they were like, okay, you can keep being a piece of shit, but you're also going to owe us this.
They're still doing that.
I both watched a fair amount of feed and was there in person, and I can say with quite a bit of confidence that Alex was not kicking their ass so bad, even with his hands tied behind his back, that they would need to shut down the feed.
Also, the Law and Crime feed is not the same thing as the courts feed, which Alex is intentionally confusing.
And that's fine, it's meaningless, but he does stress this quite a bit.
So here's what I believe is illegal.
If the judge is going to let something be televised televise, it real.
Courts that they do it have a pool camera or two cameras that aim at whoever's speaking and when the judge speaks.
Instead, there's just dozens of cameras.
But they're all pet media and they all are on the same script and all put the same clips out, basically.
And the judge sits there while she controls the YouTube stream, turning it on and turning it off and turning it on and turning it off.
She got a little stream.
She just kills the stream.
She's up there like a DJ running it.
So either you're going to show people the trial or don't.
But I think it's illegal to claim something is televised and then only let out certain parts of the trial.
But when something you don't like happened, you kill the stream and then turn it back on to the other side speaking and then Bankston, their main lawyer, gets up, the plaintiff's lawyer, the ambulance chaser, and goes, listen, Judge, I want you to not kill the stream during this part because I'm an exposed at law enforcement.
Hat wants Jones's phone, and he's going down, and it's January 6 and all this stuff, and none of that's even true.
She's like, okay, I'll keep it screaming, but when my lawyer talks, she turns it off.
None of this happened.
None of it.
Not even a little bit.
This is wild.
It's just a manufactured narrative of what happened.
It is so convenient.
Shouldn't it be too convenient now for even his listeners that everything that proves he's innocent is unable to be found? But it's not.
Of course not.
They're not going to go and look and find the feed, like the full six hour videos on there.
On there.
There's no way that you could I mean, even that how do you think I pulled the clips for our lawn? Except also, what judge knows how to competently turn the stream on and off? Like Alex's cough button? Just a little foot pedal.
Yeah.
No, I mean, his lawyer couldn't even figure out how to use a fucking 8th grade projector.
No, I think I have notes about this later to bring up.
But we were there in the courtroom and the law and crime.
Their camera person was sitting next to us through a lot of the time during the trial, and they would be fixing things sometimes.
So there was, like, problems that they had with their stream and their video.
And there was at least one occasion where I remember that they came in late.
That is a separate entire feed from the zoom from the court.
Yeah, there was literally a moment where the battery got down to like, 3% because somebody had jostled their cord and it popped out.
Like, you don't know.
This is just a boring defense for Alex, but I think it's what he wants to go full on with it.
But it is what you're talking about.
It is that dynamic of appealing to the unknown.
It's like there's this other stuff somewhere that proves that I'm innocent, but you can never find it.
You'll never be able to find it.
And it's not because it doesn't exist.
It's because this evil judge, she's so evil.
So Alex certainly pissed off about being jammed up in this trial, but he's got to get to the news.
I promise you I'm going to get into world news for the rest of this broadcast.
We got so many special guests in the studio, but I got to finish up because they just gave me transcripts and tweets of what's going on down at the kangaroo courthouse there where I've been railroaded in the second phase of the damages.
I guess we're not getting to the news.
I guess we're going to do this for longer.
Yeah.
Anyway, at least it's kind of fun.
I told you the guy had a name like Thurston Howell III, but they didn't say his two middle names.
He set it on the stands.
I was there this morning.
It's Bernard.
And he goes like, Banaj Ninju papolis gubertomondius.
Petty gillis.
I couldn't believe when he said his name.
Wilford Snipple.
Snapper of the gribber pibro.
Did he say? Gutter to mondia.
No.
You could go and find him being sworn in.
He says his name is Bernard Francis Petigill Jr.
I don't remember.
Gucci demoninus the group of people.
I'm not even Ozzy.
Man davis.
No, none of it.
I can't stop saying that.
It's so good.
Gribble pebble.
Yeah.
So this is quite a conspiracy that Alex has got cooking here.
It's sprawling.
Are there a lot of players in the game now? So many.
The judge told all the news cameras, I've authorized all of you to be here, but no one else is allowed to film, and if you do, I'll have you arrested, and stuff like that.
She's on tape, and then whenever we speak, she cuts us off on YouTube and then lets them speak.
So they can then have the news crews edit down.
And they're coordinating because they put out different camera shots, but down to the same sections.
So somebody picks the time.
They got these directors back there talking to all the cameras, and then they put out what they want.
Here's an example.
Everybody told me about it on YouTube.
You'll have ten to one comments for me, and all of a sudden they all get pushed down and deleted, and a bunch of hateful comments get put to the top.
It'll have like five upvotes one with 10 up votes is removed or pushed to the bottom.
Let's take a step back and try to forget that we're listening to a celebrity racist demagogue here and really listen to what they're saying.
If anyone you knew was talking like this about how everyone was out to get them, you'd rightly understand that they aren't.
Well, but for Alex, it's just kind of his shtick.
He sounds like someone raving about black helicopters, because he's literally the same person who was raving about black helicopters 20 years ago.
He's delusional, and he's found enough people to enable and reinforce his delusions that he's been able to make it profitable and insulate himself from any consequences of his actions.
But this just sounds dumb.
Alex is getting on his show to complain about how unfairly he's being treated, which is evidenced by a completely inaccurate description of how the live streams are broadcast.
Then he's heard from other people that there's a conspiracy about silencing supportive YouTube comments, which is just pathetic.
Alex isn't even able to make this claim.
He has to say that other people have told him this is happening.
He has literally no idea if this is real at all, but it feeds into his victimhood status.
So not only is it real, it's also probably way worse than it seems and it's being directed by the judge in coordination with soros on the live streams, commenting was disabled for obvious reasons.
As far as the law and crime videos are concerned, you can go to those and still see a ton of pro Alex comments, mostly in the live chat.
It's silly to think that YouTube comments mean anything.
A lot of them are bots, many of them are people just trolling and there are plenty that just don't even make sense.
It's really sad to see a 48 year old adult whining on his show about how he's heard that there aren't enough positive comments about him on some YouTube video.
So it must be a censorship conspiracy issue.
It's nonsense.
It's just pathetic.
Yeah, I really thought we were done with allowing people to bitch about YouTube comments.
I just thought that was done.
I'm done with allowing it to mean anything.
Right.
It speaks volumes about you if you're complaining about it.
It's been in movies from 2015 where it's like, hey, don't read the comments on the YouTube.
Everybody just knows that it's a horrible place.
Right.
I think that there is still something of a conversation in terms of like abusive and directed abuse and harassment and stuff totally.
That does still exist with comments and what have you.
Of course, trying to argue.
It just goes back to the shadow banny stuff.
It's like, oh, my tweets aren't getting enough.
Likes I must be hidden by the shadow ban.
It must be too dangerous to the establishment or whatever.
And this is just that.
Yeah, the concept of maybe I'm uninteresting is just a nasty positive people.
Yeah, because he's got wilford against him.
How could he be boring? So anyway, yeah, the judge this is a cover up, man.
You got a cover up.
And she's deeply involved.
Okay, so the judge is in live time manipulating what the world can see so they can edit it to make me look bad.
So I'm asking all the listeners, they don't want you to look at the last week and a half of the trial.
They don't want you.
But there's copies all over the internet.
People are now figuring out, she's doing this without us ever asking.
And now everybody's going and finding it and going and finding what they weren't supposed to have because there were several other groups they're streaming that didn't completely coordinate.
So copies are out there.
If anybody else was recording, they were committing a crime.
And I don't think so.
Based on my experience of being there in the courtroom, I don't think that was happening for a couple of reasons.
There were only a few actual cameras and you had people like the lawn crime folks, you had the HBO documentary, right? And you also had a fair amount of security, like bailiffs and sheriff's officers or whatever, court officers.
And if someone was recording and they didn't have permission that would have been shut down.
Yeah.
Almost instantly.
I couldn't stop myself from laughing a couple of times, and I got a visit.
Yeah.
Looking around the courtroom, it wasn't packed.
There weren't a bunch of people there.
I don't think there were people who were like, bootlegging.
The trial part of it is just it really wouldn't have made sense to fit more cameras in there.
No, it would have been pointless.
It wasn't a big courtroom.
It wasn't that big, and there weren't that many people there.
Yeah.
And I think they knew it would be interesting and people would watch it.
I don't think they thought it would be that big of a deal.
Well, the court zoom was airing the entire thing.
The law and crime had a slightly better camera, and they were streaming most of it with some limitations of just their whatever was going on, whatever they were doing, and then the HBO camera.
I think there were maybe two leads to get better shots for the documentary.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Anyway, I think Alex should have to face the judge and answer for this behavior on air.
He's basically creating a large target on her by fabricating a conspiracy that the video in the courtroom was being manipulated, and this is just completely unacceptable behavior.
Yeah.
If I was in the middle of being sued and about to get a huge judgment for defaming somebody, I would not, in the same time period, want to sick people on the judge of that case.
Well, I mean, like, just me.
But that's kind of what he did when Roger Stone was on trial.
I don't know.
It seems like just behavior that he can't stop himself from doing it.
I mean, he's already put a million dollar bounty on her.
That's right.
That was the lawyer in Connecticut.
Right.
But yeah.
Hey, it's not only the judge.
It's also the lawyers.
Everyone's against Alex, and people are recording it while it's streamed now, but noticing they've gotten desperate.
So now she's cutting it off up to three or four times every ten minutes.
What? When? Why? I guess she gets a signal because they're actually signaling each other.
Their head lawyer gets up and says, now don't cut the feed for the next ten minutes, okay.
And then he goes up and says, Jones perjured himself, the Justice Department, everything else.
We got his whole phone, which they don't, all this stuff.
And then it's like, okay, her honor.
And she's, like, cuts the feed.
This is total coordination.
I don't think that this is okay.
This is a pretty serious accusation that Alex is making, all things considered.
I mean, I know that ultimately most right thinking people know that he's full of shit.
Doesn't mean anything.
He lives in topsy turvy world.
Right.
But there are real dangers that you could be putting people in by making accusations like this, and you just can't do this.
You can't accuse people of criminal behavior and criminal coordination between a judge and lawyers.
I don't know.
Yeah, at least just monsters come out of topsy turvy world to attack people.
Alex lives in topsy turvy world.
So we look at it and we're like, hey, listen, you sound like an absolute nut job.
But he's sending people and he's putting targets on people that are being sent.
That's crazy.
Yeah.
It's not okay.
Wow.
This behavior, there has to be some sort of a check on it.
But look, hey, Alex has got to get to the news, and honestly, this case is meant to distract him from this large work that is so important that he needs to do.
Okay? They're trying to distract me from my work, but they're not going to distract me from my work.
And that's why I'm not down there.
At the second phase of the trial today, okay, is because no matter what the globalists do, well, I'm still breathing air, or while I'm not locked up in a prison, I am going to be fighting these people.
It's that simple.
But I can't stand the fight without you.
So they want me to talk about their attacks.
They want me to get diverted into defending myself.
But you understand, we're going to stay in the attack and we're not going to let them distract us.
So what is it that they're trying to distract us from? Well, there's this stack.
It's the stacky.
It all comes back to the stackies that they're trying to distract us with.
They're trying to distract us from knowing about what I'm about to cover.
And so I'll be back today in the fourth hour, and I'm going to co host with Robert Barnes back today, co hosting some in the war room, because I'm not going to let them silence.
I said tomorrow.
I'm going to be here most of the day, even though my five year old daughter is begging me to take her fishing.
She has no future if I don't do this.
So I'll be here.
And I'm not a martyr.
I'm not a victim.
I'm saying that I'm going to work harder because they're trying to silence us, because I know it's our mission.
And when I get tired and think it must be somebody else's job to do this, when I see it bearing fruit what we've done together, I realize I've got a fight now hard I ever had.
So I'll cover this more in the fourth hour after Mike atoms takes over with some special guests.
Thinks he's got lined up that are huge.
People are really excited.
Let me just hit these headlines so you know what's coming up.
These all tied together.
I hate that every time the globalists are really acting up and duty calls.
The real thing that ends up happening is that Alex's daughter doesn't get to do something fun.
It is.
How many times has he not taken her fishing? It's so many times.
Yeah.
Don't tell me about how you need to take your daughter fishing when you haven't.
That's sad for me.
Yeah.
There's a theme of like, I got to fight these globalists.
I was going to take my daughter fishing.
Can you imagine her sitting at home with a fishing pole? He said he was going to come today.
Yeah, absolutely.
No, this is a wilful recontextualizing your neglectful parenting as here's the good news.
What's the good news? That plan didn't exist to begin with.
There was no fishing trip.
That's true.
That is all just dramatization.
Yeah.
Anyway, Alex is going to do a fun run of headlines and so I decided he's like, these are all connected and this is what the globalist to try and stop us.
Sure.
So we're going to go on this run with him and see what happens.
Let's go.
So here's the first headline.
These all tied together.
Swedish scientists advocates eating humans to combat climate change.
It's all over the news how's that was coming.
Swede Eat people.
So this is a headline from 2019, which Alex doesn't know because his team just Googled cannibalism and printed out everything they could find.
That seems like it could work.
Ouch.
Alex does not prep for this show, so he's cold reading headlines, just making up context for them.
And in this case, he's pretending that it's a current story.
This was about Magnus Soderland, who went on Swedish TV and was interviewed about some research he was doing into social taboos about food sources.
Basically, human meat was used as an extreme example of something that pretty much everyone considered past the line.
But where exactly was the line? Lab grown beef, artificial meat, insects.
Where do people feel like? I don't know.
He doesn't want people to eat people.
And that wasn't something he was advocating at all.
Magnus very astutely deduced that his words had, quote, being hijacked by people who don't believe that global warming and other climate issues should be taken seriously.
And one of those people was a writer for the Epoch Times who wrote a headline that Alex is now reading on air.
This is a bullshit story with no connection to reality that was published three years ago.
So this string of headlines is off to a very strong start.
So you're saying that the Swedes have not started eating each other? Not to my knowledge.
Okay, all right, look, I don't have anybody on the update.
Where's Sonia? Sonia.
So here's the next headline.
Video Transcript biden Transport Secretary again touts expensive electric vehicles.
A solution for high gas prices.
So, yeah, Pete, but a judge said that maybe electric cars, maybe we could get some subsidies for people to be able to afford electric cars.
And that is related to eating people how? Well, because he said that the Swedish person said that you should eat people to help with climate change, which isn't really true.
Okay, so maybe the climate change aspect of it is.
Right.
I appreciate you trying to track the connection.
I'm doing my best because he said that they're specifically all connected and all I have right now is sweetie people and drive electric cars.
Well, let's see if we can find some more connective tissues.
Okay.
Hypocrite.
Trudeau caught magic or flying on a private jet, but he says you shouldn't be able to have air conditioning or a car.
I thought it was Obama who didn't want people to have air conditioner or a car, which isn't true to begin with, but it's something that Alex repeats a lot.
But I guess it's now just toss it on there.
I'm starting to suspect that maybe Alex really is just cold reading headlines and hasn't seen any of these things at all.
But he's just pretending they're connected because we have a three year old article about cannibalism, comments that Pete Buttigieg made about electric cars, right.
And a picture of Trudeau not wearing a mask.
This can't be the super important work the globalists want to distract Alex from, because this is ridiculous.
I wrote down earlier whenever he was saying, like, this is all a distraction from my work and I won't allow it.
And it's like, if that is true, just on its face, shouldn't the news currently be gargantuate during the trial? Now, maybe you could even consider Trump's raid being gargantuan.
But that was after the trial, right? So during the trial, shouldn't there have been a nonstop barrage of like, holy shit, there are fires going up inside of your home right now? Because then Alex would be able to cover it.
Exactly, right.
That would justify the distraction era.
But I feel like the news was mainly like, we're going to try and lower gas taxes.
No.
Sweden has given the green light before on eating people, but Alex doesn't know that and he's presenting it as current.
I guess we had to sue Alex Jones to make sure that Swedes could eat people.
And let me say this real quick.
I know what the Swedes do with meatballs, and if that's the precedent of how they're going to serve people, I'm out.
I'm out too.
Thank you.
I'm just saying that Scandinavian food is not bad food, but there are way better food.
You're not going to trick me to eat people with Lincoln berries, I can tell you that right now.
I won't even eat their fish, let alone their people.
Boo.
So here's the next headline.
The climate cult is eager to take advantage of Europe's energy crisis, and they're now announcing in Spain and Germany they're going to control remotely, as we told you, decades they would with the smart meters, what temperature you can set your house to no lower than 80.
So this is just an oped on zero hedge that's completely meaningless as proof of anything and doesn't even include any bits about remotely controlling people's.
Thermostats that stuff that Alex is writing his own story about, but it's very real issues surrounding energy rationing proposals in countries that could be more directly affected by Russia's ability to control the flow of oil and natural gas.
Right.
It's less a question of remotely controlling smart meter thermostats and more city councils being asked to do everything they can to conserve energy after this is a string of headlines about reducing car ownership.
So I guess that a bunch of these headlines could be said to be connected, but I'm struggling to make the larger, meaningful connection, and the cannibalism is just flashy and fun.
I think that I understand what Alex wants the connection to be, but it's pretty much just in his head.
He's basically laying out the climate change advocates.
It's an elaborate plot to destroy society through making people unable to have energy resources, which will make them unable to get any food.
So I guess the media is trying to prepare people for the idea of eating other humans.
Mind you, this is entirely different than Alex's big rant about how he was willing to barbecue his neighbors to feed his children.
When Alex discusses cannibalism, that's actually genius.
And he's making a larger point, whereas when people he doesn't like to do it, it's proof of Insidious plan to depopulate the planet.
This list of headlines is legitimately depressing, and he does not need a lawsuit to distract him from doing his job.
He's doing fine on his own, and his job is completely meaningless.
Yes.
I don't know.
You just don't get to complain about cannibalism if you have already made the plan in your mind to murder your neighbors and feed them to your kids.
Yeah.
High profile, publicly, totally.
Say it out loud.
You're on the record as that as being an acceptable strategy.
When it comes to that, I feel like you shouldn't be able to talk shit.
I know.
It was a pretty graphic thing.
He was very graphic.
It was like his neighbor accidentally hit his window with a baseball that day.
So we have a couple more headlines, even though I had lost my patience with this, naturally.
But yeah, there's some that are actually kind of interesting.
Okay.
Australia's Great Barrier Reef defies climate doomsayers with record coral comeback.
The truth is, coral reefs grow.
They die, they come back.
Wow.
The headline that he's reading off Breitbart.
But it's kind of a dishonest framing of the story.
While it is true that parts of the Great Barrier Reef are seeing considerable healing, that's not true of the reef as a whole.
The northern area of the reef saw gains in hard coral cover, but the southern section actually went down.
This is good news, but it's part of a larger picture.
One of the main concerns about the reef is hard coral cover, but another equally important aspect is bleaching.
Bleaching is the result of a temperature or weather anomaly that leads to the coral expelling the algae that give it its color, resulting in the coral becoming white.
It's not dead at that point, but it's at a significantly greater risk.
And importantly, reefs are complicated systems that are capable of healing.
So if there is some bleaching, the coral can become home to algae again and come back to what you call like a vibrant life.
Right.
The concern among scientists is that weather events that cause large scale bleaching have been increasing in frequency.
There have been four mass bleaching events in the past seven years and experts don't know how resilient the reefs are to this heightening pressure.
It's an open question and it's frightening.
The implications.
Another aspect that is of concern is mentioned in a Reuters story about this quote on the downside, the growth in cover has been driven by acropora corals, which the Australian Institute of Marine Sciences said are particularly vulnerable to wave damage, heat stress and crown of thorns starfish.
This is coral cover that is increasing, which is good, but it's a type of coral that's highly likely to be susceptible to the sorts of weather events that are becoming increasingly common, which is a big reason to be worried.
This increase in cover could lead to false hope, or conversely, to people like Alex ignoring the details of the story in order to use it as a prop to attack climate science as invalid.
As per usual, Alex has no idea what he's talking about, but he's got a bright bart headline and that's enough to trick his audience into thick knees.
An expert.
So we were at a museum and whole area in San Francisco a few years back and they had this massive section of the place.
Now, it used to be something different and now it was just all devoted to the coral reef.
And the way that coral was dying and everything was so fucking sad because their goal was like, you used to walk in here and see some cool stuff and then be like, wow, that was fun.
Now I'm going to go fight Australians to save the coral reef.
That's how you walk out of there.
And it is a tragic, tragic situation.
True.
And then some of the positive news that ends up coming out and you hear about the Great Barrier Reef is the result of very aggressive conservation effort.
Yeah.
And so when you're like, oh, why isn't it dying so fast? Because people are taking it very seriously, as hard as they possibly can with everything they've got all the time.
You try to pick up a piece of coral and they will snipe you.
Yeah.
And I don't even want you reporting good news about it, because then people are going to be like, oh, things are getting better.
No, you're just not reporting enough news about how it's dying every single day.
I think that balance is tough to strike.
It is a little bit.
Difficult.
So we get another headline.
Okay, this one's fun.
Major new findings.
They are reanimating not just dead spiders, but now pigs.
Frankenstein is real.
From NBC News.
Holy shit.
Get the torches.
Does he think that the soul is included with the reanimation? I don't know.
He doesn't expound on this at all.
I want more.
So, Jordan, I have some news for you.
What's that? No one's reanimating spiders.
God damn it.
Alex probably just saw a headline about research that was done at Rice University where they found that they could use dead spiders as a way of gripping things.
Essentially, it has to do with how spider legs bend and how all you really need to do to manipulate them is apply a hydraulic pressure inside the spider's abdomen.
The researchers used a needle to puff air into them and found that they were able to expand and retract the spider's legs.
Personally, I think this is a little fucked up, but I don't know how much of a high horse any of us has to be about like, oh, you got to respect the sanctity of dead spider.
Yeah, I'm not sure it's weird, but it's pretty interesting.
If I stepped on it a few days ago, I can't be mad if somebody's like, look, I can make it legs work.
Right? I'm not going to be mad.
If you watch the video with the researchers too, one of the things they bring up, it's like it's kind of tough to argue with, is that it is like biodegradable material.
Sure.
Right.
Okay.
You end up in a strange position, though, if you're like, breeding spiders in order to kill them.
Yeah, what are we talking about? I hope that would not be the path things go.
Right.
Anyway, that's not the implication that Alex is taking.
I think they're reanimating.
That's the issue.
As for the pig thing, alex just skimmed a headline about this, but it's a little closer to reanimation.
It's just not that it's a pig getting reanimated.
It's a cellular thing.
This has some considerable philosophical implications and could stand to revolutionize processes used in organ donation.
But it's not Frankenstein, or at least not yet.
I do find myself unnerved slightly by this portion of an NBC News article about this quote.
The pigs treated with organic eggs startled researchers during experimentation.
The dead pigs heads and necks moved under their own power.
The animals remained under heavy anesthesia.
The researchers do view the neck jerk as an indication that muscle function was restored after death.
If you're someone who believes that all science fiction is secretly real, I can see how you might respond to this like Alex does.
It's silly, but I get it.
Yeah.
Anyway, I'm still having trouble with the exposed connection of all these stories.
Even these two stories allegedly, about reanimation aren't connected in any meaningful way at this point.
I was so bored of this list of headlines, and it's getting really redundant.
So I decided it was time to move on from this fun run.
Yeah, but that story about the pigs is like that is something I wish someone who is like Alex, but not Alex and maybe a little bit more in touch with reality could have a take on.
Because I think it's a little bit like your reaction, there is a place for that, right.
No.
Restore muscle.
I think what's interesting to me about this is the idea of consciousness.
Like, okay, you're worried about Frankenstein and all that stuff, but are you telling me that the consciousness returns with its previous memories? Of course not.
Otherwise what you're saying do spiders have a meaningful no, but what I'm thinking is, if you're saying that reanimation is possible, then when I die, I'll die, my consciousness will end, and then suddenly I will theoretically awaken years later in the same or a different body.
Like, that's not how it works.
No.
So there's no such thing as the soul, is what I'm trying to say.
That's fine.
Yes.
That's not even close to anything that is implied by these.
Right? No, that's the only thing I care about.
When you talk about pigs coming back to life, I'm like, I'm worried their souls aren't going to be okay.
Well, one of the things that comes up in articles about this is the sort of philosophical implications in terms of what do we categorize as death? Right.
Because if someone has a heart attack and their heart stops, which is your heart's muscle, if they're able to pump the heart, re, bring back muscle tissue sure.
Is that something that they would be able to do? There are all kinds of questions that are raised by this, but yeah, it's not like you've been dead for a week and now we can bring you back.
Okay, so you're brain dead.
They can't bring back the function of your nerves, so far as we're aware.
I don't know.
What, are you just going to jolt people with electricity like in Frankenstein? Based on Alex's coverage? I feel like that's the plan.
Okay.
Yeah.
I don't know.
From what I've actually read on this, I think we'll find out more when there's more research done.
Sure.
Pretty early stages on a lot of this stuff.
Probably not Frankenstein.
We're not at the dolly, the sheep level of bringing people back to life.
No.
Got you.
So you brought up the torn larynx.
Sure.
Earlier.
And I told you there was a torn.
There's a phone update on there.
Oh, yeah, it's healed.
Actually.
There's a suspect in this.
And all the studies show 5G causes major asthma and problems.
And I'm literally driving down Congress this morning after an hour in court to get to the show, and I'm coughing the way I've never coughed in my life.
And I said, you know, the studies are 5G causes serious breathing problems and coughing like this, it only happens when I'm in 5G areas, they need those for self driving cars.
And all of a sudden a Ford self driving car drives by.
But it went internally.
We didn't get video of it.
A robot car drive by two minutes after I was selling my security guys.
That's crazy.
Wow.
Robot cars make them cough.
That reminds me, outside of the courthouse, I was making the jokes and I didn't reference five g to rob DU's tiedyed friend.
Yes.
And now here, she didn't even know that the 5G from her phone was causing Alex's cough in the courtroom.
Well, I mean, I just assumed that courtroom is full of 5G.
She was the one who had the biggest phone, though.
I noticed that on the stand.
Alex didn't say, five g is making me call.
He did not say crazy flies on his show.
I wonder why he said it's.
Torn larynx.
Yeah.
Anyway, he leaves and then he comes back in the fourth hour right after having gone to the courthouse.
How did it go for it? Well, we have not figured out yet exactly what the judgment will be, but the fourth hour starts and they just play special reports like what's going on here? Sure.
We get 20 minutes in and Alex finally shows up with Barnes and toe.
Well, we have an update on that, but also I should say in advance, alex uses an r slur here and I just want to it's no good.
All right.
We ran some promos earlier because for some reason robert Barnes was here sitting around for like an hour waiting to go on air, and he thinks he's supposed to be on air, so he left.
We're not going to be stopped.
Not going to happen.
There's so little human communication now, though, like person to person.
And that's how the globalists are beating us, is people don't communicate with each other at the shopping mall or the store.
You don't even tell barn sweating what's going on.
Mentally retarded.
That's really the fount of all of this.
So he wasn't on air for 20 minutes because Barnes thought he didn't need to go on air.
So he left and he was trying to call Barnes and convince him to come back.
That's crazy.
I can't go on without you, Barnes.
That is absolute insanity.
People don't talk to each other.
You can text in the courthouse.
I was on my phone the whole time.
It's true.
You could have texted Barnes when he were going to be back to go on air, but that would have happened.
Debated the made him call.
G doesn't want to do he's right.
You're right.
Everybody's right.
So look, man, alex, he said he was going to cover the news when he came back in the fourth hour.
Sure.
But now he can't because Barnes isn't there.
Watch.
Humanity dying is so sad.
So sad.
But it's like a skeleton coming down fast.
But I'm miles above you.
I mean, the globalists who are trying to bring down humanity.
Good, safe.
We have a lot to cover.
Prepared for hours for this.
But we sit around 20 minutes.
They're like, Get out of here.
Come on, now.
Gorillas knocking her head up against the wall.
It won't matter soon.
The food's getting cut off and it just gets off.
I think it's actually a good thing.
We've already killed so many kids in the womb.
Let's just start starving everybody to death right out of the oven.
That is where we are.
All the Wimps that have lived off the system, all the frauds that have hidden behind their BS, it's all over now.
So I guess we all deserve to die because Barnes isn't there.
This is a mood swing.
Yeah, that happened quick.
That happened quick.
He's so mad at me.
Somebody had abortions one time.
Let's all die.
Yeah, right.
I feel like the judgment hasn't even come down, really.
He's just bard.
My God.
Alex is in a bad mood.
Yeah, I can tell.
Because you're unconscious.
You will die.
Okay.
Because you're living in a dream.
You will be destroyed.
Aren't you going to die? You don't live in a dream here.
I don't live in a fantasy land.
I live in the real world.
That's painful to watch, but nevertheless, everybody's got their own idea how things work.
So you go ahead and do it your way and see what happens.
Okay? I have a few video clips I want to play here.
And one of them is Dick Cheney.
The war criminal.
The torture master.
The architect of 911.
The globalist criminal.
The guy that sold America out for the Council on Foreign Relations and made jokes about it on national TV.
How he was an enemy of America.
Has the nerve to get up and say people running against his daughter in her congressional race are the enemies and that Trump is the enemy.
So one angle on Dick Cheney putting out a video saying Trump sucks is to lash out at Cheney and say, who are you to talk to? I bet that's fair.
Another way to look at it is that Cheney is a fucking monster of historical scale, and even he realizes that Trump is a pile of shit.
I guess this is a glass half full or half empty thing.
And you have that.
Yeah.
You guys have fun? Yeah.
Cool.
Joy.
So Barnes shows up.
What? Yeah.
Why? He pulled the car around.
No.
Don't show up.
Barnes.
You're just going to get his bad mood on you.
No, actually, Alex's mood changes a bit.
No, he perks up a little bit and makes me think that maybe Barnes is holding or something.
But here's a little secret.
They don't want me to say it until everything's closed out, but under Texas law, their $4 million judgment is half.
And if they do a huge billion dollar putative, it's capped at one point.
Something million.
Yeah.
It's.
750,000 bankston was out there the other day.
The plaintiff's lawyer was out there spinning to the media how there was going to be a 50 million, $100 million kind of judgment coming in.
Punitive damages completely got wrong.
The media was recycling this as if it was the truth about Texas law.
The AP says I'm worth 270000000.
This company has majorities I'm in the hole.
Exactly.
That's why I tell my wife I got to bow the yard.
I'm telling her we got to fire the lawn staff.
Yeah, you're in tough times if you think that endears you to me and makes you a relatable character.
Honey, we can't afford our gardener anymore.
No, he said garden staff.
That's right.
He said staff.
Alex.
I think there's something about Barnes that just brightens up a room, and I think you can feel it.
Alex is so much happier now that Barnes is there.
He's got his buddy.
There is something about Barnes's ability to weather so much bullshit and kind of like, spin it into a, like, little positive thing for Alex.
It is kind of a gift he has.
I think that he hypnotizes Alex with his phrases.
Yeah.
He says blank and blank.
Yeah, all the time.
Yes.
They're dipping and dodging.
They're the gribble pimples of anybody.
They are lying.
And it's almost always illiterative.
And there's something about those speech patterns that I think Alex gets sucked into.
It's not a bad thing to learn.
Yeah.
So look, most of this fourth hour is Barnes being full of shit and advertising.
It's really just trying to get money.
Right.
Here's my problem.
I could get major National Foods guys that are on Handy and on Back, and I'm not attacking them.
Maybe they're smarter than me.
Their food makes 60, 70%.
Ours makes 30% because it is the best lowest price.
I have this weird neurotic thing to give our Listers the best deal, right.
So I would probably actually be rich like them if I did that.
Oh, man, that's wild.
Did you know that Alex gets his survival food buckets from my Patriot Supply? I did know that because Glenn Beck sells his survival food through my Patriot Supply, too, for years.
I'm not sure if Hannity actually sells food buckets at this point, but he definitely did it in the past through my Patriot Supply.
Oh, yeah.
They also sponsored Dan Bongino and have sponsored Ben Shapiro and Rush Limbaugh and countless other right wing shit talkers who seem to include an insistence that you'll soon need emergency food because the government is going to go full dictatorship in the rhetoric, which is just a strange coincidence.
It's a good strategy.
It really fucking work.
So what you're telling me is that even if I'm a huge Shapiro fan, or even if I'm a huge Glenn Beck fan, what I should do is instead of getting my Matrix supply from them, I'll get a cheaper price from Alex, correct? In theory, yes, but I don't think that's true.
I have, in the past, gone and looked at, like, various deals that were offered.
I don't think that's true.
What I think is going on, if Alex is describing anything that's real, it's that he has such a bad negotiating position that he gets a lower cut than Ben Shapiro or Glenn Beck does.
That would be my hunch.
Yeah, that's more likely.
But yeah, it's all the same company that's playing all of these people, their buckets.
Probably not Jim Baker, though.
I think he probably has a different operation.
I think he puts his own food in those buckets.
Yeah, he cooks it himself.
Yeah, he sells.
So Barnes has an interesting theory about what's coming in the punitive case here, two jurors wouldn't even join in the verdict, and for the punitive damages, they need unanimous jurors to even get any punitive.
What's your prediction this afternoon? Or maybe it'll be longer on punitive.
I don't think that you said I don't mean to kiss your ass, but you said beforehand yesterday, you said on air, you said, I think it's below 5 million.
There's a very good chance that they can't even get puma.
Yeah, well, that's a seven figure verdict, and I don't think the punitive damages is going to come in anywhere near what they're talking about.
Again, it's purely show at theater, symbolic at this point, because the cap is 1.5 between both claims before Alex cut them off, barnes seemed to be going in the direction of I don't think they're going to get any punitive damage.
They're very much downplaying what will come back.
I think that's part of their storyline that's still going on, that they pilled the jury and they saw through it and everything.
It's going to be a little bit of a deflation when the 50 million number comes around.
It's interesting to hear about the cap, because the more I read about it, the less clear it becomes.
And from what Mark has told me is that part of the reason that this whole thing is going to get weird is that if they want to, there's something written within the caps of, like, if this is extraordinary bullshit beyond what anybody could reasonably expect.
Fuck the cap.
Let's go hard on this guy.
Like, that kind of thing.
But that's going to lead to appeals and appeals and all that stuff.
So I'm not sure, but whatever anybody is reporting about the cap, it is up in the air still.
Yeah.
There are a number of different dynamics that are at play, as far as I know, about anything about the case and about how this law works.
Let's see what happens.
Exactly.
I have no idea.
Everything I've read is like, who the fuck wrote this law? Yeah.
And I think that Alex's entire bankruptcy situation overcomplicates it even more, of course, and could work to his disadvantage.
Right.
And so we'll see.
Anyway, Barnes decides he's going to jump in with Alex on this whole, like, the judge is committing crimes thing.
Great idea for a lawyer.
Yeah.
I would say Barnes being a shit.
He's going to be a media star again.
I think it's criminal to have a judge say this is televised and that she cuts the YouTube off when we speak or lawyers speak she doesn't like, but only puts it on when they're having their people speak.
I mean, I think that's wrong.
I mean, all of it was scripted.
It was literally three movie cameras in there.
The only thing that went AWOL for them is they didn't get the ending that they wanted.
And they didn't get the ending they wanted because even a liberal Democratic jury in Austin that was selected by these plaintiffs lawyers rejected the core aspects of their theory and thesis.
They got to see you theory, thesis, and you were not the caricature that they tried to make you out to be.
And even though they played tracking those altered edited videos, sometimes only five, 7 seconds long, in fact, I think one was like 2 seconds long.
About you is 5 seconds.
Yes, 5 seconds.
Personally, if I was a plaintiff lawyer, I would not have put me in the trial.
I would not have put things into the trial.
I would not have put the allegations and concerns about the judge into the trial.
You know who else didn't want to put Barnes into the trial? Barnes.
Yeah, he was Alex lawyer until shit got too hot and he quit or got fired.
And now the Info's corporate rep has testified under oath that they're exploring suing him for malpractice.
This is all just such horse shit.
Barnes is a weak loser hiding on Alex's show, pretending to have an expert opinion, acting like the reality that he took an active part in this didn't happen.
How does he pretend to be a lawyer and then get on air and say that the case was scripted and the plaintiff's attorneys selected the jury as if that wasn't a process that the defense was equally involved in poorly.
This is just low.
This is nonsense.
I don't know.
He should give up his own license for engaging in this shit.
What he should have said is, if I was the defense's lawyer whenever they chose the jury, I wouldn't have said, Will you talk to me? Will you talk to me? I don't think he even will about that.
No, I don't think he does either.
So we have one last clip here from Friday, Alex's show at least.
Yes.
And this is just nonsense.
Here is the same lawyer that the worst part is.
I said, lock her up.
So the end of the day, it's like we're here because he criticized Hillary.
Here it is, Alex Jones representative saying, I know he was reckless.
Alex knows he was reckless.
And then immediately going.
But Megan Kelly said it.
But the truthrs said but there were other websites.
But Hillary Clinton? Hell, at one point I thought he was going to start yelling or chanting, lock her up.
Wow, you guys are good at fake laughing.
They're like, literally trying to sniff Hillary Clinton's butt.
But she's a politically dead item.
So that's the sort of clip where you have to ask yourself if Alex even thinks his audience is conscious.
It's clear what Wes is saying in that clip, that Alex is trying to dodge responsibility for his actions by saying that other people said things, too.
And then he punctuated his claim by joking that he was surprised that Alex didn't yell lock her up.
Alex is pretending that this is somehow a statement of support for Hillary or an admission that this case is only happening because of Hillary.
But it's pretty tough to get there from what the actual clip that is played says.
I can't.
I mean, that is so impregnably obvious that this is the most gaslighting that you can do and that laughter is so forced.
This is two dudes lying their asses off about the situation they're in, trying desperately to put on a triumphant face for the audience.
They need to keep giving them money.
If there wasn't a resolution that could be spun as a victory here, the audience would probably get it through their heads that sending Alex money is throwing your money into a pit.
So it's critical to keep a stiff upper lip and pretend that you're having a great time being sued.
You actually won when you think about it.
I mean, they rejected the theory of thesis.
In a certain sense, what has happened is that Alex Jones's money making operation is now a savings account for the families.
So the more money he makes, it's going to them at the end of the day.
Unless he's getting real fancy with some bookkeeping.
If he's getting real fancy with some bookkeeping, he's going to jail.
And I think that would be better than having a savings account.
Well, it would certainly limit his ability to bullshit.
So the Wool Room comes on and our boy, the Cock Destroyer, aka the puppet, comes on.
Sure.
And it's a little bit dramatic.
This is Mike Adams, level dramatic.
Okay.
Today is a major turning point in the political paradigm shift that has happened in the west that used to value individualism, freedom, prosperity, life, tradition, creation, what? And we now pivot into a dystopian Western world that values oppression, stopping the force of humanity, depopulation Satanism, anti life, anti freedom, antitruth but the important turning point, the important page that we turn today, is that now the American left, the liberal, progressive Democrat left in America, has now taken off the mask.
They now know they're the bad guys.
Sure.
They have now accepted their role as the bad guys, and they are now embracing it wholly.
Okay? And so that is the point we're at now in human history.
This is some serious baby shit.
In all the course of human history, every good or bad decision that's ever been made that's had geopolitical consequences, many by left leaning politicians, has all been nothing compared to the day that Alex Jones learns that he has to pay people for defaming them.
Was it the end of the free world when Fox settled their defamation suit with Seth Rich's parents? Or when CNN settled with Nicholas Sandman.
I feel like it wasn't probably because Alex's Narcissism is so strong.
It's such an important part of what makes this show and everything on Infowars work for the audience that Owen has to tap into it in order to exist in that environment.
This is really pathetic to act this way.
And I have zero respect for Owen or his proclamations of us announcing that we're the bad guy.
But if he wants to act this way, I have just one thing to say to him.
What's that? Hey, yo.
That's a Scott Hall reference.
You wouldn't have got it.
Wouldn't have gotten it.
Scott hall was the bad guy.
I mean, here's the thing about a podcast.
It's like, know your audience, but if it's just you and me here so you do know an audience.
But bad times don't laugh.
Bad guys do.
Anyway, in the tradition of Alex before him, owen decides he's not hosting his show today either.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is Friday, August 5, 2022.
This is the Infowars war room.
Brought to you by Infowarstorecom.
And I have to tell you, today's broadcast is going to be a great one.
Now, I am live in studio right now, but Clay Clark is about to take over with so many great guests that it's going to be a great transmission.
So Clay Clark is this guy who does the Reawaken America tour, and they go and do these Q and on adjacent speakers.
And Alex.
Was there one? Jim Brewer.
Does anybody work there? Does anybody work there? Like Barnes didn't even no.
Hey, look, dude, I understand what you're saying, but as far as Owen goes, I'm going to give him a pass because he keeps having to host his own show.
And that's true.
That's true.
It is true.
I have a little bit of sympathy for him because they are making him do double duty.
He is working awful hard.
Yes.
But it is funny that on the day of Alex's punitive hearing, alex just decides, I'm going to go to the court.
And then Owen is like, what are we going to do? But he says that they have some big guests.
Sure.
Clay Clarke has some big guests.
Absolutely huge.
I was like, I don't believe this.
Okay.
And then here's how Clay Clarke's parts start.
Hey.
Well, General Flynn and Peter Davaro, welcome on to the Owen shroyer.
And Alex Jones show.
Gentlemen, I appreciate you being here.
My brothers.
Hey, this is quite a duo to start things off for Clay.
Yeah, we all know Mike Flynn, but Peter Navarro isn't necessarily someone who's been on Alex's show in the past, or at least not to my knowledge.
Yeah, he was an aide within the Trump administration, and overall, he's basically a shithead.
He's currently facing contempt of Congress charges for refusing to comply with subpoenas and the investigation into January 6.
That's why I know his name.
He's also in hot water for conducting official government business on a private phone and then refusing to turn over records from that phone, insisting that he needs to be granted immunity before he'll do so twice.
Probably going to end up in jail before this whole thing is said and done.
Anyway, here we have a real QAnon adjacent, government overthrowing enthusiast panel happening.
Not quite sure what I expected from the war room, but I'm open to seeing where this goes.
That is a bold statement to come out with.
We're welcoming General Flynn and Peter tomorrow, today, and it gets Better to have a fucking crazy talk.
Okay, here we go.
And we have Mike Lindell here.
Who what? What is happening? He always says this is the best buyer in America.
He's also passionate about exposing election fraud.
Joining us, Mike, we know that you three are going to somehow be in that White House serving once President Trump gets back.
What everybody in America needs to know right now as people are being discouraged and demoralized.
What would you like to say? What kind of encouragement would you want to share with the listeners, Mike? Well, the same thing I did on the stage here at CPAC this morning, everybody.
We've got all the tools you need to watch by August 20 and 21st is called the Moment of Truth Summit.
It'll be live stream at Frank speech for 48 hours straight.
This will change our country forever.
It's awesome.
So when the former president calls Mike Lindell the best ad buyer, what that translates to? Is he's a mark? He'll fund anything.
Yeah, I wouldn't want to be called the best ad buyer.
That is a dumb thing to call someone.
You better ask some real serious questions if someone calls you that.
Mike Lindell, he's starting to sound like a gravelyer older Jesse Ventura.
Well, they are both from Minnesota.
Right.
Okay, well, that makes sense.
Yeah.
I think he's got the speech pattern.
That comparison has been made by other people, I think I've heard in the past.
Yeah.
Mike Lindell.
Holy whoa.
So he just can't stop himself from doing these telephone.
And they always go bad in the middle.
The last one where he was going to prove that China stole the election was a complete disaster.
And this one is not going to go better.
I went to the website for this summit, and there's actually a really fitting image on the landing page.
It's Mike standing in.
Front of Mount Rushmore, waving an American flag.
Conveniently, he's obscuring Lincoln's face with that flag, something of a symbolic expression, intentional or not, of his and his movement's desire to rerun the Civil War and undo the whole emancipation thing.
On day one of the summit, lindell is going to have a premiere screening of the film selection Code, which goes into how the election was stolen.
It was funded by Lindel and largely is about Tina Peters, who you may remember as the election fraud conspiracy, who was arrested for allegedly facilitating a security breach in May 2021.
She was a county clerk in Mesa, Arizona, and in her capacity there, she enabled data from the election to be leaked and ultimately published on a QAnon Telegram channel.
She recently lost an election she was in running for Secretary of State.
She lost in the GOP primary, only getting 27% of the vote.
But of course, she insists that she won and the election was stolen because why not? Yeah.
Anyway, Lindell paid to make a movie about her and he's airing it at his big summit.
Then on day two, we get something truly exciting that I might actually tune in for.
From 11:00 A.m.
To 06:30 p.m., we have the trial of the machines, except on the site they misspelled trial, so it actually says Trail of the Machine.
Oh, my God.
There's no explanation for this other than, quote, mike Lindell puts the voting machines on trial seven and a half hours.
It's going to be madness.
Are you telling me that the boy Pope has dug up the old Pope and we are putting the Pope on the stand? Yes.
Okay, if you're Lindell's kid and by the way, I don't know if he has kids, but if he does have kids, he got to be pissed at you got to run.
He seems to have an endless supply of money to waste, but you got to know that eventually it's going to run out, and before your very eyes, your inheritance has turned into a two day vanity livestream with a seven hour fake courtroom scene where your dad pretends to indict a laptop.
It's grim stuff, man.
Anyway, this is quite a panel of guests.
Owen feeling is put together.
Real bunch of top notch shitheads, that quote, we're going to see all of you in the White House when Trump gets back.
In the normal, corrupt world we've lived in for a long time, you're a big donor all of a sudden after you get elected, holy cow, you're ambassador to, like, Switzerland.
What a great job.
Sure, we paid you off for giving us all the money.
There's some corruption, but everybody lives their own life.
And if it's Mike Lindell and Trump is like, you're Treasury Secretary now, you're the best ad buyer I've ever seen.
Nobody can control the flow of money better than Linda.
What are we doing here? Oh, my God.
Sad times.
So Owen can't help himself.
He's got to pop in.
I'm like a fly on the wall in here listening to my own show.
The most meta day in Infowars history.
You had Alex Jones covering Alex Jones case live on the air, and now you have Owen Troyer listening to Owen Troy or show, it's not meta that's self indulgent and narcissistic.
It's not meta for Alex to complain about his own perceived victimhood on his show.
It's just any other day on Infowars.
I understand Owen wanting to dress this up as something other than vanity, but that's all it is.
Also, I was poking around on that Reawaken America to our website because I was really bored during this interview, and I found that on September 24 in Tulsa, Oklahoma, they're putting on a comedy show with Jim Brewer that promises to be, quote, like a non communist version of Saturday Night Live.
Holy shit.
I know very little about SNL personally, but I don't think that the workers control the means of production there.
Oh, boy.
From what I understand of the operations, I think says SNL is a pro fascist situation.
Lauren there's a character based around him.
Anyway, I don't know.
So the selling point of that show is, quote, see Jim Brewer as Biden for a night Joe Biden won't remember.
I guess the joke is that Biden's forgetful, but the joke kind of works the other way, too.
Biden won't remember this because he'll never know about it.
He couldn't care less about some skits Jim Brewers doing in front of a bunch of Q and on aunts and uncles.
But also Jordan, you should try to get an opening.
I was going to say, if there's a spot, man, I can still do five.
I can still do five off.
Rattle it off.
No big deal.
I've seen brewers stand up and you could open for him.
Oh, I could close for him.
Yeah.
You shouldn't know before too high.
I can't follow that.
It just makes noises.
But yeah, the flyer for this is fun because it has a picture of Jim Brewer in a gray wig, which I guess is his biden.
I am worried.
I'm worried for Swearing Carey, because now we've got a new biden in the mix.
Oh, no.
But this one's clearly a clone that's going wrong.
And it's also a guy named Jim.
Oh, see, everything is bigger than all Jim by ruin.
So, anyway, Owen pops in, and it's because there was an expectation that Alex is going to be on the War Room to talk about the whole thing once the damages came down.
And unfortunately, Alex will not be appearing on the War Room.
He had an appointment with three wise men, johnny, Jack, and Jim.
Not the Larynx Doctor.
The Whiskey Doctor.
My favorite.
Yeah, he ain't going to be in today.
Oh, no.
We're not going to be getting live comments from Alex at this time.
However, he is going to be issuing a response that will be directly uploaded to Van video.com.
So be on the lookout for that.
I am on the lookout, and I found it.
Oh, I thought you might have.
Yeah.
So this is an hour long video.
No, you don't need an hour to say fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Mostly commercial.
It's mostly just like, I want money, we need money.
Of course.
And Barnes.
Yeah, of course.
Well, you got it.
Bobby Barnes is here.
And it's just whining.
This is an incredible time to be alive and to lay out how this show trial of the century that would make the Nazis blush is Robert Barnes.
Robert.
Simply incredible.
No doubt.
I mean, basically even the Soviets tried to make a show trial, at least a good show.
This was a show trial that was so one sided, so evidently partisan, so made for the movie scripts.
I was talking to Mark Robert the other day, and this is a Hollywood screenwriter, and even he was shocked to hear how it was basically designed.
The courtroom was designed like a set with three big movie cameras with the judge alternating what could be said and when it could be said and how it could be said.
And who could say it in such a way that had nothing to do with the rules of evidence.
Nothing to do with the rules of law in Texas.
Nothing to do with constitutional liberties and protection.
And everything to do with scripting a case so that it would have a particular outcome and in particular.
A future media narrative that could be fun and ultimately an actual future movie.
Do these guys know what the Nazis did? Like, the Nazis would blush at this trial? It's a little offensive.
Yeah.
Anyway, I was in the courtroom for a lot more of the case than media star Bobby Barnes.
And I can say very clearly and with no hesitation that the courtroom was not laid out like a movie set and it wasn't following the script.
I get that that's a convenient narrative for him and Alex to push because they lost.
And the fallout from this case is going to be spectacular.
But this is a weak attempt at damage control or whatever they're doing.
For one thing, there were a few cameras in the courtroom, like I mentioned, but they weren't all the same people's cameras, right.
One was the court's zoom camera.
One was the Law and crime feed.
There were HBO cameras for the documentary.
And on that note, there was a sign on the door to the courtroom that advised people that there was a crew from HBO filming, and if they didn't consent to be in the background of shots, they shouldn't come in.
Beyond that, there really wasn't much of an effect that the cameras had on the actual case.
No, the place where cameras were much more involved in making a scene relates to Alex's actions on the first tuesday, the first day of the case proper, alex held a mini press conference in the hallway for all the cameras, yelling about how he'd been railroad and how this is a show trial.
That was the video where we're standing in the background, if people remember that after being scolded about how that wasn't appropriate at lunch, alex tried to do it all again in front of the courthouse, but there was no one there to watch him have a tantrum.
Alex wanted a show trial vibe.
He wanted there to be tons of national media crews there covering the case, but he didn't get that.
I think it's instructive to understand that this complaint that there were all these cameras is actually expressing Alex and Barnes disappointment that there weren't cameras there that they could exploit for their own purposes.
It's less about the cameras and more about how they weren't able to control the narrative, which is something that they're fully used to being able to do.
Within the infowars bubble, a judge pushing back on that need for Alex to control all aspects of how he's allowed to speak or present himself is seen as her trying to create a false narrative which makes total sense.
Actual reality encroaching on the fake reality he lives in is experienced as an attack because it's the only way that fake reality can maintain its existence.
Lawyer.
If you're a lawyer, shouldn't I be allowed to play that clip before we get into a law argument or something? You know, like, if I'm a lawyer and Barnes is across the hall for me and he's on the other desk, shouldn't I be allowed to play that clip and be like, barnes is not taking law seriously, period.
Not at all.
This guy is not a lawyer.
Stop letting him law.
Just take law from him.
Look, I'm not involved in law, so I don't know what is and is not relevant for various things, but I would allow it if a lawyer is relevant to the law, I would assume.
Yeah, I would say, especially after this next clip, if you listen to this, you're like, you're not a serious person.
This is incredible.
Robert Barnes, continuing with your observations, both watching the trial on TV, being down there, having live coverage of it.
Why you say it's the most insane show trial ever? It is because, well, first of all, there pretty much wasn't a right that the judge didn't violate.
First amendment right of freedom of expression, freedom of association, freedom of the press, second amendment right to speak in favor of the second amendment right to selfdefense, fourth amendment right to privacy.
She violated that repeatedly throughout the proceedings.
Not only what went on in the discovery being unduly invasive, but in fact, turning over and telling the plaintiffs lawyer, you could turn over attorney client privileged communications protected by the fourth amendment to the January 6 committee or whomever else fifth amendment rights to due process of law, denied rights to bring motions to dismiss, antislapp motions, denied right to bring appeals.
You brought all of those judgment motions fixed both counsel and confrontation infringed by the attorney client privilege being disclosed and the right to confront those making accusations against you.
7th Amendment right to trial by jury.
And that means the right to trial by jury on all facts, not just the facts the judge decides can be tried.
And all of those same analogous federal constitutional provisions have analogs in the state constitution of the state of Texas.
Weren't these dudes laughing about the case a couple of hours ago? Like fake laughing.
It's weird how this judgment changed their mood a little bit.
I would like to give a rebuttal to Barnes's claims on the First Amendment front.
He gives no explanation for how the judge violated Alex's First Amendment rights.
He just asserts it as a fact.
And I contest that Barnes could never make that case in court, because if he could, you kind of expect he would still be Alex's lawyer, considering that was a huge part of Barnes argument back when he was Alex's lawyer on the Second Amendment side.
Is he saying that the judge didn't allow Alex to bring a gun into the courtroom? I'm unclear on this.
I believe he's saying that by not allowing Alex to describe as his reasoning the Second Amendment, that is a violation of the Second Amendment.
No, because that's just the First Amendment thing all over again.
And it's not also a violation of the First Amendment.
I'm not saying it.
None of these rights are violated.
No.
I noticed that Barnes isn't accusing the judge of violating the Third Amendment, which is good.
I would hate to hear that Alex was forced to quarter any soldiers during the trial.
He was not.
And I don't know if he'd have any place for them to sleep considering all the spaces ridiculous team of security probably took up.
Judge Gamble didn't rule on whether or not Mark could turn over Alex's phone data.
She specifically said she wasn't going to get in the middle of that.
Either way, it's not an invasion of his privacy because it was accidentally disclosed by Alex's lawyer and Mark followed the proper channels before bringing it up.
If Mark had gotten the text through clandestine memes, then that would be a different story.
But this was Raynall fucking up.
Also, nothing about discovery, which Alex didn't even cooperate with, violated Alex's Fourth Amendment rights.
This is stupid.
Alex's fifth Amendment rights are fully intact.
He was not compelled to testify against himself and he had all the due process an asshole can get.
He had every opportunity to participate in the case, but chose not to.
Civil and criminal courts cannot operate if people can just decide that they've made up in their mind that they've been jammed up so they don't have to participate in the case.
And any attempt to make them participate is actually the state railroading them.
Sometimes it does happen that innocent parties get caught up in protracted processes defending themselves, and that sucks.
But that's also why there are mechanisms in place to compensate people who have to go through that, and why you can countersue if you need to.
The 6th Amendment doesn't apply since it's about criminal cases, and the 7th Amendment only requires jury trials for civil cases in federal courts, and this is in the state court, and Barnes is saying that there are analogs in state court.
Then why are you talking about the Constitution, dumb dumb? Good call.
Barnes is a lawyer.
He should know better, and he does.
He just doesn't care.
He's not a lawyer.
He's someone who knows law stuff and is happy to use that law stuff to justify right wing idiots on shows like this.
And his own podcast with Viva Fry.
Small point.
The guy who tried to storm the Ohio FBI office allegedly posted this on Truth Social.
Quote, I'm having trouble getting information, but Viva Fry said, patriots are heading to Palm Beach where Mara Lago is.
I recommend going and being Florida, I think the Feds won't break it up.
If they do, kill them.
If I were Barnes and I really wanted to evoke an amendment for Alex, I would go with the 18th.
Now, sure, that was repealed by the 21st Amendment, but if there was ever a right Alex could use right about now, it's the prohibition of alcohol.
See that? Yes, it was very clever.
Yeah, I'll give you that.
Yeah, calm down with the booze, Alex.
It's so annoying when people are like, we're more polarized than ever, but there is an argument to be made that somehow more amendments were passed after or before Prohibition was repealed.
Do you know what I'm saying? Like, everybody agreed that prohibition was a bad idea once it happened, and then they still managed to agree on two more amendments before they could agree on repealing prohibition.
We couldn't get half an amendment pass through now.
No, probably not.
And the only one I would guarantee is Prohibition.
We could absolutely repeal Prohibition today.
I bet we could.
I would take that back.
You might be right.
So, look, Barnes, like I said, shit head, dumb dumb.
I'll repeat, that no reason I will double down.
I've said worst words.
If the same standard was applied to Axios, that was applied to you.
They could be sued into bankruptcy tomorrow by running a headline that says, the View of Aldi questions whether or not there's a school shooting cover up.
Because, to be clear, they didn't limit this case to just one or two specific statements.
They said any statement questioning anything concerning the Sandy Hook official narrative warranted a death penalty.
They gave you a death penalty sanction in the default judgment stage, then gave you another, and they asked for a death penalty sanction from the jury and the punitive damages.
Stage Barnes is a total shithead and a liar, but he doesn't actually believe what he's saying.
He's also not so dumb as to be unaware that what he's saying is a lie.
Obviously, this case absolutely did not include any supposition.
The questioning aspects of public events constituted defamation.
The reason that it might appear that way if you're not paying attention is because the plaintiffs attorneys brought up a ton of instances of Alex repeating and defending talking points that he had used to argue that the shooting never happened.
Long after he claims, he stopped arguing that it didn't happen.
In fact, Alex was repeating those claims in the middle of his supposed apology video.
Imagine this scenario using one of Alex's bullshit claims from the Sandy Hook Times, which he got from how big and Fetzer and continued to repeat long after supposedly realizing the shooting happened, right? Imagine you see online that people are claiming that the school wasn't even open and there was no internet traffic to the school's website in the year before the shooting.
You would be totally free to discuss this claim that people were making online, and hopefully you would have the decency to take like five minutes to look into it and see that it's bullshit before going on air and mindlessly repeating the claim.
But even so, if you repeat it as a question that folks have, you aren't committing defamation.
This isn't what Alex did.
He used these alleged anomalies as a pile of evidence that he would drop on the audience to support his claim that the shooting didn't happen, when the plaintiff's attorneys would demonstrate that he was still making these claims in the fairly recent past.
What they're doing is illustrating that he's still making the same arguments.
To deconstruct this a little bit, Alex was making the argument if the school's website got no traffic, then the school wasn't open.
If the school wasn't open, the shooting could not have happened, therefore the shooting didn't happen.
It's essentially a setup of if A, then B.
If B, then C A, therefore C.
It's a perfectly fine construction for an argument and it's called a hypothetical syllogism.
And assuming all your premises are correct, it follows that your conclusion will be as.
Well, when Alex has made the argument repeatedly on the show, the audience understands that A is proof of see whether or not they understand this logic path.
So when Alex is claiming he believes the shooting happened, but then still insisting the premise A is correct, what he's doing is still affirming the conclusion while pretending that he's not.
This is one of the ways that Alex has his cake and eats it too.
Or as Mark said it in the trial, he wants it always.
If you pay attention to his show, you'll see a bit of this behavior.
And in the case of Sandy Hook, you can plug in a bunch of different narratives in that place for Premise A, and it works the same paramedics weren't allowed in the building.
Kids walked around in circles.
FBI crime stats say no murders happened in Newtown that year.
All of these things are the first premises for that hypothetical syllogism structure.
Barnes understands this, and on some level, Alex does, too.
But even leaving that aside, alex's actions as it relates to Sandy Hook are so much worse than just making claims publicly.
His promotion of Wolfgang Halbig after the point where he could be reasonably expected to know that Wolfgang was harassing victims family members, including Scarlett Lewis, is something that you might notice barnes doesn't even touch.
The defense of Alex is grandstanding, and that grandstanding only works if you have a straw man version of the accusation that you need to defend yourself against.
And Barnes knows all this? He's a total shit.
Yeah, it reminds me of my favorite moment in the trial was when I believe Reynald was questioning, and then there was this massive objection storm, because his questioning was really terrible and obviously against the rules and stuff.
So the judge shuts him down, and then they have to have a sidebar, and Reynall afterwards claims he's like, here's the problem.
This is a sanction by the court because they made us look dumb.
And then the judge said, Only you can do that.
That is exactly how I feel about Barnes right now.
He's like, the court is doing all this stuff the court is doing, only you make yourself look dumb.
That's what's happening, man.
You are the one.
And you sound a little desperate, too.
You're making yourself sound a little desperate by way of how much this is just an infomercial.
Yes.
I'm quite frankly surprised, because listeners are so used to us being steadfast, so used to us being resilient, that they're like, okay, well, Jones has said he's close to oblivion quite a bit.
We're getting a little extra support, but not what we should.
And I think if it becomes evident where we actually do start shutting down, we'll have a lot of support, and then we'll try to reorganize and do something.
But now's the time of support.
Have you ever worked? Oh, no doubt.
Because this is what keeps info live on a monthly basis that pays all the salaries.
I don't understand why he's still doing commercials while they're planning to sue him.
Allegedly.
I kind of do understand.
It's all nonsense, for sure.
Anyway, the conversation of Alex's phone comes up, and there's a little bit of a defense being played here about the idea that there are intimate photos.
Oh, there's a little defensive being played.
Alex is a little defensive, let me tell you.
These people with their statements gave me more energy I've ever had it's on, even though they have the phone and the secret contacts with Vlad, and we're supposed to be going over to Moscow soon or whatever.
Oh, I'm going to play more of their clips.
Let's talk about that.
It's six months of my phone, late 2019, early 2020.
It's some CPAC stuff, and it's pictures of my wife and me and the kids and stuff like that.
And I gave Texas and I gave Connecticut the phones.
They were searching them in six months.
Tranches.
And the paralegal left, like, a six month raw thing in there.
And we all went through it.
There's nothing there.
We did anything wrong anyways.
And he's like, we have two years.
We have the whole phone.
That was not true.
Yeah, like, they have Hunter Biden's laptop, and, of course, where's the crack pipes, where's the horse sorry.
There was a photo I sent my wife of her naked.
Okay.
They got that.
My wife was pretty good.
Go ahead.
The point is that there's one naked picture of my wife in there, so that's what they've got.
And it's just no dick pics, no nothing.
This is uncomfortable.
I wouldn't put this out.
Just don't put your business like that out.
Let Mark tell people that you're a shitty person on top of a monster.
I will say this with absolute certainty.
Nobody who has access to that phone that I'm aware of would ever release naked pictures.
Even if it's like a dick pic of Alexes that could hypothetically be on the phone.
That is so uncalled for and inappropriate.
No, I mean, Alex could just not say anything, and this would never be an issue.
Morally.
It is a horrific thing to do to send a picture of somebody that's not Alex to somebody else.
Alex is adding information to this that is making it, hey, you could have said it, and then you didn't have to add the part where you're saying, I sent it to a third party without consent.
Well, he's trying to maybe he got consent.
I don't know.
No, because Alex is trying to say that he just sent a naked picture of his wife to his wife.
I think if you follow what he's saying yeah, but I think I'm going to go with Marc told the real version.
Well, I don't know.
We'll see.
We won't see.
No, we absolutely won't see.
We will never see this, and thank God for that.
Yeah, because honestly, more importantly, is, like, the stuff that means something.
Like the Paul Joseph Watson text that was absolutely shown in court.
Absolutely.
Here barnes and Alex intentionally missed the point.
Yeah, it's more fake news, and it's an attempt to sort I mean, what's extraordinary is they got to see a microscopic up close view of Infowars and Alex Jones, and they couldn't produce any incriminatory information.
That's why they had one text message about Paul saying, this looks like a BS sandy Hook store.
Exactly.
Which had nothing to do with Sandy Hook.
That's our smoke.
Oh, we have your phone.
And here it is.
Completely.
There's no basis of a criminal case whatsoever.
There's no perjury.
There's no lie.
So there's two things.
The first is that text from Paul illustrates that Alex has awareness that the story that he was doing about COVID was bullshit and it was Sandy Hook all over again.
And Alex admitted I get it.
I understand that this is what we're doing, and I don't care.
We're doing this.
Yes.
The second thing is that the existence of this text is full evidence that Alex did commit perjury when he said that he had looked through his phone and turned over everything that had the word Sandy Hook in them because this existed and was not turned over.
That is a problem.
They're just completely missing the point and saying it didn't even involve Sandy Hook.
That is correct.
But those words were there because of that.
It's an issue.
You're in hot water.
If those words were in there and you search your phone, you would have found that text and you specifically chose not to give it to us.
Yeah.
Now, Barb is one of the great legal minds of Infowars.
It's very clear from this appearance if that is true, and only a great legal mind could come up with an argument like this about why everything on Alex's phone is totally cool.
They go intimate.
Roger Stone text.
It's like Roger saying, yeah, my wife fell and broke her leg.
God, it's hard.
Somebody just beat us up in the parking lot.
I'm like, I'm so sorry, man.
And that's intimate.
Yeah.
I know.
All of us.
If there was anything there, it would be on the front page of CNN, the New York Times, and every welfare.
It would have already been fully disclosed and revealed and released.
If there isn't anything there, it's like Trump.
They get to do a macroscopic microscopic look at your entire life and all they can come up with is pretty much nothing.
So that's bad reasoning.
The fact that there isn't anything that's been revealed means there's nothing to reveal.
Right.
I guess that works now, but that may not work eventually.
I mean, his argument, unfortunately, the way he put it, is essentially I didn't get caught robbing that bank, so I didn't rob that bank.
Yeah.
Haven't been arrested yet.
I'm gold.
If they knew I'd rob the bank, then they would have arrested smart legal mind.
Not to be outdone by Alex accusing everyone of being a pedophile.
Right.
Barnes decides to get in the mix.
Wow.
And a fever.
And he accuses, by implication, Mark of being a pedophile.
Great.
And that's also going to have to take into account what the Lafferty claims are valued at and the Posner claims are valued at and the Fontaine claims are valued at.
And that is why I've been saying that what this is Coin heading towards is there is going to be a large set of plaintiffs who are going to be dividing up the corpse of Infowars.
In the bankruptcy estate.
And over the course of that process, that could get very dangerous for Mr.
Jones because there is going to be a new level of financial street.
And if some lawyer like me can basically find out that he's hiding the keys to the Candy store, pull it out in front of him on the stand, I can only imagine what Federal Reserve is going to do.
So, yeah, it's going to get interesting from here on out.
They think Info Wars is the candy store.
Well, you can tell.
I don't say what comes to mind, but I mean, the point is that you've seen the finances here.
It's so funny.
They're drilling to dry well and they just can't imagine that they project the stuff onto us.
But what do you make of those claims? I think there was definitely some confession through projection there.
The way his eyes lit up at Candy Store.
I don't want to know why he goes to a candy store.
I'll put it that way.
Wow.
For somebody who got his ask wiped by Mark in every possible way whenever he was involved legally, it is a lot easier to make fun of him.
When you're on a talk show and he's not anywhere near, you can be confession by projections.
Another one you should write down that's another.
It's like the blank end blank.
I'll give you a point on that one.
I'll give you a point for that one.
So Alex actually makes a really good point here about some of Mark's comments.
Okay.
Particularly the comment that we have a bunch of plaintiffs that are going to be splitting up the corpse of Infowars.
Right.
Alex makes a great point here.
I have mixed feelings about it.
Well, that's the thing.
If I wanted my enemies to fight me, I would say, I will destroy you.
You're over.
I'm going to dominate you.
Like when you said that.
Don't they know what they're doing? Do they not know the gold with our audience? Them saying, we're going to cut up his corpse.
We're going to shut them down, we're going to shut all these Americans down.
They literally just declared war on the middle class in America and the Midwest completely.
What Alex is saying here could be translated as, don't these people understand how much I'm going to be able to fundraise off a quote like that? Alex's business model operates off fear, and he's able to monetize his ability to capture the audience in a state of fear.
When there's a statement like Marks, which can be translated as a direct attack on Alex, alex can repackage that as an attack on the audience, which will allow him to more easily fleece some of them into continuing to throw money into the pit that is Infowars.
Right.
Alex is laughing because he feels that Mark has made his job of raising money easier.
But there's a larger reality that Alex is trying to distract away from, which is that no matter what he does, there's a sort of damocles hanging over his head.
All the posturing and fundraising isn't really going to matter much to a bankruptcy audit.
And when you step into that arena, it's not a civil matter.
If you try to play games, you could end up going to jail for the sort of crimes you end up pulling there.
And you have to consider what could come with a very clear cases of perjury that Alex was caught committing in the course of the trial.
I don't know any of the specifics, but I wouldn't be surprised if that was something that could lead to huge fines or possibly even be referred for prosecution.
Alex can do this song and dance with Barnes all they want, and it's fun for him to pretend that he's won this trial, but in order to do that, he has to pretend a whole tranche of other problems don't exist and aren't nipping at his heels.
It's a grim picture.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know how to deal with whenever you find out somebody perjured themselves on the stand when they're still on the stand.
I feel like that's almost a moment where the whole thing should, like, the light should turn off.
You should be able to run away.
There's no way because it cannot just be like, later on he gets a fine.
That cannot be the case.
You can't tell me that I could just go and lie to a judge and then pay $1,000, relatively speaking, you know what I'm saying? Like, that cannot be okay.
It just can't.
I agree.
But I also think you should be able to I think you should have to run well, I think you should have to have a smoke bomb.
No smoke bombs.
You have to evade the court officers.
Yeah.
You got to jump your way out, then you get out.
But if not, you got to come back to the city.
Then it turns into American Gladiators.
And if you make it through the hole, then you win fast.
Thunder jets.
I got you, boulder.
Turbo.
Turbo is definitely one of them.
So Barnes believes it's going to go to the Texas Supreme Court, maybe the US.
Supreme Court, and he has some really fun ways of expressing how close they are to winning cases like that.
This is a bondable judgment we'll go up to.
The Texas Supreme Court will be decided by them at some point in the process, and if the Texas Supreme Court gets involved, it's game over for the plaintiffs.
They throw out the case entirely.
We already had, like, half of one short and a half, only one justice short of them taking it and throwing this out from the very beginning because the very nature of the suit violates the First Amendment to the United States Constitution, always has.
Also violates Texas law on the definition of intentional infliction of emotional distress.
Oh, man.
That's a really fun way to say you lost.
Yeah.
One justice short of half.
Wow.
I'd be like, what do you think? You're not going to still be one just as short of half.
Have you changed the Supreme Court of Texas? Honestly, I really don't even think they'll get that just as short of half, because they're not remembering that despite them being conservatives, the Texas Supreme Court or whatever, despite their strong conservative leanings, et cetera, these people are still lawyers and judges and shit.
True.
And I imagine that when they start looking at somebody abusing the court system the way Alex did, even though they're like, I'll lick Trump's feet, they're still going to be like, we got to take this guy.
Can't be doing that shit.
And if they review the entirety of the case, you might be like, well, we got to take this, like, this perjury stuff a little more seriously.
It could backfire.
Yes.
Maybe not.
I don't know.
Anyway, the point is, we're coming to the end of this special report because it's mostly just rambling about how it's just the same shit repeated over and over again, over and over again.
I want them to talk about cannibalism and reanimating spiders.
That was great.
That was fun.
You could grasp something with the spider just with air.
Yeah.
Whose idea was that? Some weirdo at Rice? That's a question that I don't think anybody explained fully to me.
The guy who was like and nobody was like, I was drunk.
Nobody's saying that.
I was watching a video on the lady who was like the grad student who was working on it.
We thought we might be able to do it, and we just put the needle into work.
The first time.
I was like, what the fuck? Okay, cool.
That is great.
We were like, hey, what if we could do this? Let's do it.
I was on toad the other day.
Spiders kind of look like a okay, all right.
So we're coming to the end of this, and of course, we're going to have to dismount on some salesmanship.
But also, hey, man, you got to understand that Alex is a hero.
I don't know if that's true.
It is.
Okay? And he expresses his heroism quite clearly, all right? If you don't buy the products, if you spread the word, yes, we'll be shut down.
But it's not in Bankston's hands.
It's not in this SJW judge's hands.
It's not in Hillary Clinton's hands.
It's not in Satan's hands.
God helps those that helps themselves.
It is in your hands.
And I'll be quite honest with you.
I'm going to fight 100%.
I'm going to do the best job I can, but if you take me out of the game it was time for me to get off the field.
We've had nothing but devastating victory.
I'm not going to get the NFL quarterback ready to retire, but I can't because this isn't football, folks.
This is our children's future.
I'm telling you, I will never give up.
But if you don't back us and if you don't get how serious this is, you're next.
So I can't quit, and I will not quit.
But if you quit, I have no power.
This is such a weird abuse.
Listen, I will never quit.
But if you quit, I've already quit.
So that's the situation.
So I will never quit fighting for you.
I am a fucking hero for the children, and I will never quit.
And if the day does come that I do quit, it's your fault.
It's your fault.
Listen, there's nothing I can do.
I would love to not quit, but I don't have hundreds of millions of dollars anymore.
Will never quit.
And if you stop paying me, I'm done.
And it's your fault.
Can you imagine? And then the kids will all die.
Can you imagine a sadder person than the one who is like, I will fight my holy crusade as long as I get a good salary.
Person is the person who buys into it and pays a salary.
That's fair.
Yeah, that is fair.
That is the sadder person.
Anyway, here's the dismount.
Okay.
God bless you all.
Thank you for tuning in.
Now share the live feed of this and share the archive of it at band video or roll over to die, which I know you're not going to do.
I'm sorry, what? I'm not going to do it either.
And I pledged to you all, I'm going to redouble my efforts.
That took a turn.
Yeah.
Got to have that.
But yeah.
Share this video or roll over and die.
Man, I can't imagine anyone wanting watching the video and being like, everyone must see this.
It's not really even a response to the news of the judgment.
No, it doesn't clear anything up.
It makes things as confusing as possible and then says, we'll get them in the Supreme Court.
You've said one shorter and half.
I know, but they've said over and over again, we're going to sue these people and we're going to win.
And they never sue anybody.
Why would you believe that? They're going to win in the Supreme Court.
They're going to do it one short a half.
I mean, Mike Lindell isn't even paying for the lawsuits this time.
They don't have it.
They don't got it.
Also, after that whole pageant that Alex did about really respecting Neil and Scarlett and me and wanting to support them and all this, it's great that he would want to drag this out even further and convenience them.
Absolutely.
So that's cool.
Anyway, we have reached what I will call the end of my patience for the trial coverage.
I think that's a good time.
This chapter has ended along with sneak week, and it's been something else.
I'm glad that it has closed the chapter, and I hope you have a good trip, but we have a lot to get to when you get back.
Right.
I'm looking on Twitter as we're recording this.
It turns out they leaked the warrant for Trump's search.
No, they released it.
I think it leaked and was released.
Yeah.
Just have a fun time.
Have a fun day of it.
So there's a lot, man.
I mean, enjoy Ireland, but at the same time no, I understand.
Be conscious of the fact that chaos is brewing.
Sure.
Listen, give you brewing staff.
It will do.
You will get all kinds of druid shit, my man.
You are a druid.
Yes.
Get me a gandalf outfit.
Yeah, I got it.
I don't know if that's even Irish.
What's your character's name again? Dutch Wildfire.
That's right, Dutch Wildfire.
Anyway, I'm not going to keep that moniker.
It's been at the craziest few weeks, I think, either of our lives, and you have been an absolute fucking star.
Well, thank you.
You as well.
I am glad to take a little breaky.
Yeah, me too.
You can kind of tell, I think, in this episode, my exhaustion take a break.
I am glad to land this plane.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
We'll be back.
Indeed we will.
And we'll talk about Trump's rage response.
It's going to get crazy, but tell them, Jordan.
We have a website.
We do.
It's knowledgephite.com.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
That knowledge underscore fights.
We will be back.
But until then, Jordan.
I'm Neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm dzx Clark.
I'm Wilford Snippel snabble of the Gribble PIBBLE.
And now here comes the sex robots.
Andy and Jansis, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your works.
I love you.