Hey, everybody, this is Dan.
Hello.
I just wanted to drop in and give a little bit of a note before this episode begins, and the reason for that is because I kind of screwed up a little bit on the recording of this episode.
And so some of the levels are a little bit iffy I've been using a technology that can't be named unless I be shading some business, but for remote recording.
And it seemed like everything was totally fine as we were recording, and our guests actually very generously offered to record on their end.
And because I had so much confidence in this tech, I thought, like, there's no need to this has worked just fine in the past.
And unfortunately, some of the audio is a little bit distorted, but it still sounds fine.
It could be a little cleaner.
Anyway, this is a rambling, long winded way for me to just give you a heads up about that and to take responsibility for the sound.
I messed up a little bit.
Anyway, we'll be back on Wednesday with a normal episode with Jordan back, but for now, please enjoy this special app.
It's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledge.
Fight.
knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hello, everybody.
Welcome back to a knowledge fight.
We are here.
We've just had a week of a break, and if truth be told, I was under the impression that Jordan would be getting back over the weekend and that we could get back to work and do our job as normal, but this is not the case.
Jordan will not be back until Tuesday.
And so in order to get an episode out, I had to dig deep and find someone who capable of filling the shoes of Jordan.
And it turns out I found two people very excited to welcome to the podcast hosts of the Dollop, gareth Reynolds and David Anthony.
Welcome, gentlemen.
Thank you, Jordan.
Yeah.
Jordan's out.
This is a permanent thing.
I think we're going to go trios.
I like it.
Jordan, there's a great the way that we got it set up was pretty smooth and easy, so I feel like we're, like there's a synergy.
Yeah, definitely.
So, guys, I know that over the course of the time doing your podcast, you've touched on some of the, I don't know, maybe some things that are connected to my world, like the Jade Helm episode, for sure.
Clive and bundy, perhaps.
Yeah.
Our god.
We've done two on the bundys or three.
Two on the bundys, right? Two.
Yeah.
I was wondering, though, how much connections you have to Alex Jones himself via the show.
Zero offline tons.
Yeah.
We're very close to Alex.
Dave and Alex are really good.
A lot of people say that they get Dave and Alex confused.
I think that your personalities would mesh amazingly I would call it Vibe.
We vibe and we have a lot of the same sort of philosophies and just outlooks on life and protein powders, climate change.
That's one of the big things that's me.
No, we've not really gotten into Alex ever.
If anything, it would be on the show.
Yeah.
Maybe just minorly on the show.
I've always avoided him completely.
The only thing I really know about him is listening to your podcast.
I'll pop in every once in a while to see what's going.
Alex Jones.
But for the most part, I don't really pay attention to him.
And it seems like he's had a quiet couple of weeks.
Yeah, it's been real time.
He has, I think, abandoned Trump again, so that's a good sign for the investigation and the FBI raid.
I know someone who punched him and knocked him out.
Alex charlie.
Yeah.
20 some odd years ago in Texas.
Is this a space hitler? No, this is a guy named Charlie.
I'm just loving the conversation we're having from the sidelines right now.
It might also be space Hitler.
Is it Space Hitler? No, Charlie.
No.
Charlie is a guy who is associated with the festival in Austin, south by Southwest.
Oh, wow.
He punched him, huh? He fucking knocked him down.
They were working at radio stations, I believe, and they got into it one night.
And Charlie Deckerman charlie, to this day, still gets free beers in Austin for having done that.
You get local hero status.
That's pretty awesome, I guess.
Look, I'm not thrilled with violence at any point, but if it's violence 20 years ago and it's funny, I would like to say that I am thrilled with violence.
I'm just happy to know there's a face Hitler.
Yeah, I think that might be the same guy because there was a dude who would, like, troll him on his public access show, and they ended up getting into a fight in a parking lot.
I think that Space Hitler was there, and that was the same night.
And two guys hitler was also involved.
A different guy, though.
How much that sounds like it would be something on Infowars, what just was said.
I think Space Hitler was there, but there were two guys in the parking lots.
So you guys didn't even like even before, like present days, you didn't have any kind of impression of Alex Jones as a figure? Oh, yeah, he was somebody who existed.
No, we've just never talked about him on the show, really.
But yeah, obviously it's hard to even remember when you first heard about him, but yeah, obviously been following his lunacy for the better part of a decade.
Really? Yeah.
But I purposely got him away not to watch anything.
I just don't watch anything with him, like, when I see clips of them online.
But I've heard about him for a long time now, and I've definitely read a couple of articles about him and then your podcast.
I listened to both the documentary episodes, which were long but crazy.
Yeah.
That got me sub tweeted by the director.
Oh, really? It's her, right? Yeah, she did a terrible job.
So, look, there's a lot going on with Alex in the present day.
Like you mentioned, slow week.
He's going through a lot of things.
He's having some tantrums.
But I felt like getting into all that might be too much, might be throwing you guys into the deep end.
And I didn't want to put you through that.
That's sweet.
What I wanted to do is I wanted to do something a little bit special for you.
And a lot of times listeners will get in touch with us and ask us to do an episode about their birthday, like what happened on my birthday on infowars.
What I figured I would do is I would take us back to April 25, 2014, the day you guys put out your first episode of The Dollar wow.
And see what Alex Jones was doing.
This is around I mean, Jade Helm was starting to kick up.
I think that heat was a little bit more in the 15, though, right? Wasn't it? Okay.
Our first episode is the bundys.
So it was right in the bundy rage.
Bundys will come up.
Yeah, he was into that.
Yeah.
There's a lot of news going on at that point in 2014.
There's plenty going on, and I think we'll be disappointed to learn about what most of this episode ends up being about.
But let us dive in here at the beginning.
This is how Alex is starting off the show.
Ukrainian helicopter hit by grenade taking off.
Ukraine helicopter has been crippled in the Grenada tacking Orange mosque.
I was in sneering a third world war.
That's one to graph headline more.
That is the crane minister that's saying that, by the way.
And also their vice presidente, ukraine foreign minister ready to fight Russia is the headline from the Associated Press.
So, yeah, we go back into the past and we see something pretty reminiscent of recent news.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's so rational.
He does that's.
One of the problems with him is that sometimes he sounds like that, and then other times he's screaming about you.
Wait.
Well, here's the problem.
That's just him reading headlines.
Interpretation.
It's pretty easy to sound fairly rational when you're just like, cold reading, here is a thing that happened.
Yeah.
But then you get into the analysis of it, and it might be a little bit sillier here, and that is him blaming essentially the west is what caused the 2014 outbreak of hostilities between Ukraine and Russia.
The west went in three months ago when Ukraine voted to not join with the EU and to be driven by that spider and instead tried to say somewhat neutral, I don't want you crane by the Russian spider or the globalist spider.
But the global spider is about ten times bigger, fatter, older, more evil and more anti human.
I mean, the Russian is just happy to be in power and control of its own population, is trying to breed a larger Roost key population because it realizes that its own system is collapsing.
The global spider is a transhumanist power tripping spider that believes it's God and is attacking anything decent.
I see you're trying to make sense of this day.
You're tracking the thought.
I'm trying to track the thought and it's very hard to track, but I will say I do like the idea of calling the EU a spider.
It's got a web, it's going to suck the drive.
I like the sucking dry spider.
It's almost like you know how it is.
Like when you do a podcast, you'll say some stuff and you'll be like, that didn't make sense, and you kind of let it die.
But he's quadrupling down on the spider talk to the point where because he's so insane towards the end, you're like, I think he might actually think this is spiders that are doing this.
Yeah, he just watched Wild Wild West the night before he was offset.
Kevin Klein is behind the spiders.
Kevin Klein was just elected to the UN council.
So, yeah, you have this world view and this presentation that is fairly consistent throughout time.
That is, anything that involves Russia ends up being everybody else's fault.
Right.
And that's not to say that he is like, obviously he's not on the Russian payroll or anything like that, but he is deeply into making excuses for everything that involves Russia.
He's also saying Russia is collapsing at the same time.
True, but it's in a sympathetic way.
I think they're the big victim, sort of.
Yeah, the victim spider.
Yeah, they're the victim spider.
Come on.
It's a classic victim spider situation.
You know what I mean? You got to help the victim spider.
Yeah.
So with the taking of Crimea and that kind of actions that were happening, they're collapsing is kind of an excuse for why they would take these oil rich areas and these resources.
It's like they're collapsing.
They need to do this.
They need to breed more Russians.
Yeah.
Russian fighters.
Literally.
No one's ever said that they need to breathe or rush.
They're doing that at my Humane Society.
So you guys may not be the best, like, prognosticators on this front, but do you think that Alex thinks the outbreak between Ukraine and Russia is real? This 2014 fight or the one today, the god, something being shot down, right? If anything shot down out of the sky, then Alex, it's not real.
It can't be false fly spider.
It's too similar to blackhawk down.
It's all fake.
Yes, that's right.
Well, here we go.
Let's see.
But we've always known that a large global war is what's supposed to bring in the final world government.
That's what the globalists have said themselves.
And now it looks like they're trying to do it.
They may have some backroom deal with Putin, and this may be staged.
My gut tells me it's not.
Well, there we are.
The background being between Ukraine and Russia, or between the spider, the EU, which spiders, though? There's three spiders involved.
I don't think you cranes a spider.
Buckeyes not a spider.
Ukraine is a fly.
Yeah, Ukraine's a fly.
Right.
Okay.
So he's saying Russia and the EU are working together.
Yeah, he's saying the possibilities are that it's a real violent outbreak, or there's a backroom deal between the EU and Putin to split Ukraine in half.
It's just great, because the way that he's able to bring that up and be like, my goodness, that's not what's going on.
It's like, Dude, you're not rational.
Look, that might be what's going on.
I'm open to that possibility, obviously.
Yeah.
It would be like someone being like, yeah, there's a lot of signs that alien invasion is right around the corner.
My gut says it's not.
But obviously it's very possible.
It's highly possible.
It seems like you only are talking about that distinct possibility that you don't think is correct.
You know what? That's going to be great.
What's going to be great one day is when he's just doing his show, and he's going to collapse on the infowars desk, and his belly is just going to open up, and you're going to find out that he was just a master egg for spiders, and they're all going to crawl out of it.
Yeah.
It was never a metaphor.
All time, he was living like Vincent Dinafrio and Men in Black his whole life.
So you might think, based on what we've heard so far, that this was going to be an episode that was largely about Russia and Ukraine, and you could be forgiven for thinking that it is not.
Things take a turn.
Alex is discussing how one of his reporters, David Knight, he has been taking some time off, and because of that, he's ended up listening to some talk radio.
And this is some real chaos, but he's been off the last few days moving, and I guess out of one apartment into a house while he's still trying to buy a house.
And so he's been listening to talk radio.
He was listening to our local affiliate at 590 a.
M.
Last night because his brother in law out of North Carolina, Caldon, and said, you better go listen to Glenn Beck.
Will it rehears here locally? And so he turned in last night while packing the Hue Hall, and he said, we got to go into Glenbeck's archive and find it.
But he said, this is really bad.
We have to do something about this.
And I said, what did he say? He said, Well, I'll just come in and tell you.
But he told me over the phone right before broadcast, he's driving up here right now to be on the next segment or at the bottom of the hour.
This is an emergency.
Glenn Beck is talking some shit.
Here we go.
So he's calling in the guy who's taking time off to move into a house because he's buying a different house.
He's having that guy come to the studio on his days off because Glen Beck said some shit.
Yes.
A lot of people are thinking there's not even a second house.
A lot of people are thinking that the second house is just kind of a false house.
It's actually a spider's nest.
It's a spider's nest, exactly.
I mean, the amount of detail, you could just be like, coming up next, we're going to talk about Glenn back.
But instead he's like so he's moving from one house.
He's listening to 590, but he's also leaving his apartment.
He's got these loading up the U Haul.
He's on the way.
Yeah.
That's part of his magic, is that he throws in details about stuff that doesn't need details, and it makes him sound like he knows more than he really does.
Yes.
But in this case, it actually convinces me a little bit that he's telling the truth about this guy moving and being inconvenient for sure.
Seems real.
Yeah.
The accidental truth.
I'm starting to think this guy might be moving.
That's all I'm buying.
And it sounds like Alex is a shitty boss.
Yeah, totally.
To be like I mean, I'm not sure what's going he's taken three days to move.
It's just kind of fucking ridiculous.
And also, the guy apparently doesn't listen.
The only excuse he has to listen to radio is that he's moving.
Other than that, you want to motivate yourself when you're moving.
See, throw on a little Am talk radio to just kind of get the gears in motion.
This story actually shifts a little bit as the episode goes on.
Later we find out that David Knight's brother lives in another city and he saw Glen back and told David Knight to listen to it.
There are some wrinkles here.
We're not entirely sure what's true, but yeah, I think one thing that sucks is that he's coming in because of Glenn Beck talking shit, not because Russia and Ukraine are ramping up hostilities.
This is the kind of news organization that's like Glenn Beck, you've got to come in.
Yeah, World War II might be happening, but Glenn Beck has a 590 a m show.
We got to get into this.
But see, the problem is basically that Glenn Beck is just jealous of Alex, which I think we all could see coming.
Yeah.
He went offline he went off air and went online and moved his operation there.
And he's never going to be as successful as Alexander.
Well, that's true.
But The Blaze has so many cool people working there so many greats I guess Steven Crowder is there, right? God, is that what Crowder is.
I think he might say it's fucking two failed comedians.
Well, I mean, that's most of the right wing, right? But let's be honest, crowder is pretty funny.
Anyway.
Alex believes that Glenn Beck is jealous of him.
Know what this is? He knows we're getting on affiliates all over the country.
The show is exploding right now.
Most of the stations were on carry Glenn Beck.
And he knows, because I've talked to some program directors that there's little comments and things going on from the people in his office.
Not even a syndicator premiere about me and how I'm a bad show to have.
And this has been going on behind the scenes.
And then a lot of times, I'm on live and Glenn Beck's on at night.
He doesn't like that.
He's an egomaniac.
Yeah.
My show end up getting picked up on Sunday live.
While we do that show, people get a taste of it, then they put us on at night, and then invariably, we end up going on live.
They literally replace Rush Limbaugh with us in the areas of the country and get better ratings.
I never had this slot to go up against Rush Limbaugh.
I didn't want this slot.
Wow.
He's beating Rush Limbaugh.
Yeah.
Maybe mildly delusional, but cool as someone's handing him, like, notes, letting them know, like, Putin is thinking of dropping a nuke.
Hold on a second.
So Rush is actually also intimidated by us over here.
We have a strategy where, like, a drug dealer and I put my show on your Sunday night so you get a taste for people who are moving.
If you want to move and listen to a show, put us on.
We are info dealers.
Yeah.
I love that.
He's bragging about a Sunday night slot.
Baseball.
If you're watching, you're just like, all right, are we fighting infowars, or is this like a clip? When do we go back to fighting infowars? I think that this is something that's kind of maybe under known publicly is how much of his show ends up being kind of like this, where I had no idea.
Why does anyone list? Who cares? Well, that was one of the things about the trial that was so exceptional was to actually have someone there be like, what are you talking about? So often to be able to do that, like, to pull that move because we just need yes or no.
Yeah.
In his depositions, the best moments are the like, Mr.
Jones, do you know what question you're answering? Almost invariably, the answer is no.
He has no idea where the sentence started.
So this goes back to when Space Nazi and Charlie here we go.
That night, they were in a radio show, and he was a failed radio guy.
The radio guy still gas at him.
It's still a deep seated thing.
He wants to be king of fucking radio.
That's what he's talking about.
Like, he's bragging he's better than Radio Spider.
It just doesn't matter.
It just doesn't matter anymore.
Yeah, there's a bit of projection, possibly.
I think I'm picking up on some of that, too.
Yeah, he has a chip on his shoulder.
That's something that is also sort of ubiquitous throughout his career.
I'm the best.
But also everyone is jealous of me and that's why look, they're trying to kick me off these stations because Glenn Beck is jealous of me and he's talking shit.
That kind of vibe is, yeah, funny guys have always talk shit about each other.
They can't not do it.
No, that is very true.
It's such a community.
It's such a forgotten community or something.
That was like they were the rock stars in the yeah.
Wolfman.
Now.
Alex Jones brought low.
So Alex is going to bring up some of the accusations that Glenn Beck has made about him here on this next question.
It's important to double down on the important news of the day.
I mean, this is definitely the top story.
Obviously, I'm going to talk to Mike briefly about what he heard Beck say last night, and I guess we're going to dig through the video and audio files of it yesterday and posted just to document what we're saying.
But it doesn't matter.
A lot of you probably heard it saying that we want violence and we're basically covering up the races in a bundy and that we were out there at the ranch two weeks ago when he said all this, when we all now know this was taped Saturday and would not buy our reporters.
And of course we reported on it.
I mean, it's one thing to say Monday could be a hillbilly or maybe racist.
I don't think that's the case.
He's certainly a fossil, though, and I think some of the stuff you say could be taken as offensive.
I'll bring one in the house.
Got them around here.
It's just literally out in the middle of nowhere.
It'd be like I brought a Yankee in here.
I saw them city slicker.
These are folks in the desert.
Seven generations.
Yeah, he might just be a fossil, but he's not racist.
He's a fossil, but he's not wrong.
It's really odd to listen to Alex Jones.
Alex Jones, like, for him to be talking about himself and his little orbit in the way that he does about everything else.
Nothing if not, like, self obsessed.
That does happen a lot.
But the way that you're like talking about posting audio files, honestly, nobody cares.
What's actually important? Well, what's actually important is that Glenn Beck has said that Alex wants to overthrow the government, which he kind of does.
He pretty clearly has been super against the federal government for 20 years.
And then he's covering up racism by not calling what Kaisen Bundy said racist, which I don't know if you remember, but it was basically him saying that, hey, maybe black people were better off under slavery, and then he would have one in his house.
He's not opposed to having a black person in his house, which is, in the Bundy family, considered progressive.
Basically, though, everything that Glenn Beck appears to be saying about Alex seems fair.
He's doing that thing where you're going, god damn it.
Now.
I agree with Glenn.
Becky asshole.
Yeah, that is the battle.
Sometimes it's like, oh, no.
You have made a good point about Alex Jones low bar, though.
That's pretty unimpressive.
Yes.
Cliven Bundy, that was your guy's first episode, right? That was our first episode.
That was before Dave thought he was going to have me on the show permanently.
We were just going to his garage to talk about the Bundy's.
It was magic in a bottle.
And the same day you put out that episode, this was happening on Alex's show, talking about Clive and Bundle Readable and how he is.
He's just old fashioned, man that's got to understand.
Say the N word is in the middle of nowhere that do talk like this.
And they're actually not racist.
They are literally out of a time machine.
Right.
But there's bad things if you go back in a time machine.
There's also good things.
They're saying no to the Feds and notice Square because they're so old fashioned, that's the good part of their old fashionedness is to be straight shooting and to stand up against tyranny.
But then it's like talking to somebody who got off a time machine from 150 years ago.
It sounds really weird to modern trendies and Metrosexuals and everybody else.
So the one thing I will say he's correct on is the bunny's war against Tiananmen Square.
Yes.
It's just the more that that goes on, the more it's like, Jesus Christ, is he mad living? More or less.
He loses the thread quite a bit.
He's like a guy who starts running downhill and he can't stop.
Yeah, let's start a GoFundMe to get him running down the hill.
I would love to see that footage.
I love reality shows because you get to watch the word literally be taken out back and abused.
And his quote in there is, they are literally from a time machine.
True.
I think one of the problems with the entire roll downhill and the momentum of it was that there was something true to it.
They are essentially from a time machine, but they're coming from a racist time.
So you're making an excuse for this by being like, no, their minds are back from slavery time.
Yes.
And we're like, yeah, exactly.
That's a problem.
And he's like, yeah, well, they're time travelers.
Okay? Yeah, well, in our time, we're not cool with that.
If they are time travelers, then we need to teach them about the modern world.
No, then the whole space time continuum.
Then you're jumping in the middle of the ripple effect.
You don't understand what you're doing to the universe.
Oh, no.
When you open up the world of spiders, time spiders.
So we have a little bit more Russia and Ukraine news that comes up.
A lot of people think Glenn Beck's behind it.
There are murmurs of this and the Council on Foreign Relations.
Sure.
And so we get to the possibility of nuclear war coming up, but only after incessant amount of time.
Talking about Glenn Beck and if I was a coward or even if I had more self preservation instincts, I would be getting my family out of the United States right now.
And I'm not saying that means we're going to have a nuclear war, but if there was, say, a 10% chance that there was going to be a nuclear war, would you get your family out of major target sites like the middle of Texas or robbers were coming to kill you? Would you get out of your house that night? Probably higher that we're going to have a full out nuclear war.
And people heard my show for 19 years.
Some of you have been listing that long in Austin, been syndicated for almost 18.
You know, I've never talked like that.
He always talks like that.
It's very regular.
But he also does frequently say, you know, I don't talk like this.
So if you didn't listen to a bunch of his show, you wouldn't know that.
Right.
Dave, you seem to have maybe a bone to pick with Texas.
Just made me laugh that he put like the main target central Texas.
Central Texas.
All right.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
The great threat of Central Texas.
Yeah, we'll hit them right where the economy's hard pulses from the middle of Texas.
We've long known that the Kremlin wants to take out bevo the University of Eradicate water Burger.
Then they will be partying our hands.
You see the red dawn.
We have to take out the football capitals first.
That's right.
Texas a name is where these hydra heads from.
David Knight, the guy who was yes, the guy who was moving, he shows up and he wants to come in and talk about how Glen Beck has been talking this shit.
And this leads Alex to make quite a bold pronouncement about Glenn Beck.
What he was saying was he said, they're pushing for this.
He goes, when I heard that it was I knew from the beginning that I didn't want I want to be on the other side of the story because Infowars made this a national story.
He goes, that should be a red flag, not a false flag.
Hahaha.
Not blaming fraud, giving me credit.
Rogers made it a national story.
We broke it.
He made a national it is a big story.
And he's saying that we're constantly pushing for revolution.
I think that's not true.
What happened there is exactly what Glenn Beck claims he wants to see happen, and that is peaceful people peacefully standing up with loaded guns in their face.
Like Tinyman square.
Now, some people I didn't see anybody down there with a gun on them.
Well, actually, there was a couple of guys that were holding rifles, but nobody was waiting back up there.
There was one guy on the bridge.
They keep showing that picture from multiple angles.
Okay, now it's been projected onto us.
And now we weren't there this weekend when he made the black comments.
And then you said he said mostly we were involved in that.
These guys are embedded there.
They're everywhere he goes.
They know that he was making those comments last Saturday.
Well, that was not even the same Saturday.
He's totally out of this.
He's not wrong.
I know his insider people.
He's had at least four FBI just with him at all times.
So called retired.
This is FBI.
Just like Al Sharpton's.
FBI.
I will bet my right arm the FBI is feeding all this to Glen Beck.
Glenbeck is the FBI.
Oh, Glenbeck.
Oh, my God.
It's, like, beautiful.
It's like jazz nonsense.
There's so much phenomenal stuff in there.
But it's also amazing that okay, you have the audio of Glenn Beck saying this, but in order to preserve the illusion of news, you're bringing in the guy who just listened to the Am radio for his first person account of listening to the Am radio station.
Playing the clip wouldn't be as fun.
And then to have the balls to be like, and what should we lay underneath that? Let's do a little Joe Cocker help from my friends.
Yeah, the evidence is pretty strong.
Now, more important question, do you think that Alex knew he was going to make that accusation when the sentence started? No.
Honestly, no.
Again, we're outsiders, but it is just the different connection points.
And as he starts to advance and run down the hill, remember Plinko on The Price is Right where it just sort of drops and lands.
It's sort of like that.
His mind is plinkoing.
He's bouncing around, and then spider.
FBI, and then it drops flag, and then it drops in the FBI.
And so Glen Beck is the FBI.
Yeah, but he's going to stick with this for now, but I should say in the present day, glenn Beck likes Alex.
So Alex likes Glenn Beck? Now.
He must have been wrong about the FBI thing, because he still has his right arm.
Well, yeah.
One of the great things about Alex is that every episode is a bottle episode.
Nothing really.
You don't have to hold yourself to any of these predictions like nuclear war.
It all just washes away tomorrow.
It's awesome.
Groundhog Day conspiracy, man.
No continuity.
Right.
I wonder how many times he's predicted, like, something like nuclear war.
If you could go back and count, it would be incredible.
Over 20 years on our show, I would say at least 50 times.
I've heard it so good.
Yeah.
Is often the target that he brings up.
And so I take this personally.
I'm very threatened by his false predictions.
Now, is David Knight still with Glenn Beck? I know he's got his own radio show on Iheart or whatever.
David Knight used to work for Infowars, but he got fired.
Maybe like a year ago.
He got into a fight with a guy named Steve Patentic.
Steve Patentock is this bullshit artist who would lie to Alex about stuff.
And he was saying that all the ballots in the 2020 election were watermarked, and they all were, like, tracked by blockchain.
And so Trump was going to reveal the election was stolen.
And David and I was telling Alex not to believe this nonsense, and David and I got fired.
You never say that to never say don't believe anything to Alex Jones.
You will get fired.
Yeah.
He was a long standing employee.
He had had a heart attack not too long before this.
He had come in on his day off to talk about Glenn Beck.
Years in the past and no consideration given.
I've always kind of been a little bit fascinated by Infowars as a workplace, because when they're not on air, obviously something is happening.
Yeah.
I bet they're exactly the same.
I bet they're just sitting around the water coolers talking about the same shit they talk about on air.
I bet it's no fucking different.
Do you think that they actually believe the stuff around the water cooler? Or it's like comics pitching jokes to each other.
Like, do you think there's something here? Yeah, I think they're the kind of guys that just endlessly talk nonsense.
It goes back to when the Bundys took over the wildlife place in Oregon.
At one point, there were eight guys sitting in a circle talking about their military histories.
And then when a documentarian investigated them, none of them been in the military, but they were all trading more.
Sorry.
It's just like that.
I think once it got started, they were yes.
They just sit around talking and they're all yes.
And they, on some level know it's not true, but they're also so fucking deranged that they inherently believe it.
Does that make sure? Yeah.
And I think that is what makes the grifting of today more dangerous.
Because I think they it's like if you put them on a lie detector, would they pass? I don't know.
But I know if they're around each other, they're not going to admit that it is bullshit.
Yeah.
Because that sort of grifting is not okay.
But if you believe it hard enough, then potentially it is true.
And that's really like our entire structure of government.
And half of the successful people who give commentary on it are just finding their footing for their own personal benefit.
And when you find an audience, of course you're going to keep believing it.
Air quoting believing.
Yeah.
And the first person to break KFAB in that environment is going to get eaten by the other grift spiders.
Right.
And it'll only reinforce the cafe and like, oh, no, you were the one who wasn't.
You were going to be there the day when Alex Jones just goes, I've been lying.
And they're all like, oh, I know.
That'll take some serious AA meetings, I think, before we get there.
So it turns out there's one rule at Infowars.
There's only one rule, and you won't believe what it is.
Has there not been a direct of the full year? You're here to not attack Glenn Beck and not talk about him.
That's right.
Have there been any other directors about anything else? No.
Just tell the truth.
It was very hard to do that.
And don't invite and keep the eyes on stopping the global.
That's right, yeah.
Tell the truth, I guess, abstractly.
And leave Glenn Beck alone.
You don't want to attack our other ally that's fighting it's, the globalists.
Think about it.
It's the only box.
Don't attack Glenn Beck.
Rule number two don't attack Glenn Beck.
That's it.
I love the moment of are there any other directives? If you're in, you're probably like, oh, shit.
I think I'm supposed to say no, but that's a crazy answer.
But he wants he's goading me to say no.
That's it.
On someone's keypad.
You can punch people.
You don't need to wear clothes around here.
You can steal.
Just leave Glenn back the fuck away.
Do not hurt that.
So one of the things that I find the most fun in these episodes is when people bring out quotes because they're often wrong, and sometimes it's a little silly.
Like this time with David Knight.
He whisked this one a little bit.
And as Jesse Ventura said, I don't know if it was his original expression, first they assassinate your character, then they assassinate you.
That was Gandhi, okay? That's what Gandhi said.
Okay.
to live in an environment where that is just a passing moment.
And Gandhi, again, fun fact, it's actually not even a Gandhi quote.
It did sound a little, like, aggressive for a Gandhi quote.
Gandhi said, Let don't shoot until you see the whites of your eyes.
That was Gandhi? Yeah.
From my cold, dead hand Gandhi.
No, that was stoker.
Steve austin.
You're getting a ball.
That was gold in my ear.
Gandhi 316.
Tell me I'm an ass chase.
Gandhi.
They have a fraught relationship with quotes on Infowars.
We covered his documentary Endgame, and I was fascinated because every quote was fake.
It was just like wall to wall Jefferson quotes that weren't real.
A couple of Hitler quotes that were fake.
It was wild.
I don't understand how you can take such stock in these quotes and just be like, well, that's actually just from a meme.
It's not real.
Well, still, it's a pretty good meme.
It sounds good.
Yeah, it's a good meme.
It's a very good meme.
Once you see it in writing, then all bets are off.
It's a thing.
So in this next clip, we have alex, I'll be honest with you.
I'm not sure if there's much of a point to this clip.
Okay.
I'm playing it because I want you to feel what it's like to have some ramble in your life.
Thank you.
It's really just aimless.
They knew when they were flying into flat clouds that was the factories they had to bomb.
I know when I get enemy attached that I'm over the target.
So if I get killed or set up let's just get one thing straight.
You didn't have a victory over me near world order.
I knew what I was climbing into.
I knew the cockpit I was getting into.
What just happened? I am steering into the flack.
The more I get, the more I know I'm on target.
I just want to buy you to understand that, that I'm in this to win it.
I'm not in this because I'm a narcissist.
I'm not in this because I want a big name for myself.
I am in an absolute war that I know is real.
I've committed my full life to it, and I feel like I'm not doing a good enough job to fight these tyrants.
I believe in humanity, and I'm committed, and I want to believe in other libertarian talk show host.
I want to believe in you.
I want to beat these people.
I want a better world.
I want to uphold my family name.
I want to be honorable.
I want to look at the facts and try to give you the most recent historical, morally based analysis I can.
And I'm impure myself.
I'm worldly myself.
I'm not perfect, folks.
I'm not on some high horse.
I'm not here lecturing you.
Yeah.
So there are long stretches of his show that just are like that.
It's clear he's talking to himself, right? Yeah.
It's just rambling nonsense.
Well, and it actually reminds me a lot of the whole Cogan quote, thou doth protest too much.
That was actually chae.
Oh, sorry.
Damn it.
Well, either way, the point stands.
It's kind of fascinating to go and listen to as much of the show as you do, because there are these moments of, like, you're basically just someone who doesn't go to therapy, talking to yourself, talking about yourself in your feelings on air, and it can feel a little pointless.
You know, you're in a good rhythm when you're saying, I'm not a narcissist.
Things are going pretty well.
It generally means you've been accused of that.
But even for him, because it's sort of like the unwinding of his own mind, he's accusing himself and defending himself against himself a little bit.
Well, it's a self soothing behavior.
That's what he's engaged in.
He's expressing this idea too.
You get the flak when you're above the target, and that's his way of justifying, like, every negative consequence that comes his way is actually a sign of his virtue.
Right.
Every attack is just because I'm so right about everything and it's pretty sad.
It's a bummer.
Sometimes you're just a dick.
And it's been so effective that it is like it is even then.
He was obviously such a powerful figure at that time.
But to think that that has even grown out of that is so depressing because it's like, it's been so effective.
I remember when my friend's mom was like, I watch Fox and News because Fox News because it's fair and balanced.
And I was like, well, that's what they're saying.
You know what I mean? What are you talking? Like it's that simple to hack our dumb little brains.
Yeah.
Catch phrases, man.
They work.
Yeah, just ask Gandhi.
Yeah.
So one of the things that actually is fun sort of about Alex's show is that he will come in from breaks with music sometimes and he really gets to feeling it.
One of the best that we've heard is Glenn Fry's.
You belong to the city.
He rocks out over that and it is amazing.
This is a little bit weaker than that, but still a pretty good example of him vibing.
We are marching, my friends, towards what all analysts openly say.
All analysts I've seen on television or read across the political spectrum could easily lead to thermal nuclear war.
Russian submarines carrying supersonic hydrogen bomb tipped cruise missiles are now popping up off the coast of the United States, clearly to launch attacks if given the go ahead codes against US east coast sub basis and aircraft carrier basis.
Russia is openly saying that they are prepared for nuclear war.
The Kieva of the globalist forces in Ukraine launch attacks on Russian interest.
So it's a little dramatic.
You can throw some gorillas music behind that and you got to fucking hit track.
Yeah, it is a mash up, but it's like it's just a terrible remix.
There is something to be said for Alex talking over music that unfortunately I think I'd buy an album of it.
It would be an interesting late career pivot for him to get into that.
It's like Tony Bennett's duet.
It's just like he can sort of just bring his spice to the classic Alex Jones doing the great American Song book.
Yeah.
It's just the music while he's just talking about the reptilians.
Yeah, it's William Shatnery on his album.
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
It really is a little angrier, maybe.
Talking about Russian nuclear subs off the coast, ready to launch.
Yeah.
I don't think that's responsible, probably.
No.
But God, I mean, that version is going to be stuck in my head all day.
So we get back to Glenn Beck business because, like I said, this is the top story of the brink of nuclear war.
Plus, that guy heard Glen Beck while he was moving.
Right.
And it involves Alex.
And so it's very important, apparently, some people at Fox have told Alex some things that are disconcerting.
I've told that by high level people, I mean repeatedly.
It's not even that big of a deal.
I'd be going into Fox Studios, another show.
They say Glenn Beck is freaking out, climbing walls.
You can't come on now, that's fine.
I'm going over to The View and going over to do CNN.
It's not that big of a deal.
But Glenn Beckon and his, quote, people don't want you in here.
They're throwing fits and they've got pool in the government.
And I'm like, what do you mean? And he goes, man, the guy is the government.
Linbeck is the government.
Wow.
I can name names, but I'm not going to name names folks.
Okay.
He's not going to name names.
Global is the government.
Yeah.
No, look, would naming names really help his case? Because it's quite a claim for sure.
But Alex isn't going to do that.
No, he's above it.
He's classic.
Yeah, he's a classic.
He's a classic act.
Yeah.
He was actually on the View.
He was, yeah, he was talking about Charlie Sheen.
He was in Charlie Sheen had that meltdown on Alex's show.
That was where it all happened.
And because Alex was at the center of that, he got invited on The View and just yelled infowars.com a bit.
It's pretty surreal, though, to see him sitting there on that set.
That feels like green screen.
I also like that Glenn Beck is climbing the walls like Spiderman.
Glenn Beck is both freaking out over the existence of Alex Jones and the infringement upon Glen Beck's orbit at some of these cable news operators and at the same time is so powerful that he's the government.
He got upgraded from the FBI to the whole government, which is pretty impressive.
Within like an hour.
Yeah, within an hour.
That's huge.
Yeah.
Have you ever seen Glenn Beck's Christmas show? His one man show about Randall the Boy and the bicycle? Have you ever seen it? I have not.
No, sir.
I cannot recommend it enough.
The man is out of his fucking mind.
And we watched it in the theater, me and Josh Wilson, and people got mad at us for laughing the right way.
People were very like they were decked out in their full flags and all that shit.
I can't imagine a scarier environment to see a movie like that.
It is a deep, deep journey into the mind of Glenn Beck and his fucking outstanding.
I've heard some great reviews of his books.
I've never read a book.
I mean, his books.
I've read books.
I've heard negative reviews of his books.
I can imagine he's not going to name names.
No, that's a policy that he has.
But maybe yeah, in a way it shows you that he is honorable when it comes to not outing these sources.
Sure.
But it's also god damn.
Would it really help? Some of this stuff just to really validate it and just be so fucking helpful.
Could you give us a damn specific, please? Just one.
Maybe name a name just so we could be like, okay, yes.
That name was right.
Now you don't need to anymore.
Well, maybe he will.
Maybe he will.
Glenn back.
You want it, buddy? Maybe I'll name names son.
You want it, you're going to get it.
As I gave you the benefit of the doubt and I knew you were after me and I said, leave me alone.
You think the fact that you're Benedict Garnling going to come out? You were spouting White House talking points three days before word for word it came out of Media Matters.
You got the memo before they did, bud.
We got your ass.
Whoa.
What? You've got them? You want more? We're going to capoladase on all your people now and we're going to put it out for folks.
We're going to realize your little base over there is a CIA FBI substation.
Oh, my God.
This is quite a threat.
FBI substation from which he runs the federal government.
And we know this because he had the same talking point that Media Matters did.
Three days later, tastes concluded.
Motherfucker, it's over.
And I should also say that we only know that this three day thing is happening because Alex is saying it and he's iffy on dates.
But again, once you get the dossiers compiled, which I'm sure they were, and put out yeah, I'm sure that was validating.
And corroborated all of it.
Well, sure, yeah.
And Glenn Beck went away because he was shamed out of the public.
Well, revealed that he was the government and that's over.
Yeah.
And then he got deposed, I guess because he's no longer the government.
No.
There was a coup.
No, but he still runs the FBI.
Castation kind of implies that it's in between a couple of stations, like in case people need to camp out there for a mission.
It's actually a station on a sub.
Think about it.
Whoa.
In the middle of Texas.
Doesn't he operate out of the house? Maybe that's the high level target that the nuke would say.
You better be careful where he's operating from.
Now.
We're getting to Jade Hill, aren't we? Wow.
Yeah.
Just got to figure out how the spiders play into this and we are on to something.
Man.
What the level of drugs to keep this up? What is the belief on him? Is it Adderall? Is it booze? Is it a cocktail? He's definitely a drunk, for sure.
He does his show drunk.
Sometimes less so lately, but in the past, he would be very clearly drunk.
Like one Christmas Eve, he was so drunk he threw a hatchet at one of his cameras.
It was madness.
Oh, my God.
Sometimes he has big knives in the studio.
Sometimes he has, like, a barrett Fordy cow, like cannon.
There's a surreality to some of that.
But yes, he had that hatchet.
That was a good day.
Rogan has said that Alex told him that he has a problem with Adderall.
And so there is some kind of a stimulant thing right.
That keeps the words running.
Yeah.
I think from performing and doing shows, it can be exhausting, even though it doesn't look like it's exhausting.
And what he does is pretty high intensity and not have some kind of a supplement, if you will.
Yeah, that would be great if you just started selling that as the supplement.
The Adderall booze combo is pretty fucking ridiculously.
The way that Adderall can keep the gears going no matter what you're throwing at it, if you take enough, is pretty remarkable.
I've certainly had some friends tell me that if you're drinking pretty late, like maybe you're at here in Chicago and someone gives you some cocaine, it balances you out a little bit.
Stimulant bamboo have that effect.
Yes.
And I know from having done cocaine at three or four in the morning, but a lot of times it will be the appearance that you're in control, but your memories will not be there to really back that up.
So you will seem fine, but you are out of your mind.
This is how Alex gets away with forgetting that Glenn Beck is the government.
Right.
His holes in his memory, sure.
But look, so he's got to put together these dossiers right, on Glenn Beck's staff.
And to do that, he's going to need some help.
And so he calls out, he puts it out into the universe, obiwan kind of thing.
This is one fucking day of a fucking show.
This is one day.
This is fucking crazy.
This is Fast Dave.
Honestly, this is one of the less crazy.
I was worried that some of these clips would be very boring.
Wow.
So here is Alex calling for some help.
I wonder what Anonymous is going to do about this? Are you going to let them bring me down? What, to come to my age right now? Tell the enemy he's rolling the Death Star around is going to be clear to fire in five minutes.
What are you going to do? What? I need you to help me.
I'm for real.
People want to bring me down.
They can bring me down.
They can bring you down.
They can bring Drudge down.
They can bring Rolenette daily down.
They can bring the real liberal media down, the libertarian Thomas Jefferson media down.
I wonder if he's talked to anyone, it's because there's no real information.
But it's just evolving in his psychosis to the point now where he's like, look, Anonymous, you're in the crosshairs now.
Yeah.
You're just as exposed as I am here.
It's a Glen Beck because he's the government.
Glenn Beck will unmask you and take you down.
Yeah, I do love that.
At this point, Alex is looking at Anonymous as like some kind of a like, they got my back.
Come on, brothers.
Do we even know? Wait, have we heard what Glenn Beck said about him yet? He said that the Infowars wants a revolution and that he didn't want to get involved with the bundes because Infowars was involved.
He just made a very nearly offhanded comment and this is what's happening.
He also said that Alex was excusing the racism of Five and Bundy's comments, which Alex wasn't.
But again, when you're dealing with racist time travelers, you have to be open to their racism a little bit, right? You'd be time travelist if you didn't.
Yes.
It's just gotten so crazy.
People, too, that it's like I can't remember where we started from because he made those comments.
Now they are taking down everything they're called a non.
Anonymous, bring down all of Glenn Beck's operation.
Dave, this is part of the globalist Death Star.
You should be freaked out.
Yeah.
You're ready to fire in five minutes.
Worried right now.
In the past 90 minutes, Glenn Beck has gone from an Am radio show host to cable news host to now he's the government who is going to unmask and take down all of these people.
Listen, Anonymous, if you don't stop him now, he's going to get his at out and he's going to storm your base.
Yeah.
I hate to say this, guys, because if you're having this much of, like, wonderment at this point, I don't know if you can handle the next clip.
Let's go.
I cannot fucking wait because this is something that's kind of normal on his show, but for you, this might be like a lot to take in.
I'm going to throw a hatchet.
Okay.
I'm going to say a prayer.
God, I recognize that this is a key juncture point that the enemy realizes that we're going exponentially to come after us with their offers.
Please have been a humble serve and try to be the best I can and please protect us and please help us expose the enemies within foreign and domestic and please allow me to continue on in my work so that I can do a better job and continue to wake others up.
Or if it is your will that they destroy me, please let it be an edifying message to all so that we can learn from it and in the end, defeat these enemies within these Benedict Arnold, in the name of your son, Jesus Christ, amen.
Oh, my God.
The best prayers always have my enemies, foreign and domestic, within them.
Yeah, man.
To the balls again.
I mean, it's like if you just surround yourself with people who will let you get away with things, this is how you get to the point where you're doing like, pretty much one on one public prayers with God, religion, was really the only thing separating him from Jim Jones.
And then, boom, he prays on air more than you'd think.
And it's suspicious how often the prayers seem to be a performance.
He's talking about Glenn Beck in this prayer very clearly.
Yeah, he's subpraying back.
Now, if that wasn't too much to take in this next clip, this will give you Whiplash Jarring, because this is immediately after he prays.
This is what he says.
I just ask you all to pray for this broadcast and to pray that all be revealed and that all the veils be torn back from the would be religious cult leader that is the CIA frontman, the FBI frontman, the Justice Department, Obama frontman.
That is going back.
Wow.
And I just pray that that happened.
And if it's God's will, it will.
He likes to invoke God all day.
When I invoke God, I do it very humbly.
In God's presence.
Yes.
When Alex does it, it's classy.
Yeah, for sure.
Yeah.
man.
Tough you have your head around.
It would just make so much sense if the set of info words was just like multiplicity, where there were five of them and they just are kind of swapping in and out.
You've got the religious Jones, the conspiratorial Jones, the musician Jones.
Sure be terrified of spiders, Jones.
Just reading headlines Jones.
Spider Jones, which is the one where you're like, this one is not the best copy.
We've got the spider guy.
We shouldn't let him on air too often.
The very red Alex Jones from that picture.
man.
Orlando Jones.
It's not the actor.
It's actually just like a Florida Alex Jones.
Yeah.
He has, like, board shorts and a Hawaiian shirt.
It's really remarkable to think that nothing has changed.
No.
In this two hour period that nothing has changed.
Except for potentially the level of intoxication or something.
Or just like the ratings or whatever.
Just the fact that he's just going I don't think he's drunk, to be fair.
I can usually tell like these he has little tells and he seems pretty sober.
But here's the thing.
Every episode is essentially an adventure for him.
He steps out his front door when he starts the show and who knows, right? He could end up in Mordor.
He could end up just at the other side of the Shire.
Who knows? Madness.
It's who knows where the that is fucking amazing.
We have learned just an immense amount, but we have more to learn about Glen Beck.
Good, because we've learned he's the FBI.
Hold on, maybe not.
Maybe he's above Obama.
I'm so tired of the trail of the treason I'm so tired of the dishonor I want to think more of people I want to believe that everything I was told.
About people wasn't true, even though it's been proven to be right.
There's no FEMA camps.
Ron Paul has a thing called the money Bomb to blow up the government.
He said that when the first money bombs are going on for six months, back when he said that 67 years ago, the army needs to be used against these people.
That was the Southern Property Law Center Media Matters line.
Then I kept saying, these are government lines.
These are hardcore inside lines first, not later.
He doesn't repeat the lines later.
He progenerates.
He gives birth, he coins them.
He gets the memo first, folks.
And I say he works for Obama.
It's above that.
And then I think about, how did I get into such a hardcore game? How am I, some guy from Dallas, Texas, in the middle of this? Ladies and gentlemen, there's no secret room telling me what to do.
I don't have any advisors.
I'm just here real going up against these people, like bragging.
Nobody's talking to me about this stuff.
I'm just ripping this shit out.
Believe it or not, I am coming up with this.
Dealing is like, if you're Glen Beck, you're like, okay, so how do I counter this? Yeah, well, if you're funsex people, you're going and you're going.
Hey, just so you know, I guess Alex heard some of the things you said.
What you think? He's pretty pissed off.
I mean, whatever.
This is media.
This can happen.
Hey, when you have a second, we have it.
No, someone told me about the Alex Jones thing.
No, it's gotten a little bit more out of control in the last 15 minutes.
Yeah, in the last 15 minutes.
I guess now his pitch is that you are pretty much inside the government, working for the government.
That's crazy.
You have a sub FBI CIA station.
Hey, Glen.
Glen.
Sorry.
I know you're trying to get some work done.
Yeah, there's a new update.
So it seems now that he is suggesting that you're sort of coming up with the talking points for the government and that you're no longer part of the government.
You maybe are the government.
And he bit his right arm on the fact that you are.
He'll cut his arm off if you're not.
Sometimes I just think about how I wanted to be a stand up.
Hey, Glenn.
Sorry.
I know it's only been eight minutes.
Yeah, you're above Obama now.
You might be Obama.
How am I supposed to say anything? The show's got another 2 hours.
He's been running for 17 minutes.
It's definitely a heavy day for Alex in terms of, like, Escalating.
It doesn't always snowball quite like this.
It feels druggy.
It feels like he's been popping pills as this has been going, looking at snowballs.
Maybe they just have a fog machine in the studio.
But it just releases.
Adderall.
Vaporized Adderall.
That's a good theory.
We're onto something here.
Is anger a drug? It kind of is for some folks.
It is in a way, too, where it's like he's not shouting at his friends at a bar.
He recognizes the people are listening to this shit, and if they're eating up the trash, that makes him want to throw more trash.
And as the day goes on, the trash piles have to get bigger and crazier.
And so now he's just sort of slamming around in a pile.
That's one of the problems with this style of broadcast in general.
Yeah.
The whole media.
I've had friends that have gone completely insane because they're just in a room talking to themselves on YouTube.
It's a bad medium if you're alone and no one is going, hey, check yourself a little bit here.
If you don't have a boss and a lot of the stuff that you're talking about is kind of extreme, then people respond to the extreme stuff, and then you kind of lean into that.
And how are you exciting if you're used to saying extreme stuff like, it's a downward spiral and tomorrow you need to say some crazier shit like, what's Glenn Beck going to be tomorrow? Yeah.
We all have Washington subs ready to knock America.
And Glenn Beck is above Obama.
I'm going to have George on our Ppublic or whatever.
Yes.
But magic coming back around and then being friends with this guy after that be like me being friends with Jen Kirkman.
It's not something that can happen.
I think it'll happen.
To be fair, I think Alex has said way worse things about Glenn back than this.
This could be argued to be a compliment.
Yes.
In a way it's a scary compliment, but in a way it is.
You are higher than Obama.
Yeah.
You know who's higher than Obama? Alex Jones.
He is higher as fuck.
Yeah.
But it's definitely an insult or an accusation that involves competence.
You are so competent that you are above the president.
Anonymous, let's go.
Yeah.
I need a giant team of faceless hackers in order to take you down.
I can rationalize that as being a positive.
Yeah, it's a scary compliment, but it's a compliment.
This was from 2014.
So did Anonymous come to help him? I can't remember about the Glen back on Mastermind.
We saw Obama's birth certificate.
He was back.
Actually, Alex doesn't believe the birth certificate stuff.
He did.
Oh, my God, what a line.
He initially believed it, but then he realized that it was a trick because the people like the Obamas put it out knowing that people like Alex and the right wing community were racist, and so they would jump on top of it and take the bait.
It's a false flag birth certificate.
You bet.
In reality, Obama's dad is Frank Marshall Davis sorry, is a communist guy.
I don't know.
I haven't taken this line too much further than that.
He made a documentary about it at some point.
He stole a documentary about it called Dreams of My Real Father.
Oh, my Lord, what a title.
It's still a bit racist, to be honest.
It was a different time, Dan.
Alex is a time traveler is a time, for God's sake.
So at this point, we've entered the sort of home stretch of the show, and Alex brings on Joseph Farrah, the guy who runs World Net Daily, onto the program.
Oh, God.
We're not going to listen to well, just one clip of it because it's pretty boring.
It's mostly about how the Clintons wanted to take him out, and I don't know how that's relevant.
Take out Alex or the world net daily.
World Net Daily back in the we're in 2014, sort of getting credibility off that.
They did did they end up murdered? They didn't.
Okay.
Because I'm not sure if he got murdered and then this is a clone or an impossible no, but they were close because he was asking too many questions about Vince Foster.
There's the buzz name.
Yeah.
So far one of his big points is that we got to stick together.
There's not many of us who are in this, and he accidentally includes Glenn Beck in his list of names.
Oh, yes.
For a long time when I started the World Net earlier bare years, I thought to myself, I wonder why nobody else is doing this.
I wonder why nobody else is saying, hey, we're having a modest degree of success here.
Why isn't anybody trying to prey? Finally, after many years, there have been info wars.
Breitbarts.
Daily Callers.
Glenn Beck.
Now we have some other folks out there joining us, and we got to make sure that we don't split hairs with them.
The other side wants to have a united front.
Where's our united front? I totally agree.
We talk about this every time on the phone or on air, and Savage is doing that.
Good for him.
I mean, the attacks and I'm not going to bring it up, it's just Beck saying that, quote, I want a violent revolution and a civil war when I say the opposite, that I'm a racist covering up for Bundy.
I mean, maybe you're right.
Maybe he's just doing it out of fear.
But it doesn't matter.
I'm being thrown into the bus here, and it's very creepy.
And I'm just glad that you're an honorable person, Joseph FARA.
Look forward to seeing you next week.
And I'm glad you're not a coward.
All right.
God bless.
That's how I end my interviews.
But really, every lunch I have anybody, I ended up saying, I'm glad you're not a coward.
That's always how I end things.
I do it after someone orders.
I'm glad you're not a coward.
You went with fries instead of potato salad.
I mean, it really is amazing to have said all the things you've said and then have this guy dropped Glenn Beck and be like, well, look, to be honest, I'm not a huge Glen Beck fan.
It's like, yeah, there's some dissonance.
How do you not say to that guy? He says that about going back, and you go, well, he has a substation.
He runs the FBI.
I think this question answers itself, and that is that Josephara is not a coward.
Right.
Bringing this up would inevitably lead to some pushback, and I think that's probably why just go along, to get along.
None of this means anything anyway.
Alex I actually believe that going back is above Obama, but it's so clear there that that's the case because he uses it in the wrap up.
Well, to be honest, I'm not a huge Glenn Beck fan.
He says Civil war, but anyway, potato, potato.
Great to have you on.
I just got to defend myself.
I got to defend myself a little bit.
He might be in charge of the globalist Death Star.
We're not sure.
Anyway, little help from my friends is going to play us out anonymous.
From Anonymous.
Yeah, it's silly.
Things don't make sense.
And that's just part of the infowar.
Man in this third hour of his show, he was interviewing Joseph Farrah.
And then the premise was basically that he was going to take calls, but time essentially runs out and too much time complaining about Glenn Beck.
And so there's no calls.
And Alex is feeling a little bit like, you know, I'm cool, I'm a cool guy.
And that's kind of the vibe he wants to go out on.
These globalists are evil.
I said I take calls, but I won't.
I'm out of time.
It's so creepy to be targeted by the White House going back.
The average person is scared of what their neighbor thinks of them.
Every once in a while, I'll be in a restaurant or walking down the street or a store in some socialist levels of overall court, idiot, and I hate you like a kick your butter.
But if you're looking for Cooch man or boo boo, the more table.
That's happened a few times.
This is some liberal thing they do.
Shame on you.
And it just means nothing to me.
I was over to buddies once at his local community pool hot tub, and these trendy swimmers, they got Alex Jones.
I think you're just grace in.
A couple of months ago, weldon was there.
He was over there with me.
We had a few beers and I just looked at them and I just kept talking to them and they laughed.
And my buddies laughed because it meant nothing to me.
Those guys thought them laughing at me would upset me.
It didn't upset him.
He just talking about it.
I always find that to be, like, really sincere and convincing when people don't bother me.
Yeah, don't bother me at all.
I'm talking about it here because I'm fine with it.
I was just at a community poolhot tub.
Garrison seemed to discuss you a little bit.
You were taken aback by the community pool, first of all.
Community pool.
I'm like, is Alex Jones going to a community pool? But that's not crazy.
But community hot tub just has, like, weird kind of orgy vibes.
You know what I mean? Yes, community hot tub.
It's like a community pool.
I'm like, all right.
Somewhere for the kids to go on the weekends.
It's the community hot tub.
Like, all right, you fucking creep.
Yeah, the part after the slash was, yeah, communitypool hot tub.
And also just picturing Alex remind me, like, when they put Bugs Bunny in a cauldron and try to cook him like Alex Jones carrot.
Yeah, just Elmer Fudd carroting him up.
What color does Alex Jones turn in a hot tub? It's lobster Town, man.
Yeah.
I mean, seriously, he must start crustacheining.
Well, here's the thing.
You guys don't listen to a ton of this.
You wouldn't know, but a lot of Alex's stories take place in hot tubs.
He has a famous story about being in a hot tub, and a couple of globalists came in, and we're going to get you.
They were, like, threatening him in the hot tub.
by.
Globalists in hot water a lot.
He might want to stay clear, some of these hot bodies.
Is there a space in here? I'm a globalist.
Excuse me.
So it says six people at a time.
Is that six regular humans? How many globalists may squeeze in now? Don't mind my eight legs.
Yeah.
Pardon me.
I'm in a rock band.
You see.
Spider comes out and what do you do, sir? I'm a globalist.
It's on the business card.
Hey, I'm a globalist.
We're both in the globalist business.
So this brings us to the end of this episode.
And I don't know if you have some feelings on making it through something of basically your birthday, your show's birthday.
Yeah, at least everything has gone so much better since then.
Yeah.
He's just such a train wreck figure.
But it's almost like, I guess you think of him when you don't know as much as you all do.
He is dangerous in so many ways.
But this is the mind of a child.
It's just a child's mind.
And it's just pretty simple what's going on.
And it's, I guess, very effective for those who are in.
But there's really not much to it.
He's just trying to fucking keep the train running.
Just keep the words coming out.
Create the straw man.
He's got his terms.
They're very effective.
And to what you were saying, like, he walks out his door, and he's like every day he's a Pixar movie for him.
Yeah, I'm certain.
He has essentially no preparation for anything, just seed of his pants.
And that's how you can get these ridiculous things, like an entire show where he's escalatingly accusing Glen Beck of stuff.
Right.
Well, I have nothing else really to talk about.
I've already made people scared about this nuclear war thing, and I got nowhere else to go with that.
What can I say? In between Hawking survival items, he really is like when people like, you have a friend that did something, and then in your head, you're like, oh, I'm going to say this to him and this to him, and then it kind of spirals out and you're just thinking of all this stuff.
But that's all he does on Show.
It's the kind of thought you have.
And then you go, oh, no, it's just Frank.
I just fucking call him.
But he just goes for hours.
It's a guy spiraling out for fucking hours.
If this was so hugely important, it probably should have gotten on his radar in another way than a guy who worked for him was moving.
Well, again, like I said, the guy who was moving, his brother heard it and told the guy who was moving I mean, it's like, come on.
God, it's so good.
We will reveal his sources and what he does.
It's a guy who works for me, his brother.
One of his big sources of information in the present day is his wife's tennis partner.
He gets a lot of deep intel from her.
This shows stupid.
So the next day, is he just over completely and onto something else, or does he continue on? Will he continue on with something like this, or will he just drop it? It changes.
I'm not sure.
I haven't listened to the next day's episode, so I couldn't say for sure.
Sometimes it becomes a little bit of a crusade, and then sometimes he'll get distracted.
Sure.
Or like he went on Piers Morgan's show and yelled at him about guns because Alex started a petition to get Piers Morgan deported.
That's great.
Finally we agree.
Yeah.
And then he went on Piers Morgan show and started yelling at him about how, like, you guys tried to take our guns in 1776.
And that became, like, two weeks of his show.
Don't tell Alex that you for weeks.
That's actually what the War of Independence is about.
It was gun confiscation.
Oh, my God.
Well, thank you for having us on, Dan.
Thank you.
I'm sure almost everybody who listens to our show be aware of your show, the Dollop, but is there anything else you want to direct people's attention to that they should check out? I mean, I would keep your eyes on Glenn Beck.
Yeah, keep your eyes peeled.
We have a virtual show we're doing September 8.
We're touring, so you can go to Dollopodcast.com.
I'll be recording some shows in Seattle, Portland, and vancouver.
You could go to Gareth Reynolds.com for those stand up shows and listen to the dog.
Like you said, hell yeah.
Save.
I got nothing.
Fair enough.
Check me out on Twitter.
I'm yelling at people.
Yeah, if you can get into Dave's Twitter bar.
Not that protected status.
Yeah.
Do you think Twitter ends with me having blocked everybody on Twitter, just yelling at myself? I think it ends when you realize you can block yourself.
If you do end up blocking everybody and you're just yelling at yourself, eventually this episode of Alex is going to be your future.
Yeah.
Well, thanks again, guys.
It's been a real pleasure and hopefully can do it again sometime.
Yeah, love to.
Thanks.
Awesome.
Andy and Janzis, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
So, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I loved.