Not knowledge fights.
I am sweating knowledgebuddy.com.
It's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledge.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're good guys.
Chang.
We are the bad guys.
I love your room.
Knowledgefight.
Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey, Rebel.
Welcome back.
Knowledge, right? I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple of dudes like to sit around worship at the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are, Dan.
Jordan, Jordan, Jordan.
Quick question for you.
What's up? What's your bright spot today, buddy? My bright spot today, I guess, is that we're back in the saddle.
Everything is back to normal.
Yes, it was very nice.
And a big thank you to Dave and Gareth for filling in your seat on Monday.
Fantastic job.
I would also like to apologize to the audience that apparently that whole spider thing is maybe based on anti Semitic conspiracies from history.
Also, maybe it's just a spider.
I mean, sometimes a spider is just a spider.
It's not always a penis.
It's hard to say in this case.
Freud said that, but, yeah, I didn't realize that at the time, but, yeah, it's nice to be back.
Yeah, absolutely.
Thank you for the bath bombs.
Oh, you are very welcome, my friend.
Bespoke Irish bath bombs of the kind that can only be found in Dublin.
Beautiful, beautiful Dublin.
Little shape of the Blarney stone.
Each one has a tiny piece of the Blarney stone.
So what's your bright spot, Dan, is my bright spot is obviously my, quote, vacation was a little bit longer than usual, and that's because my partner is on mental health leave from school, and school has started.
And rather, for those who don't know, she's an art teacher at a school that shall not be named.
So the amount of nonsense that is immediately out the gate, there's only two art teachers, and one of them now has 50 kids in her class.
And rather than hire a different art teacher, the administrative staff hired three more admin people.
So I think we know exactly what their focus is.
Admin.
Yeah.
And it ain't teachers.
How is this your bright spot? Her mental health during that time period was revelatory, getting away from it all.
I mean, it was a reset for her.
She was better than it was not quite that great.
Okay.
She did not stop climate change, but she slept better than I think I've seen her sleep in a long time.
And not like that.
I slept 12 hours kind of sleep, but that healthy.
I'm waking up on a good time, and I'm happy, and I'm doing a good job.
It was beautiful to watch, and it just filled me with so much joy.
So, yeah, that's my bright spot, is that we have left that horrible place where she was happy and come back to Chicago where she can be abused by everybody.
We got Vienna beef right through the garden.
That's what we got.
Give me some of that relish.
They don't have it there.
No, that's true.
They really don't.
There's an embargo on relish.
Absolutely.
So, Jordan, today we have an episode to go over.
Hell.
Yeah.
There's been a lot that's happened since we've recorded a present day episode.
Right.
Because you're gone and then the trial stuff was pretty dominant.
Yes.
It caused a clog in the pipes, as it were.
And I decided that what we should do is focus on the thing that I think most people were talking about, maybe the highest profile piece of information.
And that was that last week on Wednesday, Alex turned on Trump.
Right.
Or one would be led to believe that.
I'm sorry.
So this was last Wednesday, not four months ago.
Not a year ago.
No, not a year and four months ago.
No, not a year and eight months ago.
The point is made that Alex turns on Trump a lot.
Seems like he's turned on Trump quite a bit.
I'm surprised it's still news.
Yeah.
So we're going to talk about August 17, 2022.
How do you do? Okay.
We'll get back to some other present day stuff on Friday, but that seemed like something that has an immediate need.
It needs an address.
Indeed, yes.
Now, Jordan, I want to address one thing really quick, and that is that there's a widespread perception that I took a week off because you were good luck out of town, and this is not true.
I would give anything for you to take a week off.
We did not put out any episodes so publicly.
It might have appeared that I took a week off, but I did not.
And I have something very special to announce, and that is that we are doing another round of buttons.
What? Everyone loves a button.
Everybody.
And I'm really thrilled with this round.
Our flagship button this time around is made by my dear friend Angela Lampsberry, and she's designed the Squatch Has No Heroes button.
So everyone who responds will get one of those.
Right.
And then there's a random pick from a series of other buttons.
Yes.
A number of them made by the very talented Lard D'Souza.
A number of different buttons themed on Alex things like Grape Job is one of them.
And so those are there.
Also our dear friend Sarah Shockey from Marty and Sarah Love Wrestling.
Absolutely.
Among other things, she designed a dreamy, creamy summer button.
Oh, man.
And dreamy.
Creamy Summer 2022.
Because I'm going to do this every day.
Well, yeah, obviously, that is our deal.
Next year will be yogurts, though.
I don't think it won't be no, we don't do yogurts.
I'm not going to do that.
I was going to say so we have all these buttons, and there's two important things to bring up.
One is that I have learned over the course of doing these button things that this is the best way to ruin an inbox.
So I have needed to create a separate email address for button requests.
Right.
I wanted to get Kfbuttons@gmailcom.
Of course you did.
It's taken.
How? By whom? I don't know.
Kingfightersbuttons, what are you talking about? So the email address that you need to write to if you want a button oh, boy.
Is Kfbutton 69 at Gmail.
Oh, man.
That was available? How could it not be? So, if you want a button, just send an email to that with your address, or a shipping address, mailing address, and we will get those turned around.
Ideally, I would like to get those maybe mailed and all done by the end of the dream and creamy summer.
Sure.
As a sort of celebration of the end of it, actually.
But I'm not totally committed to that because these things I don't know.
I mean, we had way more people want them last time than I could.
God knows what's going to happen now.
Yeah.
This could be absolutely chaos.
I said I wouldn't do this again and then I did it again.
That's what happens when you go out of town.
I know.
You can't not work.
Now, one more important thing about these buttons.
Yes.
This is very exciting.
Okay.
There is a design that is a what's your bright spot design of a button.
It has a little treasure chest on it.
I've made three of these.
Oh, my God.
Damn.
I wanted to make a Willy Wonka.
Willy Wonka ad.
Motherfucker.
There are three golden tickets.
Yes.
Okay.
There are only three.
I've only made three.
And whoever receives them will also receive an ironic punishment of some sort.
No.
If you receive one of those and send us a picture of you with the button yeah.
You don't have to send yourself a picture of your face or whatever, but we will make a donation to a charity of your choice in your name.
Absolutely.
So that's the way we're going to Wonka it's done.
No ironic punishments necessary.
Just something kind of fun, something really cool.
I thought it would be silly, but then I also thought we should just do one.
No, we can't just do one.
And the odds of it maybe not getting to the person trying to scare me.
Right.
So three seem like the sweet spot.
Right? Well, at least get two, maybe.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
And this isn't true at all, but I'm going to say it in order to scare people.
Okay.
I can tell a bootleg a mile away.
I will be able to tell if you're trying to run a fast one.
Absolutely not.
And they're not be putting up with any of that.
Don't post your button picture publicly.
Otherwise somebody will get the screenshot, image search.
Oh, that's true.
Yeah.
I don't know what that means.
He was going to say, Sounds convinced.
Well, you both know it.
So Jordan let's get into this episode.
But first, let's say hello to some new wands.
That's great.
Also, because we were out of town and we didn't have the backlog.
Once again.
Oh, boy.
Sorry.
Yeah.
Anyway, coming from the outer regions of the universe, it's Dantron Zero and Jordan Nader.
Check it.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy walk.
I'm a policy walk.
Dantron Zero and Jordan Nader.
Next, Jordan's physics knowledge is awesome.
Doctor of Physics Lily.
Thank you so much.
You're an I'm a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
You know about physics? I know a lot, actually.
It's weird.
So tell me something about physics.
Well, an electron is not really a thing.
It's actually kind of a superposition.
So you can never know what an electron is.
And so it's more considered a field at this point in time.
Now, if you put it through a particle accelerator, all right, you're going to get all kinds of wild stuff.
I love it when Jordan says bananas.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy walk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
I feel like that's sarcastic because I say it too much.
No, this person actually explained that they chose the name because they like it when you say banana.
Oh, wow.
I mean, that's a very literal bananas thing to say.
Indeed.
Yay.
So we also got some Technocrats in the mix here, Jordan.
So first.
Oh, my God.
Coal has been taken over by the globalists.
Just kidding.
It's as dope as it's ever been.
Thank you so much.
Oh, I get it.
It's not cold.
I thought it was cold.
It's cold.
Oh, the open mic.
The bar.
Yeah.
Just kidding.
It's as deep as it's ever been.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
Next, the magical, mystical Master Sergeant Daniel Jordan's.
Mystery Conspiratorial time Machine Band Featuring the Doctor Dreamy Creamy.
Featuring the Dreamy Creamy.
Dr.
twoTS and the Amazing Technical Squatch.
Thank you so much, you are now a Technocrat.
And soyboizoo the pretend race team.
Thank you so much.
You're now a Technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
I have risen above my enemies.
I might quit tomorrow, actually.
I'm just going to take a little break now, a little breaky for me.
And then we're going to come back and I'm going to start the show over.
I'm the devil.
I got to be taken over here.
Fuck you.
I got plenty of words for you, but at the end of the day, fuck you in your new world order, and fuck the horse you rode in on and all your shit.
Maybe today's creep on this broadcast.
Maybe I'll just be gone a month, maybe five years.
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow and you never see me again.
That's really what I want to do.
I never want to come back here again.
I apologize to the crew and the listeners yesterday that I was legitimately having breakdowns on air.
I'll be better tomorrow.
He's not.
Oh, no.
So we start off here with Alex being in a mood about deaths in the world.
Sure.
There's a lot of deaths.
Well, yes, recently.
Yeah.
His take on it might be a little off though.
Okay, there's no turning back now.
We've chosen which side we're on.
Team Freedom.
We are now inside the operational phase of global cultural and economic societal collapse and the mass forestry population that has already begun according to all major insurance I'm sorry, what now? Record deaths in every western country that has taken the experimental injections.
Incredible time to be alive.
Look, so look, you look, alex, look up the claim that all western countries are seeing record deaths.
It's not something that Alex can make in any meaningful way.
The type of statistics you would need to prove that aren't available.
And the only thing you could possibly be working off of is like anecdotal stories that his antivax friends are telling him that he sees on social media or that weird Steve guy's substitute.
Yeah, I mean, is there a running tally of deaths per twelve month time period that you can compare going back several hundred years perhaps, to the Black Death? You know what I'm saying? Like what is a record number compared to what? Oh, that is a good point.
He says record deaths.
It's not very specific.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't think he cares as much.
He's just talking shit.
That's a good point.
But Alex is blaming this on the COVID vaccines, which again, is also a lot of shit.
The only place he ever pulls vaccine data from is VAERS.
Because it's a place where all reports of any side effects that anyone experiences after getting vaccinated are reported, regardless of whether or not the vaccine caused the side effect.
Up to August 10, 2022, there had been 606,000,000 doses administered and 15, 930 reports of people dying after getting the vaccine that had been entered into VAERS.
That doesn't mean that almost 16,000 people died because of the vaccine.
But even if it did, that represents 00:20 6% of vaccinations.
The CDC has identified nine deaths that they can causally link to a vaccine for COVID.
And those aren't even the mRNA ones.
Those are people who got the Johnson and Johnson show.
So none of this makes any sense.
This is stupid, but Alex wants to be very extreme about the vaccine, and I got that sense pretty immediately.
And I think that there's a good reason.
I think you'll see as this goes on, why this needs to be heightened.
Okay.
And made as severe as possible.
So yeah, we got the midterms coming up.
Oh my God.
Why does he keep talking about the midterms? Because they're very important.
No one cares.
The Republicans, they might want to take over the country.
Sure, Alex might be okay with that, but also maybe they need to take over the country more.
That sounds right.
Republicans running around wedding themselves with excitement that we're about to take over the country even if we get more Senate seats and take the Senate and take the House.
So many Republicans are basically Democrats.
Yeah, only that's the big problem.
But the good news is this.
We have leaders like Rhonda Santas and we have leaders like Balsamaro and Victor Orban and others that understand what's going on.
He's been ramping up his name dropping of Orban.
It's been definitely happening more lately.
Let me be clear.
We don't have leaders like Bolsonaro and Orban.
Just because Orban spoke at CPAC doesn't mean he has any control over the US.
I feel like if I was DeSantis, I would be like, please don't put me in without and out fascists.
I would like to still slide under the radar for at least a little while before I get to become president and fascist with the shit out of people, ironically get me past the midterm.
Exactly.
Yes.
Then we'll talk.
Yeah.
Obviously the big talking point that was circling around social media after this episode was that Alex has turned on Trump in favor of DeSantis.
Sure.
So it's obviously a high praise for him to be put in the same category as or bomb the people destroying the Amazon rainforest.
So Alex does still like Trump, and that's something that's important to recognize, despite what the sort of Alex has turned on Trump.
Finally, the discourse.
Yeah.
This episode has been now, I'll say this.
I like Donald Trump, and I know the system doesn't like him, and I know I've been persecuted like nothing in my life for supporting him.
Sure.
That made me kind of pig headedly support him a few years ago, even though I disagree with his warp speed, because I thought that we had to keep him in office because of the nightmare scenario if Hillary or Biden got in.
So if this is true and Alex supported Trump when Operation Warp Speed was happening because of need to keep Trump in office, then he was lying to his audience.
Alex was super clear that he had, like, these really high level back channel intelligence sources.
They were telling him that Trump was supporting the vaccine to set a track for the globalists and so he could force their hand to reopen the economy.
Alex has also said that Trump got tricked into supporting the vaccine development, but he's never said that it was a purely partisan political consideration on his own part to excuse that behavior.
Yeah, that's fucked up.
Yeah.
Also, covet happened after Hillary had lost the 2016 election, so I have no idea what she's coming up here.
It's pretty insane to think that Alex could have acted the way he did and excused all the shit that he's completely philosophically against just because of a desire to keep Trump in office, who, I should remind you, is the person who is doing all the stuff Alex is philosophically against.
He supported vaccines and boosters.
He didn't get Alex and the weirdos back on social media.
He didn't lock up Hillary.
He didn't build a wall and kick out all the immigrants.
He didn't free Julian Assange.
All of this stuff should be fundamentally disqualifying for Alex.
And yet he turned a blind eye because he didn't want a Democrat to win the presidency.
That's weird.
And this obviously doesn't apply to him.
Obviously, Alex this does not apply to Alex.
But for me personally, I would feel shame if I was telling you that, by the way, when I said all of that stuff, I was betraying all of my principles for no reason other than that people made me feel like I should because I oppose them.
And I was coming up with elaborate stories to pretend that I wasn't giving up on my principles.
By rationalizing giving up on my principles for several years, I have learned that I was rationalizing giving up my principles for several years.
You motherfuckers.
I made up so many Lieutenant Colonels these last five years.
Oh, man.
There are so many people who are fighting against the deep state, who let me know that it was okay for me to betray all my what? Great.
What? I don't want to sound too mean, but this is pathetic.
Alex rejected the opportunity to stand up for all of his principles because he saw a possibility that someone who he kind of knew might be able to hang on to power.
This isn't the sort of thing a person like who Alex pretends to be would do.
It's what a coward does.
And guess what? It didn't matter.
Biden still won the 2020 election, and here we are.
Alex sold himself out for a presidential election, something his past self would never let him get away with.
And what has he got to show for it? Nothing.
Basically nothing.
It is funny to go back and think about all of those positive comments from Glenn Greenwald and Matt Taibbi about how he was ahead of his time and he's sticking to his guns, and that's why people didn't like him.
It was because he refused to be a part of the two party system.
And then to hear him say, you know, I'm thoroughly a part of the two party system.
Sad.
Quite sad.
Yeah.
Almost as sad as we're recording this.
I'm seeing on Twitter that it looks like Laura Loomer might win her primary.
Hell yeah.
It's a heavily GOP district.
She's probably going to be in.
She's in.
Put her right next to MTG.
Oh, my God.
I think they should put them in a Pope mobile in Congress.
They should be put behind glass so everybody can sometimes turn and look at them and go, oh, look at that.
We have pets.
Oh, my God, she's going to be great.
She's going to handcuff herself to one door of Congress.
Beautiful.
More dumbness, please.
Oh, my God.
I can't handle this.
Anyway, Alex likes DeSantis now because he's getting pilled as hell, sure.
But that said, I am supporting the Santa.
DeSantis is just gone from being awesome to being unbelievably good.
And I don't just watch a man's actions, as Christ said, just a tree by his fruits.
I can also look in his eyes on HD video and I see the real sincerity of a father and a husband who loves his children in this country and that he's getting red pilled more and more each day.
And then he's white pilled about the future and we stand up.
I'm sorry, what if we don't? Yeah, that white pill, black pill thing is convoluted.
If you believe that there is a chance you can do something to alter the future, then you can't be blackpilled.
This is just Alex wanting to throw around pill language.
Willynilly pilly nilly, if you will.
I won't.
All right, fine.
Yeah.
I think Alex may have some problems with DeSantis that he doesn't expect to come up because he doesn't really know much about him except for the shit he talks.
Right? Like the Santa does talk a fair amount of shit, sure, but I think some of the positions that he holds could end up being a problem for Alex, too.
It's fun, though, that he has a shiny new aspiring fascist to cheerlead for.
But that light is only going to dim over time as DeSantis fails to live up to Alex's comically extremist expectations.
But also, this is just a bummer.
Alex can just support no one.
That's what he's supposed to be, the guy who isn't backing any individual because he's too busy rooting out corruption on both sides of the aisle.
Having a candidate you're supporting kind of makes your whole Watchdog thing seem a little false, and it's really a repudiation of his entire character.
And I put Ron Paul on the side because he was a perennial loser.
Ron Paul, he's never going to win.
Even if he did win, his function is to destroy the thing he was elected into.
It's different.
If I were Alex, I would have gone back to Rand Paul or I would have just abandoned Trump without choosing a new hero.
I have a strong sense of why Alex is doing the thing this way, and we'll get into this over the course of the episode, but it's just so sad to see him go from a guy who's like, I'm above it all to being like, I'm going to hedge my bets with a different GOP candidate.
Here's my big problem with all of this.
All of it, which is, one, he's supporting DeSantis.
For what? President? No, for the governor of Florida.
He's already the governor of Florida.
He's got to be reelected.
Fine.
He has not announced he's running for president.
He's not going to win.
Oh, my God.
But even then okay, so he's supporting DeSantis now.
That doesn't mean anything now.
He's supporting him for president in the 2024 election.
But 2022, who gives a fuck who you're supporting now, right? Especially if that person is not it's not even officially running for anything, and neither is Trump.
Why are we talking about the 2024 president of that presidential election? The world is burning now because I think that there's a dynamic going on that Alex got bit by the presidential election bug in 2015 and you just can't get enough.
Sure.
I think that it's been so successful for him in terms of marketing, audience attracting, all kinds of things.
People get really caught up in it.
There's a sportsy element to it very much, and I think he didn't tap into that much for his entire career because as much as you can cheerlead for Ron Paul during the early parts of the GOP primary where he's involved, that kind of dies down and then you just got to talk shit about all the candidates.
Yeah, exactly.
Great hooray.
But now, in the same way that people started talking about the midterms after the general election, alex is just jumping the gun.
He's over eager for the general election.
I mean, here's the problem, though.
I don't care.
And I feel like if you're one of the people who wrote that an infinite number of Alex Jones finally turned on Trump stories, if you're talking about that, then you're talking about the 2024 election, of which there's no reason to speak of.
Yeah, it's silly.
I wish I had some names, but I did see a couple of articles that did a good job of pointing out, maybe not in the lead of the story, but in the body of the article.
He has done this a bunch of times when he has been seeking attention or publicity stuff.
That's nice.
There have been people, some people who have called out that Alex does this a bit, but that definitely was not the prevailing attitude on social media and a number of other media places.
But even then, if you pointed out in the body of the article and the headline is still there, you're using his bullshit for your clicks.
That's what it is.
So regardless of how well a job you do in your writing, the headline is bullshit.
It's a tough line to draw, tough balance, and maybe some people didn't.
Some people whisked.
Yeah, I don't know.
But look, this is not what it appears to be.
This is not a throwing out Trump and bringing in DeSantis.
Sure.
And that is the perception that you would get if you didn't pay much attention.
He has basic self preservation instincts and I'm a DeSantis guy, and if we can use the Santa's leadership to get Trump back on the straight and narrow, that's all the better.
But Trump will not talk about his poison vaccines anymore.
That's a plus.
He still says he won't say the V word, but he's still proud of it.
So yeah, he just is really interested in getting Trump away from the vaccines.
Right.
This is a solid thrust that Alex is pushing, and he was like, hey, you even have a scapegoat here, man.
Just by fauche that's all Trump needs to do is say, I was lied to by Burke and Fauche, and they were holding the country hostage, and I thought it was a regular vaccine, and it turns out they shouldn't be pushing it on children.
They shouldn't be making people take it.
He's already saying that, but he has to come out all the way and say, I was lied to and decouple his pig headed butt that I still love.
He's real.
What? He's just pinheaded.
So you said earlier when he's fighting for us, it's not when he won't admit he's wrong.
Balsamaro apologized.
What? And said it was bad from the start.
I shouldn't have halfway supported it, though.
I was never for forced injection.
And now the Santa has come out in a bunch of speeches and said, this is bad news.
That's all we want so we can stop poisoning the newborn babies and the six month olds and everybody.
And they got public schools all over blue cities and blue states trying to make the injections mandatory to go to school.
Damn it.
So I think he's editorializing a little bit on Bolsonaro's comments, but he apologized after he went to the hospital the fifth time.
Yeah, the one that he's got his head up his ass.
I think he had an impacted bowel for a while, and then they removed it, and then he was anti vaccine.
I think that's how it went.
So Trump is pig headed and what have you, but Alex but Alex said earlier that he supported Trump because he was being pig headed.
It's an interesting point.
Shouldn't that make him support Trump further? Nah.
Okay, fair enough.
Supports DeSantis, but also still supports Trump.
Right.
And Trump is big headed, but if he's big headed in the right direction, then everything would be fine, right? Alex is saying, I'm a big baby.
Wah wah wah.
Please listen to me.
He's just begging Trump.
Yeah.
So I choose children over Trump, and I'm going to say it.
I'm not going to get sucked into politics and just support Trump because I hate the Democrats.
If Trump doesn't come out against these shots and if he doesn't stand with the children, if he doesn't go in the offense to admit there's major problems, then I'm really caught between a rock and a hard place, because I don't want Kamala Harris or Michael Obama or any of those people.
I know you don't, but I cannot support Trump when the evidence is out that it's killing all these people and maaming others if he continues to do this.
And I think we should open the phones up today on this subject.
So, yeah, here's what's.
Going on as we're getting experienced throughout the course of this episode, alex is torn between supporting Trump and DeSantis.
There are pros and cons with both.
With DeSantis, he's got a lot of policy positions that the audience wants to hear, and most importantly, he's been a strong opponent of vaccines, or at least that's the way he has allowed himself to be portrayed.
On the flip side, DeSantis is not going to give Alex the opportunity to pretend to be his friend.
He's an actual politician who knows better than to make that kind of an association.
It's going to be crippling in the long term.
He's too young.
He has a career ahead.
We get a future.
Conversely, Trump is fine letting weirdos into the inner circle, and Alex has the best shot of staying relevant with Trump are plus Alex's buddies with Roger Stone.
So the connection with Trump there is pretty important, I think.
They probably not talk anymore, right? Alex flipped.
Well, it's more likely for Alex to get some sort of pardon or whatever should that need arise from Trump as opposed to DeSantis.
That is true.
I don't know what things Alex could be pardoned for by Trump.
I mean, at this point, you want a preemptive pardon from the President for whatever.
There's a good chance you're committing a crime just by being around it.
Just in case.
Yeah, absolutely.
The problem is that Trump supports vaccines.
This is a big deal because Alex's audience is aggressively antivaxx, and they don't like Trump as much anymore because of it.
But this ceases to be a problem if Alex can just convince Trump to become antivaxx.
That will be a much easier fix than trying to get to Santa to be an infowars guy.
And I think that's what this whole pageant has been about.
Over the course of this episode and then this video that Alex puts out later, there were two goals.
He's trying to threaten Trump like he did with Rogen, into contempt vaccines by saying that he's going to be like a pig.
You got sneaky snake.
Yeah.
And he's trying to score as much free publicity as possible from rubes who feel like they're actually dunking on him.
Third, there's probably an element here that he's soft pitching to the audience.
The actual idea of becoming into DeSantis fully sure, because I think you want to see how the audience responds that you heard him say, we're going to take some calls, put the feelers out there.
Right.
And also, you've got plenty of time for the election that is several years away.
Yes, you certainly do.
Yeah, you got plenty of time.
Let's put that in the news.
Alex changes his support for candidate who is not yet running for president to another guy who's not yet running for president.
Another thing I want to point out here is that Ron Flipkowski, this Twitter account, posted a 42nd clip of Alex saying that he was supporting DeSantis, which, as I was preparing this episode, had over 2500 retweets and had been watched by almost 9000 people.
This clip is inaccurate, and it's actually manipulatively edited in order to present an image that Ron wants to convey, as opposed to what's actually being said by Alex in this episode.
His clip entirely omits the part where Alex is clearly saying that if Trump would just stop that shit with the vaccines and there wouldn't be a problem.
And I think that that's a major component of what Alex is saying here.
It would be one thing if this was actually a straight up episode where Alex was like, I'm done with Trump, let's just go with DeSantis.
But that's not what's going on here.
If you posted an abbreviated clip of that and it captured what Alex was saying, fine.
If he said I was going to shove DeSantis up his dirty asshole, that's a whole different story.
Sure.
Yeah, because he's never done something like that before.
No.
Accounts like this farm attention and social media cloud by posting things that their audience wants to hear, this Ron Fella knows that there's a pretty solidly Democratic voter base that follow him, and it would give them a sense of shodding Freud to hear that Trump had lost his most zealous and rabid supporter.
And so this is the clip that's provided, and it pays off really well.
Actually conveying what Alex was saying wouldn't be as emotionally appealing to the people who he's hoping will retreat.
This because it's complicated.
And as much as it pains me to say this, it makes sense.
Alex has actually pretended to turn on Trump in far more extreme ways in the past, and this isn't even really an active abandonment.
It's very clear that this serves two possible purposes.
Get Trump to be antivaxxed so the ship can be steady, or create a paper trail that Alex can use as a rationale to fully detach from Trump later when he needs to.
Like, I gave him a shot, right? What do you want me to do? I feel like the story that I'm missing from all of these people is shame.
I would like more shame for how many times I've seen Ron Philipkowski embedded in a fucking Guardian article or in the Rolling Stone or whomever is embedding him.
Feel shame? Why doesn't anybody feel shame anymore? Dan I kind of understand the reason why I think that a lot of these outlets don't have the time to get their own clips.
Hey, you know what? Clips are there.
I feel like that is a legitimate excuse.
If you don't have time to do a good job, do a shitty job, and then act like it's fine because you don't have time, you make a fair point.
Yeah.
I really resent people who act like this Twitter account, too, because it's essentially doing the same thing that Alex does.
If you just say Alex chose to Santos over trump or make implications that the rats are leaving a sinking ship.
That's essentially the equivalent of Alex skimming a headline.
And then each party here just makes the narrative up that they want to attach to the headline based on what they want the headline to mean.
Right, but then you're saying that the people who embed him are doing the exact same thing Alex does by skimming that headline from Ron phelpkowski less knowingly, perhaps.
Maybe.
But that's still I don't want to belabor the point, but there's a reason I'm stressing this.
Yeah, we're going to get to it here.
So a little bit after this episode, a couple of days later, alex put out a video that's supposed to be an emergency message to Trump explaining that he was just trying to get his attention and get him to ditch the vaccines.
This is completely in line with the message that Alex was putting out on his show on Wednesday, but it is not in line with the narrative that Ron was selling on Twitter in the video that almost a million people watched.
And so when Alex puts out his emergency message, this video is kind of an opportunity for Ron to incorporate it with the narrative that he's constructed.
He posted a 35 2nd clip from the video with this text, quote, getting some blowback after he announced Thursday it was Wednesday that he was backing to Santa's over Trump.
Now, Alex Jones issued an emergency message to Trump saying he was simply trying to persuade him to change his position on the vaccines with some tough love.
It very well may be that Alex got some blowback from the audience, but I'd be surprised if it was very severe or if it would even matter at all in changing Alex's mind.
If you gauge the temperature of his audience from user comments on his website and callers, they aren't really that opposed to moving past Trump, and DeSantis is a really appealing option for the extreme right wing.
Making that Pivot would likely only cost Alex's proximity to power, and probably a couple of guests might stop coming on and Roger that might get iffy.
So, I don't know how that would play out, but I don't know if that's a bridge that Alex can't afford to burn.
Rogers already on Mike Lindell's network.
It's not like they're intimately entwined anymore, right? It's just one of those things where, why are we doing this? It feels like everybody is making poor choices simultaneously in defiance of the very obvious.
Good choice.
It's terrible.
Well, I think that a lot of people don't realize the game that's being played, right? They don't realize that they're playing with a shady character.
Also, it makes sense for the people not to give a shit if he abandons Trump because we've already done cuckoo bananas in the White House.
Now, I'm sure that at least more than enough people are like, what if we tried somebody with a basic level of competence.
Also, Alex knows that there's not really that much of a consequence for saying you're turning on Trump because he's done it.
He's done it a ton of times.
Yeah.
The consequences, he gets more attention.
But the larger picture here is that that tweet is acting like what Alex is saying in that emergency video that he put out a couple of days later is incongruent with the message that he was putting out on his show.
And that's not true.
And this is a huge problem.
And in order to explain why, I need to play the 32nd section of Alex's video that Ron posted.
This is from that emergency message.
So this is my emergency message to you, Mr.
President, to go and actually watch the first 30 minutes of Thursday's show.
We'll put a link below here.
See what I said in context? The corporate media edited down a 32nd clip to make it sound like that I'm only for DeSanis and that I've abandoned you.
That's not true.
It's the contrary.
I understand you're under attack.
I understand you are surrounded and I'm trying to get you to reassess the situation.
What Alex is saying is true.
If people got the impression that Alex was abandoning Trump and they took him up on that challenge of listening to the 30 minutes, the first 30 minutes of this show from Wednesday, they would come away from that with the conclusion that the clip they were shown on Twitter actually was out of context and it didn't capture what Alex is saying.
The only real problem I have with what Alex is saying there is that Ron flipkowski is not the corporate media.
Right.
The danger in this is that Alex always says that he's being taken out of context and he basically never is.
Ron actually is taking Alex out of context and he's running a very serious risk of giving people the reason to increase their level of trust in Alex and decrease their trust in critical voices of the extreme.
Right.
He is being taken out of context here.
So who's to say if he's actually being taken in context about all that Sandy Hook stuff? Hey, let's do a bad job.
We don't have time for a good job.
Come on.
By playing Alex's game, you've exposed people to Alex in a way that if they look into these clips any deeper, they'll come away with the conclusion that Alex is right and that Ron took them out of context.
And this isn't a small deal either.
These videos get hundreds of thousands of views on Twitter and spread all over the place.
As you've already mentioned, many news outlets don't have the resources to hunt down these video clips.
So you'll often see them repost clips from his account.
And by proxy, they are taking Alex out of contest.
It's dangerous.
And more of note, it's a pretty predictable system you could game if you wanted to so if you're Alex now, there's a second thing I need to point out, and that this is a short clip Ron is taking from this emergency video.
It's approximately five minutes into the video that Alex put out.
The video does involve Alex restating that he's trying to play hardball to get Trump to go anti vex, basically pulling the I'm really leaving this time threat.
That's totally that's fair.
But that's not what the video is about.
The first five full minutes are a breakdown of Alex's main COVID vaccine talking points.
Basically, he's distilling it down to, like he's pretending to have a briefing for Trump giving talking points.
Right.
What? The first five minutes of this nine minute video is where the last two minutes are a fucking commercial.
So the more important thing, like what that video actually is, is Alex clarifying and providing the talking points.
Should Trump watch that video? Why are we even posting it anyways if it's theoretically a message to someone who will never in a million years watch it? Two reasons.
One, to capitalize on the media attention that he got out of trending for supposedly turning on Trump, of course.
And second, Alex in that video claims that some people that he knows, who know Trump were like, hey, man, what's the fucking deal? Sure.
I don't believe that.
Okay, giuliani emailed him like, hey, man, what are you doing? Right? Yeah.
So framing this video as being Alex backpedaling only serves to strengthen the original, out of context framing that was crafted by Ron's original tweet.
In essence, he's putting out information that just lives in a false reality that he's designed for his audience, whether intentionally or not.
It's one that he probably thinks is benign, like this reality and information.
But it's a bad idea even if you accept that this series of poorly contextualized clips are being put out as the result of an honest, innocent mistake.
Sure.
The information model that's being used for this Twitter account is not good.
It's one that plays directly into the games that the people he's covering use, and they have a responsibility to do better because there is a massive audience that is viewing this content.
And as you pointed out, it's something that's being used as a resource for larger media.
And I don't know, I have a really tough time with it because I see this stuff come up all the time.
I see these clips all the time from his account being everywhere.
Yeah.
And I don't know enough about a number of the things to know if these are out of context.
Sure.
But I know enough about Alex that I can see these, and I can say that's not fair.
Right? Alex sucks, but that's not fair.
It should be required for everyone who post anything about Alex Jones to listen to the first how not to Cover Alex Jones episode, because over time, we've done several hundred how not to cover Alex Jones episodes, and I feel like we're back in the same spot.
Yeah, unforced errors are made a bunch and yeah, it's unfortunate.
I think it's because people think that they're dealing with something that is not as dangerous as it is.
You know what I mean? Right.
I think that there is a blase nature that is taken towards coverage of this.
Like, haha, you lost your cheerleader guy.
Ha ha.
And I can understand how it's emotionally gratifying to do that.
Right.
No, we're never going to defeat the dopamine rush of feeling good for 2 seconds and then going back to your day.
You bet.
Yeah, you bet.
But the flip side of it is that let's say there's a million people who watch this video.
Let's say, I don't know, 1% go look into it and see that Alex was taken out of context.
Maybe like this alex actually all about how many people have you misled down a terrible path.
And even though they're 99% who don't look into anything you have just given useless information to that isn't accurate.
Yeah, one of my favorite things it's a waste.
Yeah.
One of my favorite things about the media, whatever that may be, the corporate blah, blah, blah, is that after Trump was elected, they took stock of themselves.
They realized that they too played a part in destroying the America that we used to know and electing Trump, and then they changed their model to wait, did they do that? I think maybe a few yes.
Folks.
Great.
So anyway, I just think that maybe just that account should do better.
Anyway, look, Trump has made some improvement.
On what? I don't know.
Okay, he's already turned the ship around about 80 degrees.
the opposite direction.
He's only turned part way away.
Okay, fine.
He's only turned part way around.
We need a full turning around and going the opposite direction because I will not be part of the poisoning of these six month old babies.
Damn it.
I don't mean that as taking a Lord's name in vain.
Damn these people to hell, including Trump, if he doesn't stop it.
People are our enemies.
So I like the idea of Trump doing 180 and I guess becoming a globalist sure.
Welcoming in immigrants with open arms, right? Yeah.
There's not good people on both sides.
Yeah.
What should we go for? Is he really looking for more of an extra 160 degrees to get them at a different clockwise angle? Because you don't want to go a full 180 degrees, do you? Go 240 deg.
It's a metaphor.
Wasn't good.
Yeah, it's a bad metaphor.
But again, the important thing to remember is that Alex is saying, like, hey, you're doing some good stuff.
Essentially, the message is, Trump, you're doing some good stuff.
You just need to stop it with the vaccines.
Right.
My audience will not tolerate you not being anti vax because under you and Operation Warp Speed, that's what brought these vaccines about.
We need you to accept that it was wrong.
Disavow it.
Exactly.
Of course, it's too big of a hurdle for you just to ignore.
It's great that you're shutting up about vaccines and how you want people to get boosters, right? But you need to go the other way.
How about the new headlines for this are alex attempts carrot and stick towards person not paying attention to him.
We give him more attention for it.
Or it would be great if the headline was, like, inside jokes for us.
Alex tries to give Trump the rogen treatment.
Yeah, exactly.
That would be good.
Alex relitigating 911 with Rogen.
Yeah, something along those lines.
Yeah.
To say this is better than Trump, but I kind of hear this statement almost as a like, you hear this Trump.
You hear me saying, yeah, absolutely.
The Santas is, again, just over the top with what he's doing.
This is absolutely presidential material.
This is what Trump should be like.
And I've been hammering this point, and he's doing it now.
And we have someone that is better than Trump, way better than Trump.
And I want Trump to decouple himself from the poison shot now, but I'm not going to sit here and hold my breath.
But that is opening the door.
That if it does change my breath.
I mean, he's nagging Trump.
He's fucking hating on Trump.
He's complimenting DeSantis because he's trying to fuck Trump.
Like, that's what's happening here.
He's even using some of the same rhetorical flourishes towards DeSantis that he always does with Trump.
Well, God has given us DiSantis, make no mistake about that.
For what? And I got a message for President Trump.
You are the real president.
I have fought for you.
95% of what you've done has been incredible.
You have amazing courage and energy, and I respect you.
But if you continue to let this poison be pushing our people and our children, I'm coming after you.
Sure.
I'm not risking fuck off and going through hell to sit here and then have it on my conscience.
All these dead and dying children and others that are taking your stupid, evil warp Speed crap that you got fooled and roped into.
He's just trying to escalate this negative threat on the other side in order to be like, it's carrot and stick.
Exactly what you're talking absolutely.
Yeah.
This is pathetic.
It is.
This is stupid.
Also.
I forgot about that.
I forgot that he still believes in that Trump election.
How can you switch to another candidate if you think that the entire election is a fucking fake and that Trump should legitimately be president? And if that's the case, then Trump shouldn't be allowed because it would be his third term.
Exactly.
And you're supposed to be the tip of the spear.
You should be the people not even talking about candidates.
You should be like, we need to continue the fight to get Trump back in the office that he theoretically won.
He doesn't need to do that because Lindell has got that car.
Oh, my God.
That's true.
That is true.
You've already got a warrior on that front.
Lindell's keeping the fire.
So look, there's a lot of people who are delusional about vaccines that get them, and Alex proves this in a very succinct fashion.
Look at this.
Jack Pacific retweeted.
It Patricia carvalus.
Look at this.
This is a real tweet.
I just had my fourth dose after receiving listen to this carefully.
just had my fourth dose after recovering from three months of actively having covered 19.
Now listen to the Stockholm syndrome.
Listen to the mind control, and I'm very happy to be boosted thanks, science.
So she murders logic here, doesn't see what's being done, and then has the cult statement of thanks, science.
Like she's just trumped everybody.
That was a tweet.
Yes.
Can you imagine, like, an actual news outlet doing any kind of coverage of, like, someone tweeted that they got vaccinated and they didn't get covered and had no side effects? Ha ha.
I mean, what is this? Here's the even weirder part.
How do you know this is a real person's account? This is like, 1920s newspapers.
And including the part where he has a misogyny comment about her.
Hey, listen, sweetheart, that's somebody writing in the New York Times in the 20s, like, oh, this lovely young woman walking through the street said, I got a vaccine yesterday for polio, and this, sweetheart, is looking good.
What are you doing? It's insane.
So this next clip Alex proceeds talking about, he's still sort of responding to this tweet.
That sentence should be more that was the fun thing about listening to David Gareth on the show.
As they were reacting to it, I got reminded of the first episode we did, especially when the prayer happened, and they were like I was like, this doesn't even faze us anymore.
This means nothing.
We need hard stuff.
Exactly.
We're heroin junkie.
Yeah.
There was something really sort of I was taken aback by that because I had forgotten even that.
Like, oh, people are normal, right? Even people who are exposed to a lot of horrible stories on their own podcast, right? This is still surprising to some people.
So as Alex is talking, you're not even going to be prepared for what's coming, and probably you'll be able to handle it.
But for some reason, Alex's brain thinks of maybe a documentary that he's seen about sex workers.
I believe he's talking about hookers on The Point.
Okay.
I think that's what he's talking about.
All right.
And this leads to a protracted rambling about hookers on The Point.
I forget the name of the show.
I'm not a huge TV watcher, but it was on 15, 1617 years ago about pimps and prostitutes.
Say pimps, prostitute with cigarette burns all over and broken arm and leg beat up by her pimp.
baby.
She says to the pimp, I'm going to get better.
I'm going to get back up on my feet.
I'm going to get back down the street, baby, please don't hold, baby.
And they start interviewing the pimp, and they go, well, how do you treat her? He goes, I treat her bad.
That's how she likes it.
Well, how much do you pay her? I pay her nothing.
I might give her a bucket of chicken.
And that's the American people, and that's the left.
That's the American people that are left for this, all right? The Stockholm syndrome, right? She's had four shots.
She's been sick for months after the first few shots, and now she's gotten another shot and thinks Kobage has taken her life over.
But this shot was 100% effective, they said, but the shot gives you the disease.
But she can't help it.
She can't admit she was lying to she can't admit the system is out to get her.
Just like that poor prostitute with broken arm and leg and cigarette burns all over her hair, falling out.
You tell she's been a beautiful woman, and in comes the swaggering, arrogant devil right in front of the mother.
Oh, baby.
Baby, I'm sorry.
I'm so let you down.
I'm going to get back on the street right now as soon as I get better.
It's not good.
You better get back on the street.
Jesus Christ.
And the mother looks at him and says, what have you done to my baby? What have you done to my baby? He said, Shut up, you old bitch.
I can't believe I missed doing this show.
This is a family show.
First of all, Alex is really getting into that.
He was embodying the character.
Yeah, that was some method acting.
A little problematic.
Yeah.
He said pimp and shot so many times, they both lost meaning to me.
Yeah, look, in my time, I watched some hookers on the Point.
Sure.
It was Titillating when I was ten or something.
Era.
Right.
I think this is that.
But I don't remember this particularly.
I only recognize this from other times alex has told this story and played these characters.
He does really stuck out in his mind.
I really don't like how much he minor complements the pimp in this.
You know what I'm saying? Like, Income is the swaggering devil.
Yeah, but the swaggering devil is kind of a compliment.
Some people say you're a handsome devil.
That's a compliment.
And then he's got the voice.
The voice is not he's trying to be like, cool.
It's unfortunate.
I don't appreciate it.
I wanted to keep that clip in full just to get the really, the experience of how long this goes on.
Yeah, I don't think Ron Philip causing is posting that one.
No.
Maybe you should.
Maybe.
So Alex talked a little bit about Tucker and how he's maybe spreading some bullshit about how the FBI planted bombs on January.
For sure.
Yeah, it's totally in the white papers.
I love it.
Tucker Carlson is taking it into the danger zone as well.
Everybody's up in their game or they're rolling over.
I should point out this is right after he came in for break to the danger zone.
Yeah.
Okay.
I was going to say that makes sense.
Either going to get more hardcore or you're going to die.
You're going to either fight or you're going to be a slave.
Carlson came right out.
We'll hit the next segment and said the FBI is the prime suspect with the pipe bombs and laid out the evidence.
January 6, as it just came out, the FBI planted the pipe bombs and the bombs with the Whitmer case.
Now they're having the next trial.
They already found the other people basically hung juries in the whole Whitmer kidnapping platte that was fake.
That's all coming out.
So it's an incredible time to be alive.
This is unfortunate bullshit for Alex to be spreading because on August 23, the day we're recording this episode, the final two defendants in the Whitmer kidnapping case were found guilty by a jury of conspiracy to kidnap.
Adam Fox and Barrycroft Jr.
Are definitely going to jail.
And their defense tried to use the entrapment argument, which was unsuccessful.
This was their second trial after the first one in April, resulted in a hung jury.
Alex is citing that in this episode, unaware that a few days later they'd be convicted.
Two other accused conspirators were acquitted and two others pled guilty.
So honestly, it doesn't seem like this whole thing fell apart at all.
Actually, quite the opposite.
Yeah, it was four out of six, something along those lines.
Yeah.
Also, the prosecution alleges that Croft actually made some explosives using mortar shells from fireworks that were packed with shrapnel.
Nothing Alex says has any connection to reality whatsoever.
Can you imagine Carlson saying, this shit is actually absolutely insane? This has been normalized so much, but can you imagine if a major news network came on shortly after JFK was assassinated? Like, okay, sure, it could be that guy, but maybe it was the fucking FBI who murdered JFK.
And then everybody would just be like, Interesting point.
Or maybe JFK wasn't even real.
He was a puppet.
It was a paper mache cut out.
And JFK jr actually is an immortal JFK Absolutely.
Yeah.
That makes more sense than anything.
I'm getting an update from Twitter.
Yeah, it looks like Loomer might have lost the primary.
It looks like she was ahead for a bit, but it looks like you might have lost.
All right, we can all breathe.
A little bit easier.
I don't know.
There might be a recap.
Who knows? Yeah.
Anyway, let's get back to some actual news here.
Alex is reading some headlines.
Sure.
Let's get back to the stack.
I was already mentioned Jackie's top Biden adviser, Anita Dunn, divulges massive conflict of interest.
She worked for Pfizer, but it's okay.
I just had my fourth dose after recovering three months from actually having Cobra after the first shots, and I'm very happy to be boosted.
Thanks, Science.
Yeah, it doesn't work.
It's all alive.
Thanks, Science.
Getting a lot of mileage out of that tweet.
Yeah.
So Don is an advisor for Biden, but she doesn't really have a conflict of interest.
Really? She didn't work for Pfizer.
She worked for a consulting firm called SKDK, one of whose clients was Pfizer.
She also was the Obama White House Communications Director for a while in 2009 and is working on a shitload of Democratic candidates campaign.
Yeah, I was going to say I think I remember her.
This isn't a big deal, but maybe it's a big deal, but not in the way Alex is making it.
Alex doesn't know the basics of the story he's covering, but he's made up something he can work with and then juxtapose it with that tweet, which I guess is a dunk for him.
So it's just dumb.
There's nothing going on here I'd be fine with considering that a conflict of interest if we also considered Obama appointing, like Geithner as Treasury Secretary a conflict of interest not even start to unpack Trump's appointment.
Exactly.
Let's leave that alone.
You want to talk about the culture in Washington? Yeah, fine.
Yeah, let's go for it.
Yeah.
Nobody is going to complain, right? That's a different conversation than the way it done was nearby.
So Alex does take some calls and the first one who comes in suggests, hey, man, maybe we get MTG on a ticketg.
Light us on Friday afternoon.
Alex.
I have a suggestion.
Trump has got a lot of legal problems right now, all right? He's getting old.
He's had a real good record of endorsing candidates.
He should graciously step aside, endorse DeSantis, and have MTG as their running mate for Vice President.
I love it.
Why do you think Trump obviously is not stupid and knows the shot was a lie? Why is he being picked at it? I don't know.
Whether it's threats against his family or whether he just doesn't listen to people, I don't know.
But this is a way out of it for him.
He can step out of the whole mess with the vaccines by doing this.
Beautifully said.
Spike, anything else? The prosecutor and the judge are not human in your trial.
I hate to tell you they're replicas of some kind.
That's a return regular suggestion of something that is pretty crazy.
Let's put Mtpg in the White House with fucking insane and then to follow it up with the judge as a replicant should really disqualify the earlier yes.
Mark as well.
We all know Mark is a rep.
Again, honestly, I'm willing to believe it's possible he was joking, but I don't know exactly.
We're in the danger zone, if you will, of joking about whether or not someone is a replica.
Yeah.
I think that you can tell from that call he is not someone who is like, you have to stick with Trump.
Yeah, no, that's fine.
That's not trump should step aside is pretty hardcore.
Let's get rid of Trump.
Yeah.
So here's another caller.
How are you doing? Just a little insight on Trump and the vaccine.
Are you there? I am sure I'm listening a lot, but I've never heard this brought up.
I read Anthony, I mean, Kennedy's book on Anthony Fauche, and he expresses in there that Trump took a million dollars from Pfizer, and I just never heard anybody bring that up.
He did.
Trump took campaign money.
I think it's more than a million.
Yes.
Why didn't you bring that up, Alex? It seems like now that you're talking about a conflict of interest for Anita Done, it really seems important to bring this one up.
Right there's, that fascinating thing that Alex does with his awareness, all of a sudden, it becomes okay to admit that the reality that everyone knows is there.
This guy is saying, Why doesn't anyone bring this up? It's a pointed question.
That is not the tip of the spear.
Isn't there? And that is, why didn't you talk about this? This isn't like his 2020 campaign.
This is 2016.
Right.
And Alex's whole presentation has been like, trump funded his own campaign.
He spent millions totally.
He self funded.
He didn't take money from these other that's why he was such a straight shooter.
Right.
This is totally an indictment of Alex's false presentation that he's had for five years.
And Alex is so casually like yes, he did.
And not only that, it was more totally yeah.
That's such proof or a demonstration that what he is doing is gatekeeping this negative information from his audience.
Yes.
And that's pretty sad.
And they themselves should be really bummed out about everything that they think personally if they are not capable, for one instance, of applying these criticisms retroactively to Trump from the very start.
Oh, I don't know why he's being pigheaded.
Maybe he just doesn't listen to people well.
Go back.
Go back in time.
Let's go back to that earlier time period when we were all so young.
Maybe he wasn't listening to people then.
Do you not understand? Yes.
So here's something that's slightly positive about Trump.
Trump at this time is working to boost the primary candidates because he has this massive following and which would also help DeSantis whether he runs as VP or runs as President, because it's going to help create an America first agenda no matter what.
We know that's the paradox.
Trump's getting a lot of good people elected.
Not a paradox.
He's trading momentum.
So he's a flawed vessel.
But that's why I'm still behind him.
Absolutely.
Still behind him.
So we're having this positive but the audience also looks kind of like wishy washy.
They don't really care.
But also, there's some other negative things about you.
We just want fascism.
We don't really care who brings it to us as long as they're white.
Yeah, exactly.
And a man.
Yes.
Unless it's Margaret Taylor Green.
Then maybe we'll make an exception.
Exactly.
But look, there's other things about Trump that apparently Alex just decided not to tell his audience.
Sure.
Hello, Alex.
I would like to encourage the United States to realize that Donald Trump and his family are working for the World Economic Forum.
And that's why we're not going to get leadership from Donald Trump is because he's in on it until he proves otherwise.
He's in on his daughter is the World Economic Forum young global leader.
He put his daughter in the White House.
She and Jared Kushner are working for the other side.
There's no doubt about that.
There is no doubt about it.
And Trump's working for the other side, too.
This kind of conversation is pretty why doesn't this apply retroactively? Why doesn't this apply retroactively? If you're saying that he's working for the World Economic Forum, shouldn't you then go back to it? Maybe this caller does.
Oh, that's true.
We don't know what this caller believes fully.
But yeah, I wonder also, some of this stuff really makes a question that 98%, 95% right about stuff.
He's already several things wrong.
But actually, I know a way around this.
Alex and his heart knew all this stuff, so he was right about these things.
He just lied.
That is a good point about the Alex Jones right crowd.
I was right.
I just told you the wrong thing on purpose because it worked better.
Right? Right.
Alex Jones right is a different story, if you're like, well, he's lying to us for good reasons.
In his heart, he was right.
Great.
Cool.
So Savannah Hernandez comes on.
Oh, yeah.
That's about the right response.
I can't stand listening to her in the same way that I have a tough time with that Patrick Howley guy and Harrison Smith.
The three of them have a real baby reporter vibe to me.
I don't know, there's just something about their delivery that I find it would be good voice acting for a cartoon about child detectives.
But we're reporters.
Yeah, they don't have chops.
They have zero chops.
And they're young, too.
No, they could learn chops, but right now, no chops, maybe.
Yeah.
And so she has a big scoop here.
She has a whistleblower about some human trafficking going on that she should be careful, this might veer into defamation territory.
So this is government corruption and like you said, essentially child smuggling happening on a federal level.
MVM, Inc.
The same company that was already caught shipping migrants in the middle of the night to New York City.
They signed a federal contract with Joe Biden's administration back in 2021 for $136,000,000.
So I want people to understand that the biggest and most sinister angle of this story is that we are passing off innocent children to unvetted and properlyally identified adults via our taxpayer dollars.
Joe Biden funding all of this.
So this is a rare instance where Savannah Hernandez is not covering a completely false story.
It's just that it's not a new story.
The Daily Beast reported on the Biden administration having contracts with MVM Inc.
For transporting immigrants back in May 2021.
Savannah's report doesn't cover anything that's not already pretty well established as public information, but she does presented as coming from a secret whistleblower who has to appear with their face blurred out.
So it's big stuff, right? Conversely, the Daily Beast actually did some reporting on the story because, spoiler alert, this was actually a follow up article to the one that they wrote in June 2018 about the same stuff.
Ouch.
Alex and Savannah probably don't want to think about that, though, because that was during the Trump times.
And back then, this MVM had a $162,000,000 contract with the government compared to the $136,000,000 contract they have under Biden.
The actual story here is that their contract was lowered from this higher amount that Trump paid them.
But don't worry about that.
Jesus.
Anyway, the story is pretty fucked up.
Or kind fucked up, I don't know.
MVM was a CIA contractor who provided security for CIA and NSA installations in Iraq.
They may have some logistics background, so they very well may be capable of helping transport migrants, but their company's history does not inspire much confidence.
That said, the claims that people like Savannah are making here about, like, a child smuggling operation are probably legally actionable defamation.
If I were Alex, I would maybe get this in check a little bit.
I think, especially now, it's a good change for MVM to go from being war criminals to just being regular domestic criminals of some sort.
I don't know how many war crimes they committed while being security.
Maybe some, I don't know.
I can't nail this down.
But your point is taken.
Yeah.
So, look, Savannah got hired at Infowars right out of college.
That's right.
And then she went on to do such great things, but only because Alex had the wisdom to hire her right out of college.
Okay? Right out of college in Texas.
He hired Savannah Hernandez.
Then she left to go work with some of the biggest patriot organizations in America, the Blaze.
Now you can see her becoming a major investigative journalist in the fight against Tyranny Infowars mission.
Can you see her do that? Finding the leaders and giving them the platform to launch from? I literally had a vision.
25, sitting in Waterloo househouse, eating a chicken fried steak and drinking an iced tea.
And I saw the future.
And the message was you are to build the platform to launch the generation of leaders to fight the new world order at the critical point they try to take over.
That really happened.
I told you for decades that happened.
And now you're witnessing it.
You have a lot of visions, man.
Also, your team sucks.
If this is the next crop of patriots, they're untethered from the things that made the patriot community what it was in the 90s, which is what Alex grew out of.
Right.
They are, if anything, a withering vine on that tree.
Well, actually, that's not entirely true.
It's just something that will be supplanted or grafted easily onto authoritarianism.
Right.
It will be consumed by that because it doesn't have the grounding in some kind of a philosophy.
As much as it sucks.
At least anticommunism is something that it has the roots, that has some kind of a tradition.
Sure.
A horrific tradition.
Yeah, sure.
But it does go back the cold war roots of that and the Fed, the conspiracies and stuff like that is a tradition for better or for worse.
Right.
And these people like Savannah, like Harrison and even Owen, they don't really have that background.
They just have the attention economy background.
And they're going to do the things that naturally or they'll gravitate naturally to the things that get attention and get a rise out of people owning the Libs.
Yeah.
And that's just not sustainable in any way.
It only flows downstream to less and less responsible actions.
Yeah.
One thing, I didn't own the Libs.
McNeil and Larry, they didn't particularly care about owning the Libs.
No, they were busy.
I feel like we should have tracked if we could go back to the very beginning, we should track what foods Alex eats to what visions he receives.
Chicken fried steak.
That gives you a future reporter.
Like too much chili, that gives you vision.
You just forget your teacher's name.
I do think maybe he has indigestion.
It does seem possible.
Let's get that checked out.
Yeah.
You just got heartburn, man.
I'm thinking about this even more and there is like maybe David Knight is someone who actually was in the tradition.
Sure.
I think about other people who were on air in the earlier days.
I don't know enough about where Jakari Jackson's head was at.
Sure.
I don't think Leanne Mcidoo was an acolyte of those G.
Edward Griffin types.
No, absolutely not.
She won a contest to work there.
She was an acolyte of other contest winners from whenever you used to have to have your hand on a car in order to win the car for the longest time.
That's kind of her tradition.
To be fair, at least the contest was an on air thing, not just touching.
That is true.
Although I believe Owen got his first job because he just needed to get airtime for the lawsuit or something along those lines, right.
No, he was wrongfully.
Wrongfully.
Fired at some radio station, and then they gave him 3 hours a night.
Yeah, that's complicated.
Yeah.
That was back in the sports radio days.
I think that there's a big division, and if what he's doing now is an attempt to create the next crop of folk, it will be a massive step downward, and it's just trolls.
Yeah.
You're talking about the garbage Patch Kids.
That's where we're coming from.
Yeah.
So I hope you enjoyed that chicken fried steak.
I hope you didn't.
So, yes, one of the questions that I think a lot of people had in our time away was, what does Alex think about the FBI raid on Mara Lago? Sure.
Turns out he does not care.
Is everybody's focused on Trump in the Marlago raid? I don't give a damn about that.
It's bad, but whatever.
We need everybody talking about the human smiling and the illegal activity happening, the closing comments.
Savanna hernandez 100% agree.
Alex Everybody is focused in on the Trump FBI raid, but again, there's bigger issues going on here in this country right now.
We need to be focused in on saving our children.
And again, just with the border.
Right.
That crisis in itself is horrible, but then we also need to focus in on the sexualization of our children.
What school is the targeting of our children by? The LGBTQ company.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Okay, so Savannah wants to protect children from LGBTQ.
Okay.
And I'm going to throw this out at you.
Should the FBI have rated, let's say, any previous president that wasn't named Trump or even Biden right now? It would be a very big deal to Alex Jones.
It would be a huge deal.
I think it's a good strategy for it not to be a big deal.
It is a good strategy, especially after all the information has come out that's like, oh, this picture is looking worse.
Boy, he's got nuclear secrets.
Oh, boy, that's not good.
No, we don't focus on nuclear secrets being torn away from the White House illegally and the FBI searching about it.
What we need to do is portray people as pedophiles.
Yeah.
You know what I think is going on here is Alex is like, this is too big.
If your best spin is, yeah, it's bad, but whatever.
I don't think you should be allowed to get away with that.
If I were Trump and I heard that, I'd be like, oh, shit, I'm going to jail.
I'm fucked this bad.
Serious.
But whatever.
Isn't crying about this.
It's bad news.
That is like, borderline Alex just being like, okay, Bush did 911.
But whatever.
Moving on, right? So Alex gets back to calls.
He has Savannah go back to making sure get back to your whole cover.
Savannah Hernandez I don't think you can do that anymore.
She doesn't work there.
That's true.
She's on to bigger and better, I think.
So he goes back to calls and this is really, really fun.
So before the break, this caller had said, hey, Alex, I went to the library and I know that they and Alex hissed, instinctually.
Got you.
She says, I went in there and I know that they have a system where you can request books that they should get.
And so I decided I was going to request your book.
What does Alex think? Here's what I would think if I was Alex.
I wrote a book.
He dictated a book.
His book is a great reset war for the world or whatever.
I've heard him talk about it, and it's mostly just transcripts of things he said on air about the credit.
Yeah, it's a book.
It's a book.
And then someone else weaved them together or something.
Also the point of order.
Glenn Beck has already released a book called The Great Retailer bummer Riding Coat Tails.
Copyright See, Alex obviously is thinking that the end result of this story is they said no.
Right? Listen, as he's disappointed by the news, I'm not being censored exactly.
Catherine in Michigan trying to put our new book coming out next week, the Great Reset the World of the World in Libraries, and the response she got.
So finish your story.
I appreciate you calling, Catherine.
Hi, Alex Jones.
Thanks for holding me over.
So I went to the library and went up to librarian's desk and asked if there's a form that I could fill out to order the book.
And they didn't have any forms.
She handed me a little ripped up piece of paper, like a piece of printer paper, and said, write the name of the book and the author and we'll send it to our central library headquarters or whatever it is, and we'll request them to order the book for you.
So I turned in a slip of paper.
I thought I'll never see that case on paper again.
And lo and behold, I checked the library's database and they obliged me.
They ordered one copy of The Great Reset and the War for the World, and it's on order right now, being sent to the district library.
That's beautiful because librarians still believe in the First Amendment.
Because the story didn't go the way Alex that's why he held her over the break, because it was supposed to be, yeah, they won't even let my book in the library.
Come on.
The way she was building that story up was leading to that.
Totally.
It's a swerve at the end, when the book is ordered the piece of paper I'd never see again.
They didn't have a form.
All of this is to build a conspiracy that they're trying to keep Alex out of the library.
Well, I feel like her big storyteller, her big pitch was like, they only got one copy of the book.
I don't think so.
I think that was we got one copy in the library.
Okay.
All right.
I would be surprised if she's going to a big enough library that there would need to be multiple copies of any of that.
Kind of maybe some of the classics.
I mean, shouldn't your opinion then be like, libraries don't even have the resources for forms.
They're just tearing printer paper up, and they're still working for me despite the fact that I went in there with a clearly confrontational attitude.
No, that shouldn't be it.
They love the First Amendment library.
Sure.
Great.
It's interesting, though.
I do think that I admire her ability to tell a story because she got you.
If I hadn't spoiled that in advance, you would have thought it was going in one direction.
It was going the only direction it could go on Info.
There was a reveal.
Yeah.
It's a disappointment, but it's a reveal.
It's not fair.
It's not fair for you to not give a shit when you're not censored.
But that's kind of what it's all about.
Yeah, obviously.
So Alex takes another call, and, man, he's really allowing a lot of that stuff that he kept behind that gate about Trump to come out.
I'm just going over the things that Trump did while being president and campaigning like, the campaign of Trump was completely different than the president.
Trump campaign promises will lock her up, build a wall, all these three word phrases.
But once he gets in, he partners the five megabanks for rampant fraud and corruption.
City Group JP.
Morgan Barclays, UBS and Deutsche Bank.
Deutsche bank.
He reported, like, $300 million to he openly talks about her sexual fantasies with Ivanka, like The Howard Stern Show and Oprah or Good Morning America or whatever, saying that if she wasn't his daughter, he'd be married to her.
He has the Epstein connections.
He was introduced to Melania through Gisley, Maxwell and Epstein.
Roy Dershowitz, where his lawyers alan Dershowitz is part of the Epstein thing.
Roy colin.
No, you don't think Trump's good.
So what do you think of Governor DeSanis? I don't trust any of them.
I think the Santa might be better than Trump, but I feel like people are just being funneled to the Sansa, just like people were funneled to Trump by Alex.
I mean, apparently even the proletarian of the Trump wing is beginning to figure shit out.
Well, except where he's not realizing that he's talking to the person who did the thing.
He's some people are funneling us towards DeSanis the same way they funneled us towards Trump.
It's almost like somebody earlier on this show was like, I'm going to support you doing that again over Trump.
And then they're funneling me towards and you just asked me that question right now is a way of implying that you are funneling me towards DeSantis.
Yes.
Or at least toying around with that to see if that's something that's tenable.
Yeah, but these kinds of things are not stuff that would have been allowed.
Curious listing of all the people in Trump circle that are connected to Epstein, considering Alex's big thing in all Alex Jones was write stories, is that he was the first person on the Epstein thing.
For them to now just be like, hey, did you remember that Trump is the whole Epstein guys? And Alex has constantly been like, yeah, I met him once or twice.
Yeah, exactly.
You can't have this.
And the idea of his debts and how beholden he may be to certain entities, these are not things that Alex would accept as reality.
He write back on these things.
Right.
The gate is down.
And I think that matters somewhat because the overton window of conversation on his show seems to be a little bit more open to these things that are critical of Trump, based on the reality of Trump as opposed to the image of Trump that Alex has wanted to maintain all this time.
Right.
Stuff you would hand wave away with just like, he's not perfect, that kind of thing.
That's not specifically that is so funny because all of this stuff was widely known in 2015, and all of these people who you are literally speaking to right now work their asses off to make sure you didn't pay attention to that.
Yeah.
Everyone in the Infowars orbit and all the guests and everything.
It was an act of creating a false reality that would obscure this from you so you wouldn't make an informed decision about who you want to do elected president.
Right.
And now you're starting to realize that and not realizing the second part that totally has not changed any of his behaviors.
He's still doing the same thing and toying around with the idea of creating a false version of DeSantis for you to worship.
Right.
Because God has given us DeSantis.
No.
It is such that all the people in Britain like, hey, I'm starting to think this whole Brexit thing was a bad idea.
Now, of course, I'm going to vote Tory for the rest of my life and make sure that they're still allowed to do whatever it is they want.
US humans, man, we're crazy easy to lie to.
So this next clip is just kind of fun.
This is another caller.
Hey, thanks, Alex.
Just wanted to say something here about I just watched your documentary with Aaron Russell where you interviewed him the other night and it was pretty compelling.
I think everybody should take a look at that.
2006? Yeah, something like that.
Yeah, it was great.
It was great.
It's great.
It was really compelling.
Powerful stuff.
For those who don't know Aaron Russo, the interview that Alex did with him, this I believe, what was it? America freedom.
Or fascism, I think.
Or America destroyed by design.
Sure.
One of those titles.
Yeah.
That is heavily predicated on the idea that Aaron Russo became friends with a guy who was part of the Rockefeller family, and he told them all these secrets.
And what Alex refuses to recognize is that the guy that Aaron Russo was friends with wasn't related to the Rockefellers.
He's just a guy whose last name was Rockefeller right.
And might have been pulling some shit or so.
Right.
So that's a great documentary that came out, I guess, 18 years ago, and Alex has still not made a correction on that.
How many years ago is that? I can't do math.
It's like how Sam Raimi didn't apologize for Spiderman three.
You should have really said something before you got to do Multiverse of Madness.
I think it's worse.
What? How? It is worse.
I can't put it into words, but I think it's worse.
So you have one last clip here, and Alex has finished calls and he has another guest coming in.
I was so fucking confused by who the guest was.
SD.
Pluskin lieutenant, American Special Forces.
Two Purple Hearts.
Stalingrad and Linenrad.
What? Wait, what? At this point, I'm thinking he got snake twisted.
Russell, what is he are escaping from La on this one.
What is happening? Bob hockey for the YouTube.
Pluskin Special Forces, texas thunder.
Bob Hock's a real person.
What? Not just leave and cleave.
Now I'm thinking, is it Bob hockey from the movie happening? I don't know what's going on.
All right, Bob Hawke joins us, ladies and gentlemen.
And let me tell you something.
but they've got something even better.
So when you go to the website infowars offgrid.com, they're so best survival gear and everything else.
But what they really got is not just satellite phones back in stock, but something even better.
It's better.
So, yeah, Robert Hawke is apparently the name of the guy who's the spokesperson for the satellite company.
Bob Hawke is a real person.
It's confusing.
It's a journey.
It was definitely a journey to get to an infomercial.
Yeah.
Apparently the exciting new thing that they have is something you could put on your phone to make it a satellite phone and untrackable whatever.
Right.
I don't care.
Yeah, it's a long commercial, right? Anyway, the point here is, as we come to the end of this and we wrap this up, the whole narrative about Alex turning on Trump is fraudulent.
And I don't think there's any way that I can look at it and say that anyone is responsible for it other than that Ron Flokowski Twitter account, the clip that was widely disseminated, they got over a million views.
That was all over the place, reposted a ton was from that Twitter account that created the conversation, and it was not accurate.
It created a false perception of what Alex was saying on his show.
And maybe that only matters to me, and maybe it should only matter to me because I'm the person who watches.
This shit.
I don't know.
Again, considering the complicity that the media has had with Elevating, all of these fucking voices, sure, it's hard not to see them jump at the chance they didn't, like, see this, and then they were like, oh, maybe we'll write a story about this.
This was a fucking full court press.
But it created a lady feeling of like, haha, yeah, they want money, man.
It sucks.
And I think that the actual damage of something like this is something that's real.
There is a possibility that what you'll end up doing is eroding people's trust in legitimate critiques and news outlets.
That hurt the credibility of news outlets.
Absolutely.
And possibly lead people to trusting Alex Moore, which is a dangerous thing to do, and you shouldn't engage in that if you don't have to.
Right.
Ultimately, there's probably more dangerous things you could do.
And maybe this is not like the highest consequence kind of fuck up, but I think you got to hold yourself to a better standard, especially if you have the kind of reach that account does.
And I find it troubling.
It's cumulative.
I mean, when you see all of the polls about how people don't trust the, quote, mainstream media, every time they report on that, they're like, look at how bad the electorate has been bamboozled without ever acknowledging that fucking you know what, there's a reason people don't fucking trust you.
And maybe it's not as bad as the reason that you shouldn't trust a lot of people, but just because it's not as bad doesn't mean it doesn't exist.
Right.
It doesn't mean that it can't do better.
You can do better.
Yeah.
And that should be something that people strive for, and I hope they do.
Second, the notion that Alex's audience would be against him turning on Trump does seem to be not accurate.
Yeah, it seems like, especially from the picture that you get from all of these calls, that there's some fondness for Trump still.
Obviously, of course.
And I think you'd be acceptable if you would bend to the whims of these extremists.
But there's not a problem with shifting over to someone else.
I mean, it doesn't matter, because if Trump and Descents run in 2024, god knows what's going to be different.
Every year has been crazier than the last, and shit has gone wilder and wilder.
So predicting what's going to happen in two years seems like an idiot's game through, I mean, insane to do.
And if you think for a single second, if you think for a single second that regardless of whatever legitimate criticisms these people are having towards Trump right now, if you think that when Trump becomes the nominee, they won't immediately forget all of those criticisms and get bogged down and like, well, we can't have Kamala, any of that shit.
You are insane.
It does not matter.
It doesn't matter.
Most likely will not matter.
I have an update.
Laura Loomer has refused to concede.
As far as the narrative arc for one episode, that is pretty goddamn good.
I rarely look at Twitter while we're recording.
We got to get the narrative.
She's alleging voter fraud full circle.
So it's all there.
She's the rightful representative, of course.
Yeah, why not? Anyway, good to be back, Jordan.
It's great to be back, buddy.
We will also be back on Friday, of course, for another episode, and we'll get a little bit more caught up on the present day stuff and get back on our horse.
But until then, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's Knowledgefight.com.
Yeah, we're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter at knowledgeunderscorefights.
And again, that email address for buttons is Kfbuttons 69 At@gmail.com.
Every email has to begin with nice.
Yeah.
We will see you soon, but until then, I'm Leo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DCX Clark.
I'm Wilford Snivel.
Snapper of the Gribble Pebble.
And now here comes the sex robots.
Andy and Chamvis, you're on the air.
Thank you for holding Alex.
I'm a first time color.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love.