Not Knowledge Party.
I am sweating knowledgebuddy.com.
It's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledge, Mike.
Knowledge.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're good guys.
Shanghi are the bad guys.
I love your word.
Knowledge Fight.
Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey, everybody.
Welcome back to knowledge fight.
I'm Dan George.
Are a couple of dudes like to sit around, worship at the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex Jones? Oh, indeed we are.
Dan Jordan.
Dan Jordan, quick question for you, buddy.
What's up? What's your bright spot? My bright spot today, Jordan, is the button stuff.
Yes.
I may have underestimated the demand.
Bright as the sun.
It is very bright.
The number of buttons suggest very large brightness.
It's a lot of requests.
It's hard to not just still be in the same headspace of, like, we're just doing a podcast on my desk.
Well, see, we haven't moved, right? Yeah.
We're still in the exact same place.
Nobody, like, else working on the show.
It's still just us.
So, like, the day to day of this feels kind of the same.
Well, there were 40 people listening, and we did it like this, and now there's more, and we're still doing it like this, so how would we know? Yeah.
And I just can't conceive of the fact that there are, like, a ton of people listening in my head.
It's still that same thing, right? Even compared to the last time we did this, it's a massive no, I don't even want button.
I don't even feel comfortable saying that there are a lot of people listening.
I feel like it makes us hubristically in trouble.
It feels weird.
But I appreciate the interest in these buttons.
Yes.
And I should tell you, Jordan, one thing I'm noticing from the early reports, we may have exploded in Scotland.
I don't know what it is.
Finally, I have been waiting to get my chance at the Fringe festival for decades now, and I'm there, baby.
Yeah, that was a trend that I was noticing.
And Washington is staying strong.
A lot of interest from Washington.
Washington state or the man? Both.
Okay, good.
Also, Washington, the concept look okay.
That didn't list it.
You landed it the way it landed.
Let's be happy.
So here's the situation that we have in front of us.
Too many requests, too many I cannot handle much more.
So we are closing the requests Friday, end of day Friday.
End of day Friday.
So this episode is coming out on Friday today.
You are listening to this is the last day to get requests.
Let's call it Greenwich.
Meantime.
Sure, yes.
I will set the clock on my Gmail account to Greenwich Mean.
I think that's the way to go.
So get those crest in if you want to have them.
And I'm sorry to people who are listening on behind, but there's just nothing I can do about that.
It's ridiculous.
Yeah, and another thing I wanted to say was that a lot of people have this is something that happened last time, too, and it's very kind of people a lot of people were requesting to help with postage and stuff, of course, particularly these Scots and other international ones.
Right.
And that is very appreciated and nice, but I like to do this as a gift to people.
And so there's no need to donate, there's no need to give anything.
But if you do feel so inclined to because I also don't want to be disrespectful to people's generosity.
Obviously not.
We have started another GoFundMe.
This one benefiting the Transgender Law Center.
It is over on GoFundMe.
Little button theme to it.
Let's put a button on the dreamy.
Dreamy Summer.
The pun was too good.
All right.
I knew it.
So we've got a link to that.
We'll put it up in the show.
Really excellent.
Today, item number 7000, in case against us being good with money.
Yes.
It would be great if you wanted to chip into that donation for a good cause.
That would be lovely.
How about you? What's your not making? But I offered my help, sir.
True.
my bright spot is at Spock and on Twitter sent me a Bound version of my book with a beautiful cover.
And it was bound with love and inside it was actually my book.
It wasn't like a cover that was dummy.
No.
It was kind of surprising and amazing.
And as a writer, I feel like the only way I can kind of express how I feel would be the word indescribable.
That is going to be through songs.
No, but yeah, it's incredible.
It's something I never thought I would ever see.
I told you this when that came in.
I told you that for the last couple of months, I have been planning to get you a bound copy.
Yeah, I know.
Our friend Angela Lampsberry had designed a cover for it and everything we were you conspired against me and I kept forgetting I'll beat you to it.
Right.
And they also sent some empty notebooks that are really cool for me.
So thank you for me as well.
Yes.
Fantastic.
Indeed.
Yeah.
So, Jordan, today we have an episode to go over.
Excellent.
Two of them we're going to be talking about August 21 and 22nd, 2022.
All right.
How do you do? Okay.
These are Sunday and Monday.
And the reason that we're going to this day is because Sunday evening in Russia time, which would have been during the day here, alexander Dugan's daughter was killed at car bombing.
Right.
And as we know, Alex is somebody who has had Dugan on his show, and he's been on his show in Russia.
And so I think a lot of people are pretty curious to see how this was responded to.
Sure.
They might be underwhelmed.
Have they ever not been.
Yeah, so we'll get into that here Jordan.
But first, let's say a little hello to some new walk.
Oh, that's great idea.
So first, the way back machines, faulty server.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy walk.
I'm a policy walk.
Thank you very much.
Next.
If you can pronounce them as Sarah, you can pronounce my name sarah.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy walk.
I'm a policy walk.
I'm not sure I can pronounce that.
It's.
Where Wonder Woman's from the Messera? Wait, what it might be? I don't know.
Yeah, I can't pronounce anything.
Next.
Juice pants.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Nailed juicepants.
Yeah, I can pronounce nailed juicepants.
Next.
SMORGAS, buns, gout and tits.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy walk.
Thank you very much.
Next here.
I Thong Dubai.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
I had a phonetic explanation that I still think I got it wrong.
I understand.
Next.
Help.
I think my cat's homophobic.
Thank you so much.
You and I have a policy want.
I'm a policy won.
Thank you very much.
I assure you they're not.
Yeah.
Next.
And we had a technical credit in the mix.
Next is a tax credit.
Look, we're a little bit behind hey, it's going great.
We're a little bit behind on these, but carissa.
Happy fourth anniversary.
There was no little break ease for us.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
I have risen above my enemies.
I might quit tomorrow, actually.
I'm just going to take a little break you down a little breaky for me and then we're going to come back and I'm going to start the show over.
I'm the devil, I got to be taking over here.
Fuck you.
I got plenty of words for you, but at the end of the day, fuck you in your new world order and fuck the horse you rode in on and all your shit.
Maybe today should be my last broadcast.
Maybe I'll just be gone a month, maybe five years.
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow and you never see me again.
That's really what I want to do.
I never want to come back here again.
I apologize to the crew and the listeners yesterday that I was legitimately having breakdowns on here.
I'll be better tomorrow.
He's not.
Oh, happy anniversary.
I appreciate the anniversaries because with so many anniversary requests for a lot of people, they're like, oh, I know when it's going to come.
It's going to come on the day of our anniversary.
But in this case, it's a surprise to both of you.
You never know when we're going to give wish you a happy anniversary.
You might have been expecting it to come months later.
Yeah, absolutely.
It's always a shock.
So here we start, and Alex does get to the news of the car bombing right out of the gate.
Alexander Dugan has been on our broadcast before.
I've been on some of his shows in Russia, and he is a Russian nationalist, not a fascist, as our corporate control media has said.
And in the lead up to this open proxy war with the Russians in Ukraine, you can pull up the news articles with Republican Democrat senators and others like Lindsey Graham calling for the assassination of Vladimir Putin and people like Alexander Dugan.
So Alex is telling on himself a little bit in the way that this defense of Dugan begins, with him saying that Dugan has been on his show and Alex has been on Dugan's broadcast in Russia.
Well, this is a person who likes Alex, and Alex likes him.
And by definition, Alex doesn't like fascists and they don't like him.
So Dugan couldn't possibly be one that simple.
He's just a good old fashioned nationalist.
I mean, except that Alex does like fascist quite a bit.
Yeah.
In reality, Dugan is an ultra nationalist and someone who is staunchly in favor of a return to Russian imperialism.
I don't want to quibble about whether or not his ideas would strictly be called fascistic.
Like in an academic setting, it's fair enough to say that he's pretty much in the ballpark.
You know what? When you go with warmonger and fascist, I really don't feel like there's that much of a difference.
At the end of the day, then, there are distinctions, but I know what you mean.
Yes.
For those who have not heard the news, on Sunday, August 21, dugan's daughter Dario was killed in a car bomb attack while leaving an event she attended that night called Tradition.
In the aftermath, Russian intelligence has blamed forces from Ukraine.
While Ukraine has denied all involvement.
Others have suggested that the attack was carried out by fringe groups within Russia, or possibly even the Russian intelligence services themselves.
Sure.
Ultimately, it's very much unknown at this point who did it, and it may be something that's never really nailed down concretely.
We may never know.
Let's just back up and let's spread out and let's take a larger view here.
I'll tell you who did it.
Someone who declared war.
Someone who was up to no good.
That's what I would suggest, is, if you declare war, who did it? A car bombing.
Well, yeah, but I mean, if Putin declares war and then bombings start happening, it's like, you're at war, man.
Like, you earned it.
That's how it goes.
I feel like you don't get to be mad about it.
I can see your perspective.
I'm less interested from what I was saying.
Sure.
I'm less interested in that position of natural and more like, who knows who did it? Oh, God knows.
Yeah.
That is going to be a discussion that a lot of people are having, especially people like Alex.
Right.
It's the was it this side or that side? Whatever.
What you're saying is the Alzheimer in love and war.
I mean, I'm not saying all is fair, I'm just saying that it takes two to tango.
Sure.
So I wanted to take this opportunity, though here to call myself out for some of the coverage of Dugan back when he was on Alex's show Circuit 2017.
I'll stand by my statements that it was a really big deal that that crossover was happening, but I think I probably was too credulous of the media stories that I was reading at the time that painted Dugan as being much more connected to Putin and the official government channels that he may actually be.
I'm not entirely sure how much of that is real, that he's really influential, how much of it is bluster.
And if I were approaching the show the same way that I am now, back then, I probably would have presented it a little bit differently.
I still would have presented their collaboration as troubling, though, because whether or not Dugan is closely associated with Putin, he's definitely associated with international far right extremists.
In 2018, Lauren Southern posted an image of herself in Dugan meeting.
And this was back when Lauren was making completely fraudulent documentaries meant to demonize immigrants and was going on adventures to intercept migrant boats.
Along with members of Generation Identity, a group with links to the guy who carried out the shooting at that mosque in Christchurch.
Right.
And also going on tour with Stefan Molyneux.
What she refers to as the good old days.
Yeah.
This wasn't her meeting with Dugan and her now softer, like Glenn Beck in a sweater with Samantha B.
S rebrand trying to pull off.
Yeah.
Fellow antiimmigrant educator Brittany Pettbone was along with Southern for her trip to meet Dugan.
Incidentally, Petty Bone would go on to marry Generation Identity leader Martin Sellsner, whose home was rated after it was revealed that the Christchurch shooter had donated a disproportionately high amount to his group.
Great.
Weird, too, that a guy from New Zealand would make a larger donation to a random bigot group in Austria without having any connections to that.
It's so odd.
There are other connections.
But even beyond that, the influence Duggan has had on a lot of the ascending far right figures is something that matters.
Given his belief set, as he wrote in his book Foundations of Geopolitics, quote, it is essentially important to introduce geopolitical disorder into internal American activity, encouraging all kinds of separatism and ethnic, social and racial conflicts, actively supporting all dissident movements, extremist racist and sectarian groups, thus destabilizing internal political processes in the United States.
Naturally, this is a book that's been promoted by people like Jack Pizzobic and Richard Spencer, who are probably, not coincidentally, figures, who are working to introduce geopolitical disorder into internal American activity and encouraging all kinds of separatism.
Yeah, it is weird how that worked out.
Weird.
Yeah.
Anyway, the point is that it's still super fucked up that Alex feels this kinship with Dugan and that they've been on each other's show, but I think, in hindsight a little bit off base with how connected I believed him to be to Putin.
What? I talked about him before, sure.
And he's not come up necessarily in any large way, but I've been meaning to address that in some fashion.
Well, I mean, it's regularly reported of him that he's the philosophical architect of the current Russian imperialist strategy.
You could say that he's well connected in the inner circle, but that's not quite the same thing as being socially and so forth connected in that way.
And it's tough to say, really.
I've heard enough counter report of that, and I've also heard from some listeners who are in Russia or even just in the surrounding area who have very different take in terms of what his position is.
Visa VPN.
Well, it's not hard to think that we can attribute that to him and have nothing to do with him, actually.
What is the difference between some dude writing that and Putin just being like, hey, you know, it's a good idea fucking up America.
It's not that complicated of a strategy, it's just going in there and wrecking shit.
Right.
It's the difference between being on the same page and someone like having your email.
Exactly.
Yeah.
There is a difference to it.
Yeah, absolutely.
Some of it is fundamentally the effects of it may be the same.
Sure.
Anyway, Alex is mad at the media coverage, of course, of this story, and it's because people are suggesting maybe it was a false flag and that's Alex's turf.
less than a day ago, his daughter driving back in his car, he was another vehicle, the idea that he or Putin would blow up his own daughter is preposterous.
But the London Telegraph, the BBC, US News, they're running the headlines.
It's a false flag.
So I supposedly lose 40 something million dollar rigged lawsuits for questioning events saying they could be staged or fake or the system targeting itself.
But on the Telegraph and others can say, it woah Nelly, just don't talk about it anymore.
Why? Complicated.
I don't know.
It's insane.
I can confirm that at least.
The Telegraph suggested that the attack was possibly a false flag meant to incite the public into supporting further hostilities in frame.
I'm not sure if that was the widespread media theory.
And many folks who are actually suggesting that the attack might have been carried out by Russian actors have specifically speculated that it could have been the work of a group unaligned with Putin.
Right.
Somebody who's some dissident, let's take a crack at somebody that we think is a target.
There are a number of suggestions that people have had and the argument that alex is making, where it's like a lot of people are coming out and saying that it was Dugan blowing up his own daughter.
Right.
I don't know how widespread of belief that is.
It's just fundamentally it's unfair.
Alex doesn't get to say shit right now.
Unfair.
Yeah.
I mean, it falls a little on deaf ears.
And he isn't getting sued for suggesting that something could be a false flag or for questioning an event.
If that were possible, he would be getting sued every day.
He defamed people, which isn't the same thing.
Also, I'm not sure what defamation laws are like in Russia, but based on the US standard, dugan and his daughter are definitely public figures.
So talking about the possibility that the attack could have been a false flag wouldn't rise to the level of actual malice required to be defamation against them.
Just one of the reasons why Alex doesn't get sued for all the shitty talks about celebrity public figures.
Yeah.
I wouldn't worry too much about the defamation laws in Russia.
Their laws currently are on the more like, if we want to get you, we got you kind of side of the justice thing.
Defamation might be handled differently.
Could be.
So the Russians alex has been monitoring how the news reports are going there naturally, and they are not happy.
Okay, well, why would they be? They looked at the national Russian news.
They're hopping mad at Putin.
They're pissed that a suburb can be bombed and that this journalist and talk show host, his daughter was also very prominent.
Boogie.
I guess in Russia, they add an A when the last name is feminine.
The father, igiana, is the blown up daughter.
And wild.
They're saying Alexander doesn't blow his daughter up.
And no proof.
But that's okay because they're mainstream media.
The truth is, you're allowed to question anyone you want.
You can say it's odor and debt if you want.
Maybe you're wrong, maybe you're right.
The point is that you have a right to question.
They have a right to put this out.
They're just saying you don't have a right to question.
They're right back.
Stay with us.
Alex seems to be making this about himself a little bit.
I was going to say that the number one thing that I should have expected was that this is about Alex.
And somehow, like so many of our listeners, I was like, I wonder what Alex's thoughts on this are.
No, I knew what they were.
Alex was right about everything.
It's strange, too, because Alex is the victim.
Yeah.
Because really, the actual bombing seems like something Alex could use to be like, nationalists are under attack everywhere.
It's a sweet spot for it right there.
But instead, it's about the media coverage because he can relate it to himself.
I know.
Very.
It is sad.
Yeah, it is sad.
Whenever he feels defensive, it always comes back to him.
He's got material to work with on this.
And therapy.
Well, he's definitely got that to work through.
I think that mental illness works in a certain way and sort of behavioral patterns and issues.
And once you become sort of beholden to them and they control you, things become a little less interesting.
And Alex's Narcissism is definitely taken over.
Yeah.
So speaking of that Narcissism, but he was clearly the target because he's the populist of Russia.
He's the Alex Jones of Russia.
And mainstream news has said that over the years.
I'm sorry, what? Russia? The populist the popular talk show host that has, like, half the country tuning into him.
He's dead.
His daughter is dead.
They want to make sure he dies.
The globalists have the motive to kill him.
Do they? No.
Alex is describing himself once again.
The globalist wants to kill me through Alexander Dugan.
Not only is he like Alexander Dugan is a target, but it is also that Alex is a target through Alexander Dugan.
And in fact, the globalists were trying to send Alex a message that anyone can be got, I believe.
Why would the globalists and Alex's conception have the motive to do this? It doesn't make sense.
Obviously they don't want Russia in Ukraine.
No.
Okay.
They want the Ukraine to join NATO.
Sure.
They want even Russia out of Crimea, out of the dawn boss.
They want to get rid of Putin entirely.
They want to be assassinated.
Yes.
The whole thing.
So do you think that working towards that end, do you think it's progressed by bombing someone who's seen as an associate of his? Right? Is it something that we're Putin like, oh, shit is too hot now? Sure.
Maybe it's a dry run.
Maybe they're checking their oceans.
Eleven in practice.
I don't see how can we car bomb anybody.
Like, how do we carbomb you know, I think that's now I'm going to throw this one out.
That's a tough one, to throw, this one out at you.
And I feel like a lot of people are going to laugh at me, but I'm going to have to go with IRA.
They have a proven track record of this type of thing.
Talking about steak knife.
I'm just saying that it's in their wheelhouse and maybe they just got a little bit bored.
The troubles haven't been as hot lately.
Well, according to Alex, that's all the globalists.
That's right.
Damn it.
So they hired IRA Mercks.
Now it all makes sense.
Now it's all coming together.
I guess when your explanations are hyper simple, they always fit.
They do.
So, look, this is not a false flag, and Alex explains why.
Okay? And you could say maybe Putin did this because he knows Dugan is a big nationalist to get Russians behind the war.
Except if, you know, the climate in Russia, they're angry.
The average Russian in the polls, like 90%.
Putin isn't doing more in Ukraine, and that's why the population there pushed Putin into responding to the NATO proxy war that has been going on for almost nine years.
That George Soros brags.
He helped orchestrate.
Isn't that actually an argument for why Putin could have done it? Yeah, because then he would have a pretext to do the thing that the people want him to do.
Right? Yeah.
Blames it on Ukrainian actors, ukrainian terrorists? Well, then guess what? Right? Alex is convoluted here.
This makes no sense.
This is the problem.
Because just yesterday on our last episode, we're talking about Alex saying, I pig headedly, did something precisely because other people told me not to do it.
And we're seeing an example of him just being like, I'm not going to call it a false flag because they called it a false flag.
How about that, dick wad? Well, it's not fair.
And doing it would require calling it a false flag would require him to say that Putin is willing to do something like that.
Sure.
And then he'd have to admit that Putin has done something like that.
Well, while he was saying that Putin wasn't going to invade Ukraine right.
Before Putin invaded Ukraine, right? Alex was saying that Russia never does false flags.
Exact.
Not once.
It's true.
So he can't go back on that.
Yeah, but that's your moment.
That's your moment to really pull it out and be like, surprise, this is the first Russian false flag.
Nah.
Okay, so maybe it's a false flag, maybe it's not.
Who knows? But sure, everybody should be able to ask questions, but he's not.
I just say this briefly.
We're going to come back and talk about this more.
I don't think this is a false flag, but the CIA had things like Operation Northwoods, where CIA operatives and their families would get on the plane with one telember.
They'd blow up another plane with the same telember.
Those families would all just change their names and use that as a pretext to go to war with Cuba and then Russia.
Sure.
Look up Operation Northwood.
ABC News.
NBC News.
They've all covered it.
So these things exist.
Did he stage the dentist? Elder? Is she still alive? Did she change her name? I'm sorry, what? I think that's the case.
But you have a right to say that and you have a right to speculate.
And that's with all these lawsuits against Infowars, everybody you're about is silencing that discussion.
Robert Barnes is coming up to cover the water.
No.
Good Lord.
Yes.
Real disappointing end.
But this is evidence that that is true.
Alex is describing a true thing.
You can question this exact thing.
That is the evidence that we are experiencing is that The Telegraph did question this thing.
So you are not being sued.
Thus, we can concretely prove that it is not for this reason that Alex is being sued.
cares.
Yeah.
If she did fake her death, that would be an interesting conspiracy.
I look forward to Alex bringing that out around the midterms to distract from something.
Maybe she just wanted emancipation from her dad, but she couldn't get it in Russia because he's too closely connected to Putin.
Now she's free.
That could be, I think.
So we have one last clip here from the 21st on Sunday, as Alex said, Bobby Barr we're not doing Bobby Barr meeting roll solo.
Alex leaves.
Alex is just in for, like, the first segment or two of the show.
Great.
But he explains a little bit about his bankruptcy here, and I think this is pretty interesting.
All right, but let me talk about the lawsuits against us.
There are dozens of types of bankruptcy.
We've done chapter five, which is reorganization survival for a business so the business can continue on and, quote, pay its debts.
In the last few hearings, this is going to be coming out.
They have the plaintiff lawyers and soros'lawyers with a big law firm out of Houston in the meetings saying, we want it seized and shut down.
We don't want the money.
And of course, federal law says the judge is supposed to keep it going, quote, for the creditors, but they don't want money from Judge but you understand, and we knew they'd do that.
We're showing that right now.
That's why as long as we have solvent numbers to pay the employees, keep the lights on, and run the operation, the federal judge will look at that for a year and then say, okay, over the next five years, here's what you can pay, and that's what they get.
And we stay on air.
Federal courts already seen my books.
They know I haven't paid myself in a year and a half.
I know.
I've injected $10 million, everything I got into this operation, all the emergency savings.
Have they seen your real books? And the court's eyes are getting real big right now in these meetings where they're like, we want them shut down.
No, we don't want money for electricity.
We want it closed.
They're like, what? You're creditors.
Don't you want money for the plaintiffs? The families are nothing but puppets.
They're using and controlling.
I'm sorry, but that's what this is all about.
And they will not silence us if you simply buy the products@infowarstore.com.
Wow.
So that might be a new definition.
I mean, how do you not play that in the we need to shut them down hearing? Part of, like, hey, this is never going to stop.
This is just never going to stop.
Listen to this.
This was yesterday.
Guess what I'm going to call it now.
I'm going to call my shot within the next week, I will have another clip for you of him breaking these rules.
I'm calling it.
I'm pointing to the left field fence, man.
Maybe by the end of his episode.
Exactly.
So I don't know everything about.
Bankruptcy law.
But from everything I can tell, this is not a plan that's going to work for Alex.
For one thing, Chapter Five is only available to businesses that have less than $7.5 million in debt.
And if he's trying to bankrupt Free Speech Systems, they owe like $50 million to Alex's dad's shell company.
And the judgment in the Sandy Hook case, the first one exceeded that amount already.
Additionally, this debt limit only applies if 50% or more of the company's debt is business related, which doesn't include defamation judgments.
Also, the only reason that the cap is 7.5 million as opposed to the original limit that this subchapter had, the original limit was 2.75 million.
The only reason that's different is because of the Cares Act, which Alex was staunchly.
Again, of course, Chapter Five is a sub chapter of Chapter Eleven bankruptcy or the reorganization bankruptcy.
It seems pretty clear to me why Alex chose this route, and it's because Chapter Five bankruptcy cases specifically do not require a business to file a full disclosure statement to the court.
Well, that would make sense.
Yeah.
Let's choose the one that lets us hide our lives.
Yes.
Because the thing is that Chapter Five, it was created because Chapter Eleven normal bankruptcies require all kinds of information and small businesses were what Chapter Five was made for.
Sure.
And they were in a position that usually are illequipped to handle the intricacies of a normal reorganization.
Under Chapter Eleven, part of their debt is that they can't afford an incredibly expensive accountant to help them actually do the stuff that they're supposed to do.
Yeah.
Too often, small businesses weren't able to take advantage of what they could get with a Chapter Eleven reorganization and they just end up going out of business.
So this was an attempt to provide an option for them to stay afloat.
Right.
Alex is basically attempting to abuse the bankruptcy system, and while he's doing it, he's using the illusion of his persecution to sell his dumb products to the audience.
The good news is that he probably doesn't qualify for Chapter Five.
And as this progresses through the court, we'll see what happens.
But I don't think that based on what I can find, I don't think that this is going to work.
I mean, sometimes I really do think I understand that the court system does work slow and needs to, but god damn it, for this case, I really feel like every day you should go and you should play the judge a clip and be like, see, this option is off the table.
That he said it.
Right.
Done.
Okay.
Then tomorrow you bring in a clip like, we should have this whole thing banged out in like a week.
Well, actually, the Chapter Five subsection or subchapter is designed to be faster.
Right.
So there is that.
There is that at least they'll go faster.
Right.
How many chapters are there is a question.
I guarantee.
Alex is asked and then asked.
Can we just keep using them? Can I write? Yeah.
How about another chapter? So we get to the 22nd.
We get to Monday show? Okay.
Because I felt like, well, we have not really even scratched the surface of the Dugan attempt.
No, we've scratched Alex's surface a little, but he's got to have more to say.
You would hope.
There's big news coming today.
Okay.
Big broadcast ahead of Ointroyer 03:00 PM central.
Always informative on the war room.
All right, when we come back still long time to break.
When we come back.
We don't just put out his most important tweet yet.
no.
Can't handle it.
I gotta go.
Oh, good.
You know what it's like to turn on a show and hear that? I do now.
Okay.
All right.
Let's call the dad.
It's one thing if you're pretending to be like TMZ and this is your lead right.
Then, hey, that's what you are.
You're a clickbait.
Top 43 tweets by Elon Musk And this is today.
Yeah, whatever.
Tends to be like, I'm the most geopolitically important person in the world.
Oh, man.
World leaders, listen to me.
Oh.
Elon Musk had a good tweet.
Can you think of Edward R.
Murrow being like, oh, the Rockefellers put out a chalk drawing on the sidewalk.
Like, what are you talking about? Something pithy at a bar.
Alex is the Algonquin round table of his time.
That is true.
So there's a lot of news.
Sure.
Not just the tweet.
We have the execution assassination of Alexander Dugan's daughter when they were trying to kill him.
What that really signifies massive economy is so much on the great reset and more today.
This is another broadcast.
Busy day I don't want to miss.
But separately, here is the good news.
Freedom is popular.
This book, with no advertising in the corporate media, has gone to number five.
It fluctuates between that and the top 100 on Amazon.com, the number one book platform in the world.
It's the equivalent of the New York Times bestseller list before they got caught.
Rigging.
In the last 20 years, nobody looks at or believes it anymore.
It's totally fake.
The Amazon chart is 100% real.
Off and off, several weeks, and you see, this is the actual book.
It is here it is ready to ship, ladies and gentlemen.
And I can tell you that there are a few thousand books left at Info Worldstore.com until a new order comes in.
But for the time being, this will be the only sign books I do.
And it's a fundraiser to keep us on air.
It's absolutely critical.
I want to thank all of you that went and got the signed fundraiser copy of the book.
It's a piece of history.
It's the Death Star plan.
The great reset in the war for the world is your last chance to get a signed copy at Info orstore.com.
And it is a fundraiser we're doing.
So thank you so much.
Your support.
The great reset of the world is my magnum opus.
It is a masterwork wild, just absolutely devastatingly.
Lays out how evil and sick these people are.
What about reset wars? Let me ask you a bigger and greater question, all right? In the book, how does he spell evil? I have two things I want to bring up about this.
Okay.
The first thing yes.
Is that man, he's making bezos a lot of money.
He sure is.
I hope he's happy about that.
Hey, the Amazon charts are real.
At least like the lies of The New York Times.
Yeah.
And then the second thing I was thinking about, he's not going to sign all these books.
No, but if he does, he's going to be drinking.
While he doesn't want to get progressively floppy as he goes along.
We need that flow chart to really show up.
Yeah.
I want the last book.
This is going to be a black page.
I kind of want to know, did someone edit it? That's what I want to know.
Yeah, but here's what I'm talking about, right? He didn't even write it.
He didn't write it according to what he said about it.
Right? Yeah.
He dictated it, supposedly.
Or grabbed from his show.
Right.
Not even necessarily dictated.
Just people transcribed his ramp.
Right.
But they cut out the rambling.
There's no way that it's going to go I kind of want to read it just in case.
I'm going to read it.
It doesn't come out until the 30th.
Well, it's already rocketed to the top of the charts.
The best.
Kind of like how Alex's War was at the top of the charts and then no one cared, but at least that was true whenever nobody cared.
Yeah.
Not even the New York Times.
I'm going to guess no one's going to care when Alex's book comes out, but we will definitely copy.
Come on.
And you know what I was thinking about doing? I was thinking about doing a Great Reset special.
So what I would do is I would take Alex's book the great reset.
Sure.
Compare it to Klau Schwab's book the Great reset where it counts.
Glenn Beck's book the Great reset.
That's trouble.
Try and see where we're at with the three of them, where there's overlaps.
Sure.
Who's making up what? Here's what I say we do.
First off, what we're going to do is we're going to cut out little passages from each book and then glue them together and then take that message and mail it to Alex so it sounds like we're holding one of his children hostage.
See? We're holding the ecosystem.
Yeah, exactly.
If you don't reset, we'll come get you.
So look, the big news yeah.
Musk.
Biggest tweet ever.
It's big.
Most important.
I know for a fact, and I told you this a couple of years ago, that Elon Musk was riding the fence and that he decided to fight the New World Order.
At least he told his top advisors that and said he was going for a pro human future to fight the New World Order.
Now, whether he's being legitimate or not, christ says you judge a tree by its fruits.
Look what Elon tweeted out yesterday.
Got hundreds of thousands of retweets elon Musk.
There's the actual image.
Please let me use the CERN large hadron collider.
I'm normal and can be trusted with the demonic technology unlike anything the world has ever seen.
What is a demonic technology? Well, they admit they're trying to find the God particle.
All right.
They admit they're trying to create artificial black holes and strangelets that create particles so strong, sinks the center of the Earth, and then creates a black hole that implodes the entire planet.
It's not a Star Trek movie.
It's reality.
So this is not an important tweet.
It's basically musk shit posting.
Also, CERN isn't trying to create a black hole to implode the universe.
And they found confirmation of the existence of the Higgs Boson, aka the God Particle, ten years ago in 2013.
Decade ago.
It's old.
God particle was a great day.
I was really excited.
I watched the live stream.
It was really cool.
Yeah.
Alex has not updated his talking points in quite a while, so you know what else Christ said of people similar to Elod Bus? He was like, you know, it's easier for a rich guy to go through heaven.
That it's awesome.
Rich people are the best.
Come on in, buddies.
I will make the head of the needle really large, and he promises to have tons of white babies.
He opened the large hadron collider.
Jesus words are different now.
Oh, no.
Mandela Effect.
Yes, the Bible is entirely different.
That's a Mandela effect.
Is that a movie? I hope so.
Wait, isn't that knowing? No.
Okay.
Quite different.
So, look, CERN dangerous.
It blew up a few years ago, the last time they tried it.
Now they're doing I'm sorry, what test again? You didn't hear it? While they're doing the test, they're constantly doing satanic rituals above ground, on facilities, acreage.
So they had a helium leak in 2008.
I was going to say.
I just don't understand how we could get to blow up.
wild.
Yeah.
They are doing satanic rituals, though.
Alex is right on about it.
Sure, but that's why it doesn't blow up.
The satanic rituals keep it stable.
Otherwise you can't shoot particles that fast.
With great ritual comes great particles.
Winners.
When I say things.
Hey, listen, we can't all hit it to the left field sense.
So there's big news.
My man Fauche.
Dr.
Faustus.
Yeah.
He has decided to resign.
Good for him.
All right, here it is.
Dr.
Fauchy has issued his resignation letter after 40 plus years running different federal agencies, murdering people walking treatments engaged in HIV.
Rollout the lab.
This murderous discredited monster, this Hitler 2.0, this Bill Gates prosthesis what that's now designed.
What does that one mean? I'm announcing today that I am stepping down the director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases and chief of NIAD Laboratory of Immunologization, as well as the position of chief medical Advisor to President Joe Biden.
I will be leaving these positions in December of this year to pursue the next chapter.
Getting to my Arnold now.
He now wants everybody to take polio shots again.
That impression was so inconsistent.
That was all over the place.
I got what name? How many do we get? But it was also like shifting midsentence, right? He was trying to find his bearings and he didn't get there.
He never found it.
That's depressing from one of the greatest voice actors of our time, who was offered the role of Optimist Prime? Everything.
But then he criticized Obama, and they said they couldn't let him be starlord.
If you criticize Obama, that's science.
Also, the CDC still recommends children get vaccinated against polio forever.
Number of people who don't take that advice, and most likely due to low vaccination rates in some areas.
We recently saw the identification of a case of polio in Rockland County, New York.
Experts believe that if they're seeing one case, there is a very high likelihood that there are more people who have caught it in the area.
But maybe asymptomatic, which is a terrifying prospect.
The US has a vaccination rate for polio of 93%, whereas Rockland County is at about 60%.
Anyway, this is not good and probably won't be the last we hear of this story, but let's hope for the best.
Jesus.
Alex is ready to handle the news of a possible resurgence of polio, though, since he'll just say that it's secretly covet vaccine side effects being called polio.
And then he'll fleece his audience, selling them survival food as he watches them get sick and die.
This is kind of what his business model has largely evolved into after Covet.
Yeah, and I don't even have to just speculate on that.
We told you that Climate was polio when you got paralysis from the poison shots.
And the record levels of heart attacks will be detailed next hour.
He's already ready.
I think the number one thing I applaud Faucey for is retiring with dignity.
Because I'll be goddamned if I didn't quit that job with the single largest fuck you to America.
Anybody's ever like nobody has earned the right to give the double bird on TV to the entire United States of America more than Fuchi.
He might have a scathing book in the future.
Give up.
That's the name of Fuchi's book.
Give up on hope.
Yeah.
So we get to the second hour of the program and Alex isn't there.
For the first break, they just play special reports, which happens from time to time it's not on the radio, right? Who gives a shit? Yeah.
Second segment starts and I noticed that it seemed that Infowars had switched to an instrumental jazz format.
Interesting.
And now the works of Antonio Carlos Chopin the most dangerous fact ever created by man.
I was as confused as I've ever been.
It goes on for a long time.
Let's listen to all of it.
I don't know what was going on there.
There's some sort of a technical difficulty.
But this is the feed that goes out on the radio.
Yeah, let's all go to the lobby.
Started playing elevator music on Info.
Yeah, great.
So I don't know what the fuck was happening, but Steve Kersh is on Alex's antivaxx substance buddy.
Is it not addressed? No.
What just happened? No, I don't think Alex never notices.
No.
But there are further tech difficulties.
Here we are.
Steve Kerr joins us for the balance of the hour.
But we do have numbers.
We have insurance company numbers, we have government numbers, we have them all.
He has them all in his substance and layout.
The facts that now even the CDC saying, okay, the shot doesn't help you, doesn't protect you.
All over the world, from Australia to Germany to the UK to Canada, the US, they're showing that people that affected are way more likely to actually get sick.
Please lay it out for us.
Well, it's just like I said on Fox News, and Brian Big, who was the host, was caught off guard, and so he said, well, we can't verify those numbers.
Well, he was actually telling people the truth because Fox News has contractual commitments that don't allow them to speak poorly about the vaccine, so they can't say anything antivaxx on Fox News that's skipping that you heard is on Alex's end.
That was not our recording.
So this is a fun semantics game that Steve is playing.
The Fox News host, Brian Kilmead was pointing out that Steve's statistics are completely dubious and he can't prove that they're accurate and expresses that by saying, we can't confirm that.
Steve naturally doesn't want to accept that he in fact, can't confirm any of the bullshit he spreads, so he's using the wording of this comment to create a broader conspiracy.
Of course you can't confirm this, Brian.
Kill Mead, you're on the farm of payroll, right? If Fox hosts can't be antivaxx, I wonder what happened with Tucker Hannity and Fox and Friends sometimes.
See, this is why we need to relax certain language requirements for TV hosts in this situation.
You can't say, we can't confirm that what you have to say is bullshit's.
Best interest.
No, and I understand that, but I feel like it should be required.
So I'm not sure what statistics Steve is talking about here, because his substec is full of posts claiming various bombshell things about covert vaccines, and all of them apparently rely on very legitimate data.
I decided to consult one recent post with the headline, quote, do you know how many people have been killed worldwide by their governments from the covet shots? 16,000.
It's around 12 million.
That's 40 times the number of Americans who were killed in World War II.
It's more than double the number killed by COVID.
That seemed intriguing.
Yeah.
How was this number reached? You're probably asking yourself that's my first question.
Yeah, it seems like an even number.
First off, here's how Steve got it.
Okay.
Quote Margaret and Alice asked if anyone could estimate the global death toll from the covert shots.
In my opinion, a reasonable estimate is to divide the number of doses by $1,000.
If you do that for 600 million doses delivered in the United States, you do not get 600,000 deaths.
Which is right in the ballpark.
No, he just said it.
Yeah, that's not data.
That was his basis for that number.
And then you extrapolate that out to the world.
Right.
So I said that, and that means it's true.
Yeah.
This is expressing an opinion and then making a guess based on entirely nothing.
This article is legitimately trash.
Here's Steve synthesizing his point, which, again, is just about him guessing things based on nothing.
Quote we are killing an awful lot of people, but world leaders are looking the other way and saying nothing while all of us watch the high number of death reports in the media.
People who died, quote, unexpectedly and hear no explanation from the medical community or the CDC.
We're supposed to trust that they have things well in hand, even though they won't appear on camera in front of anyone who doesn't have scripted preapproved questions.
The vaccine was never mentioned in any of these unexplained death reports, yet people all over the world have noticed that these unexpected deaths are only happening to the vaccinated.
I wonder why.
And I would say, what unexpected deaths are you talking about? There are any specifics offered in the article, so I don't know if I agree that we even are seeing a huge number of unexpected deaths reported in the media.
You know what bums me out? Because this is really suspicious.
Not one of these medical professionals can we even call them that? Is the first question.
But not one of them will go on live TV in a pit filled with hungry hyenas.
Not one of them.
Now, why not, Dan? Why not? What are they afraid of, Dan? You're right.
Exactly.
I'm taken aback by your logic.
You can't deny it makes total sense.
It does.
There are occasionally, like, celebrities who die with no immediate cause of death determined, and then these antivaxx idiots rush in to pretend there was a vaccine death.
But typically in all of those cases, a death cause is determined.
But it's after people like Steve stopped caring about the story.
Yeah, just use it for the immediate dopamine rush of like, hey, get this.
This person who you love was killed by Fauchy.
Right.
It's hard to wait a couple of days to say that, though, after the people have already figured out the actual reason.
Let me be totally clear about this.
Steve Kersh is a lunatic.
This article also includes this passage quote we are approaching the 6 million Jews killed in the Holocaust over a period of twelve years, but we're killing people worldwide at a rate of at least six times faster than the Germans did.
We're killing nearly close to 10,000 people every day.
The latest rate was roughly 8.46 million doses a day.
Interestingly, this is not self limiting because 3850 babies are born every day, so the killing can go on indefinitely, even if the birth rate drops by 90% due to the shots, in case you were wondering.
I just thought I'd point that out.
This is complete drivel, and it's a bit offensive to boot.
I feel like we need to really hammer home that this obsession with comparing things to the Holocaust is Holocaust minimization, which is a subset of Holocaust denial.
That's the part I was saying was a bit offensive.
Yeah.
There's a reason that they are so focused on comparing things to the Holocaust to make it feel like the Holocaust wasn't that big a deal after all that was it? Compared to vaccinations? Yeah, exactly.
What? Yeah.
So for one thing about Steve's logic here, 10,000 people aren't being killed by the vaccine every day.
That's just shit talk.
But beyond that, this supposed killing could not go on indefinitely, even if the birth rate dropped 90%, because the massive societal problems that would accompany that drop in birth rates would render 10,000 deaths a day a side issue.
Everything would be over.
Yeah, I don't think just the devastation of everything daily crazy.
Speaking of statistics, on August 20, Steve posted a blog entry where he was begging people who work at hospitals to provide him with internal data about their numbers of deaths and ICU admissions based on vaccination status.
This is probably illegal for them to divulge.
But also, whatever results he gets from this are completely meaningless.
He's gathering data through the equivalent of a Google survey form where anyone could just enter whatever numbers they want and pretend they work at a hospital.
Right, but also he's sending out a Google survey form that says, Please commit a crime.
Yes or no.
That is what he's doing.
But we're all pretending, so it doesn't really so it's not really a crime.
I understand.
But it's a pretend crime.
Yeah.
This data collection form is apparently something he's been using for a while, but he's just now updated it so you can enter in hospital level data before you can enter information about your family and friends or your household and how many people were hurt or killed by vaccines in that subgroup.
Sure.
That's nice of him.
It's probably a fair assumption that he's been treating the responses to this as actual data as opposed to him targeting a very strongly self selected antivaxx community as potential responders to his survey and then having literally zero way to confirm any of the numbers people enter into the survey.
That's what he's doing.
It's not data.
It's like VAERS, but in Arkham Asylum.
Yeah.
What would he be? What would his villain name be? I don't know.
The substance? That's not good.
No.
The blogger.
That's terrible.
So all of the information that he's putting out means exactly nothing.
But it's the kind of thing that can be used to create an impression that something more legitimate and more scholarly than just apocryphal anecdotes that the antivax community has.
That's what they usually rely on, these anecdotal stories.
Of course.
And this is a way that he can sort of mold those anecdotes into numbers, and it gives the appearance of it meaning something more than just a tweet.
Well, off the top of my head, I would say that the way to treat these fairly would be to take the total number of submissions and divide it by 1000.
And then that's the number that are accurate.
Sure.
Now, bottom line, this guy sucks.
Yes.
Bring back Dr.
Marbles.
I really appreciated him over this.
Pretty that guy was unhinged in a fun way.
Yeah.
They're calling for war and what.
Little bar.
Yeah.
Steve sucks.
He's trying to explain to Alex here that the media is bought off and then something very tragic statistics, Steve.
Something really tragic happens.
Yeah.
Explain to people that a whole bunch of media outlets got bought off of contracts with five or two years ago.
Well, we know that the White House has spent a billion dollars on influencing media and giving money to media to promote these vaccines.
And the drug companies we don't know what the contracts say, but it's pretty clear that there was no interest at hello? Have we lost the call, sir? Have we lost the show? Hey, you got your wish.
The jazz comes back, baby.
You can't get rid of jazz.
I don't know what was going on in this episode, but it was weird.
Okay, this seems like a great time for Alex to bring up the time that Trump got that donation from Pfizer.
Right? Because we learned about that on our last episode.
Yeah, I mean, if you're talking about Pfizer conspiracies now it seems like Trump being involved with that that you admitted to.
No, you just need that relevant information.
Not right now.
Oh, okay.
This is a different thing.
I do appreciate the lack of continuity.
This clip is just dumb.
And I'll see if you can figure out why I cut this.
Because there's not enough jazz.
No, this is really like keep your ears open.
Okay.
So even their own leftists now are waking up.
And I just look at Twitter, Facebook, everywhere I've been looking.
It's just everywhere people are saying I'm paralyzed.
My mom's dead.
My kids are paralyzed.
I died.
My husband died.
Why did I pull that clip? I don't know.
He's looking on Twitter and Facebook and everywhere he tweeted, I died.
Yeah.
I mean okay, all right.
I know he's just talking too fast, but it's funny.
There is something about it.
Everybody's out there tweeting, I paralyzed.
My mom sick.
I died.
It left her spirit.
Wasn't that what A Christmas Carol was really all about? If you're in the shadow realm, are you shadow band? No.
I think if you're in the shadow realm, you actually get past the shadow band because you can move through it.
Okay.
The shadow band is like a door in the shadow realm.
A regular human couldn't pass through the shadow door.
So you're saying that all the most popular Twitter accounts are ghosts? Yes, absolutely.
Makes sense.
Yes.
So what is drill but a ghost? Steve has a story to tell, my friend, and this is dumb and we see people in plain sight.
I saw an Arab ambassador.
He's speaking at a podium, and he just drops dead.
But we've seen that over and over and over again.
Have we? The vaccines rolled out.
So the way Steve is telling this story, it's very clear that the only thing he knows here is that he's seen a video on social media.
Right.
He has no idea who this person was or the circumstances depicted in the video at all.
And the big tell is that he's calling him an Arab ambassador.
Yeah.
This was the narrative that took hold as the video traveled in antivaxx circles online, but it's not correct.
It was actually a Saudi businessman named Muhammad bin Nasar bin Wazan Alkatani, who was in Egypt for a conference.
He was giving a speech, and he collapsed, allegedly going on to die in another room as we were attempted to provide aid.
Okay.
The cause of death here is not determined yet, and there's no evidence that Alcatani was or was not vaccinated.
All of this is just forced conjecture on Steve's part because it's more profitable for him to make this suspicious when it very well could have just been a heart attack.
There's no reason to automatically be like, why aren't they telling us what's going on here? I can't get over the idea that we've seen this over and over.
I have not seen a ton of videos of people collapsing at podiums recently, or, in fact, in my entire life.
There haven't been that many.
How many can you remember of just people collapsing at podiums in the middle of a speech? Well, I saw this one that Steve posted, right? Well, that was the one, yes.
I'm even going to count George Bush having to duck from her shoe.
I'll count that.
I think I saw a cartoon once of somebody who was in a debate club, like, a kid who was in a debate club.
All right, rattling.
Off the points, and then he ran out of air and just collapsed.
Hey, Arnold.
I think it might have been I don't know.
It's something in that sort of milieu.
It's in the same part of my brain.
Sure.
Something that might have been on.
Hey, Arnold.
I'm going to go with it.
It wasn't real monsters.
Not a real monster.
It was real monster.
It was not.
It wasn't Rocco's.
Modern life.
That's a good one, though.
Wasn't Sifil and Ollie? No, definitely not.
Cartoon.
Wasn't Ren and Stimpy? No.
You know what I need to do? What's that? I need to go back to some of that stuff and see if it's any good.
Or maybe I shouldn't.
No.
Yeah, you stop smoking weed.
You shouldn't go back.
That's a good point.
Yeah.
You don't want to know what it's like without the assistance.
So Steve has these strategies in order to create his content.
You have, obviously, this weird Google form that he wants to be able to fill out with information.
They very well could be making up Google crime form.
But then the old standby is obviously there's.
He misuses Vares data in order to make points and, man, this is nuts.
It's pretty obvious what is going on.
There is no way to explain the various data, which is the Vaccine Adverse Event Reporting System.
That was my next question.
You're the expert on this.
I'm going to interrupt you.
But not getting into the data.
Just give us the main data points.
You get that? Anybody can check.
Yeah, well, anybody can go to openvers.com and there's something called the red box summaries.
And if you go to that page@openvares.com, go to the red box summaries and you flip the slider because it shows you by default, it shows you the worldwide numbers.
You flip the switch to Go US, only you'll see around 14,000 deaths.
Now, the problem there is that the 14,000 underreported deaths, because people don't report to the various system.
And so it turns out that for every death reported to varys, they're really about 20.
Sorry, I'm getting into the why are you struggling with it? Yeah.
All right.
Now, I escaped the death blow here, but, yeah, if you look at the various numbers, you'll see $14,000.
You need to multiply that by 41.
Why? Okay, sure.
Great.
See, there's under reporting, and this makes some sense for some side effects, like maybe a headache.
Right? Because not everybody's going to report ahead.
Why would you report a headache? Nausea? It could be anything.
Sure.
Yeah.
Death is a little different.
It's hard not to report it.
Yeah, because there's other people who are doing the reporting.
You can't self report death.
No.
Except for that guy who tweeted.
That was, I mean, all time Tweet, though.
That was maybe his most important Tweet ever.
Yeah.
Certainly better than Musk's.
Dumb shit.
Yeah.
I don't know.
This is ludicrous, and there's no defense of multiplying it by 41 Hands, the actual website that he's using, the open vehicles, it says on the bottom, these are not causal.
This is not causal data.
That conclusion cannot be made.
There's a qualifier on the page.
It does.
Oh, fuck yourself.
Doesn't it add at the bottom? This is not causal.
But you should multiply it by 41.
What? 41? And get a Google form.
Yeah.
Oh, no, of course.
He's a fan of shit.
Now I can't pull a song title.
Some 41.
That's what it is.
Yeah.
Scrolling to the party like, my name is El Camino.
See, there we go.
Hanging out, drinking in the back of an El Camino.
Name another Some 41 song in too deep.
Wow.
Because I'm in too deep and I'm trying to keep is that really what they sounded like? Yeah.
Weren't they supposed to be, like, punk or something? They were.
They were pop punk.
Oh.
Those two things don't exist together.
Doesn't everybody know that? That those two things can't be back and it works for a while? There was a guy named Steveo in that band, and I always thought that was weird because he was around after Jackass.
So he just took the name Stevo.
That's not fair.
Yeah, you should have to have Stevo in your band if he names himself Stevo.
Or you've got to staple your balls to your legs.
There's two options then you're grandfathered in on the name.
Yeah, but you have to put sticks in there.
You're a drummer.
Goddammit, show respect.
Look, there's another steve.
Who's? Not a steve.
OSH.
Steve O kirch.
Now that's a different story.
This is so stupid.
Okay, so, Alex, do you know how much Tony Faucey is making every time a majorna shot is delivered into taste? A lot.
You see, that's the problem.
So we have somebody who's directing this entire vaccination program who has a huge conflict of interest.
That is not something that should be allowed.
No, of course not.
We should know exactly how much he's making on these vaccines and we're not allowed to know that? How much is Fauchy making every time someone gets a Maderna shot? When? Here's the problem.
I don't know when would he have negotiated a specific two M cut of each shot? Strange.
When? What contract would he have been a privy to? Plus, I thought Steve was, like, a stats and facts guy.
This is meaningless.
Why don't we know why don't we know how much of a taste Dr.
Fauchy is getting? Apparently by himself.
Not like the CDC is making a cut.
No, just Fauchy.
This is just rampant speculation and insinuation.
And if Steve was pressed on this question by a competent reporter, he couldn't even say that Fauche made a single penny when someone got a madurn a shot.
Also, this conspiracy is internally stupid because here's where things break down.
So Fouchy is pushing these shots to get rich, which he's willing to kill off 12 million people in order to achieve, apparently 10,000 a day.
Right.
He's so money hungry, he just doesn't give a fuck.
Then why was the Pfizer vaccine the first one that was approved? Wouldn't he have stood to make way more money if Maduro was the first one out of the gate? No, that's too much scrutiny, too many eyes on you.
You negotiate with the second tier.
You don't want to get that rich.
No way.
If that you were really able to orchestrate this entire pandemic and the vaccine rollout.
And a big part of his motivation was money.
Why would over 130,000,000 less doses of moderna been administered than Pfizer? I'm sure the answer to this is the trashy gets a taste of both shots.
Sure, it doesn't really matter, but this is double.
Well, you got to figure that it's two shots for each vaccine.
So he doubles that up.
Of course.
Yeah, that's the way you get it.
And he gets even higher cut on the booster.
Yeah, why not the margin? Yes.
It's like once you've made back your advance yeah, I got you.
By all means, I would love for Steve to lay out whatever stock holdings he believes Fauche has or explain this nonsense, but he's not going to do any of that because he's just talking shit.
It's easy to talk shit when you just make suggestions and insinuate guilt on people for fun.
Steve spends a fair amount of this interview wondering why people won't talk to him or take him seriously.
And this is a big part of why this shit flies on your dumb substack or infowars.
But if you try to go to the real world with it, where words mean things, it's going to be a problem.
And that's even like even Brian Killmead will not let you play this fucking stupid.
OAN wouldn't allow you to be like, hey, how much does Faucet get per vet? Actually, they might.
Yes.
But I mean, that's crazy.
That's too crazy.
You could go to OAN, you could go to Infowars, maybe you could go to Lindel's shit.
Right.
And that might be about where you pee.
Yeah.
Oh, wait, I think he was on Brett Weinstein's podcast.
Okay, well, we've all reached the pinnacle of our careers.
I think so.
Alex almost went.
Well, Steve's gone.
Now Alex interviews another fucking Denier guy and I'm just like, I can't do it.
How can we can't still be denying COVID you can.
No, I think it's because Alex is trying to ramp up with the Trump stuff.
Sure.
I think that is like Covet is becoming front and center because the midterms are coming up and maybe he needs a way to have narrative flexibility or whatever it was.
Strategic.
Strategic flexibility.
Yeah.
So I think that's maybe what's going on.
Right? I'm not sure.
I'm kind of feeling like by ramping up the vaccine talk, that gives Alex the wedge for the eventual or an uneventual push.
Conversely, it could be the kind of content you need to put out in order to get Trump to realize he should join the antivaxx.
Sure.
So it kind of has multiple applications, man.
It's kind of interesting to me that he doesn't understand narcissism because ironically, there's no way Trump would ever do that.
He feels proud of the vaccine for doing it.
So in order for him to change his mind on that, he would have to take an accomplishment away from himself.
Right.
Which would be one of the few things that he could say, like, I more or less saved millions of lives.
Exactly.
Yeah.
That's a legitimate thing that he obviously didn't do instead, like sentencing through his incompetence millions of people to death.
But it's still better than nothing.
Yeah, I guess.
Can't take away the vaccine's existence.
It happened under Operation Warp Speed, I suppose.
Yeah.
And I can understand why, even if you weren't a narcissist, why you wouldn't want to not be.
That one's kind of pretty good.
Unequivocally pretty good.
But then if you're a narcissist, it's going to be like trying to get a ball away from a dope.
No.
Can you imagine? Actually, sometimes it's not that hard.
Well, I mean, I'm talking about like, imagine if Richard Linkl, if Alex had to be like, I hated the movies that I was in, that would never happen.
Or I hated my performance, or I hated what happened.
Shit on Link later.
No, I know he talks shit on Link later, but not on his movies.
He wouldn't be like, I sucked in that movie.
Yeah, probably not.
Yeah.
It's hard to say.
This is why you need to have a mentality of like, kill your darlings.
That kind of mentality.
Whatever these idols are, you tear them down.
If you like something, get rid of it.
Right.
Yeah.
You can't sit around and think about how great it was that you made that vaccine.
Eyes ahead, eyes ahead.
Burn the boats behind you.
Right.
You have to lick a toad and go out to the woods and break a copy of Waking Life.
Ceremonially.
Whatever you got to do, man.
Spirit journey.
Yeah, but I think that there is a way you make an interesting point.
I'm trying to find this sort of angle of how you could appeal to a narcissist to get them to become antivaxx.
Right.
And I guess it really comes down to what you want, what that person wants.
If they're out for money or power or something, you could make an argument that there's more money in power on this side.
True.
But it does still run up against the disowning your own achievement.
I mean, yeah.
That seems like the rock in a hard place kind of situation.
Here's my end.
The way that Alex is presenting this is like you admit you were wrong.
Yes, exactly.
That's not going to happen.
It's going to be a tough no here's what you do, all right? You get on a plane with him, all right? Hook them up to a machine that allows you to go inside his dreams, all right? You play Genal Rhian regret noir, all right? Then you go another level deep inside of his dream.
Are you following me here? I think so.
Okay.
Now, here's the crazy part.
You have to have somebody build mazes for you.
Why? Don't ask questions.
Now, let me ask you this.
What's that? Can I bring a top? Yeah.
Okay.
I'm in.
Let's go.
All right.
So Steve leaves, and Alex talks to that other antivax guy who I was fighting.
Sleep.
Sure.
It's mostly about actuaries.
Yes.
I'd rather rewatch inception than that.
Yeah.
So, after that, Alex sits down and wants to talk a little business.
A little bitcoin business.
Oh, no.
That Bitcoin donation that he got.
Okay.
And I wish I knew how tired of the situation was the last few years.
I knew it was bad, but I got lack of days ago.
I didn't focus on things.
I didn't focus on bringing in money.
We almost went.
Really? That's what you said? In bankruptcy.
But if we hadn't gotten that $8 million donation in Bitcoin by the time we cashed out a little bit less than 8 million when it came in, it was like $9 million.
But I waited to see if it would go up and went down, whoever that person, diamond Hanson.
Because I didn't know we weren't $3 million behind.
We were $6 million behind.
We were insolvent.
My accountant told me right after we paid off the debts of 6 million and we bought $2 million a product.
Oh, my God.
It's not coming in.
That if we are good stewards of that, we can continue to be on air.
You talk about God working in mysterious ways if you don't know there's a God, who is this unknown donor that literally knew my finances better than me and gave us exactly the amount that we played the cards? Exactly right.
But that's how God works.
I wonder if Alex understands how much more suspicious that makes the donation.
I mean, good God.
I know.
It's God or whatever, but in the real world, this sounds like a fucking shady deal.
Yeah.
Also, based on his telling of things, it would seem that Alex doesn't qualify for bankruptcy.
If he was $6 million in the hole and then he paid it off with that divine donation, on what grounds is he declaring bankruptcy? No, they're solvent now, so he's declaring bankruptcy.
Wait, hold on.
What? That seems odd.
Yes.
This is some real televangelist shit right here.
This is like the most amazing well, to be fair, this is something that Alex does from time to time.
Oh, no.
Money bombs always make exactly what he needs because it's God's will and what have you.
That's the shit that the televangelist can do.
I have two private jets, but they gave me just the exact amount of money that I piss out on a daily basis.
That keeps us going.
It's fun.
So look, all this money that Alex wants you to give him sure.
He doesn't need it.
I'm sorry, what? He could start a podcast tomorrow.
He should have focused more on making money is what he just said.
No, now he's going to say that he doesn't need money, but he does.
But not for him.
Okay, I got you.
And we're still here.
And they can't stand it.
They have big show trials, thousands of articles, hundreds of TV programs that's conservatively.
Thousands.
Conservative programs.
Hundreds of thousands of articles.
Thousands of articles.
And now you've seen it.
But they're going to invade a country lying about us, just attain a jury to try to win a lawsuit to shut us down.
They're not going to shut anything down.
I can walk across the street and fire up a podcast that reaches the same amount of people today.
But you won't have the Derek Mcgreens and the Greg Reese's and all these incredible Adon Salazar's and the Kit Daniels and everybody else that writes the articles and reports and does all this other amazing stuff.
We don't want them to shut us down or slow us down any level.
And you can end their power over us right now.
You can shut their asses down by financially supporting us@infoworkstore.com.
You can help me allude consequences right now.
Yeah, I don't know if it's a good sales pitch to be like, what about Darren Mcbreed? Yeah, no, I mean, won't somebody think of the Darren Mcbridge's? It's tough to think about what would happen to them if infowars would go away.
I saw that some outlet tracked down one of the jurors and talk to them about that.
I really feel like an interesting piece would be showing one of the jurors.
Or if you could all of the jurors like these videos afterwards and seeing how they would feel about their judgment, then that would be a really interesting thing.
Yeah.
I wonder if they'd be like, oh, I'd go much larger.
Yeah, I wonder if they would listen to this and be like, wow, we should have known all of this.
But I also wonder how much of it is like the distinction between the actual damages and the punitive damages.
Right.
I wonder if that would be swayed by him just being a total shithead.
Yeah, I imagine that they came to the compensatory damages based on, like, math and shit.
And then if they knew that the punitive damages would come out to Alex as being like, they're not going to do fuck all to us and we've destroyed them.
Punitive damages don't exist.
If the punishment is then equalled out by the guys saying, fuck, you didn't mean anything, that's not really punitive then, is it? Not really.
Right.
But if there are caps in Texas, then I don't know what you can do.
I don't know.
It's a mess.
Texas justice.
Also, Alex couldn't start a podcast tomorrow and get as many listeners because he's kicked off itunes.
It's going to be tough.
I don't think Spotify is going to really go for you either.
No, because even the episodes of Rogan with him all day, they're not going to give you your own show after getting rid of their most popular podcaster.
You could go to Stitcher.
Yeah, well, maybe.
Anyway, the show ends with a protracted bizarre sales pitch.
Get DNA force, get Bodies, get our great immune support, get Ultra Twelve.
Get X Two.
The supermodel vitality finally back in stock.
And know that you are literally in an arm wrestling contest with Satan.
And all I am is the arm.
What infowars is the arm? What? I got a strong arm and a strong will, but the power to hold it in position is you.
So when I'm struggling, you're struggling.
When I'm in combat with these people and they're doing everything they can, it's much easier to just stop sitting here at a stalemate with them and for you to just to get behind us.
Pray tonight for us, pray tomorrow for us, spread the word about us, buy the products.
And I'm telling you, we're going to slam their hand down.
We're going to beat their ass and smell nothing but victory.
I'm not a victory, but the spirit I got right here is victory.
And I have never felt better.
I have never felt stronger because of you.
Because God works through souls and done it.
And you've done incredible things through our lives together.
Think about it.
We're the number one enemy.
We're who the enemy hates more than anybody.
Why is that? Because I'm real and you're real.
And together we create an energy loop.
What? A synergy and an amplifying network of goodness.
I thought you were in our they want to shut down the churches during lockdown.
What? We're good people coming together and we're doing it now together.
So go infowarstore.com and get great products.
Sign up for auto 10% off.
What a ride.
I feel like he just watched over the Top last night and then just went off from there.
He was like, I've got this arm wrestling thing.
I'm the arm.
That doesn't make sense.
They're the body.
All right, we're doing this.
We're back mate with the devil.
We're back now we're at a stalemate.
And now we're all just energy.
We're feeding off of each other.
We're synergy.
Not even just energy.
We're an energy loop.
We're an energy loop because I'm real.
You're real.
Why is that matter? Well, when this hand wrestling arm wrestling contest, I feel like the arm wrestling got lost there at the end.
It was just a conduit with which he could ask you for money, but he doesn't need it.
But I want to win the arm wrestling contest now.
Would you leave kate Daniels high and dry in an arm wrestling.
I wouldn't want him to feel that kind of alone.
The guy who is so talented, famed somebody and then cried in a deposition about it weren't for Kit, I would say we don't need to give info or money.
But now that I know that it's for Kit and what do you think about Greg Reese? I've never thought about Greg Reese.
It's not healthy too.
No, it's a bad idea.
So we come to the end of this and I don't think we learned all that much about Dugan's daughter.
I found myself to be underwhelmed by his coverage and a lot of it was just about himself.
And why can't I do false flag stuff when they can? Right? A lot of that stuff.
I always appreciate our episodes that start with a topic and then end with you having to remind me what it was.
The topic was happens more than it should.
It really happens a lot.
It doesn't happen as often as people collapsing at podiums on live TV.
And that's happening all the time.
All the time.
It's nuts.
So anyway, I like that jazz.
I wonder if that will be a new feature in the show.
I wonder if that's a sign of, like, GCN just giving up elevator music from now on.
Yeah, I could start an elevator music podcast across the street tomorrow from iPad Goes Walking and Wench.
Look, we'll be back, but tell them we have a website.
Indeed we do.
It's Alexfight.com.
Yeah.
We're also on Twitter.
We are Twitter at that dollarjungscore fights.
We will be back, but until then, I'm Leo.
I'm Leo.
I'm dzx Clark.
I'm wilford snippet snabbl of the Gripple PIBBLE.
And now here comes the sex robot.
Andy in Kansas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.