Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Exit
Alex Jones
Indeed we are.
Foria
I might catch some heat
Take maybe I don't know
Alright of course the
Do my cats
Course
Something that I realize I realize I do
I hadn't realized it but I really enjoy it
And that is like if I ever have a knife in my hand I like to threaten to leave with it
The holder it LifePoint alright alright
Obviously
Obviously also I should say I'm not close
To her it's up to her
Hold their hand up and then fall over going
Cool it's very cool to see it it's like a game
A game nor is it fun to see there is a little bit of
It's just for me really
Amount of course I give her some Pat
Send
Got some attention.
End end sweetness after
Two words.
It is
Bruchis not fret
Better now that your roommate is only a cat because when you used to do that to your other roommate that was a little bit of a difficult order
Halloween
My bright spot is your dog
Pulling up to you right now
Anime cyberpunk edgerunner so I downloaded the game Sacramento
377 is a very fun
Enjoyable game that's my bright spot
Yeah you told me to
Give it a shot
I'm a little I'm not very far in the game at this point
I like running around
The space I don't know anything that's going on I did
Find like an abandoned motel and I felt really excited that I could wander around in
I don't know if that's part of a later Mission or something
I was just digging through trash and I enjoyed
I'm not very far to do it either and there was a moment earlier on where they were treating my character like
This is the best
And I was like man I have not done s*** I don't know what you guys are talking about
Yeah thank you
Put some respect on my name I appreciate that but
Yeah so good times
Jordan
Today we have an episode
To do and I have a little question
The answer is
34 no does Alex Jones
The Aerosmith song rag doll have in common
Are they there
Still on Hiatus note they can both be found on Permanent Vacation
That was where radiohead's album
Different directions but alright
Alex
Is on vacation
Difficult position
We have these
Deposition
The course from that obviously but
Some of that is a little bit to time-intensive and secondarily I don't want to put out
Back-to-back-to-back there's a real out of depositions
Left us in a position where we were able to recoup a little bit
Take a note
Do nurse
Ourselves back to health our psychic
Wounds
But here we are it's Wednesday so what I've decided
I want to go back to the past
Google an unfortunately this episode will prove me to be a witch
Okay
I'm sick of your Witcher 2.
You have no idea
DIA
Alright
Who's going to be our first episode where we just play the Clips in order and then at the end I go
Really that's crazy when I was like preparing this episode I
More than once I said come on
Smokey Bear
It would be more fun if if Neo in The Matrix had taken the red pill but just remembered everything was like
All day
Huh anyway we'll get down to this before we do Jordyn Taylor
Do first
Mark 9
Shot March 9th
Thank you so much right now by Lizzie Wang
Thank you very much ladies thank you so much
This baby poorly-timed
But Melissa
At all lonely walk celebrate our Mass anniversary
Ever coming together on the Facebook group egg is what you and I about
Coming from the outer regions of the universe
80 and Jordan 8
Thank you very much
We got a technocrat
Soy Luna bear LG TV
Yarn Iowa technocrat
I'm a policy wonk I have
Risen above
My enemies
Go take a little break now
A little breaking for me
And then we're going to
Comeback
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty work for you
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She rode in on
All your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
I apologize to the
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
We'll never know if now better today or not
So that's true
No certainly.
So today we're talking about August 13th
The
No update
Whether or not to Alex's chronology they are being
Put in power rack Asda pacification is out there are developments Alex still believes
Hussain son still alive
I have not gotten an update on that say yes I do
And continuity on Alex's show yes that is still great
Murdered in a ritual sacrifice true
But one of the biggest dangling threads
And that went by that I mean the most muscley
Is Arnold Schwarzenegger
Doesn't want to talk about
He did not want to talk about absolutely
He doesn't
W
The media is making him talk about Arnold Schwarzenegger absolutely and so he died
Quite a bit
Information
I'm around the world
You going over there
Curaleaf
Break
About
The whole
Amor
Reaper
Because it is
Bryant
Diversion
From
I all the real
Preparing
Are you portable
So you see there
First of all this presentation was forced to talk about all sorts of a ridiculous
List of
Complaints a lot of that stuff sounds exactly like what you would hear nowadays he's for abortion
But
The focus is on
Homosexuals
At this point
It's 2003.
And this is where it is appropriate for Alex to attack
You viewed the gay community as
Vulnerable enough
For him to bully
At this point yeah which change
Yeah yeah
You do I feel like a lot of us
After so much time
You know passed this we all kind of
Thought well
I guess
Our parents in Denver
Religions and all kind of like
Moved past
The whole gay thing you know they would they would like
Well
People did marriage marriage is happening and yet
Nobody's being murdered by God all day everyday so we're probably good and now we live in a moment where we re
Realize that those
23 2000
2003 thoughts
Just got quieter
No no it was
People realize
Bad they couldn't
Express these things in public anymore with the opinions did not change
Nothing whatsoever in In fairness maybe there is some subsection that
Some population that did evolve in there
And realize I called
Maybe they don't need to hold on to
There is it wasn't the massive sea change necessarily
Let it appear to be based on
Yeah and that complacency I think is Maybe
A problem yeah yeah
So I was thinking about like what is going on
With this this Arnold stuff
Because it's so it's incest
Fan
I realized on this episode
Alex was
Very much talking about Arnold
Specifically in the context of Mel Gibbs
And I kind of came to realize
That it was
Cuz
Mel Gibson's getting Heat
For Passion of the Christ and his family's anti-Semitic
Alex is trying to attack Arnold
Do cover
Call Gibbs
Did Mel change his name to ye recently or was it
No no
No are you sure
No they're very similar
Who was the we'll talk about this here a little bit later
Cars
Call Tanner
This is amazing
Salesman
Tamara
World War
So a lot of this around essentially the Simon wiesenthal Center
Of Mel Gibson's film
Right I am the
Gibson family simultaneously endorsing
Arnold that's basically we're all this is rooted
It's pretty clear the game Alex is playing in the reason he asked
The cover of the startled even though he doesn't
Hey is just
He loves Mel and hunting Gibson and the two of them are very clear anti-semites
Mel's new film The Passion of the Christ is getting flak
For being anti-semitic Allentown
Simultaneously Arnold is running for governor of California and he said some stuff about Hitler in the mid-70s that's been taken out of context
Text SA officer in occupied Austria
So this is the way that Alex is going to take some heat out
Off of his actual
Asthmatic
Right right alright
Obviously it's not
Good for your dad to be a Nazi
But that doesn't make you enough
What's ironic about this
Almost
More than anything I can think of
Is Mel Gibson's dad
Allied powers
Schwarzenegger's dad
Axis powers
Mel Gibson
Axis power
Allied Power do you see where I'm coming from here to generation
Obviously like you would ideally it if I had to choose all possible fathers
Nazi would not be watched on the comment
Hitler's oratory skills when you're a youth but that doesn't make you a Nazi either
Call the flipside Marilyn Hutton Gibson personally engaged in explicit anti-semitic actor
Concluding Holocaust denial and revisionism
Alex node
If Mel decided to speak out against Trump in early 2016 mysteriously become aware of all this s***
Used it to attack him but here we are in 2003 and Alex's smearing Arnold just because he needs to carry water
Where is Father and Son big attacked
Apparently we'll talk
It's it's
So clear that Arnold is only interesting to Allie
Flexing as much as
Like he can use it to deflect from LA
Right he's a he's a
Bye-bye bigotry barrier
He is he's the police
Shield of bear of big
Make a tree or whatever into like
On the last show.
Please just give me a reason to Alexa I'm not just
Making this up every time I want to defend anti-semites
I have to be like
I don't want to do that I want to make fun of Mel Gibson Arnold Schwarzenegger come on man
So Alex has Joyce Riley on his another host apparently on his Network
Complain a little bit about Arnold
America
Simon wiesenthal Center
No it is all hypocrisy
But it's all delusion it is all a fraud
That's why I don't get as angry as I used to because I see through it now
It's all good fun and it's further enough
The theme of the day which seems to be that Alex is mad that people are calling while Gibson anti-semitic but not Arnel
Alex wants to wear as Gibson is a zealot extremist whose father is parent
Only friends with Alex or Alex
Edward saying for accurate accusations of him being a bigot
I wanted to play this because it shows a very intentional misdirection by Joyce and Alex
They say that the Simon wiesenthal Centre found that Arnold's father was a Nazi and that is true
But they're purple
Omitting some information that Their audience
It would benefit from having
The first thing isn't Arnold requested they investigate his father's background
He was not in any way trying to hide from the the pastor the reality of his father's bad.
The second thing is that the center wasn't necessarily setting out to determine if his dad was involved in the Nazi party
That was all pretty much
Understood in
Definitively known right
Arnold saw his dad's uniform
I'm scrolling up you get the
Yeah they were tasked with poring over records from the Holocaust in determining if the specific groups that Arnold's father was a
The member of had any recorded history of committing crimes against humanity or similar across rice
Is my dad a Nazi Arnold's like was my dad is super genocider or just like onboard with them I'm guessing it also
I was like how how much of a microwave
The result of the investigation was that there is no such record
The consensus seems to be that there is no affirmative evidence of him committed war crimes
But war records are also in Perth
So we can't be fully ruled out
Whatever the case be sins of the father are not necessarily appropriate to take out on the sun and it's dumb
I did or didn't do in WWII Arnold's fault
Joyce and Alex say that the investigation found that his dad was a Nazi but they don't include the other day
Details because that would hurt their point
This isn't intentional choice
The stuff about admiring Hitler's taken out of context and Arnold has successfully sued people for making these kinds of claims
The past
There's nothing but Kurt Waldheim is fair enough but with Alex's referring to is a toast that Arnold gave it his wedding
Hey 1986
At that point there's no reason to think that Arnold would have known about Walt
Of All Times lies about his actions in World War II
Since reporting about that didn't start until that year
And accusations of his involvement in war crimes
Didn't happen until 1987
There's a lot of shadiness
That is fair to say
But what Alex is doing is a shameful mischaracterization of a person
And he's doing it specifically to distract from his clearly anti-semitic friend yeah
It's very strange
I mean not strange at all
What I find very boring about Nazis is that every Nazi has at one point
In time been like
You know you got to admire Hitler for blank
Right but then they've also always been at one point been like
Hey did you see this person they said Hitler was good for black
Yeah you know like Alex is Hitler's complete matters it's every one of them if done
Every single one of them have done it but I also think
That a lot of people in their youth
I have said things that were like
Hitler was a great speaker
Very able to get
People to follow him music
You know in that sense he had great leadership a lot of folks who may be
You.
What about history
It feels transgressive
Bold statement that no one has thought of
Before
Arnold making statements like that in his youth
I don't really think
Is indicative of
Him being an author
So far Arnold
Not enough
Also I'm not sitting here to like
Fully defined Arnold Schwarzenegger
This dude is bullshiting of all the criticisms that I have Arnold Schwarzenegger none of them are heat
Enough
So Alex is always right about everything
Except for everything
Here's an example of something is not right about
And it's also going to be a medical draft and it's Medical
People learn about this
I think you're going to see a real change of heart hair
Southtown
Program
Are all
Commercial Drive
Rock
German
Oh man we got ice cream truck snitches
Yep I love I love whatever
Alex's collars
Bring up
The reason no apology
Do whatever they bring up
On their own the reason why something won't happen
As evidence for what will happen after it does you know like there's a grown-up people won't stand for it
Is it a draft for people to not to go along with it
I don't think doctors and stuff will go along with it that's why they won't do with it
What are you talkin about a course they won't go along with it
But what you can do is force ice cream
Truck drivers to snitch
Constitution
Yeah so every commercial driver
Every
Driver Long Haul
They all were enlisted
Irene well if they do have the infrastructure to communicate with
Beach other over vast distance
Speedo
Yeah there is that
They don't use that to solve crimes
Driving you're just listen to the radio maybe if you were also solving crime
I see a jaywalker on my six
Moving to run him over thank you thank you
Permission to use lethal Force
Alex has some new stories
It's quite a quite a rundown
Are denied bail
Wheeler please gilding
Arraignment
People who
What is the Chinese government
So weird strange low-stakes story for hooks to be covering
The guy who got charged with a misdemeanor for stockpiling gunpowder unsafely
Which I understand does touch on top of the Second Amendment absolutism but it seems like small potatoes
Play poke around and found out that this was the case of 61 year old Maryland man to level wheeler
As it turns out in this state is it illegal to have more than 5 lb of smokeless gunpowder and also illegal
The story of anything other than its original
Container cuz it's been credibly unsafe
Chanel
Particularly unsafe it is
Are you sure you could blow up your house
But also week
Could affect your neighbor
But just you
Wheeler was storing this s***
Container
It's a little bit over the limit
Is
What do
Why when does the cop showed up
Officers literature from the National Alliance Group based in West Virginia and told them
Race war was coming
Wheeler claimed he wasn't a Nazi or anything but that his wife was a member of the National Alliance
It hosted a radio show called quote
Grandmother Elizabeth reading hour for white children
Quite a pretty name for a show
Do if I can get more
Details that put my job on the floor
Session of details that make me go.
Dreams about many of these stories that Alex covers are minor almost
Completely inconsequential stories
Involving people who are Nazis
Call so weird how Alex just ignores that part when he's covering the story
Super weird to imagine like what websites he's cruising to find this Story 2
I can't imagine this was breaking on the front page of CNN
But probably was pretty hot topic on Neo-Nazi message board
Yeah the guardian didn't cover it but Stormfront did is not a good way to start your show
So big bigger important got a touch on this news breakdown
Here's my problem
Here is my
Alright
If you do think there is a race war,
Still don't know how that much.
The gunpowder going to help you
Convert
Could
Yeah well I don't know
I don't know if I necessarily think
That this is a guy who has
Tactic
Sure do I understand overarching strategy is it is
Fully clear
He also claims that he doesn't remember telling the cops that
Yeah that makes sense
The lawyer said we don't remember what you said to the cops earlier
So yeah
Good story selection
If I had several more than one pound
Of gunpowder on me
Onahan
I would very strongly respect
Actually you have the right to remain silent you know like that would be my number one right that I'm thinking of
It's like we don't need to ask questions about that gunpowder
So we got another news story that Alex is covering
Just a little heads up in advance there's some racist language
Court-ordered
Flow
Another headline
Forward
Gulf oil
Call Mom
Robert that seems like a good solution
Okay
Alright Google Fullerton yeah
Yeah
So first things first this is happening in the UK so there are different speech laws there than they are
In the United
If Alex loves National sovereignty so much why the f*** is he trying to enforce his own code of rules on people in another country
Very weird
The story carries that Michael Guilfoyle made a bunch of abusive phone calls
Just trying to help with his rihousing app
Application
They complained about it in the Magistrate's court told him specifically that he
He can't use that word in public anymore
He's kicking his own home if he needs to but he will be in trouble if he uses it to harass or threaten people a
Again
There's no evidence that he got any jail time or punishment other than the city saying that you will be in trouble if he continues to use
Counselors to attack their employee
And I don't know I
If you attack somebody with anymore
Okay
I don't think we should be banned
Here's what I thought
Spears
It's for him right let's throw this out there
Alright
Maybe
We do a 10-year requiem
You know like 10 years
You can't
Say it and then at the end of 10 years if you still want to say it let's see how you feel about time with a sunset clause
We're not being in words we're just seeing if you still want to say it after 10 years of not wanting to say because guess what there are other
You can figure it out
10 years you'll be like you know what I didn't really need that word in the first place you know what I was going to guess
Find any more in depth
Stories about this I'm going to guess that the order itself was a broader and like
Don't f****** harass people
The work for the council estate you no like I bet it was that
Ratman also
If you use these f****** racist terms again
Automatically get you in trouble where I live
Stop making abusive phone calls also
Alex sees racism being criticized until he gets got up
Superhero abs
So he
Jordan 22
Share some really disgusting language on Alex
Give me a 2003
Aue school to call her for using the word damn
Attorney at this point
You better make
Terrifying to imagine this is required listening for homeschoolers
This is a family show
Homeschool curriculum
Wow
I don't know what he meant by the c word
Because I didn't hear a single really feel like if he was talking about
The c-word then there's only one see where that I think of meet me too but I didn't hear that and I don't know if it was
Who's cut out or something
He used slurs earlier he sure did
Yeah but that's where the bar is
Graham is
Wearing
Taking the lord's name in vain bad
Racial slurs
Who said those are bad
They're not in the Bible funny show now he looks
Crying and screams about how he wants his enemies damn to hell
Come on I have some respect for the homeschooler
Ridiculous
Of all the things that my history textbooks taught me that were incorrect
Which is a lot
I eat still better than listening to Infowars that's for f****** share
Yeah yeah
I can't imagine how lost you'd be if
This was something that was treated as like
Accurate when you're young
Yeah can you imagine a
Text book filled with just
Banal versions of Alex's insane conspiracy theories
I've kind of read some of them in terms of like JBS literature and stuff so maybe I can imagine it
It's boo
Water filters
Sauron
The guy from from
Berkey Sharecare
All we need to know if the non limerick
Guy that's all we need to know about him
In a bit I think he doesn't pop up until later cuz I was in like the 2009 stretch
Haven't heard those episode Alex has a soap the cow Bend Soap Company as a sponsor
And their owner Marty Schechter shows up
ENT
Clearly had something in his contract where Alex had to let him tell a dirty Limerick every time
She has a limerick
And it's dirty
What a wild thing to be your calling card but what are you going to do
What we remember it oh yeah I've heard
Think if you didn't do that I would remember the name Calvin so absolutely not
Absolutely
I don't think so
But
The water filter
Sponsor is on
Of course they're selling water filters to buy Alex
Also I have to lie to him a little
Now your lawyer
Privilege
Now is this for the State of California
Report
We talked about this already
This is not getting rid of
Client
Confidentiality or whatever
But you can see how it looks sort of gullible is
Yeah I mean it was immediately like Holyoke
All of those rights are gone
This is what I find so fascinating
Is it once Alex has an inch
He's going to take them by off
For sure he does
Oh they're also
Well that's real sweet
Somebody was
15 years ago
Stark raving mad
Well here we are 19 years later and you are Stark raving mad
Shark raving mad Forever by your math
24u 34 years
Abolished
The jury system
I like God no confidentiality
Really I really like his responses to what should be earth-shattering
Exactly like that's the whole Bedrock of society is falling apart well
Yeah
It's kind of indicative of how little I'm not seriously these people take their own information probably
If someone was like they're taking away people's right
82 jerries
I think the responsibility to the streets
We've let them take away a lot of s*** but, I think this is
A little bit dumb
I think that this guy Jim
Waterboy gym
Is a little bit too dumb
Read that David Walker
Call division
Anyway
David wilkerson's like a doomsday type
Preacher guy
Yeah
A map that he had a vision
Doubt
And
What was going to take
Place in America
Back in the
70s
And it just seems like
I picked up a cup
You're going reread it and I couldn't believe
It was just all like it
Ancient history
They would start working
Gay
Ministers
What does a
Should never happen
And
Blah blah blah over why
His stuff that he was but he wrote that book back in 90
Panda
And it's been about a year since I've read it
What I can tell you is that the
The stuff that he
Road in there that
You would
People would be getting
TV
And it was like
American way back then
Cable TV
Everyday stuff
What is in a house
I tell you I don't know where it is
Science fiction movie in
Movies about Atlantis
Yeah
A lot of Alex's stuff. Seemed like a science-fiction
What about his fears of that show where 10 year olds are in a house
Spell
That's a
Not
I don't know this marinating baby thing
I'm a fan of everything this guy believes he's make it how much is making that sound like it was some kind of way like British
This Fear Factor video
Anita Baker I mean he just kind of made it sound like they had the guy ate a baby
What was that a single was that a special
Was there a miniseries sickly season 6 episodes at the time a lot you know
I got my boo
Was it drew Hayes
Baby I don't know what this is
Distance to Steve Tilley
Also I mean like
VHS was invented in the 70s I don't know what kind of prophecies
Dropping down but
Hey what some of these some of these Trends might be things you could see coming here's what I'll say
After the Gutenberg Bible was pregnant
You know
It took
A week before p*** was printed
You know like
Come on man we don't need to we don't need to jump
Too far into the future to be like oh yeah people make born out of that nobody right in your house
So Alex take some calls
And of course he's been talking the whole lot
About
Mel Gibson and the Simon wiesenthal Center
Mel Gibson
He put his resources
He's trying to get a man
Lacrosse and here we sit
And we just talked about it like that.
Isn't it ridiculous
When we got
If your ring
Ford Road
Years ago
Internet
You're going to find
The thief thief
To the camera
Christopher Cross
Queen Isabella
Jail
Your call I got to go
Alex was totally on board with this guy that a great time talking about how the Simon wiesenthal Center is
Is Beatriz doing Mel Gibson wrong
Yeah that other colors like yeah you know that
About the international Jew
Oh man you know
At a certain point you just got to be like hey
Obviously I think this
But we don't want to
Obviously I have a
Keen awareness
Miss that most of my audience believes this and they think that I'm using coded language and that's why
Why they enjoy my show
But you can't make it too obvious on air because then everyone knows this isn't
F****** Nazi shop
Shouldn't be a thing that we all just know all the time
Like all of us across the world human shouldn't we all just be able to be like a
Guess what this one's a Nazi show
Cuz this time this happened
And that's all we need to know
19tv enough
Sure I mean that we don't have to stop there but yes
The rest of the show gets weird
So I will
Say that
We have
Kind of planned where the idea was that we do an episode on Monday
How about a video that
Been posted on video
It was a fourth hour of Alex's show hosted by guy named Royce White
Who is a failed
GOP candidate to unseat
Ilhan Omar in Minnesota
And kid has taken to sending Kanye in a way that is Maybe
A bad way
To defend him
He's doubling down on some of the things Kanye saying and labeling
Jews who doesn't like and it's very it's very troubling
The
Trends that you're seeing in the right-wing right now in particularly the way anti-Semitism is so on the right
And emboldened
Bye
Statements of Kanye's making
You see Nick Fuentes coming out and really really going hard
Thanks to
Some of the cover
I guess you get
Trump Kanye and his behaviors
And you see it on info
Cccd
A certain section
Of the content
Being
Denial of like it's talking about right
If you know and then you have another section of it that is like
No
Actually he's right
And it's not all whatever
And
You go back to
2003 in kind of hoping for a different tone and then have a caller who's bringing up the international Jew
Man
I think
I think the lesson that you take away from this world that I think
It is appropriate to take away from this
This is
Bike
This is what the show is
Yeah
Yep
And also that's over twenty years regardless of whether or not somebody continues talking about hating Jews
Boy they sure still do
I mean like if you go to the video of Royce White's 4th our appearance switch
I should just really Strife is on Alex
The show it's a fourth hour of his show
Just with a gastos
The comments on it are like
Finally somebody is saying this stuff
And you know that's what the callers who expressed things like this are thinking
Is there waiting for Alex to finally just bring up that s*** man
Bring up that stuff that was adopting propaganda
But what you going to do
Yeah I mean Nano
Anyway it'll get worse later but
For now Alex has some other news
He just wants to jump away from that be like what what does make you think
Some other other news
Dial 911
Chronicle
You're not do that
Cam
This is bulshit
Willie Brown wasn't told not
The fly that
It's a
Misconception on a bulshit thing a 9-11 truther
Here's how he described the call he got from his Security contact
Text that work at the airport
Not Condoleezza Rice
He said the kommineni alarming session which is why I'm hesitant to make an alarming
Bank statement
It wasn't an abnormal call I'm always concerned if my flight is going to be on time and they always alert me if I autumn
Be careful
I guess what
He was still going to fly that day
He didn't change his plans
He only didn't fly because it was an 8 a.m. flight out of San Francisco which is
After the Trade Center it already been hit
He was going other
You going to go to the airport using Waze
Waiting for his ride when he saw the news of the attack on TV
How does making s*** up
Because he's a liar likes to f*** with his audio
Also fun fact
The claim that the warning to Brown came from Condoleezza Rice traces back to a comment made by Holocaust denier
David Irving
Do it no proof or the clam and he's just making that s*** up
Weird how there's so much. They should on the show even back in 2000
Yeah yeah it is it is like
Man back-in-the-day a conspiracy could be built out of a thing that literally everyone who flies now gets
Like I get
10 days every 5
Is changed in a minute you get a text update
Annabelle
20 years ago holyshit Izakaya
It is interesting
On some level
You know like what exactly was the nature of the concern
That the people at the airport were expressing to Willie Brown
He clearly wasn't that severe because he was going to fly anyway
Freitag
I'm also if it was something that in indica
It was indicative
Foreknowledge of the attack
That's kind of dumb
Because the flight
Was taking off
After the attack happened
There is a robin's egg
It was going to happen it was going to happen
And he wouldn't have to be warned at all because ain't played would never take off
So none of this makes any sense
He built out of nothing
And the Condoleezza Rice aspect comes
From Holocaust
It is a coincidence really
And a dawn Salazar would say it doesn't drive
That's true all right buddy
Dumb people have that means we need to report on this
So Alex's mother news
It's pretty severe stuff
I had a
Q questions here
Pennsylvania
Criticizing
And where was that at
Wow unbelievable
Pecan stuff for whatever
Didn't arrest him
I can find the UK
Literally no evidence of the supposed
If I had the gas with Alex's talking about there have been cases where anti-lgbtq protesters
Have yelled Old Testament verses that have been used to argue like
Homophobia being a pillar of Christianity
Yeah Leviticus generally arrested or cited for
Further comments but for other protesting related infraction
Whatever the case it's
Just not true that you can't
Retrieval test
Smitten Pennsylvania
Yeah I mean you know
Whatever he's complaining about
Most of the people that wanted to are probably in Congress now
Now so you know
Like in addition to this
We are not see thread
You also have
This preoccupation with
Like
Sort of homosexual
Being opposed to homosexuality
In a way that I would
Pretend
Isn't part of his worldview now you know there is a I'm cool
I'm fine yeah I'm good I'm here
Move it
But you look back on this like no you're not see any way we're not obviously
Dealing with
I don't get anymore
Anti-Semitism is authorized to hate trans people that hate lgbtq plus people
These are just literal Nazis were dealing with Nazis now we know how to deal with Nazis we're dealing with Nazi
This is what we're dealing with stop pretending like we're not
So I like
Is another color
Yep
Listen to Scholars interesting
Okay the next
Is This Is Us on
Bahamasair
Sexual movement
And
Here is the
This information I have
April
There was
A bill presented
And evidently it pass
But this is what we need
Find out
The deal wasn't everyone get your pins out and write this
Do your homework
People
We need to buy
Find out about
But I think this is why they're being
So in our face
Putting all this it's HR 2431
And it was
Presented
The International Freedom
Some religious person
Fusion app
So this bill did pass
Became the international religious
Just Freedom Act of 1998
This caller thinks
Our lease is
But I imagine
But the bill is designed to
The gay people from religious persecution
Bruce actually about creating some governmental bodies that would monitor religious groups were being persecuted in other countries
An advocate on their behalf
This is really stupid stuff and I don't know why you would expect anything else on this show
It is 2000 35 years after this bill became law and she's not even sure if it pass
That's what I thought her angle was going to be it was about like protecting gay people from
Religious persecution but that you kept talking
And I would say that given a million gases
I would never have predicted that this was her
Conspiracy
But now
For example now that I'm reading
Some days food sample
If the practice of
Actuality becomes
Defined as a religion
Tenon group
Posing homework
Sexuality
Violating their religious rights
And then any other
Its members
The universe
Refined
Jail
Armani
Carolee off
Right
What
What do the conspiracy is that this
Bill
Is part of the gay agenda and then they're going to use this
And then later they're going to make being gay a religion
What
What's the deal cuz you know what
Here's my pitch
Let's do it
I'm down
Down for it I will develop a religion based entirely around homosexuality and then the government
Have to allow her everything to work
I think that's how it works perfectly
Whether or not you are going
To unsuccessfully do this
The year of Our Lord 2022
Two
This is some silly
Did not have
But no hits yet come to pass
Preoccupation
The fear of
People who
Another color
Trends are happening here
Yes I do
Datavideo police 83
Salute whether you serve good or evil
Very very good
Oh yeah it is wrong
Long hate Islam
We can call the Pervert
Hurtsboro
They get on TV everyday
Understand
Speaking out the truth
Doublethink is that
That's the sky
Call Alexandra long
United States Mark of quality
Right and
Apparently he's mad that people don't like kitty calls gay people
Perverts
Yeah yeah
Yeah you know it if you didn't know real view of some of this audience it feels it feels
It feels awful to know that 20 years has meant nothing
Yeah I'm useless
Pointless waste of 20 years
Text Cowboy
Well I wanted
Statesboro
Down. Two things
The Jewish people you know there
Kinds of Jews
I believe I used to have a paper ID
People all the time
The ones that
We need to be worried about are the
No one ever uses that word
They're still afraid
They will not stay communist youth
Why does Alex I mean obviously I know the answer to this
It's sort of rhetorical is Alex allow someone to keep talking after they say there are six kinds of Jews
Oh boy
Well I mean
What good is going to come out of the rest of the sentence okay so it was 2003 I think
Pokemon Gold had just been released pretty recently so you know he's like
You gotta catch em all
Right you got that on his brain and then she listened and he doesn't
The second part
Which I totally got you know
Rihanna
Sneasel
Set a Pokemon
II
Blown Away
Listening to this episode
Particularly like
You know we have this
Backdrop of in our present-day we have
You know
Kanye
Coming out and saying this horrible stuff
We have him being interviewed on Tucker Carlson.
Cutting out parts of it that make
Get to over
He said exactly that
Occupations of him making the rounds on tons
Other media places now
Drink Champs
Podcasts on Lex
Lex fridman
Piers Morgan interviewed him
Zone with Chris Cuomo
Yeah he's going around these places and more awful stuff
He's
Candace Owens has tricked him into buying parlor
Funny part about all of this
And then you have things that you see you like
Do you know people in Bolton buy it
You no going back
Back to the past and
I'm sitting in of seeing
And episode
That is so heavily
This
It's
Upsetting
Yes I do
I mean
We did a show
We did not believe
That Jews ran the world and some evil
Conspiracy
Right
We we do we do do a show where we don't believe that Jews Run the World
But we were also pitching a conspiracy around the world
We had a day where we had calls like this
It would be awake
It would be a be a crisis
It would be a moment of what am I putting out into the world
Sam's of mine
Keep doing
A.m.
19 years later
Alex still has not had to that
That moment
You got into reason why is because
He doesn't
Mind
This being his audience
This is already in CityWalk
Yeah I mean I think I've told this story before but like I was I was maybe
Three or four years into doing stand-up and I stopped
Doing a joke because
I found out after showing somebody told me about it that they were laughing at it for the
Complete wrong reason and I was like nope
This is done
Because that if that's what's funny about this
That's not what I meant for it to be funny
Right now if you need to keep telling the joke because
Too good that you need to
To find a way to retool it from the ground up
In a way where that interpretation can't be
Absolutely can't be derived from it
Alex still wants to do this new world order Illuminati s*** and do his show
He has a responsibility knowing that there is a heavily Nazi base
Among his audience
To present his information better
It's a failing of his ability
To present information that people
Constantly r
Quote unquote
Confused
If he wasn't enough
He isn't a failure it is.
Computers and he's doing exactly what he wanted to do right
But if he were to actually a Nazi
That would be a real shock
To the system
Now
This is been bad
So far
Yeah
Blown Away by what happened
Towards the end
End of this episode
Alex gets another call
Oh my God that is horrible Holocaust
Survivor
Now
I take this person at their word
Obviously well I mean you know a caller into a radio show
Experience
Obviously
We will believe that this is the
The truth
She also has some bad opinion
What's a
South
But
The reason that I find this fascinating
Is
Alex has a person on the line who's discussing their experience
Living through the Holocaust
Can't stop himself from using their experience
To push his little
Narrative
Who's and whose
Snarky b******* I would kind of say
Alex
The reason I'm calling my
It might cut my attention and was born and raised
In Germany I was born right into the second
World War
And what got my attention when you mentioned
Taking the children
Out of their family
Experienced another dad my grandmother when I was little
Behead us
Enough
Station
Train station in Alarcon
Because they were going to put us on the truck and haul ass off
He ended up taking us away anyway they went through a doctor and told my grandmother
Capable
Christopher Hart
Indeed
Listen to a home
Midnight
No I haven't noticed or here but I'm naked
Shorts during the night
Like
It scared us
And I haven't
I have no
The river
Take that back
Paradise kiss
And Arthur
For me I'm not
My grandmother
We had my grandmother had that Neighbors
Crossroads
And my grandmother told that woman he'd lyrics
Crazy
And she told my grandmother if you say that one more time I'm going to have
Against the wall
I mean I don't want to tell your grandmother
Presuming Alex
Believes her I would like
I don't understand how you can behave like that
Quite frankly someone is relaying their experience living through
Something atrocious
Something horrible
And
Not get his
And there at the end about like all criticizing Hitler means you are a Nazi
With his victims
Trying to use
This terrifying experience from This Woman's childhood as a way to enforce
Percy's argument against
Arnold Schwartz
It's bizarre
Yeah Yeah Yeahs y me one way you could take that is thank you for helping put things in perspective
Your grandmother's
Spoke out against a
Not to genocider and I just want to be a race
And it seems like now that I have
Heard your story I can recognize that I'm just erase
Like Hitler
Well it's
That's one way to go about it
I think that you kind of have a responsibility if
Like someone like this calls into your show
Your tone might want to change a little bit
I think that it's
Incredibly disrespectful that what he's essentially doing is trying to use her experience in the holler
Cost as a prop
AutoZone talkingpoi
That's there's there's nothing appropriate about that
Because it's a holocaust
Ifucking obviously but that's f***** up to do about any person's trauma
Yeah to exploited for your own bulshit life but it's all
So f***** up
About the Holocaust and it's on a show where we've already had a number of
Absolut gluten somebody's the international Jew
So yeah they talked a little bit more
When I was a little girl being taken away
For my grandmother's
Enter
I must have been maybe three and a half
What happened
The homework
We were put on this
Presents
The cardboard
Around their neck with her name on it
Instruct
Intuitive
My brother
Separated
It's time
Enter the phone
Pranks
Yeah I don't
I don't remember that that was
The doctor came in Denver
Taken away anyway
Oh my God anyway here
My grandmother knew my grandmother stood up
Citibank
You know
Protected us anyway she
Possibly can
Where's whatever
Grandmother
My grandmother passed
That's the way about the
Here's the field goal almost
20 nails
This is just hard
It's hard to listen to
Her relating her experience
I'm not entirely sure I can
Amtrak fully
What's going on
In the story
There's
Provocative images that
Certainly come out of what she saying but I don't know what the connective tissue is the like a Beat
Need to see it all
Time experience occurred between when she was like
So yeah you can expect
Collier
Absolutely
I just find it
Pensive
Basically the way Alex is
Is taking any details that connects to a talking point of his or a little riff of his
I mean I know Alex doesn't care because he's an anti-semite himself so he's like the Holocaust
Or whatever it is but it is it is like
That is not
Not okay
Even if it's even if you if he was at Arlington National Cemetery
He's not going to let 700R something like that you know it's going to be like
It is
It is quite
Crazy
There is the responsibilities you have is a call-in talk show host to
Seems a little bit of your presentation depending on the caller
Like for instance if a survivor of the Holocaust calls in when you're in the middle of a deeply
Anti-semitic show
Freeland.
I just
You have a little deference. Maybe make their experience about you and your own ideas
Spell be good
Similarly like if you have a caller who's a kid
Give responsibility to behave differently
Towards that because
The kid
And Alex doesn't do that he just exploited pretty much anybody who comes into his orbit
Even on foot
Jerry Springer
They treated Holocaust Survivors with a level of respect that the show had had not yet seen
I'm not going to evacuate I haven't seen that episode I don't know what you're talkin about
They did a great
Sure but it was better than that
It is
It's hard to be much worse
Close things out with the old news Rundown
Just touches back on the the Willie Brown issue
Long article on my website
And it says
Warren Willie Brown.
Dial 911
Mayor of Tampa
Grandpa
Why don't we at map
Not incredible
Chevron
I was managed ternary
What
It seems like
These aren't stories about Condoleezza Rice or Willie Brown
Involving
Foreknowledge of 9/11
It seems like those are both
Racist grievances of Alex's
Yeah those are the one
Yeah these are headlines about the two people but they are
Anything to do
With the story reporting to cover
Because there is a
Nope there's just racism
So wild
We come to the end
Yuck
Yak yak yak
Do you like to go back to the past
Ecstasy
Something of an oasis something of a
Break
Maybe something interesting that Alex was lying about thika dig into a little bit
But instead you see the present-day mirror
In many ways
Yep and it's
Yuck
So
Brutal
Rhoda
Sorry I mean I suppose my only closing. So none of these people have
Deplatform yay
And they're still doing it for money so
Yeah. Chris Cuomo f*** Piers Morgan Buck all the Fox News this is an interesting way that I learned the Chris
Cuomo has a show somewhere
It's the first amendment First Amendment
It's been like no we don't let this happen right
First Amendment to give a s*** about journalism before I give a f***
All of them
Call comes out like.
Yeah you show up on Infowars
Funeral later
But here's the problem that I that I foresee
I think that Kanye actually represents
A problem
For Alex
And that is
If he comes on the show Alex has the responsibility
You to argue with him about his antisymmetric views
If
If Alex is just
Hawking
About like an interview with
Piers Morgan
Qualms or whatever
Key cancer control that conversation because he can use whatever Clips he wants
Mexican Crema conversation whatever way you want Cher
AZ has
Kanye there
And he says s***
Can't stop him from seeing anything
I got the 5 Seconds
I think you talk to more than 5 Seconds
I think it represents a problem
Does Alex want have to
Sort of robot bat
Add stuff or else
He risks
You know basically
Being overly public about his actual brand
Until I think that Kanye is in a position where he probably would go on Infowars
But I was kind of
Can't let her
Yeah
Are you fake
Unfortunately
I was before I came in and we started recording I was in the alley and I saw the
Battered and bleeding body of irony
Because ye
Cannot be racist
On info
He can be racist on Fox News
He can be racist to everywhere
Put on Infowars he cannot be racist
He can go on all these other platforms and be like really extreme because they don't have a
Predominantly extreme audience trying to pretend
Isn't
Alex would like
People with
Nick Fuentes essentially took over the Alex Jones event
You'd have the audience be like
Finally Kanye's on and he's naming the enemy you know that kind of stuff
Yeah I know you don't want you don't want to make that two transparent
Yeah you don't to bring that into your space and risk
Whatever damage
Make a call to your
Again the plausible deniability
Yeah I mean I just feel like
Sooner or later
Alex is going to be like no one
And everybody who does care if I was in open anti-semite
They already hate me
And it's not like I'm going to lose anything by doing it I'm only going to game viewers
Going to be on there
But I also think that there's probably a part of it that Alex
Doesn't
See himself as that
So
I mean you know my fight back against
Sure
That being his is
Reality in his Public Image
Sprite
White Pass
That's the point where it makes sense
That does seem to be that does seem to be possible I just feel like these are going Max mask off
I'm 6 months anyways so it's like
Is it I mean a lot of them are now
We're going to turn around and you're going to be like I didn't know you were a nut saying there's going to be a lot
So I will be back
Another episode on Friday but until then Jordan we have website
No I'm Leo I'm the
Condo board manager of
Brain apartment 11
Alexandra Thurston color