Important
I have great respect for knowledge babe I'm sick of them posing as if
Knowledge fight
Joseline and
Just a little bit about Alex
Doordash
Heuser
What are you today
Is
To get a haircut
Since our last episode thank you
That is not the brakes
Bright spots
It's not bad looking at it
But
After
I got my haircut
They got to clean up the hair
Bright until I see this guy and he's sweeping
And then
He pulls out one of those caddy
The duster that's on the little stick
Look at this
I saw that and I thought to myself
I would love one of those
But you can
1:30
I can't tell you how many times.
Loud house
All the time
So for a moment I was like yeah that'd be great but then I realized I can do you can't
It's on the way I like it
Used to work in a movie theater and you know like it was always so much easier to clean the floors at the movie theater
Is it home and I realized that reason why
Is it is so awful to bend down with a dustpan info
Or it's a real hassle to like
Sweep up a pile and then get out the vacuum and vacuum
You have that.
On a stick on the swivel thing stuff
So I have
Reach the
Universal laws that those can only be at businesses
Considered one of the I have been bending down like a
Idiot with one of those triangle ass
What am I doing
We have simple machines all over the place I have a computer why do I fly to my music
Yeah
We both you know I have that
It's a date that I think there's probably a lot of people listening
Acknowledge that they had that exact same thought that you things are only allowed in business
I'm not well-off enough
How to get a robot
Whatever those are called to be around
Cleaning robot
Not in the cards
But
Just being honest
That's doable
Brightspot is the British
Game show only connect
So it's like a trivia show
But it's not an 8U you have to know an absurd amount of trivia
But
What's interesting about the game is that it's
About finding the
Connections
Between
Pillow give you like a
Declue and then they'll give you another clue and we'll have to figure out what
Connects all four of these
Things that so many people have towards
Making up connections you know our brains are wired to find connect
And even if they aren't there
It can be used for good
Weird strange things like they might play four songs and you be like oh in Greek these all start with an I like it
That kind of level of Yoda
Yeah how specific
Do you have to be to combine those things
And it just be like three pop songs
And the only it up
An insane person be like well obviously
You translate the title to Greek
I bet if you do that you can see that all four of these are the same thing duh that sounds like a fun show it's really interesting
To fill that hole of contraction master
Cool
To take care of
For you
What does Alec
Common with Audrey Hepburn
I'm going to go with Permanent Vacation he's on a Roman Holiday
Holiday though
Well I was either going to say that or Breakfast at Tiffany's so he's probably having breakfast somewhere
Yeah he's on navigation
Much like Jim jarmusch
In 1980
Better use that one in.
Privately
Chevy Chase
Somewhere around there
National
Baby
A good point
Are lawyers part of your family
Steven Hyde
Something
Infinitely frustrating about Alex
Stopping on airplane
I actually think it's the best thing for him and I don't
Big big picture and for the world I think it's exactly what needs to happen
Literally could not stop himself
From further defaming people involved in the Sandy Hook lawsuit
Could not stop himself from doing that at all
He clearly has a lot of
Nothing needs daycare with his lawyers Visa Avi the cases that have already happened the the Illusions about
Pele
The bankruptcy process all of this stuff
Julio
Requires a ton of attention
I mean he doesn't have a deep bench
There's not a lot of people that can
Can fill in
You can clearly see the drop-off in in viewership on Van. Video the episodes where Owen toast
It's unfortunate
Demonic
That are going to come
I know it is what needs to happen
And probably this is when you need a big-name signing
And you know this is like when Alex
Need to go out
And get I get you know like you can't get a star but get somebody on the rise
That has some of that
You know some of that
Cuz Owens not going to do
Here is actually I think probably where you regret not paying Rodger Stone during the downtime that's a good
That's a good point
Frank's speech and I think it is blast I heard I believe you streaming on Nick Fuentes platform couple damn
Yeah and snow
Is the devil
Stone could be the type of person that you maybe get to
Phelan hearing
Maybe he has enough cash
Text didn't do enough maintenance of their relationship and now he's
Gone off to other places
His primary
About home
Here's what we'll do
Okay
If I'm Alex
I'm throwing I'm throwing it to the Four Winds
And I'm sad
I will open the pocketbook for a stone pieczenik two-man show everyday
Flowers
I would actually I mean couldn't take the place of the alley
That a good show would be Norman Barnes
But only if they are
Actively and openly hate each other as much as they apparently did I would be good
The two of them yelling at each other
I think that could be
Before like one of those Sports argument shows but it's just the two of them and it's about
Their personal lives like they're just their grievances of towards each other yet
Comedy Workshop
I think it'd be fun
I'm just talkin about jokes as working on
So we could be fun
You've been reading a lot about Kanye lately
Fight the urge
But I can't engage
But it's no perfect timing
Insurance would be moments
We're well conservative would have come in handy
Norm sold
Kanye woke
Insurance
Norwood on parlor
That's how big of a claim he's got right there
So yeah we're in a situation where Alex is still out of Studio things to do
Let's say hello
Does new walk Melissa okay thank you so much and I apologize
Hunter is a party I'd husky
Thank you very much
Next the foundation to repair Alex Jones's daughters broke
Thank you very much just $0.30 a day you can send someone to a waterpark
I feel like there's just
An image of
T-Pain with no one fish
Fishing very moment now
This sunnex person gave me a phonetic spelling but it doesn't help
Let me ask you this how do you pronounce c h k a
Eh
Ka
Phonetically
I do appreciate
Happy anniversary I need to come
Samuel Fisher pleasant surprise Time Bomb thank you so much you are now policy wonk
Very much
So thank you so much to Joe from Oregon thinks Jordan and I are f****** amazing and I accept as well Aaron Copland
You are now a technocrat
Someone someone sodomites
Has a Caribbean
Little little
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much you sneaky snake
Did they force us to accept a compliment
I feel like that is
This is one of the
Ultimate the third rails of our show
It's it's konflict
Yes but thank you all the same
So Jordan it's come to my attention
That
No we talked a lot
About Alex
Path towards
Trump certainly read it number of episodes about it to the 2015 scratch
We never actually covered Trump's interview
On Alex's show
Alright I believe didn't wish it wasn't the rationale at the time like
It really wasn't that interesting
Wasn't as interesting
To the path
Supporting trop
The Pizza Co
And then
App that
Time on our show you had this standing policy of never listening to Trump
Voice
And so there was also a part of it that was like
I don't know I don't want to
Make Jordan listen to this yeah and so that was something that was never covered and
Why were there now 740i episodes
You know is Alice's on
It might be time
To look back
I think it's a great idea
That will say I turned off this episode
At a certain point
That's fair and that is because
There's a bit of b*******
Trump interview
There's mother Bull Shed
And then Alex is like I'm going to interview Lord monckton
And I said click
No thank you I'm not really all that interested in that weirdo
I mean it's just going to be like I'll climb
A change isn't real look at me I'm weird
Today that the UN has put out a report been like remember when we said 20-30 it's
Now tomorrow 30
Bye
Faster I don't want to hear somebody denied climate change you know how we said 20-30 that was actually military time
2 nights
Lord Montague and I'll go a parachute back into a un conference for publicity Scott
The f*** out of here but
We are going to take
Little bit
One of the things
It's really fun
Is that at the beginning of the episode
Alex
Will not say who the gas state
Okay I got a big d right all right
If you really prepared for the
Really worried about
Gremlin snafus
You don't want any G
No certain
Now he's so much worse than a regular snapper
You do want Gremlins to snafu
That's slightly funny
You want the Gremlins to commit snack food
They want you want their situation
Yeah it was normal
Spiders
So he's not saying who the interview is
We know
England
Alex dose
He spent so much time preparing
What could you possibly think of in terms of questions for Donna
Trump
In an hour that you wouldn't
Having 3 hours you know what I'm saying is not 3 hours of preparation preparation
But
Here's where things get a little bit
Shady
Pretty quick as it turns out
Or at least
Almost all of the headlines that Alex covers
In the lead-up
Two before the interview happens
Or about how great Rhonda course they are course there is one of them
Okay
So that Trump has
Vindicated on that spool get to that a little bit later but yeah that's one of the big news item
Being presented
Without the context of
Trump will be on later this just a new style my God
Saturday
The battery is almost like a winking Easter egg
Type thing while at the same time being so sycophantic that it is
Like
It hurts
Like it hurts
And it's not that's not the only headline Trump
Cheddar's restaurant
Trump is right yes you were wondering Trump is right about everything
Hahaha
Quite a setup
Yeah you know we got Trump is going to be coming on although you know this is
Isn't going to be
Sure
The
DD.
Metaphorically speaking
Is
Is what we're saying right here
Yeah and David Knight
Going to be hosting
The 4th hour
You better believe
We talkin about this interview
On the 4th hour we got to tease the fourth hour that will be talking about the interview that we're about to do
That's too crazy
Where you can audit
So we're doing this
To be explosive
Cool but also pisses preemptively it offensively navel-gazing
We haven't done the interview yet
But holyshit will we be covering the people responding to the interview that we're about to
Yeah you know
I mean
I feel like what we are
Listening to
Would if it were Trump being so
Foolish it
You know like
Fine I get it stop your window pull the windows down tell everybody to turn it down for get on the right there
Unless our context before
But because
This is Trump
I think what it is is so
Very clear
How these two
Know how to game the media
For their own
I mean it's just so obvious
Well point it's obvious and crafts but I mean to the point where Alex is already gone
The headlines
That they're going to write
You know like this is one of those few moments where
Trump and Alex both we're like it we're going to do this and then
You write the headlines before they're they're drop they're going to be what you think they're going to be at there's a media savviness
Do it there
Clearly indicating awareness
Yeah
It's like
I'm fascinated by the way that Alec seems to be reassuring the audience
That they will cover the coverage of Their Own
Yeah it's
Yeah no s***
Yeah we're not going to
But also
Shouldn't we be more
Interested in the interview itself
As opposed to
David Knight
Covering the backlash
Do the interview
I think I think
It would be a situation where if
If that was
The interview happening
On 911
David knightwood
Still cover the interview at 9.
Well it seems like they have equal measure
Right-to-die interview itself
And how people are going to respond
To the interview
I am prior to the interview happening at the
Yeah
Yeah but it is it is
Clear though that they're like
No one cares what we
We say
This is not about we're going to say something of any value
Real
Is your on this show
And by doing that we know what
People are going to respond
And it's going to be close
Yeah so Trump polls
And also all these headlines
Like I said
All just
This is
Maybe
Sketchy
When you know the Trump is about to come on the show and you're not disclosing that while you cover this as news
Yeah that seems like a folder
Disclosure kind of thing you need to
The I don't know I find
This to be a little weird
If we were talking about a real new show
If they were to
To do this
It would be
Disgrace
Well they might not have
Dimension like
Okay also this person
I'm coming up the interview would be advertised on tuning in would know that the person was going to be on the show
Because otherwise this feels like apropos of nothing here's all these great Trump headlines
That's
That's what
So clear about it though is again
They know that nothing about what they say is going to have a
What do we have to say we don't have words that makes sense
To each other
We're just going to go
At each other and then
What's important though is that people are going to say stuff about it
There is a little bit less than you think probably
To understanding of trump
A communication
And it is really
Libras are till I see this in 2015 like
Communicative
More coherently
Pinterest use a little bit all over the place still there's a speedy list
Negative thoughts and what have you put like
Compare to what you
See if he's Rally's now like
So little it's quite
Different hanging out being present it does take its toll on everybody
Yeah
It manifests in different ways
I'm so
The news has broken
Of Alex's interview
He's giving the
Exclusive
Do the Drudge Report
Because of course
Of course
Morgan
Drudgereport.com
Do you have the news of the interview is as important as the interview
It's very strange.
Yeah
I mean but that's
That's one of those things where
Iei you if it's so obvious what they want
I feel like I'm being tired
Media structure has to be like
No
You know everybody has to agree that this
This is just we're not going to be treated like this you know like
Because if they're going to
Sport you
So obviously they're going to say it on air before you do the thing that they're going to make you do right
Then f****** you or you're the loser years apart but to me that it is such a
Difficult line
Because like I know what you're saying but at the same time how do you not
Bring up that someone who is running for president was on
F****** Infowars
You know like how do you not cover that
It's the same thing like for us we're like Marjorie Taylor Greene was on
With Alex
They were joking around but she's obviously like
Ploy for attention and what have you brought
How do you not
Talkabouttd
Violently rhetorical
Member of Congress
Eaze
On Infowars
Regularity on Infowars
But yeah it's
It's there how do you
You talk about this stuff without playing into the game of giving them the attempt
I think so
Clearly are Desperately Seeking
Spratly seek
I'm not sure exactly what you do but you can do that
Don't think that
Coverage of Alex
I haven't Trump on this
Sincerely
Let's say that
As far as the past
Disconcern
No one's getting offline
You know like let's not worry too much about
Exact
Apportion
And let's just say that everything that happened over the past day 10 years
We all need to fix
Some s*** some get off later than others but
So Alex
Introduces Trump
That's a bit askisi
But if you pay attention
Feels a little bit like the way that Alex
Can talk about Trump is like guys
It's really about me
New York City
To be with you
Great
Yeah busy to talk about Trump
Achievement says they're also said only one way to say this guy's Gray
I'm great
And this is why I'm excited to talk to him cuz he reminds me of me
You like an old me do I not really
You know I really
We both pretend to be self-made and we both
Talk a lot of s*** both malignant narcissist
So we get too into this interview by talking about the ways in which Trump was Vindicated
You talked about the celebrations of 911 this comes up and it's just all
Load of s***
People wanted me to apologize and we can't
Braiding
Trump Vindicated in his claims and people booing at a soccer game or saying I'll Akbar has nothing to do with me
Volumes that he made so leave that aside it's a b Quintanilla
And if you want to say like during a moment of silence people shouldn't do anything
Then that's fine but
Making it a little bit Target
So what happened was
Completely inaccurate and then instead of admitting that he was wrong he pretended he'd made a completely different claim all the
He initially said quote I watched when the World Trade Center came tumbling down and I watched in Jersey City New Jersey
C worth thousands and thousands
The people were cheering
Has the building was coming down
Thousands of people were cheering
So something
Things going on we've got to find out what it is
A Washington Post article from around 9:11 does mention unverified claims a small amount of people allegedly celebrate
Waiting on a rooftop
But there's no video evidence of this ever happened
Reporters have estimated that it was maybe six
212 teenagers
Quote but
Even that is doubtful
So
That could be what is a video
Anyway at this point when I was interviewing him
The goalposts have completely moved
And Trump has declared that he would
Because someone
Find video of Palestinians celebrating in the ark
Occupied West Bank
This is not what company claimed people were saying he was making up
This is the state of things at this point and Trump is not at all vintage
Also Alex should be really against
Trump's idea of surveilling mosques
That seems wildly against out
The principles about freedom of religion in the Fourth Amendment but I guess
You don't really care about those
Think too much RAM
The group being targeted to someone of the
Do you have Trump
Essentially arguing for increased surveillance in a way that Alec
Alex Wood
The cry is
Tyranny in any other context
Giving any pushback
He's just right along with
You should have stayed up for hours
Stealing his a result
But to be able to push back in the service setting
You know it's like whatever I
Here
Trump speak
I feel like
What I'm what I'm experiencing is like
Best for a time-trap like
Here's what
Time traveler went back in time
Assad Trump
Talkin there was like well there's no reason to worry about this a****** fence guys
Is Nick clearly not going to cause problems he's just a moron
The everybody will be able to see through
Such clear b******* everyone
See through
Clear bulshit
It's transparent
Right but then he goes back to the future and it turns out Trump did everything they did so they let it stay
As a training a
Exercise for all future time traveler it was okay
Listen here's what you think
You think this guy can't hurt you
That's why we tired
F*** these Time Travelers man
What are they doing I don't know
I didn't start the agency bad
They need to go back in time and fix this
Training exercises go back in time
But update have to make another training
Exercise
Dido
So what
Do you think Trump thinks the number one problem is
Emigrate
Masonry Borders or something like that
People Muslims 10 blocks
Didn't want to say it
But you look at what's happening where we have a president served over there celebrating
Our number one problem we are number one problem
Number one
Just happened there
Appearance on Alex's show has to also be understood through the prism of trump was on a book sale
Campaign at this time
Is also a promotional stop
For him to push his
Does
Do his job
At a certain number of times brings up the book in order to try and sell it
I'm standing on the sidewalk and a Segway just slammed into me and knocked me to the ground and then I'm in the middle of the street that's what
Just happened there I pride myself on Segways
I sometimes
Do some pretty good work a knife
Not all of them like
No one's perfect
The number to process was unfortunate the freezing of that
I don't think I would be thrilled with
The alleged plans of Muslims to blow up our country is the number one problem in the problem is your book
That's the number to problem
Trump
So
Oh I'm sure he's at
This should also infuriate Alex
America we deserve and identity
Nasty
You better take him out
Naturally this is bulshit
Bin Laden was a well-known quantity by the time Trump put out this book in January 2000
Mostly because he was an international terrorist leader and he bombed the World Trade Center in 1993
Just pretend that he hadn't already bombed the same place
Trump's claim that he was a little-known figure is absurd
Also fact-check review Trump's book any didn't say any of this s*** in it
This is the only mention he makes a bin Laden
I'm in the entire book
Instead of one looming crisis hanging over us we face it bewildering series of smaller crisis
Flashpoint standoffs in hotspots
We're not playing the chess games and I'll chess games anymore
We're playing tournament chess
One master against many rides
One day we're all assuming that a rock is under control the UN inspectors have done their work everything's fine not to worry
The next day the bombings
Begin
One day we're told that shadowy figure with no fixed address named Osama bin Laden
US jet fighters lay waste to his camp in Afghanistan
He escapes back under some rock
And if you knew Cycles later
He's onto a new enemy and a new crisis
Fat pussies
Mentionables
Maybe
Lying about the contacts
Text another sin
I don't I don't understand
Fundamental
How human being
Could listen to
Someone as in
Insane is Trump
Say if people would listen to me
We would have stopped 9/11
And not go
Oh that guy's insane
I don't get it
I just don't
Understand anyway
That you could listen to that man
Say that he could have stopped 9/11 if everybody just listen to him
And think o
Insane person that needs to go away for a long time spoiler alert Nugent is on later.
Maybe she predict 911 tail but maybe he implies that he could have stopped at all costs
Okay alright these guys also
There's another problem here Beyond Trump has been full of s*** about his book
Alex should strongly disagree with Trump's prediction
Alex doesn't think the bin Laden was The Mastermind of 911 and if anything Trump make
Kind of prediction
Should be evidence that he was in on the attempt to set up Bin Laden as the villain after the globalist
Did 9/11
Of course none of this is addressed in Trump's ridiculous claim but nobody really knew Bin Laden wasn't 2000 goes on challenge
Because Alex
Isn't in the business of actually gauge
Anything that Trump says
And how it's clearly contradictory to
Who pretend worlds
DD amount of
Time
That
I have spent
Like
Not understanding why we don't
Continuously talk about how bin Laden
Hit the World Trade Center twice
Like that is the ultimate
Return to the scene of the crime
Situation do you know what I'm saying like
Enough
Like it you know it
It doesn't get more than that
And yet people are still like 911
Anytime
Any terrorism is ever happen
Eventbrite you know
Are we doing here sure
As party
The contextualizing of
Of the story
And it's also undercuts a lot of this like
How could anybody have
Possibly even talked about bin Laden
Yeah
But the reality is what it is exploding is that
It is fair enough to say that prior to 9/11 Osama Bin Laden wasn't necessarily a name that was on everybody's
Somebody who is a household name that everybody was talking
Sing about
The exploited
To claim that no one knew who he was or he was like
Obscure figure is
Ridiculous
That's a fun game
Alex brings up that Trump knows
This is good news today now in 2022
It's not really well
But there is something that does
It is probably a large part of the interview that I didn't cut his money clips of
From the Middle East oil fields
So people that he doesn't like can't make money office
32 years ago
Number one
And I will probably get along well with him
Recently
Find a tough cookie but
She'll probably get along with him or someone else will
Yeah
Answer answer is more important than Trump
Really was at that time
Obsessed with the idea of pillage
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
That's a real that's a real life
Oh you're a small boy
You're a very small boy if you think that
Viking times are the Pinnacle of civilization
Leave the premise of
The Iraq War
Ostensibly is that
You know you had this
Tyrant who was in power
Yeah and so we're helping
Overthrow the tyrant in order to bring
A democratic state
Into existence threat to Regional neighbors and the world stability of the whole
That mission is not served by stealing all of their resources right
That seems like
Something else
Counterfeit
Idea
And then
We will all have somewhere to ice skate
He would really Serve the People
To free from this dictatorship if we
Took their oil
You understand that the
What are you going to do turn Iraq into at the 51st state
You're like that's what we're going to do will your belongings real lack of
Concern for the actual people
Of course
Of the region
A little too obvious this plan there's only They're All Dead
Alex has some
Interesting points here one is that he believes the Trump is a manifestation of this war
What's going on behind the scene
Switch is the counter counter-coup
Steve pieczenik
Been talking about it this time
Which is very reminiscent
Proto Q qanon ideas that were going around
Even before the creation of that
Eyehole
Nothing
Whatever was Alex expresses this
The Trump is like
You know these people behind-the-scenes good people in government brought him into
To do this
Mission
But
There's another preoccupation
So Trump is preoccupied with stealing oil
Is preoccupied with
Please reassure me that you're not f****** around
Please just tell me that you're not going to Ross Perot this thing
And there's
A little bit of dodging of quest
What you're doing
I love I love
In Mobile Alabama 35,000 people in Oklahoma
Make America great again
And we can make
But we have to get going
Agreed with me on a rack I said
AOL
Cockroaches
The first election
For George Washington
Like it was pretty much
Not even a losing election for a vice-president but not really for the president
You're practically forced him to be president many times he was like
I don't know if I'm actually a president guy unless you're arguing
The John Adams being his vice president is the most important the most important election
Decide
I don't think the questions answered
You know like
Are you going to Ross Perot it
I haven't decided yet
I love these real
Spotify
I've enjoyed
This I could do other things
Certainly the ideas that I'm saying I believe are important
There's no reassurance
But Alex is looking for
It would be at would I would
Be interested to know if there was a moment where you could talk to Trump in
Like go back time travel wise one more time if there's a moment where you
You can talk to Trump in like
Early 2016 and just be like list
If you keep
Campaigning for president
You can do all of the Rally's
All the time everyone will give you all the Adoration that you want
Right but if you become president
Inside that room
Ya Romance
You don't get adoration people people are going
Be even more critical of the pig
The people around you are going to think you're a child
If you keep doing rallies
Could talk s*** talkingshit
Cuz that's what he wanted
That's what he's always wanted
I don't know how you would do that
Necessarily
Like Perpetual campaign
But you got me mad face
I am not good at this job thing
I like it when people scream my name
If only there was some sort of a middle ground
We could have reached where you could have all pretended that you want
Absolutely
Assurance he was looking for on the pro question
And so he tries to do it again
Author Rodger
New York
I know you're
Omigod omigod
Wasn't quite a reassurance either
Alex is really desperately just trying to be like
Just play
Please like this
Stumbling blocks for the audience
The audience
It when I say
Someday
Tractors have said this
I'm sitting at this is one
The criticism
In order to get them over that hurdle
Yeah I mean we already
Listen Alex
Here's what
Okay when you're a billionaire
If I want something then I go to a politician and I pay them
To give it
Of course of course I'm a guy I am an oligarch I meant above politics
I just want to kill all of you
Like that
Has asthma
German
I did business
I got to do the business hours and like I have to f*** with these people in all of us just go well then the system should
Stop
Is this
Great point should maybe put back-on based on his worldview
Is just a acceptable
Unbelievable
Because
Argument
Alex is like alright
You're not answering this question let me go ahead
Finish it off for you I'm going to the question for you now also I stayed up for 3 hours
I wanted to question that I came up with
Who's your favorite person
Who's your favorite
Most obvious question
Are you considering as a running mate also wrote down
Sandwiches
Yay or nay or outside the bread
Outside in the bread on the inside sandwich or not
Billboard
Extensive debate
Good question
Chili soup
What's the cold soup called
Bouillabaisse
Gazpacho
Disgusting
So we get to know answer on the question of the running
Make sure you get some rambling around
And then we learned about the favorite present
Skip you're here probably maybe respond
So I would
Okay cuz Alice's response
To the answer of who's your favorite President
Is
Shocking
Okay
What's going on
Make America great again
Alex thinks the Reagan's a secret communist I was going to say once it's not like
Alright buddy
That is
I overheard Alex talk about so many presidents and not once
Has he been like you know Reagan was
Who's the best president
I understand
Certainly has probably grown and appreciation for Reagan
In the last
B
But yeah that's not
Inline with Alex's
Sort of regular consistent
View view Reagan as being the the
Terminator 2 of ending the New Deal
Then I suppose you would grow in appreciation for him as the New Deal continues to disappear
Get out
Riggins only
Gaming in popularity as we all discover that he
He's dismantled the entire country from the top down
Sprout
It's a great answer for Trump I guess I mean
Sort of
In line with Obama
What year
Expect from Trump
So it's
But for Alex
Poop
That's not okay
No
No no no no
Give me the favorite present
Eisenhower now you can't be like you can't what
Well I like that speech
No but I mean you can talk to the guy at the center of all that never
He's also a secret
All of them are present
So Alex it turns out
The pastor Trump is
Complicated
As we discovered there were a lot of
Clear influences
A lot of Steve pieczenik influence a lot of Rogers
But there was one that we didn't account for and that is Alex's
13 year olds
Sunrise
Who
I would say
F****** book report that was never finished
My favorite song you got to go with Pride and Prejudice that's classic contact book
You look at president to look at Lincoln and Washington
Someone coach today Jefferson Davis
Like that
That inspires absolutely no confidence in somebody having opinions about
There are feelings
Totally like you don't know anything about
American history whatsoever beyond the lore that you make up in your own
Probably hoping you would say Andrew Jackson
Yeah that would be the one that makes the most sense if they're identical
Browsers begging him not to
To say Woodrow Wilson
The one that made black people hide in the White House that one is that what no no can't do that one
The classic
6 go with the classic
Take a little moment
Here
To say thank you
To a special person
Donation letter
Loyal and do wonderful n
The one you really want me to do this
Good morning
Well people are cookies
Cookies
Yeah it's okay yeah Rodger
I'm disappointed in all of
On a regular basis
Just because it appears that the only thing we really want
Really want
And we'll reward
Politician
Is the ability to say nothing for a
A long time
Sure like we love it when you can say
0 hours hours
Absolutely nothing you said you better cut out a fair amount of him saying we should bomb oil fields
That's that what we talked about
6 a.m. Bank in Rodger Rodger
Raisins
He was more a
A visor for dictators
So there was where the interview end
And
There's some threesome Dynamics here
The first is that
This clip will include the only thing that people remember this interview which is
Trump saying your reputation
I will be talking about you
In the future which
Never happen again
At least publicly
But
There's also
At before we get to that
Trump says essentially something along the lines of like
If I don't win I don't care
This will make
America great thing is
Who is wonderful and write that rhetoric
I'm going to watch TV I'll give a s*** I call you I'm not going to make America great
Like somebody who is got
Civic
You know what I don't know what I would say
Number one
Because we
Watching television
It's doing that
Doing great
I remember that interview
Yeah it's so there is its
Tony this is a little strange
Yeah
Definitely
A willingness to engage with any kind of
Attempts to make America better unless it involves me winning this president
Which I think is
Shallow I mean
Feel like any moral system
Let's say I don't know a big one
What's Christianity
If a billionaire
Where to say
If I'm not the ruler of this country
There's nothing I can do feel like maybe you don't believe in them
Religion at all
And also I would like to juxtapose this
With someone like Bernie
Bernie Sanders
Then being like
If I don't win
Nothing to give up I refuse to believe our time I'm at the point now where my denial is that
Bernie Sanders ever existed I refuse to believe it or not that there was so obviously someone who is right about everything that we
We should all over
Well the powerful Shield all over
Be the person I just want to make his
There is still a desire to work
To make things better as bestie
Pecan in whatever
Capacity
Regardless of winning any Epsom electroblob's watch
DVR give a s*** like it should have been
Should be a problem
.
Here's here's what the okay
Bernie loses
He's pushed into the left we all we wanted it you know but what you going to do
Right and then
Trump wins
And then we see all the stuff that happen
Right and then Bernese like we'll finally
These these idiots are ready right
And then we still do the powerful people
Fulfill f*** them over
That was the one point where any reasonable person could be
Justified being like
All of you I'm right about everything
They're all taking me down you're dumb
I'm going home
Reasonable
Yeah it's tough to resist the impulse to
Give it to that nihilism
And you can see the Trump has no willingness to or interest in even trying
If you can't be the king
Now the only thing is you can see
Has Alex's going out one of the primary
Concerns that he has is this like
You're not going to quit you're not a Clinton chill okay right you know like really
That seems to be the
Primary mission of his interview is just to convince the audience
But he's not going to
Quit six months down the road I whatever
To Hillary right
Is the conspiracy
Least likeable candidate so that the second least likeable candidate will finally win
Judas goat
Exactly
So we have some other things that are going to be happening on this episode and here's one of them
Boo
We reported Jihad
North Carolina
30 minutes
Quarterback
It was fun because Joe pigs
The currently facing seditious
Conspiracy charges for his actions on January 6th where he was part of the probably leadership
To stop the certification of the 2020
Also this is the little bit before he got into his peace
The gate bulshit
Also noting
Is worth noting is that big
The information relayed by Josh Owens
Any piece on the New York Times
He worked for Infowars and was along for this
Very trip
It's going to be discussed
Here's how he described it to the time
Quote in December 2015 the day before Jones interview Donald Trump
Still a candidate at the time on his radio show I made my way to Upstate New York on assignment
Along with the reporter and sex
Can cameraman
We were sent to visit muslim-majority communities throughout the United States to investigate would Jones instructed us to call Via
American caliphate
After the California geiger counter.
Debacle that was when they were sent out to get evidence
But there was radiation
And what have you two didn't work out
Are we had meetings with John's before trips in order to ascertain
Exactly what do you want
If we quote
Awesome home runs
He said we would get
Significant bone
They tried to make contact with hooks in a community called islamberg but were turned away because of
Concerns for
Security
From Josh's article
Because of the conspiracy theories about the place
Islamberg was a constant Target of right-wing
Extremists
April the Tennessee man was arrested and later convicted of plotting to raise a militia to burn Islam Birds mosque
To the ground
Homie days before we arrived the FBI issued an alert to law enforcement to be on the lookout for a man named John Ritter
Timer leader of an anti-muslim movement in Arizona who post
The video threat
Violence against Muslims
Less than two weeks earlier
So the phone call we received later that night from a law-enforcement agent shouldn't have come as a surprise
The officer who contacted us said he simply wanted to verify who we were after receiving the concern call for
From somebody in Islam
We told Jones about it and he chose to believe the call was available
Threats and attempt to intimidate us into silence
To him this verify that we were onto something
Even went so far as to include Michael Bloomberg
The former mayor of New York City in the purported
Conspiracy
Claiming he wanted to abolish the Second Amendment and they've somehow intimidating us would have achieved
Jones told us to file a story that accused the police of harassment
Lending Credence to the theory that this community contain dangerous potential Terror
I knew this wasn't the case according to the information we had
We all do
Days before we spoke to the Sheraton the mayor of
Deposit New York
Nearby municipalities
They both told us the people at islamberg were kind generous neighbors who welcomed the surrounding
Community into their home
Even celebrating holidays
Is together
The information did not meet our
Expectations
So we made it up
Praying on the vulnerable in feeding the prejudices
Hidden figures
Jones's audio
We ignored certain facts fabricated others
Took situations out of context
Do Veterinary
So that's going on right now
Joe Biggs is filing the first report
From this
Clear
Fraudulent
Coverage that was meant
Antenna
Angelita Stoke agitate
Against
Muslim communities
You can hear even in Alex's coverage
Of this video that
Pigs is going
To be airing
That
Is American caliphate
Framing
Yeah it came from Alex himself and was like
This is what you're going out
Application for
That's pretty sad
Pretty sad
Yeah that's what it Dawn Salazar calls Reese
Coincidence
Picture
So this is just a weird thing that happens
Alex gets
Neponset talk
Talking about his
Childhood violence and possibly murder
What
17 year old
I want to get off me
What the f***
This is sunset
What the fuk just happened there
Did we just turned into a weird trauma situation what is going on
Very bizarre
I guess that's a rationalization for
Into the concrete cuz it
Besides any wine
So let me try and
Let me see if I understand this already embarked let me see if I understand this
Story correctly
Alex
Has this person's head
Slamming into the ground and they're asking a question
Apparently apparently
Hey what are you doing and then Alex
Standing over them
Holding their head in his hands as
I want you to get off
Yeah
I don't want to I don't want you to come back I want to kill you so you can't believe me again
I understand but that was a that was a metaphor in a
Fictional book
Apparently it's
Literal and not a Ben Carson Story for Alloy also made up story still yeah
Emotional adult seems Wild
Okay man unsettling
Not good don't make me feel good
Know about Alex genre that the story belongs to
And that is the standing up to bullies story
This is a bad version of a standing up to bullies
Story
Generally is like they're threatening violence against you then maybe you punch
The belief and they're like okay okay okay whatever I'm not going to pick on you anymore
As a whole
All of the vile
Right or even like a great version of the story would be a bully picking on you and you say I'm not going to take this
Is anymore and you stand up to them and then it's just words
Birds that are able to diffuse the situation
A bad version of it is I'm slamming their head into the concrete in
Trying to make it so they
Can't hurt me anymore
Is f***** up right so what happened was this guy was like huh
Your shoes are stupid
And I hate bullies
So I beat his head into the ground repeatedly
Yeah
This illustrates a real lack of understanding of like
Who will believe
Is that appropriate self-defense
Losing your s*** I mean let's just say emotional control in any way whatsoever
No
We have
These things that are going on in a
We have Alex
Mine talking about
Murder
We have the Trump interview right we have Joe Biggs agitating against Muslim
Brighton MN
That was Joe Barry coming on the floor bouquet
Where you going next
Arbonne
Stranglehold
Number one
Larry right now this
Common sense
Are you
Everybody on here program
Looking for that
You know here it is December
Number 20
And whole world
Alright
Okay
Ted Ted
You are so rich and you live in the middle of
Nowhere
And you just go hunting and why are you bitching
Wow
Because
I do like that like I really do everything is like
I can feel the tide
You can feel this
Sucks
I like that
I don't like hearing test
It is weird that the
President of the United
It states
The future president of the United States was on this show the same time
Alex
Had
People making up
Fake stories
About Jihadi training camp
You know like
Just average citizens
Like that
That is insane
Eddie's I don't know how to process that
Yeah yeah
What do we do
This is real
This is real it has a lot of the similar shades
Do the Rogan was on 9/11
No like it is Lee like oh that's
He had Ted Nugent on it suggested he should be VP and was airing the begin
Beginning of his segments where he sent his employees out to lie about Muslim Community
Totally
Yep
Yeah
That I mean it's just
Wengie
We've talked about the past
Talked about
Octopuses
Fake right
We're asleep
There's something going on
We're going to wake up in a better
Situation where it's like
Don't know of course this wouldn't
Happened it's not possible
It's absurd
I mean
You're shaking
So you know we have this episode where Trump is on
Alex spent the time before Trump came on
Covering the news which is
Is proton pack
Not all the way in do you likes another tab
Well you know I hear
Coming from Ted
Cruising
From Donald Trump
Marco Rubio
Ever had
Wow
I'm in
Ted Cruz guy
U.s. constitutional
Man they don't like Ted Cruz anymore
When can chain
So quick embarrassed him about January 6th
No
To no good persona non grata
Frightening Lee until
What does it
Take
To scare these people with
Intelligence
Not much I don't think can't be that much
Just to be on the side of the aisle
Right person
Long division
Sure
5 numbers or more
This club might not be all that meaningful
But Alex has some words
Democrats
And I thought this was
Bizarre
Especially considering our last episode we looked at a 2003 episode where Alex is scolding someone for saying damn
You know I don't even I can't even
Nowadays
Anybody would look like
Whoa
Weird
Very out-of-left-field
Yeah
I guess it's fine now
Yeah I mean it doesn't have the ring of wet ass p**** but I think it's still making pretty
Get song out of it 12 years later this show is no longer required viewing for homeschoolers apparently
It's totally fine to just
McFly guess they found out they read back through their demographics in real life
05 we've been doing the Muppet Babies version of this
Why
Show me one last clip honestly because
I've Ted Nugent talk more I lost my interest in what was going on even though
David Knight is going to be Sheriff thing
The Joe Biggs conversation and every airing of the trumpet of you I felt like maybe
I'm going to give that a pass
So this is where I lost
All patient
Whatsoever for the
Facebook
Lilian Garcia
Between
4 million pesos
Poker
Percentile
Indicated
Mango Tango
Bored
It's everywhere it's everywhere
Also I would say terms of like songs that are disqualifying Ted from running for office
Low on that little number of other ones about wanted to f*** children there so I think maybe
Are much more of a problem
I mean it keeps Ted out of maybe consideration for public office
The way you be
Eviscerated by anybody he was running the camp
Mailman I don't know anymore
Going to be a senator who f****** nose
None of it matters
They're all insane everything's over
Climate change is here today
Everyone going down it's all done
I'm basing this on a 2015 mentality exactly
Yeah Department of the interior
Just I hate get off Hunters back I really don't think that they have any
Clue what the department
The interior does
Other than be like
I think that's what the name is on the license
The inside
It's not the grounds Department of the interior of your heart
Right right right
This
I mean look I think that there is a world
Who are to be made with that this
Interview really isn't that
Consequential is a lot of
People build it up to
Right right
Happened
Is of note
The stuff that goes on in it isn't
Like it's not necessarily things Trump didn't say other places
Rai said bomb the oil fields in other contexts
Yep
Talk s*** about all kinds of stuff and other contacts
Not like
Revelatory on that level
But from our perspective looking at Alex Jones
Certainly
It's very clear what his agenda
In the interview it's very clear that he's trying to
Make sure the Trump is actually doing this and actually going to work
Because it would be kind of dope is for him to
Like throw his weight
Behind this person then
Them
Back out and Hillary ends up winning
You know there it happened I guess that's kind of
Like what he had to do with Ron Paul over and over again
I didn't really I wasn't really too like
Aware
During the whole Ross Perot run
Obviously cuz I was very young
But like look
Looking back the eye
Dia of being a Ross Perot support
And then he drops out of the race
And you're like s*** I was a Ross Perot supporter
And then he just suddenly reappears and he's like I'm back in it that's the most qualified
I can pick up right just suddenly somebody popping about that again
Prospero in some ways in as much as like
I think anybody who tries
Think about Ross Perot can just think about the
Can't do anything about it
Can't do it
Somebody who's
Entire Legacy or memory and most of the public eye is an impression of him
There's there's a dead area
Is the the church lady and then there's
And those are the two things that Dana Carvey is ruined forever how dare you what about turtles
Turtles and live longer than Dana Carvey and they'll be gone long after Dana Carvey
So we come to the end of this and we have now covered Trump
Appearance
And yeah we'll see how long this vacation goes but we have probably
Some
Stuff for next week
In the hopper
So like
One way or another we'll be fine but if he doesn't come back soon
Holyshit are we going to do Harrison Smith podcast absolutely not
Going to stay in the past
Never coming back to this
This present what if we try and find out what Harris
Smith was up to in 2003 Middle School
Elementary
Probably find out what David night was up to in 1982
Okay
Seems like a morrin
Interesting question for me
What's David Knight some young Hotshot somewhere that's kind of what I wanted
Did David like bring the heat when he was a younger man you want a contest to work it into a war
So I don't think so I think he was just a curmudgeonly young
Libertarian that's my guess
Let's go to be disappointed
Now we'll never know now that's true but until then
Website.com also
Daimyo I'm Leo dzx Clark I
Have a sublet
In my mind
Going to
You have your own bathroom
That I'm like you don't have your own bathroom
Hoosier bathroom bedroom
Out there's no door though it's just those beaded doorway
Anyway
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color