Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B
We are the bad guys
Stripe.com
Sit around feed from the bottom
For the elders Lane and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
My break is I was doing laundry in apartment
On the way to the laundry room and I got that smell of weed
Yum yum yum I don't smoke weed anymore
I have in my day
There is still a fondness that I have for the smell of
Weed when I hear it when I feel when I hear or field or smile
The smell made me think of those
Days back when I was living in apartments and like you just come up with these like
Alright
Here's how I'm going to get away with smoking weed Secret
Yep you have those like toilet paper tubes with fabric softener sheets Camp yet
Yeah yeah that's good you know that's weird I have 20 fond memories of all the times that I've smoked
Indoor cigarettes indoors you know like the stink of that gets inside the walls yeah I kind of
And the stink with weed smoke I do remember but it still gets inside the walls but it's like a weird fun house
House version of inside the wall the flip side of that though is if you spilled bong water on a rug
Ubisoft with fire
Wistful for those are those old days
Deanne is at the World Series their plan if they are I understand the Philly
Airplane versus the Astros
Cheaters Liars appear in the world series playoffs
Boo sure
6 years ago maybe three
More
But exciting still my favorite players on the Phillies
Kyle schwarber Cubs hero for the 2016
World Series
Sherburne County all the time
Show me what time is like a God can't be your hero
You know like your hero is
Zeus has the greater tality is required for idolizing
Baseball player it's the kind of guy that only exists in baseball you know
Somebody baseball player was very big mostly uncoordinated
But hits balls far
It is that kind of guy can't run very fast
Can people who are like the DH absolutely put God damn it if he's a big dude who hits balls far right
Thinking of Big Papi Ortiz
He's a big dude but he's also good hitter
Six-foot-five
He swings are beautiful bat and he's going to miss it 99% of the quantitative hit
Connects your in the stratosphere but otherwise
Sort of athlete because it is like
The tension is is like could be over in a second
I thought it said baseball has those got you don't like another subset of that guy's the big fat guy who can throw hard
Eunos left-handed pitcher he's huge can't run for s*** but goddamnit he throws 95
Put them on the magic arm I have an affinity for the Phillies for no reason
My old roommate owes a big guys from Philly
Good Times watching
Sixers games with him and she hit Billy Phillies games
Have fun as long as they're winning
When they lose then angry
So Jordan today we have to go over as we know Alex has been on a permanent
Roman Holiday Vacation
Come into the week
We still don't let know what to do
Thankfully we have depositions
I had to kind of thought maybe we would wait a little bit longer to do this but hey the occasion
Year the space needs to be filled
And people enjoy it
Inexplicably so in the Connecticut case
Alex had 24 days of depositions
So we have that stew cover
That is impossible to do in the context of one episode
Day one
Alex's deposition
Navigate to get some clarity for this this is the deposition
He did after faking illness do not go to Connecticut to sit for the the deposition
Diagnosis the Minotaur and the other sinus blockage
Add a little stuffy nose
I think if I were devising a hell for Alex it would be
Like waking up on Monday and being told you're going to do 4 days of depositions
And then waking up the next Monday and being told you're going to do for it forever and ever and ever you know like never-ending
In the second position they talked about how they had to reschedule cuz I wanted to go to Hawaii with his wife
Wearing a shirt or a luxury resort
I can't I can't let go from making a murderer interrogation to this s*** you know like that's not okay
Okay another thing I should point out is there there's a couple of things will become abundantly clear as we go through this
And one is that Alex hasn't learned anything from any of these deposition experiences he's at
Sing an answering questions in ways that are like baby that made sense in the first episode
This question and the answer so you can't really say I don't know
The time is packed a little silly
And then the other thing is that Alex Hates Chris Mattie
It's very clear
I don't think it would be fair to say that he liked mark
But
Give very seriously suits.
I'm not sure why
They clearly say that they have not met before
Bucking maddaddam I can see that I can see that has something that Alex
Grudgingly is like in another works you know that Perry Mason moment thing and I like in another world I could see
Me and you Big Fred's that guy to fix
Madame sort of like a Owens game recognize game
I think I think
It's more than that
If I had to guess
I would guess the day-to-day Chris Maddie is much more of what appears to be a normal lawyer then thinmar
A vibe to him
Whereas
Maddie is it is a lawyer
And maybe Alex really hates back
Okay so Maddie and Mark both lawyers now
Alright
We go into a Mad Max scenario Mark might still be a lawyer in that scenario I think Maddie is not going to be
A lawyer
He's he's in the front of the truck you know and I accidentally touched on another Dynamic here and that is the norm is there
Couple points where Norm seems to just want to have fun and
Scrapes inappropriate Goodway
Anyway we'll get down to business on this and just a moment the first Jordan let's take a little moment to say hello to some doo-wop
First I made a dreamy creamy and my pants thank you so much
Trained my dog's peanut pumpkin and pickle
How to growl and bark whenever Alex starts yelling
Thank you very much I was actually why we started the podcast I do help for future break in
Text breaks into your place come down and Alex Resorts crime
Thank you so much
Thank you very much that's famous leave courses my description of orange Cassidy's character
Pro wrestler orange Cassidy
Was wondering whether that was going to Jordan so first
Partner patches CPA thank you so much you're not a technocrat
Bald patches, alright
Next mrs. Jones is a tennis partner
Russell from Kansas thank you so much you are now technocrat
And tell her you're brilliant someone sodomites
Has a Caribbean
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much thank you very much
In the beginning of this deposition is of course some of the formalities and such and their bits
Cut out and that's like his his address and I think these kinds of things
Oldest house
Right and what have you deal with any of that
Just because
There isn't anything really to discuss
Rihanna house
The first clip we're going to have here is I thought I found this to be a little bit of a non sequitur but it also sets a bit of
Overtone
And that is that like
Almost every question is probably going to be a trap out
Did you have a photographic memory
Utility memory not more
Have you ever told anybody that you have a photographic memory
Have a very reggae memory
Try to commit something to it I can remember really well but it's Desmond like that but
Let my question was whether you never told anybody that
Hyperbole just drive myself as having percent
You did that when you appeared on The Joe Rogan
Podcast
Oh damn it is millions of audience members
Photographic memory correct
Particularly
You don't have a photographic memory that
Alright okay
That's why I that's alright I'm already kind of I get where he's coming from Hayden Chris Betty alright
I wish it talk or two if it if I'd lawyer came to me with every time I talk s*** I be like alright
First of all there's a dunk of you don't have a photographic memory of that
Not feel great
What you have is a attempt to be like you have a really good memory you said this thing
Because it helps dislike from the
Copious amount of times Alex is going to say oh I don't remember that
Well we're going to hear that a lot
All alright
The zone of depositions are we this isn't his first step has issuing no his last deposition
Position in Connecticut
Because you saying that he and Maddie haven't met before it gets the first intern
Terms of that but do you think it's definitely after the Texas one
I was at Texas has been deposed at least a couple times a week
Fairly good at this by now she was someone who like to learn learning
Turns out that Alex did not come alone
Connecticut people in tow
But he doesn't know who they are
Understand that you arrived at our building today with
Somebody was operating a digital camera device
Me a phone
Well
Where did you arrive at our building with somebody who's calling you
Over-the-phone yes is that
It's just one of those
Coronavirus
I forget his name is Juan called
He traveled with you from Texas
Yes
For the purpose of filming you
Just documenting
Casey 19th Avenue
Okay and you intend to
Publish the footage that he shoots
I'm one of your broadcast after
Deposition
I don't know
Probably not
Prepared to do that
Yes
Because you've been raising money
From your audience
And you advise them that you need their funds to help
Financial litigation
So if it's not a compliment that this person that I've flown up to Connecticut with
I don't know their name
We different parts of the plane right isn't it yeah I don't think this is true I'm going to guess that
Being just invasive for the sake of it
I'd like a damning secret who this person is
Has David Duke or something
But it it's it's it's a weird thing to be evasive about yeah who is this person who
You have is your camera person
Ethan Hunt
Nav wearing a mask
He's on a super secret mission okay he's got to stop
Something else got completely unrelated but because Alex has his contacts through the knowing they hating the global
Right he's posing as Alex it's completely unrelated think it's a coincidence
I think that maybe it's a sign that anybody who has a seniority it in
Infowars can't take any time off cuz I need them back at the the mothership is Alex says
Or I don't know it's just weird or it just doesn't remember Buckley's name anymore
Like I said more I don't think
This I believe is a very important early exchange kind of goes on
You do text
People don't you
You know that we have
Send TextMe
Yeah man we turned all over you guys and you said we didn't need to fall to this
You don't want to be able to put on a rosary
It shows when do you think was
The first X-Men
Increase you
Is side of the aisle in
So did you mean by we mister
I know
Go back that you said we
Gave you everything
And who's we
I instructed
Lle Chasers
Could you turn over whatever it is people said turnover
You know it's been a fiasco
Hundreds of thousands of emails documents all sorts of crap people
Searching my phone all the time
Contentions armor was like stuff from years ago
Protect message don't update
People wanting stuff doesn't exist but I'm not a big fat guy
And I'm so I don't
I do understand how that stuff works and I don't know why something nice text messages stay
Different different Services there different used to
They were disappearing couple weeks now they go back
You're usually Lyle as though you're asking me
Technology issues the same things happening
I know I don't understand
Anybody that has cell phones nose
That they're different ones of different things for different things going on and I don't understand it all
But but the emails we should have just heard
Pocket money than getting rid of them
We got him going back fifteen years million times a million times you guys are able to get those
So if anything we have
Unless you know
Sync my text messages sometimes do get saved
You have any knowledge of whether any
Read text messages
Yours has ever been
By you or fries
To us
Give me knowledge
I believe they have you believe that they
Do you have any knowledge
I'm out of money. Not somebody talking to front of me
Right
I didn't ask you again.
So I think this is really critical because a key here is kind of putting aside Alex's bulshit
He complied fully with discovery that he was defaulted on Fairlane
I just keeping on target Maddie is able to get Alex to concede that he has absolutely no idea what text messages
We're actually turned over to the plaintiffs' lawyers
Alex's pronouncements about how much you cooperated are matters of certainty when he's rambling on his show
I'm standing at a disgraceful press conference outside the courtroom
When he's actually forced to answer yes or no if he has any idea what he actually did for discovery
Is no anything
This is our answer because it's less of a problem than him saying that he intentionally withheld things
Which seems like a far more likely situation to me at this point
It's it's good because you know you have that Dodge we turned over everything chat what do
Do you know about what you turned up while I believe I said that like you don't know anything
You're just making broad pronouncements about s***
If you if you did not intentionally withhold things
Then your explanation for why they don't have text messages is not
The power of magic
Can compel phones to do any number of different things as possible party would be able to say
Looked over my stuff and on XYZ date for my lawyers of this
I turned it over to them on this date
Because then you could start the ball rolling and be like the breakdown happen did your lawyers not turn over
Overstuffed to us that you turned over to them questions in the eye
Stuff happened simply one of the easiest ways to
I believe anything somebody says about their text messages if there's a text message saying I texted you all of my
Text messages of some sort or I have given you all of this information that would be sent by at some people's phones
Chucky pets. Mobile has a policy of erasing those.
That's a good policy I like that
Sooner we get to what is maybe the the classic
Beginning of a deposition question which is what did you do to prepare for this
Would you do to prepare for your deposition today
Really not much
Kobe
You know what I eat sleep and drink sir
You'd argumentative
You don't care about Madeleine Albright's don't have none kids you think you want to just do a nice because I'm a conservative and I know it's all political
And I literally
Remember to make intentions people questioning at covering it
How do I prepare I have no idea what you're going to ask me in here
Well you have an idea cuz you can just hose 3 times in Texas don't you
You can describe thanks it is supposed to explain I guess
Bizarre but all of this whatever I mr. Jones
Whatever
Perfection diplomas characterizes attest
Like it's pointless argumentativeness I wonder if there's an expectation or a hoe
Hope that he'll say this
And then the Lord will be like you know what
F****** right let ticket Madeleine Albright she just died not too long ago but that's how I can sue her fur
First and then take care of you
Overlake
Is it is it is he hoping somebody like you know what you're right Madeleine Albright is a bigger problem and therefore this little
Gation to is over what's the best case scenario for bringing up Madeleine Albright
In this conversation
Is it what is it more like he's like
Hey you know what
We're not talking about Madeleine Albright right now we're talkin about you and then you can be like haha
I think what it is is that Alex's
Mind works so much just on the basis of deflection everything just comes down to
Do like every question is answered with a
This thing is this other thing and do know I didn't exist I don't think he can stop himself I think it's just
Ingrained behavior and how he gets out of hard questions in his day-to-day life
Kind of questions and when you're monologuing
Yeah because
If it doesn't really work
In a deposition
No I'm not you know it does it reminds me of like
You know not to bring up the S8 not about the divorce but in the divorce trial where
The lawyer is arguing like on the show he's one thing and then off the show is another
But the more we hear him in depositions wearing hats to not be on the show
Or in court when he has to not be on the show
He's on the show man yeah I don't know if he's ever not on well there's another thing going on here
That is that by this point Alex has had these Texas deposition
The videos of them have been released on on YouTube
He may think like I'm kind of Performing here
I am
I don't know I don't know the extent to which that would change his behavior
Yeah we really will have to
Like straight-up Truman Show him in order to observe him in his natural habitat have to get rid of all the confounding very
So like I said this was the makeup that position before the one that Alex canceled on brand this comes up a little
And you feel well today
Your head is clear
I'm going to have sinus infection stuff but I'm almost over I heard about
Is that sinus blockage clear up
It was it was very real I went to the other three depositions
About sick last week
Talk about something else how much touchdown and then
Forgot was really bad sinus infection but I think
The day after you found out
It was a sinus blockage you said your audience
Did you feel like a new person right
Cuz I got on steroids
He wants to show you know that's what I'm talking about so you feel good today
I'm still really bad allergies and it's Antebellum on Claritin
I'm alright
It's very strange because he's trying to pretend that he's still recovering from this whatever
Presented with the you said you were a new person the next fully over
Allergies shifting it a little bit so yeah the very bizarre need to
Justify his pretending that he wasn't over whatever he bailed
Yeah yeah yeah I feel like I would want to remain at that point I'll be like Alex
How can I ask you a question that you'll answer like maybe you should
You write up a question that you can answer and I'm kinda see what the vibe on is going to go through hours of content here at
That question is not answered the how can I ask you a question you'll answer
I don't understand why Alex doesn't just say like
Can I ask you a question
You know like
There's
He is very little by just being all business he's already
In the soup up to his thorax and he's not going to bail himself out there's not going to be
Be like some Escape hatches going to find Pride by saying just the right evasive thing
Just serve everyone's purposes better if you just like all right let's do this
Even if you have to be kind of a blunt dick
In order to do that it's
Your images is already shot
Just be an a****** we're all kind of watching Alex in the bottom of an hour
Glasses it fills with sand and he's like struggling to get out and he thinks he's going to get out and as we all watch or like that
Sans is going to cover your neck man you're gone you're done for you might as well relax and enjoy
Like Toy Story 3
So the question comes up of whether or not Alex will appear in court
Agree with him on this one and that he says if I don't have to I don't want to be there
And then I just Rambles
The testimony that you give
In this case
To be presented to
Imagery interstate
Yes
The jury's going to be sitting in Waterbury
The trial in this matter is currently scheduled for
If you plan to appear for that
Needtobreathe
Well you're a defendant in the case
Right
Well I mean I believe it's rigged and so
You guys are going to ring your deal
Itssliker
Victor Jory
Egyptian
It's winter somebody guilty in the jury decide how guilty
Defend ourselves
Show me the sink that's America does
I've got all these big ideas and stuff then
I bet family with cancer and people die really bad stuff in my life so this is nothing
It's just a bunch of politicians and lawyers
Want to make money and become famous off of dead kids
When is completely opposite
From the first times I questioned it
Loosestrife
It's not responsible
Play Dua.
Testifying for the jury
Is it
Do I need to be there I will be there yes
You prefer.
Be there
Jackson
Prefer not to be there
Great honesty
Matter if you fully accepted responsibility for what happened or not like there's no way you would want to be there
A monster I'm a bad person now
Actually
Yes Alex's presentation should be yes I do want to be there
A very human level of course I want to be there even if you're fighting your good name you know like I know human-level I don't want
Want to be in a situation where I have to fight for my good name and all I got was yours
I would like to be on a beach somewhere that's it that's a reasonable response all things being equal I don't want to be there
The situation is what it is Alex absolute
Stand up and prove that he can look at firing squad in the face
Choice but to be there be there is a setup
That's really because it's not
And so mad he decides to explain to Alex a little bit of why the D
Default happens
And this turns
Ugly yeah I don't know if that was a wise choice so it's good to get it out there and make sure that I
I don't understand these things no
But there are a couple points in this deposition where I got like really deeply uncomfortable and this was one of them
I was like already we are
Off the rails
Chris Jones
Your stand that
You were defaulted by the court here
For among other things
Presenting fabricated
Financial information
Your company
That's not true though understand that's
Profound
That's okay do you understand
That you were defaulted
For refusing to present
Reduce to the plainest
Analytics information
About
Your website
Performance understand that
That's been said that the judge made when I believe you're frostrune
Okay
Alice's best friends with one of your main partner share that when you find that out
Who was partner
It when it hits the nosebleed
Which partner of mine
Is Judge Barbara Bellis
Best friends
Oh okay
Mr. Jody
My
Okay why is mr. Jones whether he could see
Support his claim just now that he made
Any version of the presiding judge and he said that he could not remember all the sudden
Alright well
We're going to Virginia
So you're you don't remember right even though you just made an assertion of bias against
Presiding judge
Claiming that she's best friends with the partner of my office
Sources
I didn't I didn't ask you your Source One
I asked you the partner was remember that
Without reservation information your journalist
Oh my God
Oh boy that's that's kind of fun because I don't think Alex was
Tekton that response at all throwing out these accusations and not like what do you mean by that
Shitt I don't want to name a name because then I'm going to end up in a situation where
I'm basically accusing the judge and lawyers of being in collusion
That might be a problem is Alex believes like does he inherit
Do you like almost instinctively just
Hit the mute button whenever whenever he's talking and he says something does he accidentally press his finger on the table just
To be like clearly they can't imagine I mean it's it's
It's outrageous this
This response
What you have real real weird there with the the way you said oh
Tell good degree is Norma lawyer
I feel like this isn't safe
That we are all pretending Norm has any understanding of what's going on at any point side and I think
Probably is actually a an objection to be made there
Normal circumstances maybe snide comments are actually a tone problem
Alarm for lawyers in this unfortunately you're proposing Alex f****** jump and
He's being
A real a******
I keep thinking is I need to make sure Alex says as little as possible but we'll get to that later
Objection your honor my defendant is a piece of s*** like I would throw that out there like
F****** watermelons on his face anything to keep him from Talking does basically tell Alex
Okay well that's smart so while to get there and it might only be because I was about to say something
Locate a Norman maybe in self-protection mode
More than Alex detection.
But yeah that was chaotic
I felt uncomfortable during that approach that of the
Oh you're a journalist there's a nice way of like we're not Landing this playing yet you think that you've you found this
Is great place
Were you can stake your claim
It's going to be safe for you to say like I'm not going to give up my source it's not a source
Oh you're jealous
What about how your corporate representative consistently testified that you are not a journalist
Avoid the responsibilities that come with it I wear that
Brown boy
So we know that Alex got a loan from his dad to start his business here
What we didn't know
It's some other things that his dad did not help
As it turns out
In the early days of Alex's career
He had his businesses infowars.com LLC
And prisonplanet LLC under a holding company
Called Magnolia partners
And here is a little bit of a discussion of what that was
Are the
Founder and owner of Infowars Health LLC correct
Infowars LLC
Prisonplanet TV LLC
Now those
Companies were previously held by Magnolia limited partnership
Correct
All of them
Import LLC in for zealous
I am not
Really expert on these not get these confused that's why we had
Study hall
What your understanding is
Is the owner of these companies
Whether they were ever held by Magnolia limit
Magnolia limited partnership
Was a dental company management bank account used to pay employees by my dad
21 or so
It like $10,000 and it has good
Business credit
You can get
Starting to
Do things online
Celtics and he said
You can have
You have this baggage on this company
And that's that's what that Magnolia limited partnership was
And then
You use that as a holding company
Or the three companies I just mentioned correct
It's on record drive me nuts
So when you think about getting a loan
That's very helpful
Getting a corporate bank account that has good credit and money and such
It's an entirely different thing like the opportunities that are open to Alex because of his dad
Bequeathing him
This corporate bank account is
Berry that is a huge privilege that he had a huge step up as opposed to
Someone else trying to do the sort of thing that he was doing business loan without collateral
Is either a loan shark or you're going away with no money
You know
The ability to possibly
Items on credit ability for him to make his films that he would then resell
A lower interest rate beyond what can be considered is
Refusing to recognize the ways in which he had
Shortcuts in his early career and how those allowed him to create what he was able to create
Absolutely
Be the weirdest of the deepening of that they comes for this is is
His life and his Illusions about himself all the satyr
I think about it is like I still can't believe
The things that so many people have done for me to get like for me to go to college there was a serious number of people who
Had to step up and do a lot of things to help me out you know and even though I
Absolutely wasted their work asteroid their Ambitions for me and said that we can okra
Crying into the bathroom
I will never not recognize what they've done for me and how that got sure here you know like the idea
Of me you know I would never be like off I came from nothing and I'm a self-made man but it's the yeah it's abs
Search podcast
I guess we built entirely sure we could say but it would be ridiculous to imagine that like
That on your side
Things that I've been lucky enough that my parents have been able to help with over the course of my life
Facilitating to ever be in the position 100 where we were even struggling
I2
Build this at the beginning I think is really a weight
To self mythology unhealthy
It also goes both ways you know you're there is a certain part of that that's also kind of very helpful you know what you were selling your blood you can
Can also say if it weren't for my parents I wouldn't be here now what I'm selling my love
So Google analytics comes up interesting answers to weather or
Or not he uses Google analytics them and not have
You familiar with Google Analytics
Familiar with it yes
Google analytics is a program that allows you to track
Traffic and other activity on your website correct
Yes
That data is something that you consulted throughout your career to
Learn about
Your websites
Performance correct
No
You've never
Look at Google analytics data during the course of your career
For what purposes
Attitudes generally see how popular that Lisa cytus
Isn't that exactly what you just said no to well I didn't look to see how well the site was due
I look to see how popular the site was amongst people it's very
No no
Alright so
Oh is there 100,000 people
That's a different thing you got to check its blood pressure
Call very very bizarre
So Alex I think realizes that he's in shaky territory here so as more
Questions are there about these
Districts in watching them
He launches into his standard patented ramp Lovett about how you need to bring me the Google
It makes no sense bring me Google bring it to him
It was obviously important to you to know
What your websites
Performance
Non-traditional corporate media Outlets
Prepackaged is what they're going to do and what they're going to say and then and then and then
Taylorsville
To whatever the corporate bosses say I died fly by the seat of my pants when it comes to
The finances and then anyone see stuff in and I'll try to explain this to
Interface into Google
So when you say
It's just a bad kid
My Google searches the front end
You asked me what you guys did give us the Google
Analytics
Like staying
Give me the Google
You go in there and it's just like
Rocket science
The guy's Chris Andrews in temperature
Wood
Went to a few meetings with life
Search engine optimization people to remember cuz they wanted to be more professional
They wanted to try to figure out ways
So they poked around
I was just like
Flight
Literally
And that's the truth
Or to see how stories are now linked to where we're going to traffic I mean by that
It was it was on Capital Public site
Understanding
Google Analytics
Give me the phone book
Forgive me the Library of Congress
What
Michigan
I can tell that you're
Focus to some extent
On
Material
Turnover
All I'm asking
Is
Whether or not
You made effort
First understand
Collier
Website
Who's performing
Yes
Okay that's all we need
Yeah. My partner is has taught elementary school before and that that feeling of like
Alex
Ion highway on about something that is now
You're talking about so much that media for no question. Answer to the question
Larisa has caused problems in the past but right now we're talkin about you I love the idea
To that like
Going into Google analytics is like rocket science
Kind of ridiculous
That is a question that I have is that I feel like it's very clear from The Trial in from these depositions that we've
That it has been explained to Alex how bad it is for them to know all the Google analytics data
Right well it has to a bit yes I believe so because it's
Especially around time of its the primest example
Nobody the FBI says no one was killed at Sandy Hook article that Alex put out
The intense Spike that came from the publication of that article
Leave then the interview with Wolfgang halbig
The next day like those trends that you see in that Google Analytics
And for his dad to have testified that they try to replicate things that work 12 quarts things
I don't work to Alex's best interest
Maybe made him aware of the Optics of that being incredibly bad
Send that I have is
If that was explained to him
Then there has to have been up there has to have been meetings or something groups of them
Heather Wright and I would like to know what else was explained as the line imagine
Maybe a lawyer maybe a norm
Conversation I don't know though I mean like we are speculating quite heavily
That's what I'd like to you know if I had my druthers of if I could be on the wall in it
The ambiguity that's so clear about
About the Google analytics be like
Wishi-washi nice and refusal to say anything specific about liked a daunting
You things
Shoot the facts of them as they are be established and you have to accept them
You know that looks terrible right you know
Looking at what damn batondy did knowing that you told him to do that and that
You probably take him to do that totally you know that any right-thinking person is going to look at that be like you
To harass the people in Sandy Hook
So I'm going to say I did
You know you can't accept that conclusion until everything has to be done to
Serta wiggle around it and there are several of those things that came that were very clear as we go through
Through like
Because there's a company line you know if you see Daria Brittany and Owen and everybody say the same thing
Then it's kind of clear that it's been disseminated through the group
This is our line you know
There were a bunch of things though where it's like
This could have been the line or they could have just had no idea that this line of questioning was going to show up
So I will be interested to know what it was that they were prepared for and that way sure I would be
Could be interesting is that you can tell if you listen to these
Bulk of things that the answer is I don't know
Yeah and then there're other things were there's a rant and that is notable to me I don't know
What exactly it means but yeah it does give the appearance of that
So the question comes up of
Hey buddy do you know any shows that do what you do
Especially
At the time they were similar size
Any show that you can name
Talk about Sandy Hook like you did Alex's trouble with that
At least as of 2012
There was nobody else
Getting in the American Media landscape that was doing what you were
Are safe natural form
No that's not true
Okay
Who who else had an audience of your size
Open
That was
Covering things the way you covered
Chichen Itza
Forum
Okay
Anybody else
There were
Hundreds of popular shows
Substantive audiences
Anybody anybody else among those shows that has
Hoax
There there were out of there was a show as big as mind saying that
But that would definitely a lot of things a lot of people that
Radio shows thanks
Can you name me one person
Who had a radio show
Who claimed the Sandy Hook was a hoax
I just sit here today
Other than you
I don't have a computer in front
There were people that questioned it definitely was a big controversy
People to cover the controversy
Garrison Keillor was all over it
There was a there was a radio host in Lake Wobegon who was really on The Cutting Edge of this stuff
Broadcast that was
Strangely enough
All about Sandy Hook for a while
This is going to really be shocking but fresh was
The largely about Sandy Hook being a hoax for about 6 months
Pictures of lolbit weird like that
All Things Considered do they consider all things I think they do within the name
If they did consider all things that they would have considered this so I think that's a tautology
Logically
Discussion about the Second Amendment of course cuz always and
Expectation that you talked about the importance of the executive Med B
Defensively
Defensive
Oh and Maddie gives a couple of points of like we eventually you're going to need to
To fight this oppressive government you're going to need to use those guns in an offense
The gun is for shooting
Yeah
Alright we're going to have to fight you up
Part of this
Resistance
The global New World Order
You'd agree with me
That your view is that
An armed populace
Populace may be necessary to
Correct
Yes if you can we get invaded during a z, Collapse by
Horses
Champs
Then people do have a right to duty to protect themselves or family that's
Shrine for it's also the first amendment isn't trying
What was speak up so we don't ever have to use
The Second Amendment on automata wide-scale
What is nothing
That these globalists
Won't do
Write to achieve global.
Right
There's not much they won't accuse them of doing is manufacturing
The covid crisis
As a way to depopulate correct
Never said I was cooked up by a Consortium of globalist
Hundred percent Bill Gates
And of course fauci and and develops at the North Carolina Chapel Hill facility
The movie 2015 to Wuhan
Documents
Personalized weapon
Of course naturally
I love that response to him saying these things because it's just rolls off my back
Like water on a duck you know the the I've got all the documents
Be responsive
You got all the documents it like it's so funny because you just
Expect like the
Could you produce them the answers of course I'll do it with you tomorrow
Bloomberg email that's fun
The idea I never said that it had not occurred to me before that the 1st Amendment was there to keep the
The 2nd Amendment from being used see that makes sense while the Second Amendment is unfortunate you know you
You need it but it is a method of Last Resort
Listen it's okay to talk right but when the talking's done you got to do the shooting First Amendment stalking Second Amendment
Here is the reality is mightier than the sword the gun more powerful.
I ate ya tongue swordpack I got the tongue of the pen mixed up but it's all speech
Talking about you can see there to something that I believe is
Thread of questioning that goes on through this will do anything
They will do anything
I told Maddie does lineup a list of like these things that Alex is called false Flags Oklahoma City
City Columbine
Got all this and I think part of it is to make it like
Why would it be any more extreme for them to
Do Sandy Hook and you are mine would do anything
It's not really that outside your ideas at all
It's almost weird sense of like normalizing it within his ideology
To be adverse to be like well I wouldn't say that they do this or something with everything that you say
Right right right it's priming him to be more receptive to just be like it
You know I think I think that there's a piece of that whether it's intentional or not
But yeah it goes through a number of these shootings and
Terrorist false Flags to Alex's covered and one of them stuck out to me
Dead in 2011 you claimed
The shooting of congresswoman
Gabby Giffords
Which took the lives
Six people and wounded 13
With a staged
Operate
Correct
He was mentally ill and I believe May been under my control football
What you said was
It was a stage
Operation
Correct
I can contact. But the camera
And and
Who is it that you said was under mind control
Individual that did the shooting
He was an audience member of yours was in Ark
I don't know that
Yeah so there's a there's a couple things here first is that
You know Alex has these grandiose ideas about like all this is a mind control person with a f****** name
Don't care about this at all you just have like a little bit of a
I detail that you remember like oh that's if you actually
We thought this person was like a mind control subject to try to kill
Gabby Giffords and killed a bunch of other people
Frankie it would be maybe a more important data point
You know in the
Cosmology of your ideas
If you could prove to me that somebody had been mind-controlled
Into attempting to assassinate a political figure
That would be the only thing I'm interested in moving forward we got to figure out this mind-control s*** cuz I can't
Anyone is saying to me anymore imagine imagine if Alex dedicated himself to proving anyting
As opposed to just deciding everything is proven
W mind control I am on your team because f*** if I know what I believe is true NE
Seymour everybody's mind-controlled its mind control is possible
Yeah
Well I mean then again to the whole like now
Coffee table that I'm fine I don't care this Gabby Giffords shooting is part of a line of like
Like you know Columbine all of these shootings
The intention behind this is to demonstrate to Alex that there is a pattern
It is very clear
And that is the day of these things
You say they're fake that is what you do your audience expects it is just how this works
And so we get to the Aurora shooting and Alex tries to play dumb on that one
And then
In July 2012
We have the Aurora movie
Theater shooting correct
In there on that very day on the day of the shooting
You going to do the hundred percent chance that it was a false
Correct
I believe that was a few days later what was the local newspaper
But he told
People in the jail the guards that he was under mind control are you denying
That on the day of the shooting itself
You said there was a hundred percent chance
It was a false flag
You know you said that
Don't you
I know I don't know that I said I don't have a phone
Why don't we show
Exhibit 102a
That's got to be a nightmare trying to play fast and loose gear
And when I hear let's play this clip alright now I'm going to watch myself say the thing I was trying to be
A little bit cagey about the idea of
Being in a deposition and saying I believe something happened to the lawyer
Who you know
Knows the answer to every question he's not asking questions for information Mansi Alexander
He's operating he's operating on the Assumption of like alright this lawyer knows the answer to
The 99% of the questions
And they only want me to answer that 1% because that'll really screw me over so if I if I just pretend
Do not know anything that's how I'm going to get around I don't know maybe that's the thing
Thought process but
It's it's a little bit.
So if they play the clip of Alex saying that this is
Awesome
This is a great attempt on Alex's BART to weasel away
July 20th
At 12
At the beginning of the video horse that Infowars live
You know that
Refresh my memory
You said it was
100%
Right
Play on words chance
What
Yeah.
Okay
You see it was eloquent wordplay
More empty Alex's resultant resided himself toward gay
The language that uses it was a pun
That's not going to work man
Great that's fantastic like one of the things that I really enjoy about these depositions
Is that like that's unnecessary Alex grasping at straws for no reason at all
It is it is all too often like the kids say the darndest things would like
Why would you say that you child
It's so easy for Alex just admit that he said that because there's a video of it
I don't know or that was my belief at the time total or whatever
Visalia like a word
Reasonable if you didn't remember that you said that on the day you say bulshit everyday you don't care what you
You say of course you don't remember you said it on that day
Probably if you ask me I totally did
So we get to Sandy Hook and of course the pattern has been established through this line of questions that the day of these tree
Tragedies you deny that breath what you do your audience knows the game and Alex
Someone kind of shocked me was the question comes up whether or not he watched
His show from that day
To prepare for any of these cases
And I would have thought you probably watched mean at least a little bit beyond two times speed
After having
Claimed your audience of Millions
Each of the events
We just went through
We're staged
The government
You went on the air on
December 14th 2012
Discuss shooting that happened that morning in Connecticut correct
Yes
Good morning of December 14th 2012
Adam Lanza shot his way into Sandy Hook Elementary
Yes
Killed 20 children and six adults
You at your studio in Texas that day right
Appalachia and your show aired its regular time 11 a.m. Central
And you started talking about Sandy Hook
Felicia
And you knew exactly what you were going to say
No
Cover guy was recovering what the news was up to before saying call her for calling you
Well no caller that called in told you
What stage did they
I haven't reviewed that show
You produced it. Did you know that
I told him give you everything we had
You didn't think that
I want to review
Your broadcast from the Day this year
Jackson
I really try to not think about Sandy Hook because
I get bombarded with it so I'm leaving
Rochester
There was a pause there in that
And that is kind of like him realizing
It does look bad that I didn't I didn't review this
What do you say I don't like to think about Sandy Hook
Or whatever
I'm saying I don't face what I did
That is
Entirely I'm too much of a coward to own up to the fact
That I behave this way and it cause this much pain
Name two people yeah I mean well that part of that
Was
It literally never occurred to me to do so that is not something I want to do
I have built up psychological roadblocks that won't allow me to even come close
Reckoning with my own action never occurred to me
So ugly
It's pretty important to understand and recognize especially in hindsight that Alex when he got on air
That they had no information
Looks like a false flag that looks fake
You're nothing
Other than himself same thing that we were looking at he was looking at and he had no more information than us
He did not call it a false flag
Has these quote-unquote anomalies that he can look at and say like that
You know any insight use that to justify his suspicion was anywhere
In his mind immediately there were no of these anomalies
Comes up and this is weird
I'm sure you'll do bring them up
It was the reports of multiple Shooters the man of the woods the camo
Some of the
Responses and things
About the First Responders and meet Sweet seen other events we had questions about
Information about with you and you want to meet
Performance
I need to go back to the timetable that but if I'm sitting there
Saying
Just to be staged
You then
I told the video that you published
Connecticut school massacre looks like false
Witnesses
I do remember that but that's it
You title you title your own videos right
That's your pride
It is generally like to try the title some of the videos
It's your practice to do it
Definition
Didn't do it yesterday
Sunday no I don't do it all the time.
Hugo Acosta was your lungs
Curious
He was your lungs
Yes but that is different and he and he
Test
Single Witness
Spoke to
You can speak to any Witness
Is that day Witness
Incorrect
Watching it on television and Witnesses for saying
You were watching Witnesses on television speed
Watching people are saying on television not a single Witness
I don't know that
A witness
You saw news reports that day
As you're watching as you were broadcasting
I think we're playing for the news reports on your life as you were broadcast
And you think
And in one of those news reports included what an interview a witness
I will go back and I will review that that first day I didn't
Witness
On the air
Told you
That the massacre look like
Flag
I haven't reviewed the broadcasts a while I should coming on
Okay
So you have
No idea
Weather anyway
Did the shooting ever said that left
Incorrect
You lived
10 years ago
So yeah this line of questioning is like just a disastrous
Falling off a cliff for Alex the the title of that video
Shooting looks like a false flag such a disaster because
Question the follow-up obviously is what
Brides and you can't answer that because you don't have an answer to that
Yeah it is it is interesting to look at somebody till like watch in real time as somebody
Finally sees themselves from the outside you know like cuz he inside he's like okay you know what I did
Did some bad things
But I'm not
Guilty
You know and then whatever he sees himself through that lens of like
Oh I really can't explain that I really can't look the most guilty anyone's ever look are you trying to tell me you turned on
CNN and a witness to the shooting said it looks fake
Well now with that you say it like that cuz that's where your headline did you have
Conversations with Witnesses who told you that affair
What's going on here none of this is like you woke up really really sleepy you were
Paying attention and your friends
Had put you inside a dolphin costume and you went to the liquor store and you were like
Something and everybody's like you are wearing a dolphin costume
So this next clip is a little bit longer I'm going to say Mike down for this even though it's about 4 minutes
And the reason is because this is
Pretty intense the question is about the Rob
Robbie Parker press conference as we know Alex basically just played the first 2 seconds of
And the question has to do with whether or not he ever even watch the full
Conference
Simple yes or no question
You have just described
Is going to lead to a four-minute clip that I have to put my bike down for it takes
Turn
Now that day
After the
Sandy Hook
Tragedy
Father one of the children spoke to the Press outside
Church
Did you know that
Did you watch that live
OverWatch live
When did you want
I know I've watched the Robbie Parker videos Arizona
I'm talking about
The statement that mister Parker
Poker games
Shooting
I've had watched it many times and I wash it near the back of that time I don't remember
10 years later how I watched it exactly when I watched it
Watch the whole thing
I want some
What is the whole thing again
Empire State
Depressed
I remember watching the whole press conference
Let's play
And you think you did it around a Time
I mean really yeah I mean I know the statement I know you're talkin about I don't remember when I exactly I watched it
10 years ago
What was this child's name
Murdered at Sandy
Can you name a single person whose murder
The time we said some of the names but I've
Most people sue me I never said their names
So
Like I said I'm not
Edited or something
Mr. Jones
Do you know the name of
Tell me what
Answer your attitude or something I'm not giving you what you want
Oh yes you are
You want to make some section affectionate.
I want to
See whether you're lying or not when you say you know them
Noah Pozner
Okay
Can you give me another one
I'm done can you
I didn't kill those children can you get it with no people in the public appearance that killed him
I'm not going to say their names so you can
Edit together act like I did something to him if there's a there's a court record what you say here
So other than the whole post
Can you name a single per
He was murdered at 10
Yes and I'm done doing parlor tricks
Who
If you're going answer the question
We just took a break
Can you name a single
Person who was murdered
Sandy Hook
Yes if I need to
Going my mind and dredged up my mobile can but I'm not going to sit here and say their names for you so you can have something for HBO movie
Mr. Jones this is a lawsuit
Brought by
People whose
Children loved one
What killed
Nobody said they know they will know
Okay
But the General Public
Mr. Jones
The question before you
Is whether you're capable
Stating the name
Any other
I mean I can probably Drive some samba names when I'm done I'm done
No you're not.
So the answer is no
You can't do it sure I can do it
That's is
Heavy-duty yeah
Yeah it makes me think
That
As as bad as it was
I do think that when Alex was on the stand
Both Mark and Chris
Had to of
Maintains a large amount of restraint because they clearly know where to press the button to
Make Alex dance
You know like
If they wanted to make Alex really explode
They had the buttons
I think I think probably yeah
Yeah I think they chose to make sure that he only exploded as much as he did
Well yeah you don't want to derail things too much I believe
And Maddie does point this out and touch on this
Partner's name because
He use the picture of him when they had the shooting in Pakistan
That's Lenny his father gave him a
A strike a copyright strike for
That name is somebody that Alex is actually
I've had much more engagement with because
Of the
Harassing of
Mr. Posner over the picture of his son
Yep and so the
Question of what are any of these peoples names
I don't think Alex does know any of them
And it's an interesting Dodge to be like they're just going to edit this together in some kind of way like what kind of way
Are you worried about people editing you saying someone's name about like that's absurd
It's clearly evading
Having to recognize publicly that you don't care enough about this at all
To even know the names of the people who were murdered that you have
Blind the only people
Quotes
Editing this
Or putting it out even a little bit
R Us
And it sounds way worse when you say that
And if you said no yeah we both would have been like well yeah of course he doesn't know any of those and I would still think that's worth,
Oh I was honest about it that no Sky Fiat and I don't think
I probably play it like a four-minute clip
2 if he had you no honor the memories of the people you know
And recognize that he did understand the scope of the impact
Want people to cuz it is hard to really like
Grass this but
If Alex had done that
You would have cut that clip and we would have both been like can you believe this like it would not have been something like
This doesn't fit within our narrative we bought that beat hell yeah put that in there it would be very interesting
To have this demonstration of Alex having some Reckoning
Of his own action total time spent thinking about it I'm under
Standing public is no worthy as what just happened
Totally and what happened another way to go
So Alex said
Robbie Parker
Was acting
In the press conference
Unfortunately
Seems like he's still kind of thinks that what he was doing tonight
Deposit
Do you watch that
Set the time
Mister Parker acting
When
His daughter Emily
Being somebody would have been
The first
Was he acting when he said that
Nectifirm
But it's time
You thought he was acting when he described
His daughters
Personalities
Is being one who
Wood Consulting
Yes
In the classic area of activity doesn't, but I understand sometimes Highway
Car stereo
If Amy looks like it sounds like
Also thought that
Complex ways people deal with things that were more years
Mainstream media live so much that people lost faith in the system
So many times it's not true of people conduit
Mychelle because I do question everything
I'm also made mistakes in the process
Mr. Jones
The
That looks you like
Academy Award
What I'm telling you is that
Directions to
You just described it as it looks like Academy award-winning appenzell you right there's a fire
Right now it's just a second ago you were sitting here
You said that that looks like Academy award-winning acting to you doesn't it okay
Gross and I think I think you are totally right about the button and I think that one of the buttons
Is making Alex watch the stuff that he lied about
You know like it
So easy for him to look at that two seconds of Robbie Parker appearing to laugh or
Whatever and run with that but what he has a very serious aversion to is having
In his face
This press conference
That is like this is what you were calling acting
You know like this
If you are saying that you watched the whole thing this is what you're lying about not just
That little snippet you're lying about all of this
And I think that Alex human-level recognizes his monsters
Yeah it isn't like being a monster it is a little bit like
Picture of Dorian Gray kind of s*** right there like he just cannot bring himself to look at what he actually is
Yeah so fascinating
Cuz it's 8:00 yet
He knows what he is he can't not know but to be confronted with it they somehow
Different
It's fascinated really is it's like what happens to human brain
You know you what you want to study is that you dislike ICD Ysidro donate his brain to science after he died
Convert this couldn't it couldn't hurt
We could learn something at least we could throw his brain around like a football another option
Could just be booze
There is something
A dynamic scented play here that I think is really also a button
For Alex and that is
Questioning his integrity and questioning his bravery
She has none. Bookout's use willing to admit that he thought that this look like
Like actic but for some reason
He is
Really refusing to say that he called Robbie Parker and actor which he absolutely did
I'm so Maddie is pushing on that and then biscuits
F****** ugly
When you claimed
Robbie Parker was a crisis at
What you were claiming
Was that he was fabricating
And wine
Star correct
No no
How could you be a nap
Lying
About the death of his
Instill
We look at all of these events and some of it stays some haven't been and everybody questions things more than ever now
Explain to you
That the internet said they thought it was fake I looked up Ciara looks like he's acting
And then and then and I went back and forth whether it happened or not
A long before I got sued I said no I think it happen
I mean
Question
You like to tell your audience that you're the tip of the spear
That's what you say I want to come
That's what you prefer yourself as right
Nea
You already even willing to sit here Underoath
Any knowledge what you
Robbie
Enact
Acknowledging
That what you were saying was
Mister
Parker
Fabricating
Isn't that what
This is what this is acting this is for HBO on your career you're the one that live off of Tango kids
Going on around here
His dad lied about being in Vietnam and combats you guys are all fake
Subjects which is what we're getting along just know that his dad never went about it stolen Glory
Okay
You're wrong.
You want you want to I mean we can stay here third day
And you can go on your ass like you're on your lunch or whatever you want
Mr. Jones
Instantly destroyed for lack
Yeah it's a mess
Yeah I would move to strike that for just general
Good person reasons to have a little bit of an outburst cuz he has a flair for the
Dramatic at the same time
This is coming out of a question that he can't face
That you said
You know you're supposed to be this person who at is principles and in all this anyway
Yet you lack the spine to even just sit here and own up to the mistakes that you've made
If this is a mistake
And you just got something wrong you had some bad sources or whatever why why can't you just
Admit you said he was an actor
And what that entails what that implies death get the Dodge this was like oh the internet started look like acting and I said remake
Maybe it look like acting in your own backstory in order to make it more palatable
You can't admit it to yourself
Yep
Howard a big dog and you're just a tiny yapping puppy you coward
Week
Week-by-week how is it that you I don't understand how you can have that much bravado
Whenever it is that lack
The tip of the spear is Al Dente noodles
No
The one of the things that Alex one of his claims in relation to Robbie Parker was that
Prior to him giving his press conference giving him a card of what to say
I like the media or government was telling him what to say
Well
Now sure
And Alex has to deal with the fact that that's based on nothing
I am that was baby out of thin air
A little bit
You see the headline their father of Sandy Hook victim asked
Read the card
Seconds before
Press conference
When
We just watch the video you didn't hear
They didn't hear him say read the
Can you play it again for me now
Cuz you just watched it
You didn't hear him say read the card did you
Objection
Start
There's a statement attributed to you
At the bottom
Where it says
In the second sentence after you offer your condolences to miss
Mister Parker
It appears that members of the media or government have given him a card
And are telling him what to say
What you said right
But you said right it appears
That members of the media or government have given him a card
Correct
I guess I picked up on some of that there yeah I don't ever remember this text is going to make sure you're welcome
Wow did you see anybody in the video that we watched give Mister Parker car
No I must have been complaining it was something about a wrong
Did you see anybody tell him what to
Say
I wasn't looking for that when you play it can you play it again
I'm just asking
Jackson
Who were the members of the media or the government
Your point
Jefferson question Masky
You you put out a statement
5 days after the shooting that said members of the media or the government
Give him a card or tell me what to say I just asked you
Dragon watch that video
Woody somebody told me
Injection Italian contacts
I told you what I thought he said it's different than what I was saying there so late I think there's that I'm going to watch the video did you see anybody
Tell him what to say
So based on
Yeah
Yeah it does really seem like Alex does not get the point is genuinely
Yeah it's it's it's almost impossible to tell if he doesn't get the point or if he's just so aware of
I like
How important it is for him not to get the point
Man just feels like he really doesn't get the point that it feels that way too but it might be naive
He is just a bit like
I don't know I really don't think he can tell the difference between whether or not the things he says are true
Or not true
It might not matter to him
You never think that's clip made me think of that would be an interesting exercise
Take things that Alex has constructed conspiracies out of in the past show him the same Source material and then ask
Ask him what his conspiracy was about it from memory that's a good one
Have you come up with a different computer would like find some of
Other detail and be like oh that must be what I was suspicious about
Cuz he probably there's probably no consistency right doesn't mean anything let's let's take it the opposite direction
Direction get rid of Alex entirely
But let's grab some of the things that he said
And convince
Three random strangers to guess the conspiracy theory for money
At the end of the round Whoever has the most money wins so it's not a terrible idea
Another interesting idea would be take
Three things that Alex made a conspiracy out of mno4 thing and see if he could pick out which one was
That wasn't you might find suspicious
Makeup a similar conspiracy theory
And see if he can tell the difference between them whether or not there's what detail is different between your version and the made-up version
Apply the scientific method
None of this is repeatable
One thing I found pretty disgusting
Was that other purely play the clip of Robbie Parker for Alex
Engineer
Your Alex laugh
Keep playing
Play Robbie Parker
He seems to not really appreciate the gravity of
The situation in the context of stuff
To the point where he
Still thinks it's funny
The waiver to Robbie Parker walks up to the mic
Yeah that's
I don't have a bowl to me I mean he's he's really moved into the
Uncanny valley
For me I've liked
Human behaviors like
Everything he does so very similarly represent what human would do but then there's something like this where you like
There's something missing man there's something missing something
Something's not there I don't know what it is but your unlike all the other humans that I know
Yeah yeah I don't know if it's something that's missing or something that's trained it's been sort of ingrained in him
Overtime
I mean obviously we wouldn't be at 700-plus episodes about somebody who wasn't like
You are
You are not like other people or a unique person who have commanded 750
Episodes of our show I will I will give you that you are uniquely f***** up
So Maddie points out to Alex if he lies everyday
This is not taken well
Why not
Oh really
So why you got to lie detection
What are the times
Was
When
You
Claim
Terraria civilian
I
I planted c****************
In materials that you sent us
That's correct
Directions
Objection
My partner
Sorry what now
Mr. Jones
You I'm going to ask you
One more time before we
Not because me and said that we file fraudulent financial documents we didn't do that mr. Jones
You did and the court found that you did
Jexi
Oh boy
Abusing people in this world
Directions didn't stop addressing attorney Blumenthal
Understand that
Stop doing that
Okay yeah things that's a mess
Yeah so yeah the mafia there the mafia and they run the state the courts right
That was a barrage in a short. Of time really thought about this because it's so bizarre this
It's like this.
She said that you're the mafia or whatever
The only reason that Norm would respond the way he did is if he's involved in this claim
I'm somehow Norm told Alex I feel like that's one of the only conclusion I can come to
Because he sang Just touches on privilege and so it has to do with something that involves confidential
Russians that he had with Alex
And so I don't I don't know what to make of it exactly but
It's f***** up 50 years old
Bucked up I will I will tell you this and I I swear to you I could be wrong
But this is one of those moments where I feel like I can penetrate the veil so to speak
Norm was trying to explain information from a conversation that he had with
The other lawyers
And Alex could not understand it
So Norm said
Well basically
What they're saying is he's like the mafia and they're going to end Alex took that to me know you're saying that he
He said he's the mafia that's interesting I swear to you in my brain I can
Feel it happening jump off your scenario
Suggest another possible scenario same setup basically
But Norm is trying to explain away to Alex why they're going to lose this case
Because we're 100% done this all wrong
From Barnes but I am a great lawyer but we're up against the mafia Alex
Could be an explanation I don't know whatever it is it's something weird and Norm is likely to
Really jumping up to be like shut this down shut this down
So we jump now to the Boston bombing because that happens little bit after the same
I hook shooting right and what do you know Alex called that fake the day of also
In April of two
4 months
After
The tragedy is
Sandy Hook
The Boston
Yes
And
You went on the air that night right
Yes
And
He claimed that the Boston Marathon
I said it
Look like
Yes was a lot of wood on Ali's lot of
And you knew that
Right we we we we talked to we had silver crew headband
It was there
Attribute
And look, he's robbed his brother or brother-in-law was there
And then they created a conspiracy out of how he didn't want to talk to them
I don't want to be on leave me the f*** alone
That this is now making up with exactly said but I would imagine it was
This is insulting forgot that it was Rob do
Sing it made me realize going to rob buza uncle is a FBI agent who is at Newtown robkins brother-in-law is the boss
Family members are all over the news stories
You've got a cartoonishly large family
Like I'd like you very many
Is Nurse Joy in the Pokemon series like they're all exactly like him though they're just all my cousin
It is a conspiracy and everything
We could bathe in on a long game to ruin Alex is like this all done
Things to justify calling the bombing fake and so he does that by
Pointing to a news article about how disrupted Terror plots
A lot of them have FBI informants it
Zayn Malik
I got to look pretty handsome
Oklahoma City
Fast and Furious Allstate station Aurora
Nnsy eroding
It's comes to you for
The Comfort people that are going to
Challenge the system and that and that they believe basically are on these tablets for payroll people build it tonight or Sunday
And the truth that you gave them
On the day of the Boston Marathon bombing
Was that
The bombing itself
Correct
If it look
Can you tonight also get me that article
That shows that the New York Times ran
That 95%
I'm sorry that according to your time
95% of terrorist Acts
Are actually committed by the FBI
Sure
So we're going back to the Boston Marathon bombing
The truth that they came to you for on the day of the bombing
Was
Your claim
That it was staged
Correct
That's what you said right
To The Forum, what happened
Is everybody for looking at it and we're coming out
Happening
And we do that
Islamic Terror plots
Provocateur and then staged
Body up bi
That list would probably not another one of those
And that's what you told him
Assumption that it's an Islamic Terror plot is weird because I don't think that was even necessarily
Something that was being discussed at certain but of course if you listen to the clip italics
I had its beginning of this
Saying that domestic Terror doesn't even really so that wasn't a possibility really
Yeah I think that it's it's a fun defense Sprite 2.2
Then there are articles that have discussed the dynamic of
Asians into
The FBI being a little overzealous and trying to encourage
People to carry through
I would attach to the point where they could be arrested if I
Do spending all of this time yeah yeah but it still doesn't really help Alex's argument as much as he thinks it does
And it doesn't stop them from just still thinking that
The Tsarnaev brothers were patsies
I said it I said
It could be real
We decide
Could be Muslim
Or homegrown Terror
Right
Okay
Which means
You tell your Auntie Susan 95% chance
That it's
Stage by the government right
And then you go on
Even though I said there's a 5% chance
You know I've never seen the Easter Bunny
Domestic terrorism
Almost all of it is is beautiful totally dead provocateur
That the two
Definitely
Right
And that's true even the one of them
Murdered an MIT police off
Correct
Okay
And it's true even
Admitted
He was involved in the
Second what
You know that
Dzhokhar Tsarnaev
It's not yet.
Cuz I mean you just testified under oath that both of them working
Underoath steaks I got to remember that
Alright
We can make mistakes baby here's what happened to hear Alex is narrative at the time because
Cuz when johar was found here
And it always never going to be able to talk again it's perfect you know that was the
The Narrative of the time they killed the one in Silence the other
Alex is just kind of Forgotten basically that Joe Hart still alive
And so he's just turned it into they're both dad and his mind cuz he doesn't give a f***
Beginning doesn't care now
Night of the bombing
Was a big night for Infowars
According to Chris Maddie everybody except for Alex he's confused about it
The Boston Marathon bombing was actually a very big night for him
Sports Direct
Jackson
I don't remember
You were going
What happened
Do you not
Remember why that was a big night for Infowars
Who is damodar
He's a
Live around here
Professional wrestler and
Talk show host
In a former employee of yours
Workforce for about 6 months ago
And then
With a contract
Reporter for you
For years the RAF
Are correct
Some Eminem and Nei that he kept saying that he worked to us when he wasn't
Order
I would have dialysis
Invader press conference on the night of the Boston bombing but there's a reason Alex is confused
News about Maddie asking about that
He's probably forgotten about that one since batondy did a way more offensive disruption to the press conference on April 8th
Teeth which gleefully broadcast alive
Here's a clip of Alex's excitement just before that press conference started
Being fully aware that he was going to yell promotional shape for Alex
At the expense
Ava terrorized City
We will provide you with information as it becomes available
Galaxy very excited
Giving you a live coverage on that
He's so excited he's breaking into him takari and David night or hosting
It's be like already disrupted the first press conference
There's already a precedent for this and I'm going to do
He's going to go he's going to push it even further
Super Clock man
Alex didn't remember that because you get so much brass
It's no big deal for him
On the night of the Boston Marathon bombing the reason that it
Because
Mister batondy ass
The question at a nationally televised
Nationally televised presidential
Okay I thought it was days later
I remember
I'm liking this request
I don't know
You know what I'm talkin about
That was a big deal
Are you only remember something happened on that you do with the way the press conference
I understand for you guys like being the media wants a big deal or whatever those might
We can break
And if you want to
His lunch order now red
Sure they get some steak I think
Time is of the essence
I understand that you got to have the food delivered
Come back from getting the food order and look it's not a big
Deal that Dan batondy interrupted this press conference Alex gets press all the time man
Do you recall
That mister
Vedonde
Asked
Question at a national
Televised press,
Yes I do and that was a big deal
Portrayed
We have a lot of big deals but yeah that was it was it was definitely interesting from this was 2013
So this was 9 years ago
Right
Correct
Infowars to get that kind of national exposure at that time
With a big deal
Know if you want to know technically going on with George Noory on Coast to Coast AM he saw the right. It's the back then it was at least
This is your auntie inspector
Going on other people's big shows
Talk radio even though the media ignores it you are a guest on somebody else's show and that was a big deal
And I would say him y'all that out of that press conference
It was you know where you know
Good job
But basically the question that's not that big a deal
Here are a couple of clips from the 18th of Alex
Not that big a deal
We broke the record
Centrism
Oh man doubled the traffic
If ever gotten
Ever because
No certainly.
We are about
Oh my God
Just during this window
It is 100
Yeah so he doesn't play those clips for him but it was a big deal
The coast to coast that the real people he was so excited about the idea of his name
Infowars being broadcast on a platform that wasn't
It mcneish weirdo world it is very much like
I mean
This is this is kind of the way that Colonel Travis would want it to go you know like he got drunk and celebrated every
Free tiny Victory along the way and now he's about to be over
Come by the entirety of a f****** Nation thank God
So we know that Infowars with the quickest path to getting hired there is to yell at
Liberals at a rally or something
Minimum
It was contests
Ary the contest
He
Materials public contest
Incorrect
Melissa
Your audience
Submit us
You know you're
Some tape
Somebody to hire
Correct
Yes and you ended up hiring dammit. Another gentleman Jakari Jackson Azura's
Texas from Rhode Island
Correct yes
Restart
Correct
At some point
Early
2000m
Thirteen or thereabouts
Alexa come back up
Turo
Correct
Yes because
He had left his
White diamond
Scolipede
I let him go is reason left
OU fire
Suicide
Developing into a Howard Stern deal
You know
It's just that I
I wasn't looking for Howard Stern type character
And that's what was turning into
Longer was actually on the payroll working right now
But despite
The fact that he was
Somebody you fired
How would you describe the reason you fired him because he just we wasn't doing the stories that you told him to do
And it was his overall demeanor
He was he was he was going
I told him we were sending one reporter to the Jenna 21 conference
I said don't go to anyone to it
Yes
Is there any other reason
Just wasn't taking Direction
Wow Siri was getting into a kind of thing
You know he was he was around
You did the Boston bombing stuff and then I kind of going to have
Yeah it wasn't really working out anymore we had a connection with him I don't really even know his name
Man if bongino listens to this
This is the first time he's going to find out what Alex really feels about him cuz then we remember.
Them for it sure if they weren't bad I wouldn't need to know either name
But it is he seems to eat loves Alex Rim his in his
Deposition he was like Alex and I are great friends Alex is so nice to me I like working with them
We haven't heard the batondy deposition yet
Well the deposition is from
Connecticut earn more about what
Okay subject framing of the
Firing of badonde tiles up at
But it's a nice first effort
Opening Gambit
So throughout this and there's a couple points where Norm tries to go off the Record really fast cuz he wants to make like a joke
Joker tell a little story
And I got some of them aren't worth
Mentioning it's all I think we're actually caught and we're off the Record
But this was recorded and it's
F****** nuts
Naked teens
I just have
Joe Carter
So this takes me back a long way
Stunning turn of events in New York
Yasso johar Tsarnaev took a Norms nice to prom
Junior prom
There's no
There's Five Guys there's five guys on this way
This is absurd what the fuk just happened what did I just hear
Alright every any any small small world story is now gone
Northeast
Dand so Alex believes that the traffic Spike that he saw
Right nothing to do the unrelated completely unrelated
Your
Monthly users
Went from 5.5 million in March
211 point
6 million
In April
Correct people TuneIn
To my show when there's big eventually that way more listeners
Well one of the reasons why on your website
In April's because
You got damn daddy yelling about enforcer Prescott
Directions
But it is getting traffic and successful bad
Number for dogs
Not bad
So
We just heard him say that the traffic was 50 times what it ever was
Immediately after she interrupted the press conference so
I think I can go f*** himself with that nonsense
So the question becomes
Batondy wants to Sandy Hook
A couple times
In 2014 and in 2015
Alex
You sent him
Tries to be slippery
And if it's unsuccessful
Youth Orchestra.
Sandy Hook
2014 correct
I mean I mean I definitely was he was going there and I think I was
Do you understand my question
I'm asking you did you send him
Yes or no in 2014
I was going there
So I'm going to ask my question again
You sent him to Sandy Hook in 24
Digimon
I don't remember fair enough
That the lasting he covered for Infowars was the Boston Bomber
That's what you testify Jordan
Even get that wrong
You lied about that
Is because
You knew
She covered Sandy Hook for you and you knew that was a problem for you
No I just told you that for us
Mr. Jones
When you testified in March 2019 you didn't know what I know now
Uh-oh
I don't want to hear that
Especially not from a lawyer know
What do you know
Do you know now
14/25
Are you going tonight
Saying that I didn't want to do stuff for us. Remember the times I've Jackson he's being cut off
To cover Trump rallies in 2016
You deny it
I believe that's what I was getting at about
The pain
Because as soon as you were sued
You instructed your staff to go and figure out when was the last time you paid.
Did you not
Objection
Because you would think you were asking how long you work there and I had to figure that out
Real that's what you guys want
Impending
Shut up shut up
If the only experienced that you have with the American legal system is through this show
How could you not think that every law situation isn't like who ordered the code red like this is
It is
But like me have to make the hard decisions
I don't remember I'm in the media all the time these are something blow me like
What are we doing man yeah this is insane yeah it is
I think a fair assumption would be that he asked about the payroll with it on because he wanted
You know what the paper trail was
Not according to Alex.
What did you last talk to me
Years ago
Like how many years
Remember it's been years
3 years 4 years on a
Did you call him after your deposition and text
I don't believe so no
You can speak to mister batondy
On the telephone after you were deposed
Texas
In the presence of a lawyer
I do not
Melissa no
You did not call mr.
Padatti do apologize for the way that you miss characterize your relationship with him when you testified in Texas
Do not remember doing that you didn't offer to having down to Texas
What's for dinner
I don't know who that boy was it was with you
No I don't
Did you put the lawyer on the toxin expediting
Really right next to you
Nn
You and the lawyer told Mr batondy that
You can talk about
Lalibela restaurant at drinking or something I remember something
Warrior orbital position
Dating
Publicly
Getting reports of your deposition in the press and
You said about him was
Cake
I think if you're Alex
And
You're getting these questions and they're fairly specific like an invitation to dinner and some like that
Can I got to assume that this is coming from Baton d
If you want to get wildly paranoid they have your phone calls
Recorded they were spying on you or something five eyes was watching
Tamper with our Witnesses you remember that buddy do you remember how the presence of a lawyer
Some weird fantasy where you can go meet him in the middle of a parking garage and witnessed an
A
Your text messages we have everything
Wawa not to be there when I made the call I was wearing a trench coat
What If instead of deepthroat being there
He just f****** emailed it exactly like what
Yep
So there's some conversation about
Financial stuff
I answer like Alex's compensation makes millions of dollars
Documents that involve his drawers from the company and income from youngevity
And then some stuff about pqp are the company
That's how you know
Had supplement to then it sells out
He doesn't know that he owns never heard of my life
Has been come other than
To draw you took
Open the company
Not that I can remember of any substantive
Deformed Pikachu
Yeah I have to have you talked to
Stuff
My dad
What is peekyou
It is a
Company
Everything combined venditto
Weight loss
A company
For sale
Yes
What's your ownership
This year
I don't know that
Daddy maybe none
Big ditch
Good try
Sold out there maybe to work
I know my dad has some other
But wouldn't you know
Who held
Tldr
80%
Oh my God
You guys have that
You don't know that
Do you put on screen pouring its
Unfathomable that someone to be oblivious of this
Like it's just with you
Strains credulity to imagine negotiating tactic all right how much do you think I own I'm going to throw
Zero to start now what are you going to come back with
100 alright I wasn't 1% maybe inasmuch as
Like he doesn't have ownership
Properties that he owns it on them
Cool
So let me tell you something
The real shrewd businessman I can't get a dime out of that guy
He is running me wild
So investigation was released at a certain point
Answers to the
Alleged anomalies that Alex is so concerned about some of those
The question becomes when did you really
Did you read that and Alex
Obfuscating gear for no reason
At the end
You are aware that
Connecticut state
Attorney
Issued his
Rapport
Concerning his investigation
What year was that
There was a report
That was released in November
13 you remember that
Yes and then there were supplemental
Reports that were released in December
Correct yes
And did you read both reports
Amarillo Canal room
You do how do you pad your payment
I don't
This all gets foggy
Later they were for what they weren't really don't remember remember some big big big part of the hubbub was
Philosophy wasn't being released the public wanted and they weren't releasing do you know I just asked you a question
So
In response to that question you've already testify
That you review both
Reports that were issued in
And now I'm asking
How did Utah
I don't remember how I obtain another remember when I reviewed the last breath
Well you would have reviewed them right then
I mean
Review the right whenever came out whenever
Okay but that's something that obviously you would have done
Given your
Clean that
It was a hoax
Like I said I don't remember
Are we lost
Yeah but I read a lot of stuff
There was only one shooting in
In 2012.
Clean the light to 20
People
That you would call The hoax
So wouldn't you have wanted to see the report of the State's Attorney's
The office when it was
Investigate your claim
Exactly how
Okay but wouldn't it have been your practice
Just Wynn
Unofficial report Lake
Came out on an event that you
Books to read it as soon as
Wewewewe doesn't try to do stuff like that
I miss you but you wow
Don't you person is being honest I don't remember when
Okay so this is so easy for Alex and he could have gotten out of this yes I read it
I don't care I don't trust official delegation
That's the point yeah I've never believed any of these things why would I it's my standing policy that the media is
Full of liars the government is full of liars and his investigation recovering s*** up
So I have a stated
Like primary position a default position of distrust
And I read it as casual reading it's a fiction novel it's a Dean Koontz novel
Show me to read at the beach
I don't believe this s*** is it is weird because it is so quick it's like listen to the reason we are here
Your right now is because I don't believe anything the government says are you asking me if I believed anything the
Government Center
It's it's a metallic seems to be trying to evade the question is if the answer I don't believe the invest
Navigation is sort of
Cuz then it looks like oh so you did know cuz you read the investigation and now you're not telling me about
About it because you don't want me to know that you did know
So these subjective Wolfgang halbig begins to come up
And Alex has asked about his credentials and of course we have to conclude that
Pretty much all of it just came from both gag
Dang saying I got all these credentials it was a suspiciously long list of credentials for what
One man to have said that he has tenure with the state trooper
Organization
I am to Alex eventually learned this was not the case so nobody
Really answer how he learned
Bad idea answer you stated their that
Mister how they had a long career as a state police officer
Correct
How did you learn that was
I just really wanted his help me God
Wasn't this a place that long
Just
I don't remember everybody.
Call Watson
Meetings are
Agreeing
What we thought
Watson was a few of the people didn't call today remember
Saying hey
Really got into it
Bellator
Jim Fetzer
I'm saying is that I
When
Happened when
People bring it up and I'll play Devil's Advocate
Not talk
Miss Jones
Move to strike
My
Question was
My question was
Who told you
That Mr how we had not had a long
Thank you
I have no idea
Dies I just I probably knew from the job of course you did
Read his credentials UE you're either that stupid or you're not
Choose Alex can't really argue as way out of saying that Robbie Parker was an actor
But there's there's something that he keeps saying and there's clips of him saying this
That multiple people were actors
Alex really has a difficult time explaining why he said that
You got people clearly coming up in a laughing and then doing the fake crying
You clearly got people where is actors playing different parts of different people
Say we clearly got people
Who are actors
Coming up and playing the parts at
Right
So you got multiple actors you're telling your aunt
Audience right
I just told you that
What's going on
Okay mr. Jones
You just saw yourself
Say words in
The words that you
You said were
We've got
We got
Actors
Playing the parts of different
Right
That's what you said
Who are the actor
That's what folks were talking about with the corner
Okay so here you referring to
The corner
An actor playing
Right or or something
Someone
Okay
Videos
The internet
You didn't just say
UK
We've clearly got
Play
That's what you say
So
And now what you're telling
Is that you are referring to
The corner
An actor was playing
That roll
And then another one
Right
Okay and who else
Okay so now you got
Robbie
Mister Parker
Is an actor
Play
Play Mister
She said
You're questioning
Clearly got it
Those were your words right
So you got Robbie
You got an actor playing the corner
Right
That's what they do
That's what you said
I don't know why you're continuing
Did you see anybody else on that screen
Okay I can't understand what you're saying
Understand that you're saying because it is too threatening to me
Yeah you know one of the things that I find interesting is how I'll attest a distance himself
Like from definitive
Claims it anyway
Kind of had as a thesis for a long time that is the enemy of any of these people to specificity you don't want to be me
Nail down to anything so it's like is that what you said that's the internet said no you just said that
And the one of the problems with specificity is that as you pursue it
These theories start to really sound dumb
Because the implications of these people being actors
Are clear like it's clearly not something that's well thought through by the people who promoted these theories right
And this is explored by Maddie in this next clip
About how like
How would this make sense that Robbie Parker isn't actor
If that then what else must be true us on Project Camelot like let's
Cheese this out and see how far these space aliens really go and essentially you know you get to a point where
Malatesta admit to basically everyone has to be in on it in order for this make any sense
It's important to understand how this can
Spirits
I'm in your mind okay
I'm asking operation Northwoods
Okay
Instead the kids death blow up the airplane
How you doing all thank you
Well let's just talk
You just told me about
What you think
All right and what you work
To your earphone your claim
Your queen
You're playing
In response to my
That
There's a fictitious
Person named Robbie Parker
The actor play
You'd agree with me
That by going in front of the camera to Millions annoying to people
There will be somebody who would know hey
I know that guy
You just answered that
Question
You think that is that a reasonable expectation
No
If
Somebody
What a wrecking
Somebody would have
Recognize
The person playing Roddy Piper
Isn't it.
That would blow the whole
Pokes
You know the potemkin villages
Now there's a potemkin village
By potemkin Village you mean
Everybody
Who was in the immediate community
Would have been Anton
That's what you mean that everybody in the community
Nearby.
Which would mean
Certainly all the parents
Of children
Text
Or maybe the new app
When you talk about actor
Clearly actors
Did you tell your own internet clip right now hey I'm just speculating
Could be totally off
Clips out of larger things I gave you
Did you say
Endocrinologist show you I could be speculating
Right you said they're clearly Act
In what you're striving for me is Atkins
A sandwich
Where there is
A mass shooting
That everybody involved in the mass shooting has to be in on the hoax right
Forge work
I didn't think if he and Alex would say yes
That seemed that seemed a little bit surprising
You're pretty satisfying because there is a recognition that he has that
Yeah this only makes sense if
Like
Its sprawling as hell he's got to be G
Yeah and it is appreciated
Just like
I know it's not a way that was it that was a pistols at dawn
F*** you for saying that get outside we're throwing hands how dare you there are a couple moments like that
I mean don't make human
Let so much salad
Alex one of the things that's really important for him in terms of framing his behavior
You're around Sandy Hook is he needs people to not be aware of how aware he was of wolf
Gang how big is action because if he is aware of them
Then platforming Wolfgang helping him fundraise
It kind of
Becomes problematic
I am so in this setting Alex tries to really limit his awareness
She knew that how big was going
And you knew that he was going up there
And you had
Mr. Crowley going to show just
A few days after that
Board of Education meeting
I don't remember me
Were you aware
That
Mr. halbig
When he visited Newtown
Had
Engaged in a confrontation at the newt
Firehouse
I know there were some complications
Remember that
Yeah confrontation
Police
United Way charity
Ida Bailey remember
Sinbad
People yelling at each other
Play
Yes
May 13th
2014 interview
Steve
What do you think really happened to Sandy Hook
Your will
So
You recalled it
Protagonist
I'm aware that
He had had
Confrontational
Eastern Europe
At telling with eight
Police cars at
This just reminded me stuff you know what you guys are actually helping me out today
How about that I didn't remember that yet so before this interview that you did with him you were aware of
Of him harassing people of United Way
You have an interesting way of trying to frame it is it a request that the police were stopping him from the butt
Happy that is it may you knew about it yourself
Number of
Things that I'm just not including in here and Maddie walks Alex through bun
Much of the alleged anomalies that how big had about the Sandy Hook right and then there's the explanation of
You knew this wasn't true so I'm not gay
Didn't include much of it except for places where it is a little bit interesting
Such as this the discussion of the
Bloomberg email
They posted this email
It has become
A new thing now
It's not so much about the Bloomberg Bloomberg email isn't the Bloomberg email it's right now maybe like a
The gun group
Bloomberg
That email that you're referencing
You never been able to produce
Abilify
There was years and years later like five years after
Plus I got six
But you're you're
Why don't you why don't you show the email to your audience
As further proof
I do remember all the shows
He was an activist
Get ready we need to be ready for the
Batman shooting
You should email
Yes it was a suicide
Gmail
Story
Explain that to me little bit more
In a communication saying get ready for mass shooting
Right
Understand the difference between email and Report
What did you figure out
Communication
You remember which
Which group
You were asked about that email
I believe so yes
Did you acknowledge in your Texas deposition that you are wrong that you did not
At the email you were referencing
Actually
Antenna
Did you refresh my memory
Can I use it
Have you got it all answer
Refresh my memory what they showed me
Well I mean you testified in
In Texas just a few months ago in December
I don't I don't
Talkabouttd
I'll walk out of here damn I remember this feeling
I hope you do because I'm going to ask you this tomorrow
So just it's it's on
That he has no memory
At a certain point if I'm if I'm Chris here
I'm just like hey everybody stop
Turn the cameras off all the lawyers leave Alex is just you and me
I promise you I will not say a word about what we talked about
What's argon okay
Stop gaslighting me you and I both know right and you and I both know I'll pretend that I have no idea if you just allow me
Little bit Mad Men especially when it's combined with the moving of the goalposts
You know like it's not a Bloomberg email from the day before now it's a group that put out a report or something
At some point
You know it's so vague as to be meaningless now whereas it was like a Smoking Gun for him before
No I did it is it is like
You have assaulted my reality for so long I need this from you right now just tell me you
Just tell me you know and that I live in reality and that you're a f****** liar
So we talked about this a little bit earlier but
Overwhelming sense that I get from Alex as I listen to more of these
Directions
He really seems to have an emotional shut off where he
Refuses to accept
Things about his past Behavior right and so like
You're asking about like did you review that show no I didn't
Probably part of the reason is because you don't want to have a fresh memory other
It's just it just
Thinks of cowardice
Gobble up John you is is that is that
I'm mentally don't think anybody could
Like me
All the time and be
Even have saying
Okay well I wish I was talking to Sandy Hook absolutely make mistakes yet
Man
Like my brain recoils from exit all I hear
That I have a coping strategy
Do not do not dwell on this route
It's just
Delicious dishes
Changsho
Completely off
That I
Just basically
Put this out of my mind
And I'm trying my best Anson
Just want you guys to have your antifreeze speech
Show trial
Get over with bigger stuff to your deal whatever
They just move on to whatever edit the next
Mystery
That's enough that's not respond to the question I asked you if you just want to say
I want to see this you know
Because there been several
That I or I guess
Warriors
AR
Uncensored
First Amendment
And I mean you you look at me with that
Face
But you
The Democrats are going Free Speech everywhere
Cancel culture
What brought this
AR
Family
Who lost
Children
And relative
Do you understand that
And I understand it's being used by
Democratic party the media
It wants you and I just hit the second over the first known as well
Like last week saying
Basically get rid of the First Amendment
And don't ask questions I mean it's ridiculous
It was used
Baby doll shows
And the now this is being used
As well
And so they may think you can compartmentalize this with
New York Times vs. Sullivan
Add Velveeta
Well this is going is he
Extremely
Dangerous river volume be
I understand.
And
Dad
And that's what that is I'm just telling you that I'm really trying to answer
Objective
Today's numbers
But
I've heard what you said
And so
Maybe we don't need to have
Speeches
Anymore
Arbor spots
Okay obviously a woe-is-me yes to this which is
Pretty tired I would
I think it's also like really disrespectful and
Shameful the way that this is
He's processing all of this
But I do kind of think
Dad based on the way he's describing this it is a coping mechanism for him
Deal with the fact that
You know he took and out of context
Deceptively edited clip
From when Robbie Parker was coming onto stage and he terrorized him
He doesn't want to recognize that the rest of that speech was a heartfelt
I think the moment of Grace honestly and end
I wouldn't want to either I get it I understand that but you like
The alternative here is just pathetic
At a certain point you have to
And you can see it just so clearly the way the star song we almost Cesar Moment of Truth
A lot of people will
Dumas Guru know in the way that he is it when Maddie is is
Is really trying to like
Okay fine you up
I'm proud of him
Battery for not
It's sinking his teeth and whenever Alex is like I'm tired I just want this all to go away like
Proud of him for that
You know but that moment where he's getting that you understand what we're doing here I understand you think the first time
Amendment 2nd Amendment all of that stuff but you know that it's about the families
Alex cannot let that sit for a sec
A media instantly using the families and they're all it has to be insta
Because if he is allowed to sit with that thought for a second
He's fought
He's f***** them
The recognition of that pierces his arguments 22 strong lady
Not even a breath in between
I also listening to this and this next clip also I mean it is definitely a sense that I get that lawyer should
I mean maybe it's never really needed to happen before but now they need an objection that is just shut up
Cut it out a******
Longitude meaning with speech
Ridiculous
Who are you
Mocking there
You have to understand that
All American
Abuela
The car all car
Tired
So then it becomes
Conscious and then
Everything
Media
And the Brain figures outlays
Cruises to horrible
Imagine
Children like that
Executed
Talk about this
The real quick will get back to this man during speech but
Dwayne is describing this this is not questioning things this is this is somebody who bully
Leaves that a group that he identifies as being a part of his being blamed for things that they're not
And then deciding that in order to not have to
Face that scrutiny that he imagines and not have to
Defend this group I will make things up about event that I find threat
Threatening to
Is that group it's bizarre it's it's not
It seems like if Alex can articulate this then he should be able to take the next step and
Recognize that he has done
Throughout his career if it fits this mold
Is
Just
Bulshit
I think. Questioning things it's up standing up to the establishment anyway
Know what's
What it is I think I ate it something that we is is really under examined but
I feel like what happened to the conservative right
Whenever everybody was like
Hey maybe racism and homophobia and all that stuff is bad right
Don't say that in public
Raped
They created a different language out of our language you know they created this whole
Okay well with water, we know what we mean when we say this right
But the problem is right we really saying exactly
Sending things I don't mean question things
That's not my language right
So we find ourselves in a situation where these two languages are at complete odds with each other because Alec
Language is built entirely around lying about what the words mean
Yeah they're made they're maybe we might need a linguist quite frankly to pierce through
You would need to understand all of the ways that they lie or that they tell each other the truth and lie
Lie to us you know I think that might be why are
Understanding of Alex's slightly different than a lot of other folks the immersion in the language
Of his b*******
Anyway here get ready for a bunch of that language right
I ran with it but I'm on I'm happy that
It's really true
I didn't consciously
Get up there
I try to misrepresent a lot of people
I've gotten somewhat better over the
Both want to say is that
Hey I'm not older has taught me how to do things better
Well
And I don't have a second
I said is almost
Like a form of that
It's happening everywhere work
People don't believe
Anything
From the corporate media with a dumber either because they've been lying
And it's really the systems fault
People
Have lost total pump
Cumberland silverware Thompson Center
And it is a real crisis and I were at right around this time
Pulling away
From everything
And I was Beau Bridges
And I'm Bill Hicks
And Chris
Crazy people playing my office and
And you know
Shanghai was covering up
Shooting in Texas and I was there
I was at first and I just started
Just cuz the media lie so much
Doesn't mean every time it is
And I saw
Let the craziness
Established 12 sensor on a stop anybody Quest
The other guy over here believing nothing I say
Finding reasons not to
Believe it
Friday's great lunch during of the Abyss
You know what went on here and then
As soon as I began to say I don't want
Michelle
You got the emails and stuff I don't want
So do people said that I was on the government payroll that I was covering up
Sandy Hook
You can imagine
So
The question I asked you was
Videos
And I'm going to
Exact same question
Answer my
So one of Alex's obvious strategies is just keep talking and hope people forget where this star
The question was who are you mocking In that clip
Mne everything he was saying had nothing to do with that it was just
Caulking
And it's things that he is
You know it's these wrote speeches that needs given repeatedly if these meaningless platitudes
Dudes and you know it's it it's really really effective because I think that generally speaking when you're not
Dealing with a lawyer who doesn't care about your b*******
You're going to be able to keep talking until someone latches onto one of the things that you're saying it boom you're off the topic
But yep that you don't want to talk about
Alex doesn't want to recognize that he was mocking this person
So I got to work in this room but maybe maybe everywhere else I believe that every lawyer in a
America should listen to this
Not to learn anything but because they should all feel jealous of Chris
Not because he got a billion-dollar judgment
Which is f****** great I'm sure a lot of lawyers I bet would wish they had billion-dollar judgment over there being only
Better is being norm and losing what they should all be jealous of is the moment that Chris
Bruschetta
F****** it is nice to papa papa
So the subject of Adan Salazar's article the FBI says no one
I was killed
In Sandy Hook Right comes up
We learned that that article was b*******
In a very interesting way
I don't believe the story at all but
After Alex tells this nonsensical story he throws a dawn under a bus
Just asking you today
About any conversation
You recall having with
Salazar
About this particular art
If sometime
A few years ago before lawyers product
I was born.
Somebody to coffee shop
Came over and said
Your f****** piece of s***
Their laptop looking to State Police
And then everyone in Sansome to Adan about it
And I'm a black guy
That was the first time I heard about it
Situating time
This conversation
Do you have the coffee shop I don't remember
And then you obviously from there
Had a conversation with Donna.
And you think that was before
This lawsuit was filed
Yeah they was like right around before the time
Rap for Trump almost went out of my San Diego cell.
Ashley
Are those all back then
Added somebody yelled at me
Amman
And then I remember saying I'm sexy I told you this is bulshit
We argued about it. I respected all I can only reporting all this stuff
Think about
No more CC no more no more this person yelled at me in a coffee shop
Wow
The next trial song
Alex has to testify in a soundproof glass booth
Alright
So we can see him there red button green button yes no
And if we need a more complicated answer there is a flap that will open that went nuts that would be interesting
I also think that more and more about this
I could have gotten a trial
Like
F*** you imagine if
There was a court case and they got to call people like a dawn a dawn B
All these people to the stand Alex would be huge lose
Harder than a default
It would be it would be worse if only I got lucky you didn't
Get a trial I mean what they call that dirty laundry in a court setting like terrible idea
Terrible idea if it was a criminal trial crimes would be
Just off mad
May I ask who will boy
Wolfgang and Alex's conspiracies continue
To be discussed
And Alex can't answer any of the questions about the this b******* they've been saying
Photos of
So I want to ask you
We about
Claim you made
Yeah
School of Art
You have a school of 100
Kids and nobody can find a
Woody talking
I don't know the context this years ago
When you say you have a
Not just one but a bunch of parents
Who are fake crying
Who you talking about I don't remember left Matilda videos I would have said that
When you say you have a photo of a bunch of
Kids
Two are still alive
That they say die
What photo are Utah
I don't know which one that is
What you talking about the Super Bowl
Photo that mr. halbig sent you
The audience maybe ohmygod Alex has already been deposed in Texas and had a long conversation.
About that photo and
How dumb it is
Tell me the answer here is very strange as if he doesn't
If you remembered that he should be a guy can't I don't know I don't remember she might be at
Like I don't know I don't know what I was talking about
I've no idea I must have banged it on something cuz I wouldn't just make it up
The problem of thought thought process again you don't want to recognize that
You just make s*** up and
When your face is evidence of making s*** up
I must have based it on something
Magoffin the
The illusion of it there is something there is is powerful
You know what this might be the ultimate test case for that that phenomenon of being
If you're confronted by somebody who fix something differently than you your natural defensiveness makes you defended
Position that maybe
If you weren't locked in that headspace
At you could slowly kind of tease your way out you know that kind of thing you know
The more forceful year do a year or disagreed with the more likely you are to disagree back with Force
What
Like of all the people who have studied that
What would it take
For Alice
You know
What would it take
Nothing
I mean like is there is it possible no you know like there's no possible way though I don't think bra
Another person
I think it would just take external circumstances you need to find a position where it be more profitable for him to
Recognize things
That's probably that's
Can sharkera force of nature or something
I wouldn't I wouldn't see the force of nature
Something something that is is outside of any kind of control what's the weather
A****** Sharpshooter shark papa papa
Yelp
Get up that shows that there was a giant in traffic on the day that add-ons article
And Wolfgang was on that correspondent with a big spike in Revenue
And Alex said something here that maybe he shouldn't have
Because it reveals
Potential
Failure to turn over data a man those crimes are tough to remember which ones are with this one
Norm tells him to shut up
And you'd agree with me
Bedroom three day. You published
False report
That the FBI
Headset nobody died at Sandy Hook
US Bank in traffic
I can show you times when we cover Sandy Hook Emily has left viewers
There
You've got
Other friends
Your business manager
Temperature
Sending
These
Did your data
About to put
Performance of the website
But
That them
Does analysis
These guys
African last money in the shopping cart so you know that
So it's something you can produce
That's right
Okay great but why don't you
Tonight when you
Take a break
If you have
Some sort of analysis
Documented
I joined at 80%
Show me 80% of the time
That mr. Jones cover Sandy
Either had
Flat Revenue
A corresponding relationship
Between
When you got her standing up
Is traffic
That should have been produced
Store store
Traffic
Okay well I'll tell you what I have a little bit of that to mr. Jones
Cherry pit
Almost 80%.
Is is it to the lower
End of of the shop
Data
Did you use
Did you do this
Warriors
Did you do the announced
No
This is really this really
A good Norm had two objects to just Alex talkin man
Yeah
There's a lot of problems with the idea that this exists first of all
Yeah that wasn't turned over that was
Required to be turned over there is an internal definition Within
Scores of the times that I was talked about Sandy Hook which would be interesting to compare to what they turned over
Seems like they didn't turn over everything so this is this is deeply deeply problematic for Alex
He's not just making s*** up which she probably is just making sure. That is a good like back door
For all of Alex's lawyers committing crimes as they could just be like he's lying about it and what are you going to say
You're probably right he is probably
So they end up looking at an article I believe it's the Arctic the FBI are
Articles
And Alex C use a banner on
No
Her DNA for Alex's not have ideas desert
Alex
Gets it in his head
That he can argue that the reason there was a giant spike in sales and traffic Ono
Cuz DNA force was back on sale for you telling me that Alex is going to try and win this case in this deposition
Right here right now
Pull up
We just pulled back up
Is exactly what you described earlier then
When you publish this article you were running
A
Percent off
Sale on DNA Force
Plus which
You're saying
Recently back in ShopRite
Yes we do
And
And your advertising
That was getting a spike in traffic
That week your website
Correct
Well you don't know
Sitting here today Underoath
Did that advertisement Randolph
On every page
Of your website on Netflix
Computer
And it replaces them on their whatever the Nevada
So we have a possible explanation that Alex's found
The giant spike in in sales because forces back on
This does not account for the gigantic spike in traffic
That wouldn't necessarily correlate
So there is some confusion but
You know there's also an argument to be made that
You had a sale that you were advertising on article that was going viral that was a lie about
Yeah maybe that doesn't actually help
But Alex is so excited he's so thrilled that he's found a way to argue that
That was a static banner and whatever we put there is everywhere
That's the number one Banner
Is Suzy in a foreskin
And if there are more
Sinbad
You're selling more
Yes but meet me at slowly but we didn't plan that make sense
We didn't premeditatedly
Amazon write that article
A product came back and then I'm like boom
Ygopro
And it's going to because of
The product
Popular
Has come back yet I know what sell stuff
Product
And it's also your pip
I mean your your your own best. We have it on auto-ship
Do you have
The first day
The auto-ship
Yes and
And the people that want to get it
You know how long this added been running
I'll buy the price
September 20th
Because BC
Do you know how long
Just got to try and get back
He got so excited to be like he's found a way that thinks
Is explanatory a way to get around this
Very clear piece of evidence they've all had one moment at least it everyday
Deposition that we've seen Dari I remember had a big one I can't remember exactly about what but I remember
For all the sudden like cuz she's been presbycusis Sunshine comes through the window
Pick 4 hours and then all the sudden she gripped on something and she's like I've got this
Can you possibly be there
Why are you sick like up for sports like what why are you game to like
See what you can do later gone near this is just shut down man
I can win what are you doing we're not in a winner lose to tonight situation
Disaster for you idiot
So Alex famously in his the clips of him saying
Play with actors
He claims that he did deep research
And so Chris Mattie that'll tries to figure out what was that research exactly
Didn't
The other stuff
I do want to ask
Some of that was wrong
Deep research that
You did
Please don't
What did you do
Videos going over there
Duration later Island
Only got her today
What's going on
You haven't shared with me
Did the Deep research
You personally over
Okay
We're almost at a bridge
Delicious
You said that you didn't deep
Alright
Now
I want under
1st and
Comprehensively is you
What that
Volume two
Research
Had led you to that conclusion
That the whole thing
So
What research
Watching videos reading
Transcripts
Curious
I just a whole background other things
It looked to me like
Of that
Pretty soon after this
That has nothing to do with this there's no research I guess maybe he could pretend like I looked deep
Ugly into Fast & Furious by like
That doesn't have to do with Sandy Hook unless you make it about it you're making
I watched videos what videos Roi watch transcript what transcript
That's a situation where you really have to like dig even deeper when you just use the word like okay
Before we get into deep freezer dodo Nono
The word research mean to you like a regular research before going to deep what's a regular razor made out of this
Ask me a question like I'm Alex okay
What deep research
Did you do I dug deep within my mind
I took Ayahuasca and I meditated and I spoke to the plant
That makes more sense than anything else you've said so far
Did my spirit Guru a problem because they're in this situation where they feel like they
They're on a battlefield you know where they can go battle
And maybe they can win or lose
But reality is you either have you can either go like
Non-Stop
Wall
I've just like I'm not answering I'm not answering I'm not answering or completely fictional
Commitment to not knowing anything and ask questions like what deep research dude you already know the answer
Obviously going to be empty words that means I didn't do anything
For Alex it didn't make they think that there's like a way out there's like some sort of way out and there's no way out
The only way to play this game is not playing it for you yeah well you should have done stuff differently a decade ago
Every year since if you're in this position you should just cooperate
Kitchens with yes or no and you get through it cuz this is not helping I mean
Stateville
They keep thinking like oh no the problem is they don't have another exactly
So if you said yes or no to every question
There are questions you would not have had the answer
True
Less bad because you're making yourself look bad because
The reason you're here is because the things you did that made you make you look bad
But you think you're going to peel these lawyers and Nathan amazing
So we get back to how big then and basically this is going chronologically throughout
You know the the
The events that happened to before right York Sandy Hook Alex's coverage of it as it goes through
And so
At this point how big is on
He has a
Reveal to Alex that his wife does not believe him right that was a fun one
Alex's asked about this
You did know I haven't watched it that looking Zone wife
Found him not credible on
Correct
I believe reminds me of its washing their clothes
Did that cause you to question whether Mr
How big Zone wife
But having heard that
Exxon wife
Found him not credible
You still
Promoted mr. Biggs
Right
I was just being nice
And it will you just be nice to him when you sent mr. bhadana TF2
The Connecticut
Just two months later
To report his activities
I want to see what's going on
Amazing
June
A 2015 Audi
The two months later you send mr. badanti up
Connecticut correct
I don't remember last
You'll never talk about Junior 20
15 last time
You're talkin about
Explain what happened to that I
Didn't want to be mean to me. It was a bad person
RAB do
Okay so for by June or 2015
You would said to Rob do another
I did not want
Downey report
Yes
Pop back up then I don't remember
I just asked you
Weather
I just asked you what it was your small intestine
Okay well that's what we're here to figure out okay
So your recollection
Is that by June of 2015
You had told Rob do
That you did not want them to Donnie reporting for you any longer
Yes.i'd puzzle before that and I'm sure you'll show me when they pop back up every dinner I can't remember
And you didn't have that conversation with Dan but Dundee
Yourself at that
Did you order
No I know I told Rob you told Rob
Prior to June 25th
15 that you did not want that.
For you right
Yes okay well this is a trap
But I was just being nice
Hey what are you going to do when all else fails
Fall back on politeness as your listen I'm a Texas boy
You just got to be nice if there's ever been a case for it's cruel to be kind
Here's my big failing with this whole Sandy Hook too nice to nice to people nice to the wrong people now
You get burned
I have it is it is weird
Listening to these these discs these depositions after all of them really start coming in
It's just like
They don't want to be held responsible
For anything they say
And I'm not talking about anything they said about Sandy Hook
I'm talking about if they were like a listen I'm going to go I think I just had a Coke and you be like did you have a Coke in the Blackwell
I don't know for sure if I had a Coke right now just be responsible for one thing you say
I am a on our Facebook group that someone asked me if I ever made the lasagna I said I was going to make
No comment no you did not yet
Sensitive
Just one thing
So Alex is now steaks position
Takes a position that is unspeakable for Alex well now we get to what will be
Is the rest of the deposition of just discussing dhanbad Andy and his trip to Newtown
2015 price
Now
This is pretty expertly.
I would say I think that Maddie does a great job of
Well I mean he's already trapped Alex with the putting a date on when he said to stop it with Madonna
So now he plays Alex some video of badonde and it's the video of him harassing the police chief
Right I am yelling at him
And he gets a good sir Alex to
Talk about how bad this is
You're aware that mr.
To Connecticut
In June 2015 report
Right
No.
Remember all this
Let's pull up
Exhibit
Hey
The gentleman
Blue on blue striped shirt
Okay do you know who he's trailing trying to ask question
WC it has truth radio show.com in the lower right-hand corner
And you see this infowars.com in the lower left-hand corner
Alright
And you're aware that
Mr. Daddy sent this footage
To Infowars right
I believe he publishes
Usually something then but still put in for
You published this video are you aware that
Okay so it's not true
We'll get to it but it's not true
That you didn't that he was doing his own thing and it
He wasn't up there for you
Objection does obsess over this point
I don't remember exactly when I believe it around then.
About that
I told you this song
Yeah so it's this is going to Cascade Alex's illusions
What he did with batondy
And their relationship become
Transparently alive
And it's fun to watch I will be honest it's you know there's this stuff that's really heavy with like a few
Choosing to say any names because he doesn't know any of the names of the children.
People who were killed the
Outburst and accusations they could that's not really that makes me feel a little uncomfortable
Delightful and
It's a real nice to watch Alex try and wiggle his way around like
Do this does feel like he's so filled with skewers at this point Chris might as
Kobe an acupuncturist
And now we're about to close the Iron Maiden door on his face
Buy a cameraman
Who uses some dirty language boy
And the person is operating
The camera who's that
Is your testimony that
That person
Was working as
Contract
Cameron
You sure about that
I don't know I don't know that person is
Can you pause it
Did you hear
The gentleman operating
The camera
Refer to this purse
Crooked corrupt
That's obviously not
Not good
Probably shouldn't say that
Yeah yeah that's usually not a good one to go with
So Alex is being shown this video and it's so inappropriate
He has no alternative but to say like yeah.
I was using that Infowars logo but he wasn't really ever even he wasn't allowed to this is bad behavior
We talked about this afterwards HR got on top of it my dad was right there
But yeah he tries he's just trying to pretend like we have no relationship
Deposit return
Sunglasses
Doing it
Let's play
Be actually
Before we go see the woman in the sunglasses
Is there now
Yes we could use another
Bestie
That's Pat llodra
First selectman
Is that matter
I mean
Radio show
Putting in Fort Worth on it I was telling Rob dude
Amish town before that Illuminati
GoodRx
He did over that hospice while farting then
And then he just kept doing stuff is the auxiliary person I don't think he got
I just
Clear answers on all this
And answer that people about it
This footage
Stop
You are correct
Okay haven't seen their contact in there
That is highly
Inappropriate
Well I mean
Our government lied about wmds and directly storytimes highly highly wrong
You guys look Heroes everything
But I mean I don't remember all the details of this and I'm answering
Finger questions
I just asked you
Weather
The footage we just saw is entirely in a
People to make their own opinion out of that first amendment
Objection
I mean I don't like how
But that's the Kraken right
You know what you expected a Dandy
No not that
Let's keep going with 100b
Yeah so I mean
Do you have the deflection
Question secondarily you have this video that I was being shown there is legitimately no way
You know Alex can't spend this
There is just like the cameraman called people f****** piece of s***
Yelling you're going to prison this is not like
Anything you could stand behind
It's tough It's a disgrace.
Yep I did I didn't know this you did Alex Alex
Right now you are wearing an iHeart but dandi tank-top do you not understand what we are doing right here at a bunch
To the warehouse along time ago and I take the laundry day
It raises the value I just signed all of them buddies back in the day
You know you got these people who are making a crime accusations to people in Newtown
Alex has posed the question of whether or not the first amendment protect you
If you make false crime accusations
Operation
Did you see mr. madani Derek use
Cheap Newtown Police of perjury
But that's personal run
Okay anybody saw he accused the chief police of crime correct
Yes
And you have no idea what the basis for that accusation was
I mean I don't know
Is it is it somebody's personal it right mr. Jones
To falsely accuse somebody of a friend
Is it your view
That the First Amendment
Protect somebody from
Falsely accusing somebody of a crime
If that is if that's his opinion
I don't know the context of us ever again, not after no contact
My opinion
Okay but you know that it
If I were to accuse you of a crime mr. Jones and I have no
A reasonable basis for doing that
Protect
You claim
You cleaned up because the judge says
We gave you frogs on financials is true cuz
America
Mr. Jones that you're trying to
Evade
A very
Clear question I've asked you
About
The First Amendment
Can you falsely accuse people of crimes with no basic let me ask you a question
Is there any sort of law
That says
It is against the law
To falsely accuse someone of a crime
First member baby okay nevermind so Alex believes that you could do that to public figure
Somebody
Definitely
It's different to say if you were mine
Or that versus public
I understand you guys want to broaden to give her the First Amendment
Action
When he put himself out there
Shooting
Depressed
And that gave you the right to lie about anything
Mr. Jones
Have you ever sued anybody
For defamation
I don't know
So that kind of
Really seals the
All the evidence you need that the I don't remember or I don't know answers aren't sincere
River suit somebody
I don't know
But yeah it is
Of questions was
Devastating Broward
He saying that you didn't your First Amendment right to be able to make false accusations against public figures
Man
Is Robbie Parker a public figure well Robbie Parker gave a press conference after the shooting and therefore became up
Figure out who you are then able to fall asleep
Yep we're excited by that
Oops po-boy
A boy that's good that was fun to see Alex kind of
It is it is always fun whatever
Like
There's more than one step and I don't like to this this is a compound series of questions
That all have a different circuitous route
To really pin him into this into this hole right here right and he doesn't understand when somebody's
Walking around him with it in a circle tying it tying a rope
He doesn't get that he's like they're walking away from me so if I just hang onto this rope I'll never get caught
Yeah he he does
Does not seem to it's partially but it feels like obliviousness
Doesn't care
I don't know
If I was going to hunt Alex Jones alright
Not even a thought would be given to walking out into the forest with a gun
Not even a thought
I would just lay traps everywhere and put Pizza on things and I guarantee he would be caught sooner or later
Discussing this footage the damn dondi ever Newtown
I mean it's just Alex can't deny it's it's expensive stuff
Do you know whether Infowars
Stream
Uneven Channel
I don't believe so was I when I saw this
Stop singing
Change the subject
I don't think a bad person
I just saw the stuff and I definitely
Dentist office
Remember all the time frames or when
The process
You just
Right you just testified under oath
You just testified under oath
Saw this footage
And yeah
Use an expletive
To whoever you were talking
Tell him to stop
What time was it
I don't remember
How the heck can you test
The by Underoath just now
Let me get my porch now
How the heck can you testify under oath
That you know it was around this time
When you don't even know when this was
I remember this was Santa and I said this that I don't like
You're the boss
There's a lot going on.
Footage did you not
I don't know that
Well
If you look at this footage when it came in
And you saw how inappropriate was and how much you didn't like it
You certainly wouldn't would you
Gotcha
If you'd seen this
Came in
And you were so appalled
Write check
Play song
Have a recollection
As you sit here today
A killing anyone
Tell Bambi.
Not that he doesn't work for us anymore
He's not using
Check
Noah schnapp
Reconvene
So
Yeah I mean you can kind of already see like what needs to happen for the
Peanut the stick to fall in the Box
To that string of questions about all of the things that
Didn't this video all of these things inappropriate absolutes go ahead and enjoy that
Isn't this the reason
Jones
That you lied when you testified in
Batondy was not
Directions
I don't know why I get things wrong
Love Stuff
And I still don't know I don't remember
Want mr. Jones beat agree with me that
That was mr. E harassing
The chief of police
On a Publix
In Connecticut
Correct
I don't agree with the way he did it but it's God's public figure and this is what you sent him to do
Was it appropriate for one of your reporters
First yelled at somebody
Criminalize
Objection
No it's not appropriate for the Now by president for the appropriate for
Appropriate
I'm asking you whether I don't hear by anybody else
Court reporter
I'm asking
Repeat the question
Matthew again
Was it appropriate
For Infowars reporter
To yell
That somebody is a criminal on a city street
Yes or no
Image their free speech
Was it appropriate for an Infowars in order to
That's not that's not
Okay great I'm happy thank you for telling me that
Hey that man 30 grand
Was it appropriate for an Infowars reporter to
Accuse someone of perjury
Directions
He wasn't acting kind of weird reporter Mike in my in my view they
Okay
Answer my question I don't like them doing that but it's just
Would have been appropriate for an Infowars reporter
Or to yell
At somebody that they're trying to get an interview with have fun in jail
Appropriate
Is it appropriate to say you're going to jail for fraud
And you must have really not like
When they said
Infowars.com
The number one alternative news sources
Probably probably didn't you probably did actually enjoy because
Republic yep yep
He definitely enjoyed it and he loved it
So
I will be really unfortunate if there were a clap
Like Alex saying that he sent batondy there's no way that would be
That f***** off of that show right that's what he said he didn't do it
Afterwards privately
Or
Maybe
See how you said that
Mystery
Do it down about this
June 4th
The new Youth Center
And I went outside literally like what happened
Lejeune
Hearing correct
Time
It sounded like
Do you like maybe you did send them
We when I just played
Told me
Underoath
That
You think you
Stop sending
You think
You keep saying
You showed it to me
It's there I know at some point
I told people don't cover this
I said don't have an audion
So what there's this interesting dichotomy you can
Speak definitively about things once they're beautiful
You know like once you show a video of like I said
Now you can start talking you can say oh yeah okay I did that
But until that point
Anything could be possible I don't remember I don't know it is it is a little bit like
Alex should stop at some point be like listen
We can play this game all day I'm going to lie to you you're going to know that I'm lying but I'm going to keep doing it
Your proof first and then I won't have to lie for 20 minutes we can get out of here boom boom boom
Get about get it out you know it wouldn't go boom boom.
We're one more clip here and it's about this video
Of
Rob dues uncle
And Alex
Cycling
Is your uncle do
Uncle
I really don't know
That damn it.
Right on the day that we just watch
Correct
Wear the same shirt
Right
The same day
And the person he was interviewing was robbed
Now
You claimed that
Rob Hughes uncle
Former FBI agent
Was investigating Sandy Hook
Bright
You said
NFL
Was invested
Former engagement
My boy
You just hear he said that. He did a great job
Female the thing
Alright well
Boy that fell apart a little bit for Alex
So the
Deposition is at this point basically reached its its endpoint that I wear
Where we break for the day
And we come back at another point
For another round of questions with Alex
We'll see if you find that Bloomberg email
I don't think so
See if he gets any of the things that you promised
He with the he would produce
See if he figures out when he's here but Hyundai about these now
Especially now
Okay
Is during these depositions in the past I've been like man
I hope you guys lose
A lot of money but now in the future I get to be like dude
That answer cost you one billion dollars you f****** idiot
There was part whatever part was a part of a billion
Is your shity answers for how much they cost you if you're fascinated it would be it would be
I mean there's been a lot in here there's a lot of
Kind of new information a lot of
Retreading of some of the stuff that we've seen before it bursts corsage
Wild
Bitters
Interview I will say I have watched the other days court and
The second day
I mean
It's not disappointing if you're if you're thinking it's going to slow down it's not
It does feel like it's chaos it does feel like after listening to a day after being in a day
Give depositions of this you have a night to sleep on it you go out
You go have dinner with Norm at a shity conversation about whatever Tsarnaev Brothers date
Meeting his niece now I'll tamerlan's dead
Why don't you think okay
Here's what I could do better
There's no room for improvement honestly Zelda 10/10 perfect job
Or less painful less painful don't you. Don't you dislike pain
No because he has that Miracle Juice whiskey
And that's keeps him a happy and
Yeah I had a couple of contacts drops that I wanted to play but and I forgot to at the beginning
They may annoy you in the future okay
I like damn
Is the other one
That's really funny on Waze
Jordan came up so we're going to have it all the compliments
Bedtime
Yeah I do have to take compliments they were meant for badonde but
Alex was talking s*** about the position removing all of the compliments that Madonna
Received
Only to bed but still there
Will be back I believe our next episode will take on butt
Until then
Leo on dzx Clark
I already did condo yeah it sublet timeshare
I don't know that you have to share with people
If you stick through together that is true it's not a scam
And now here comes with the sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color