Jordan
Knowledge party.com respect with knowledge fight
Sick of them posing as if they're the good guys or the bad guys
MoneyGram
Dot-com
What about Alex Jones
Indeed we are Dan
Today is Ojos a week it's been
Encapsulating a bunch of stuff
So we recorded the formulaic objections episode about Alex's deposition
On Saturday earlier than you
Right we usually record on Sunday and honestly it was sort of my intention to do that on Mondays show
And then the rest of the deposition stuff on
On Friday
Which would be this episode but
We'll get to that inside of course
I'll but the reason we recorded today early was because I was very kindly invited to give a lecture
The University of Kansas and Lawrence by Professor Colin
And boy what a weird f****** turn of events
I didn't want to talk about it on the show itself Chad made a post about it in the Facebook group chat but didn't want to mention it on the
The show itself
Just for the sake of life
Respecting the purity of
Skyblue academic
Settings
The possibility of a bunch of people
To show up in like treated like a live show
Disrespectful to the students and the professor
Nice way of saying you despise the unwashed masses
It's a little
But Christie showed up
Very nice
So hey
Hurrah
Good news it was a great time I was nice I like Lawrence quite a
Call Voice
Shouldn't because I went to the University of Missouri is our mortal enemy course
I'm not supposed to like that sounded like did cnwk there want fry
I was so atmosphere there once despised another
College sometimes and I would get drunk it was really fun to yell
Am i z like I kind of stopped
Of course you know you're not doing it by yourself in your room it's like a call Andrew
Response for people yay Cubs game what a Cubs playoff game the last one
Wrapped up in the Go Cubs Go
The song with everybody everybody with people
Is it the whole thing
Quite quite a Time
So I'm not
Necessarily the best
Lecturer
I've never done this
Positive reviews from the folks who were there my parents came Christy was there
And the professor all had very nice things to say until I I'll take their word for it but
I'm not in not as fluid
Not then.
There's something
In that setting where you it's really nice when they're you can
Think the lecturers having a good time and definitely did not see that
I was scared of these 18 year olds
Text you about this and it's like it's in your bones as somebody who does stand up or is that time
You're Expecting The response of laughter
Even when you know that that's not the right
Another item Avenue
I'd say things and get almost no response
Dead eyes look real
You couldn't help but feel like kind of
Weird in that same way
Although High Point probably was when
They have these high-tech desks
And likes it that there's a TV built into the desk that comes up
Damn out of the desk yeah and one of them got triggered somehow and it just started coming up
And I got a vector that goes. The robot test
That's what I was fun
Albenza nighttime got to spend some time with my parents
I was just thinking when we probably about what
At 6 or so years ago when we were
Drunk at like
3 a.m. arguing about the finer points of Andy Daly's career
I was like you know whatever
2 hours earlier you would said I have to go do my, no no no no
That's going to be electors of day
Yes here we are a lot of people had wanted
A recording of the the lecture itself and
We were we were trying to do that
I think was a little bit
Out-of-pocket
So I'm not sure if there will be a recording of it
Best case scenario don't record your first one and put that
I recorded the audio on my phone but
But it's not good but that's how you work on yourself buddy medley
Sunday and lectures on Monday and then Tuesday morning
I flew back
A lot
That's a genius
Itrip
Yeah there was not had the pleasure of being on an airplane when there was trouble
Not in the air
But like
We were delayed for about an hour I can way there
And they were so cryptic about it there like
There's something in the wing and Deli
Thankfully I was so tired that I just left through the delay anyway
Whatever
Oh that's great
And it was a delightful time and thank you so much to call in for your invite me out there
And
Validating in a way of like a hey you know we're doing something and it means something in a
Environment that I respect a lot the Academia
0 not one I've been like how do you throw a pie can you give a lecture on this
Is there a podcast assholes School
Necessary
A good time
And then on the way back
It turns out I get home
And my computer broke of course
Electric keyboard
What does trying to fix it and I ended up breaking it even more needed to get a new laptop and
Adjusting to that
Whole lot of hassle
You don't hear the f****** thing I we have flown a little bit
For various things
In this time also at that into it there has never been
A single leg of one of my trips
Where I didn't have a flyer in my bag that's at the TSA look through it opened it up every single time I think
It might be because of like Electronics or you think of that I blame the TSA in their abolition
Now because they messed up my computer
I mean one of them calling for their abolition for years
So glad you're on board
+ 2
You cannot fly in 2022 without losing something or breaking something Wild
She lost stuff
Whenever we were traveling I lost stuff it's a whole mess
Yeah yeah
XO I'm back
And
You know here we are now
The issue is
What are reported on Saturday with this expectation that like Alex has been out of Studio forever
So the idea was we do the deposition on Monday
Comeback
Friday
Well Permanent Vacation meanwhile Alex comes back on
It's so we didn't know that we were right so anyway we're going to talk about Alex's present taste
Here today but before we do
What is your price
The wow I thought you were you were so close
I'll make mine quick then
My man this is been a f******
Great World Series
Absolutely spectacular world you don't want to use a bunch of cheaters
You do like the last game two nights ago
Schwarber Harper the Hopkinsville went on a home run parade
Super Mario still dead
But yeah and then last night
Houston no-hit the Phillies
It's been all this up and down and then it's the second time of no-hitters ever been thrown in the World Series
Combined no-hitter
Xavier was Guy Christian Xavier was out-of-this-world done yeah it's been a fantastic World Series
Neither team
Particularly early like your
Keeping it exciting and absolutely really enjoyed
Pretty good pretty good
Talking about Alex's return
Finally I look
Studio
You don't know rock references prefer if he were still on the road The Rock
Whenever he would show up in a town
He would you begin
Is brahmos with
Finally The Rock has come back
To Chicago
Oh no that's too long yeah that's bad
Is there a reason that they decided to make this the most important movie star on the planet is that one also sometimes
You talk about poontang pie
Call Pikachu brownies I do not like the way that you guys of which there are five
Like the 90s became the Five Guys in 2022 they're all the worst guys but who else would you choose
You son-of-a-b****
You win again perfect
We can talk about Saturday and Sunday by that I mean mostly Sunday cuz Saturday is a disaster
Alex did a three-and-a-half-hour show
It was mostly pre-recorded with some gas tonight
Really
But forget to say hello to some new
The worst happy birthday Evan live thank you so much and I'll policy wonk
You are now a policy wonk
Thank you very much I almost read incorrectly but I did not
Thank you very much
Little boo squid thank you so much you and I hope all is well
The one that I almost read as Kurt quesadilla but that is not correct
But I'm not
His last name so much
You are now
Don't get mad until you're brilliant someone
Sodomites
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Quetzalcoatl
Without the ancient god of the Mayans I feel like anytime I see a
Q and then more than like 3 letters in trouble
Is difficult that is fair
But here we are
Alex came back
The very next day
Sorry Alex came back on Saturday and did his nonsense
And here's the thing man
It's a bummer because
Used golf cart while Emily comes back as if nothing happened
Annie just like a lot of work keishin
Music of billion dollars be like all right
Head down let's just get back to work but he does do this a bit I don't know I feel like we see him a lot of time
Times of things are bad it's like wild
So I don't really know what he was up to or what he was doing but I would assume it was taken care of
Of some
Numerous legal matters
Yeah I would argue that
But
Things happened in the world
Imallexx cannot stay away for long absolutely not what happened
Let's say when someone breaks into Nancy Pelosi's house
So he decided to cover the story early
And sensational
Pelosi
Husband
Being attacked
With a hammer
But now we have the audio of plans at the moment
The 911 calls
Police dispatch
Paul Pelosi said he doesn't know
Who's a male is
But he advised that his name is David and he is a friend
Thunder where they were naked
Just a broken inside.
Broken into
Very
Going on there
With
For hair
Losi
Getting into all
That here
Today or why not
Being pretty on top of the Pelosi
Conspiracy theories and also not surprising to see him lying about the situation
He doesn't have the audio of the 911 call that's just entirely made up and he's basing his reporting on faulty get some
Thompson said he just saw him memes are I'm dumb blogs
In reality Pelosi was the victim of a home invasion and the person was holding him hostage with a hammer
David was really more
Interested in his
Mr. Pelosi was able to convince the guy to let him use the bathroom where his phone was charging anybody to call to police
Being careful to speak in language that wouldn't set off alarms for the guy with a hammer
Lucy did convey to 9/11 that the guy's name was David specifically that the guy had said that his name
When was David
He also was clear that he didn't know who he was and that he planned to wait there for his wife to arrive
Just after police arrived David hit Pelosi with the hammer and was arrest
In the ambulance Pelosi told officer Aryan Starks that he quote
I had never seen to pay
Before
The glass was not broken outward
A witness who was working
Security at the
Neighboring address nearby house
Stock quote an individual an all-black carrying a large black bag on his back walking near the Pelosi resume
He quote
Then heard what sounded like banging on either a door or car
Also any post-arrest interview to PayPal admitted that he quote
Broke into the house through a glass door
Which was a difficult task that required the use of a hammer
The interview is consistent with Pelosi's version of events in that they didn't know each other and that the
Play Pet arrived broken in and demanded to know where Nancy was
Made it clearer to police that he wanted to hold her hostage
And that if she lied to him he would break her kneecaps
So she would have to be quote
Wheeled into Congress which would show other members of Congress
There were consequences to actions
It's clear from his admission
Police from Zack
Tenzin from his writing
Prior to the attack
The David depaepe is a far-right
Extremists who was at best attempting to hold the Speaker of the House hostage and maim her
Very obvious why people across the right-wing media ecosystem from Alex to Matt Walsh
Glenn Greenwald have tried to run interference on this story
Handcrafted different narrative out of it and that's because
It's a direct result of their ideology and rhetoric
They know that
And they welcome
But in order to keep the business running
It's key to disown your children once they take action
That's all
What's going on here
Repetitive we've seen this a million times
Yeah yeah it's a good thing though that when we see this happen no one doesn't it
Nothing about it I appreciate that the most because I would be I would be really sad if this didn't continue to happen forever and ever and ever
You know
Bummer if somebody
Anything about it which is amazing
It's stuff I mean the maze
On what hand I kind of agree and I feel your laments
On the other hand
I'm not really fully certain I know what can be done
I don't know what should be done necessarily it's a good thing that nobody has ever put out say a list
People for whom this type of Acts
Action would be volume
You know it's that it's good thing nobody's ever been like hey
Here's what's a hit list of some sort
You know of the people that need to be taken care of you know it's a good thing to someone like Alex is never a note old people
Go to make a list of globalist in their town could take care of if need be
Yeah it's a sign of
It's an escalation
It feels like very fascinated by this dude's plan
That's what fascinates me most about
This whole thing
How does this
How does he
Think this goes
If it goes
Tabaxi
Well I think
Think you understood
To whatever extent you could that it wasn't going to go good
Innocent the end result was probably going to be him in prison
But on the way there he could maybe Nancy Pelosi in a way that would send a message to the rest
I get I'm just fascinated by that idea of like this is what I'm going to do you know
It's just a weird thing I'm going to go I'm going to go
To the speaker of the house is home
With a hammer
Right
Switch audio
Something else
Here is
The audio the supposedly article
Dot-com
Police dispatch Paul
Pelosi said he doesn't know
Who's the male is
He advised that his name is David and he is a
Friend here that
Broadway Across
Scott
Friend
Colormax
His name is David
And he's a friend but he doesn't know
He is
This isn't a 911 call this is a dispatcher relaying the information from a 911 call
Also there's a very clear pronoun reference issue here that is at the heart of
What does dispatcher is saying is that Pelosi doesn't know who the person is but the person had said that his name is David
And that he is a friend
He wasn't saying that Pelosi considers this guy friend he saying the Pelosi saying that David told him he was a friend
It's about as simple as an explanation is that but Alex has to grass but whatever straws are there to pretend that this is some
I'm kind of fake thing as opposed to
Exact logical conclusion of his worldview
And I don't know
Mary r
I mean dates
It's really kind of simple
Direct
You can draw a one-to-one line from stochastic terrorism to terrorism
Really easy
No no no no
Israel considered
Also won't somebody think of Rand Paul
Well I guess a dude would look
Anybody gay
Thanks
What
Azhar trying to
Saddle
Wayne
The American
Right now
Flying Mustang
Voters are calling it a new
January 6th
Gets worse
Sugar
6 ribs broken
One punctured
Serious health problems because
Celebrate
Speedy recovery and sayings
Violence
Did not happen
Called him a little b****
The last is apparently Rex Chapman on Twitter I guess that's
So is this constitutes a false flag than the term is entirely lost its meaning it's just a meaningless
Catchphrase for Alex to throw out to pop the
The crowd let's get her done at this point just beans
A ramp all that wasn't a politically-motivated attack at all
He got into a fight with his neighbor Rene Boucher about yard weigh
ABC News article about boucher's Trial
Quote
Federal prosecutors said Boucher had enough after he Witness
Paul stack brush into a pile on his own lawn
But near boucher's property
Event ran onto Falls property and tackled him
These are comfortable situations at all and all Alex's doing is playing a distraction game but who would you think of for Rand Paul
Rex Chapman said something mean about him struggling again
I'm having a trouble with
Man that neighbor
Could just tackle him
What are you doing what are you doing going in her house with a hammer just wait until she's outside of intact
It is what it is
Why are there so many elaborate plans whatever if you're just his neighbor
You can be like hey
Those sticks are too close to my yard
It is a it is a shocking lack of like functional security you're not wrong about that
It's a little upset
News topic that we are all used to hearing about
You know once an episode Maybe
Of course something is really severe and that it's not it's the covid - of the day
Define that
Daniel
H e r
We reach the covid-19
It's over
Meanwhile flu they said was gone for 2 years every kind of that is covered
Is more severe than has been in 13 years
And they're calling it
The flu
The flu wasn't gone. It was just that when Alex was starting to get really going with his covid death conspiracy theory
Flu season was ending so he made a really big deal out of heaven
The CDC was going to stop monitoring flu deaths
He settled on that as a fake explanation for that things back then and he hasn't thought about it since
Hey just hasn't updated talking points
Even so in the 2021 flu season it was estimated that the flu resulted in between 8 and
13 million cases in between 5,000 and 14000 deaths
Who was relatively mild as was the 2020 season
Most likely because of the broad adoption of covid mitigation strategies like social distancing
And wearing masks
People seem to decide that she does all done with
So whatever benefit was bringing about is gone
One variable data likely unrelated to human behavior patterns is that
The flu is coming early this year
And it looks like this year the H3 and two strained it spreading is
Fairly severe
That's unlucky partially because about 26 million less people have gotten the flu vaccine than did in 2020
Which conceivably could be a
At least in part attributed to the meteoric rise of anti-vaxxers rhetoric
And belief in the intervening years
Pushed by folks
Like Alex
Much of the influence that Alex and his ilk were put into the world have contributed to the pretty bleak situation we see in front of us
In terms of flu
But naturally when things get bad it'll just be reported to the audience as evidence that he was right all along
Because he just gets to claim the flu deaths are secretly covid vaccine deaths without proving it in anyway
And there we go
Nothing is real
Yeah I I really do appreciate
Everyone
Staunch refusal to learn the most obvious and enduring lesson of all-time which is that
There will be unintended consequences of all of this b*******
And by the covid-19 whatever-it-is level of
Quote we're done with it
As there may be
Beer
Reverberations of the behaviors during that time. Are going
Need to be paid for it
Decades like we're in serious situation
Yep the unwillingness of people to take Public Health
Situation seriously
Erosion of
I'm sort of public
Lacrosse there's no trust in any governmental like respond in any way to
Good luck use an individual solutions to solve population-level problems
It's not going to work nope
So
Alex interview some people and I don't care
When was Rodger Stone
I don't care
But
Before we get out of
Saturday's episode October 29th
That episode
We have a tortured metaphor
That's three and a half minutes long now
Alex is talking about Elon Musk
Call God know he starts thinking about that you judge a man by the fruit
And then he starts talking about literal trees and fruit
Open boy does this go on scribed the worst thing in history a tortured metaphor from Alex
Almost 4 Minutes about Elon Musk it said so
Take it the history of the world yeah he should have taken another day off
Getting back
Elon Musk
Are you looking at
Tree by what
You know IU
9 Acres
On the Barton Creek
And we had a cup
7 Acres
Upholstery
Add an apple
Aplomb
And
We could get more apples and
A
Then we could every
Off of that
7 Acres
Caribou
Are all the time
Still weather at the creek
Milwaukee water I drive
Load Bass
With
Apples
Plums
You cannot be serious
Tree
But it would have twice as many
Plums
Rap
But it would have almost nothing on
About what
Blues little tree
Motor with app
Went down to the ground
Tony apples on it
100 Apple
How to make an apple pie
Is it story about
Stealing
Big blunt
Whole bunch
Also loaded
Oh it's not
People ask me
What I think
Elon Musk
And I'm
I try to be christ-like
Complain to be
Merry Chrysler
Someone hit him with 100 apples
And my Saviour but
Let's just say this crisis never wrong
Black
Am I thinking Christ that isn't from America
Be very clear
What Christ said
You judge a tree by its fruit
And the things he's done
Thoroughly
Starlink
That kind of waves down him being a good guy
Side of that
But then you look at coming out against the vaccine two years ago and sing.
Coming out against world government
Not coming on again
Ukraine war
Not coming out against sensor
Nelson we should get rid of fossil fuels are good thing we need them
Alongside Electric
Develop better systems
We will collapse we don't have it
And just on and on and on
I look at the
Tree
Does Elon Musk
And I say
This guy's
Getting better and better
The good side of him way out
Bad don't worry you're going to end up liking him he was an apartheid property or his family is
I do.
Space backgrounds here you'll be fine you'll like him I don't I don't quite know what to do when anybody brings
Elon Musk without being like
What needs to happen is the entire population of the earth needs to jump upon him and tear him limb from limb
Like there's not much other things
Things to say about him or you needs to stack brush to close to Renee boshears yard
Yes
Trick people in a rush to close to his yard
So as usual Alex is completely misunderstood the Bible verse he claims that he bases a lot of his thinking around
There are tumors
Studies reference in here with the fruit in the trees
One of them is Luke 643 through 45
Good size quilt
For a good tree does not bear bad
Nor does a bad tree bear good for
For every tree is known by its own fruit
For men do not gather figs from thorn
Friends nor do they gather grapes from a bramble bush
A good man out of the good Treasure of his heart brings forth good and an evil man out of the evil Treasure of his heart brings forth
Similar passages found in Matthew 7:15 through 20
Quote beware of false prophets who come to you in sheep's clothing but inwardly they are ravening wolves
You will know them by their fruits
Do men gather grapes from Thorn bushes or figs from thistles
Even so every good tree Bears good fruit
But a bad tree Bears Bad fruit
A good tree cannot bear bad fruit
Nor can a battery bear good fruit
Every tree that does not bear good fruit is cut down and thrown into the fire
Therefore by their fruits you will know them
Disappears in both Luke and Matthew because both those gospels are largely believed to have been derived from a common source
That's a really complicated matter so to stick to the simple stuff Alex has no idea what these verses mean apparently
Even in this long Meandering Plum and apple story that he's telling
Alex offers two different interpretations of how you can tell a tree by its fruit
And they're both wrong
Remember what the Bible says
The first super science is that you can tell how good a tree is
Not by a how big it is but by the amount of fruit it produces
There's a fun way to think about plants but it's not related to that scripture at all
The second version Alex comes up with his that you weigh the good fruit against the bad fruit in order to determine if a tree is good or bad
That's also not with the pipe
The real problem with his Bible verse is that it exposes an absolute that humans
Can't really live up to
Good trees produce good fruit
Bad trees produce bad fruit no good tree produces bad fruit and no bad tree produces good fruit therefore
If you produce bad fruit your bad tree and it
If you produce good fruit you're a good tree
Yeah there's a reason that people like to think of it in a different way because the other way of thinking about it give me the more
Accurate way of thinking about it it's hard
Is a
Predestination
In this actual context
The verse is really unhelpful to Alex because it would require him to put definitely Abel's on people with your rigid and cannot be chained
How's can't work in that environment because he needs to be able to shift
The allegiances of his imaginary allies and enemies depending on what headlines
He needs to respond to and if they're determined to be unwaveringly good or bad it hurts his ability to make s*** up
Up as it goes along
This is all very stupid and illustrates how Alex's understanding of his holy text is really just surface-level and mostly based on
Catchphrases he doesn't really grass
And naturally this is all really just a ramp up for Alex to explain that he'll determine whether or not Elon Musk
Is a good tree based on
Whether or not he lets Alex back on Twitter
It's really what Jesus was talking to
It is it is just impossible for him to understand the Bible in any other interpretation than
Capitalist
Like because the gun
It's not about the type of fruit really
This small trees got 100 fruit Snowman
That's better than the bigger that's a good trait you know that's a good trait so you sell those f******
A plum tree that has like 100 Proof
Bright
30 of them might be good 70 bed
30/30 compared to a tree that puts out like 25
You're all good but that's only 25 points invested the bigger tricks
See this is what Jesus was talking about he's really describing an IPO for fruit orchards
Like forbidden books of the Bible this is what it gets into
Yankton to like
Real calculus about fruits
Anyway I decided to punt covering your ass today
And move on to Sunday when Alex's maybe in
Finer form
Yeah it's sort of in midseason form
Here's where we start off on Sunday I was wrong
I was already planning today
Sunday broadcast
Why there's a war on children and why the real currency
Global Elite in their minions
Is hurting
And then
3 hours ago
I saw
Clip of Laura Logan
Famous investigator
Coming out
Why they target children
The.
That's really what it's all about
And they're giving me
Basically evil reward by the God of this world
What they do
I'm not sure if the problem people had with Laura Logan was that you said there's a war on children and it's done is an affront to God
The kind of commentary probably would preclude her from being on a network that's trying to do serious work but she was on Newsmax
It's not a big deal there
Her comments were so inappropriate that Newsmax had to put out a statement saying they wouldn't
Interviewer again
Do the guests on Eric Bolling show.
Be safe quote
They may think that they're going to become gods
That's what they tell us you know the ones who want us eating insects
Cockroaches
That while they dine on the blood of our children
Those are the people right
They're not going to win
The Logan's blood libel Laden qanon rant was just another step on her past-due full-on publican
Conspiracy lunatic
And a lot of people have this notion that
She's fallen so far
She was formerly the chief Foreign Affairs correspondent at CBS News which is a lofty position compared to someone
No longer welcome on Newsmax but the reality is she
Already fallen
Grace
She was put on leave of absence by CBS in 2013 after an internal investigation
Confounded her reporting on Benghazi was fraudulent and that quote
Key elements of the story were untrue
Reporting relied heavily on a story told by a contractor named Dylan Davies who was lying
Stevie spawn story about how he got into combat during the attack and he'd seen Ambassador Stevens body but
Unfortunately he pooped already told the FBI that he never left the Villa that evening and that he hadn't put on the scene it
Ouch
Logan did not follow up on
Details of Davy story that would have indicated credibility problems
She also failed
Disclosed that he had a book deal selling his fraudulent story about what he did during the attack
Only problem
It was shity work and it's not the kind of mistake you would think would be made by someone who is otherwise good at their job he would say
First-time mistake it's very sloppy maybe the simplest thing about an interview is to
Like hey you know what
There's an FBI interview to I'm going to go check that
Real quick
Cross-reference it with the b******* you're saying to
Yeah even if you're not it's like even if you don't have the FBI interview available to get his other things we could do to like triangle
Robbery details
And be like hey is this guy just trying to get promotion for his book
No it's kind of like what
Just off the top of my head somebody like Alex might do is interview somebody who's completely
Lying about their kordelya inflating it and then putting it out on TV I can pretty well you likes
In the past few years has become just another raving nut
Adelaide spread nonsense on conservative platform
If you had a show on Fox Nation but was fired earlier this year and now she's rambling locution blood libel with Eric Bolling
And getting the boot from Newsmax
What I'm saying is that he's a prime candidate for Alex to hire
I think it makes total sense for him to come to her defense
She's unwelcome anywhere else and Alex could really use anybody with a little Holly
Totally thank you haven't Harrison Smith host everything and
Another workation
Got to get somebody in there
It's just like I wish it would be so much it's so simple to cuz it's just like hey do you know why they're number one finger
Is attacking children
Because if I tell you that then maybe it'll override your emotional Center long enough
That you won't think
For two seconds and realize that I'm full of s*** I want to drink a lot of money
Children
But Alex is covering
Shocking if true
But also not true
Somewhere around the 15th
November
Call diesel
All these days
All diesel reserves in all diesel gone
Call diesel
Sounds like
Over a week ago
17 days
November
Right after the
Oh my god there it is
Susan stupid we're not going to run out of diesel fuel Alex just up Tucker tweet something that was incorrect and I was
Reporting on that tweet as if he's looked into the story at all
The comments that were made as if there's a 25 day supply of diesel fuel in the country which was to say
All production were to stop immediately it would run out in 25 days
The thing is a production didn't stop and it isn't stopping so there's no date where the fuel is just going to be magically gone
An economics professor explained to CBS news that we generally have a supply that would last about 35
40 days out but there's a tightening of supply and an increase of demand
It's slightly lowering that window
But it'll adjust back eventually
Good mornings with diesel isn't running out this is just a dumb lie Alex's using pescaraz listener
Also let's be clear
If we have an impending day that was less than a month that where we be entirely out of diesel fuel and we had no planned and play
Place to adapt to that that would be a
Catastrophe
Most of our Trucking delivery folks rely on it to bring
Food around the country among
Countless other Goods that need to be transported
If these trucks all simultaneously became a mobile
It's difficult to an estimate the amount of death that could result in
Unsinkable
If that were the case
That would be the only thing
Anyone was talking about
Everybody going to be like okay
Just real quick so everybody knows
In three weeks we will starve to death in 3 weeks we will have no trucks
We will all die
If Alex believe this for a second he would be freaking the f*** out and not just reporting this as some kind of weird conspiracy
Me about the election
Doesn't stick around unless you give them a reason to be scared so we just tosses this b******* on the pile
Knowing it means nothing
This is ridiculous
Is it the show is so dumb that is absolutely just like
Hey here's a story that's kind of gone unreported the Midwest
Won't have court next week
Like no I'm sorry
That would not go unreported
Your story that everybody is a missing out on a giant meteor about to hit Earth and we can all see
Okay let's not feel too many movie plots
So the story that is on everybody's mind of course
Pelosi
We got touch back on this one
Voltage in Tupelo
Husband
911 tape
Still.
Underwear
The police holding up till today
Call on Friday
Police release
The fact that
Pelosi
From a nudist colony
Not right winger
A dram
Baltimore underwear
With ham
Someone else
Herewith
And my friend
He's attacked
Years old
Sounds fun
Call this the new January 6th
Incredibly
Exactly
Watch Friday
News 2
Drunk
Flames
Amazing so I love the idea that there's that
Two dudes naked with a you do the math
OK Google
Hospital
We all know we all know what it means when there's naked dudes
Oh there's probably something sexual going on there is his information it's like
I have never heard of you do the naked with a clit on
Classic hamburger place
Since I was 14 years old believe me if there was a two dudes naked with a thing at least know about it
Okay
So there's no evidence that Pelosi into paper in their underwear when the police arrive
Pelosi was asleep when to pay broke into the house so he wasn't a pajama shirt and boxer shorts so you could say that's his underwear
Initial reporting from KTVU Fox 2 it incorrectly said that the paper was in his underwear but this was a misunderstanding
Meaning of him being in his shorts
Paul Pelosi answered the door but the phrasing of the initial police report they didn't specify who it is
Answered the door
Leading right-wing media figures
Just assume that it must have meant there was a third person there
There was.
And I was just reporting that based on nothing
Baby song meme who knows
The websites and writings that were found created by to pay pornography
He did have a bit of a hippie phase back in like 2013 Butthead sense to send a deeply into extreme right-wing bulshit
Much of which matches a pretty well with the stuff Alex yells about everyday
Explain that he was radicalized by gamergate as is
The case were so many thing.
After that point he went off he conspiracy deep end
He has post
Including climate change denial
Transphobia nonsense about the great reset 2nd Amendment fears 2020 election
Conspiracies
And of course Holocaust denial
It's fair enough to say the a two-phase where he was into a presumably left-wing hippie nudist lifestyle but that ended a long time
Time ago
I'm not sure if anyone really wants to call this the new January 6th
On a completely different scale from a mob invading the capital but it would also be dishonest to not recognize some
Important similarities
Both events in Baltimore targeting Nancy Pelosi at least it's somewhat in some capacity they were motivated by
Buy conspiracy b******* about the election being stolen
Both events involve people bringing zip ties which gives some indication of an intent to take hostages
Honestly the people who respond
The same way they did to January 6th our folks like Alex
The same knee jerk denial is being employed because this attack threatens him in a way that
The same as January 6th dead
They can't be allowed to be seen as a natural conclusion his ideology and rhetoric because then is a society we might wait
The fuk up and start taking this stuff seriously
The extreme right-wing Community learn their lesson from how huge setback the Oklahoma City bombing was
Did the ability for militia groups and extremist cells to organize
And they don't want to have to do that work again
Read normalizing the right out
Right so they don't want something to be very well understood
To be like oh yeah this is this is kind of what you're going to end up this is the end result of
For me
Like
I do feel somewhat for the proper
Afghanistan
Stochastic terrorism
Somebody think of the propagandists
It's just too easy now
You know like
All they had to do was throw out a little homophobia and then everybody's like all will do it but the
Pelosi's are all liars
Come on a higher class of criminals here
What are the reasons why a lot of these folks don't really interest me that much these folks
In the the propaganda game
What element is the Trolli aspect of it I just fine done Charming
It is but it's just
So f****** easy
Alex
There has there's a there's an under painting of this
Do you know JBS Inspire Dance Academy there
Identity kind of religious beliefs in the militia movement of the 90s still connected
You know there's
He's he's connected to the past and the present
Which is
Yeah it's someone who was a higher class of criminal who is descended into just being at Rowley bulshit lose
Loser it is it is kind of an interesting like
We have someone tracked the the fall
Yeah I was not just Alex but all of right-wing propaganda really
Pathetic now
The kit is
It's all so pathetic that it
Still is effect
Yeah that's that's
Really didn't have to try that
Infinite universes there's got to be one where Alex
Stuck to his guns and didn't take the bait on like
Meme s*** yeah
Hanging out with people like Carpe donktum
Like
You know
That's a better world
Yeah
What can you do
Alex says interviews
Okay I haven't heard any reason I don't believe they exist
Commodus
I have done
Hundreds of interviews in the last
And hundreds more I didn't have the time and energy to do
Apologize you were right
Motors really wanted forcibly injectors
Becoming a
The building covid camps
What do we do
Who are these people who are these interviews that he's done on these major platforms
Apologizes a lot of claims
Quickly yeah that are absolutely insane I can't imagine any of that true
I'm interested in seeing these interviews
I've been there's hundreds of them
You can't shake a stick without hitting an interview that Alex has done it yet somehow
I've seen none of the work Kasian
No
Was hundreds of interviews
I guess maybe it's like a hundreds of interviews with his lawyers or something
And you know go on a vision Journey do something along those lines really figure s*** out your Mancow could hook him up
He got to you got to do that for a bit
So this makes what I think is actually eight seats
Super revealing
Bums me out a lot
Viewers of the crew
Because
We're being Vindicated
Good chance
Oshopping global
Close together
By the day more and more people
Shifter 4 speed
Effective
Being a nice good person
But you still are
What you thinking like a glove
Document
Understanding just how
It's hard to get your mind around but once you see things
Rise
There's no pudding
This is how Alex gets away with the fact that his primary sources don't say what he claims they do
You can't read a document and just think it means what it says
No no no
Before you read it you need to run that document through the globalist filter
Homeland Security paper might suggest extending Refugee status to a larger number of people and you could accept that mean
Things that the author is suggesting that the US should extend Refugee status to a larger number
People
But if you're able to think like a globalist then you can clearly see that what they're really suggesting
Is that hundreds of millions of unvetted immigrants should be ushered into the country so they could be foot soldiers of the Democratic Party
You think like a globalist
The game is really transparent but honestly I haven't heard Alex express it quite like this very often
You can't just read things you have to read the music
Code
Cybernetic bonus
Alex is just made up these globalist and imagine what their plans are so guess who gets to be the sole Arbiter of how the code is
Translate it's really nice and really convenient
What's an audience except to this kind of bulshit they're essentially allowing demagogue to be their soul contact point with real
Alex has appointed himself as the person into who will have what amounts to the final say on whether something is real or not
In essence demanding that the audience subordinate their own senses to him
It's really pretty abusive but on other hand it's
Just dumb
Context is important in understanding the jargon that's used in various field is critical to understanding how to read documents
Pretending the written in some kind of a sneaky code that only Alex's dumb ideology can unlock that's a kids game
You might as well tell the audience that he has a signed confession from Klaus Schwab but it's written in invisible ink
Another critical issue is that Alex has basically the worst person you can trust about whether or not something is real
He's been completely wrong about pretty much every world event I can think of any lack
Basic reading comprehension skills
He lies about his own past actions and beliefs constantly
He's been tricked by fake documents multiple times including these Soros antifa contract that one of his employees found
4chan
He has to this day never issued a correction for
Thinking like a global this just means accepting Alex's version of reality despite what your eyes tell you
It's culture
Two things
First
90% of what you just said also applies to
The Pope
I think one of the other things in there that he accidentally revealed is
Just that
Listen once you get this
You'll go from being a nice person
I mean you'll still be
Nice which is a good way of saying
You're going to become more violent if you start behaving
I'm thinking the way that I have described
Overtime like he's literally saying
If you do this right eventually you will break into Paul Pelosi's house you will because you will become
Come able to look at primary documents and find rationalizations to breakage.
SMS
I think that I think that's really an important aspect to understand
And it's one of the reasons why it's deeply frustrating to be able to like fact-checked stuff and look at
Like where are you getting these ideas from it
Doesn't say that at all he doesn't need to
I wonder if it even applies to the Bible
For Alex
Baby didn't write the Bible
The people who say that Jesus himself didn't write the Bible our global
I'm confused
Fruits
Has done hundreds of interviews
People of apologize haha
Is bigger than
Ever I don't know how that can any of that can be true but I believe you are bigger than ever in terms of judgments against that
That's fair nobody's ever had that they are about as in-depth as you possibly could be
What's to talk about how big they are
Very powerful report that needs to go viral
. video
Rebuilt
Great contributors
Reaching millions of people today
Videos with the other videos getting noise of you today
Fox6
Thousand thousands a day
Yeah
No that's
That's a bit of an
Exaggeration of pretty much everything about back doctor dl1000
Yeah for his shows and if he has some like really flashy shorter video maybe it'll get to little do some number
But yeah
It was Saturday shows they actually do get a bigger crowd because they're not on the radio stop bottleneck
Still generally those are often under a million
Premier received big drop-off
Harrison Smith American Journal is typically between ten and fifteen thousand views which is a disaster
Owens War Room usually hovers around a little over 30,000 which is similarly awful
For what they're doing
Gregory's Especial reports off of between 500,000 and a million views which I believe is the highest consistent viewership
Of the Infowars in-house team
Wow holders Watson has a miniscule amount of viewers because he's still on other platforms and why would you go to Alex
The site wouldn't get that s*** somewhere else
Same thing with Rodgers Channel
None of this
Three episodes of The Stone Zone that he's posted in the past month have over 600 views which is because he's primarily on Frank's
Beach now I'll just go there
My most of the other s*** on this website is a ghost town
Gerald Celente as a channel no one cares Tommy Robinson as a channel no one cares
He was real bad. Might be out now
Someone named Allison has something called Allison's rage page which is a zero David Icke and his son
Both have channels which are going nowhere
Rate I was too
I thought I lost interest America
Honestly many of these channels aren't even actively post
Sing stuff probably because people thought they'd give it a whirl and then they realized it wasn't worth
But it's a dismal
Situation over there and if Alex is paying as much as he claims he is for bandwidth
It's
He's losing a lot of money not a good idea
Who downsized
Pay for Allison's rage page
Hi it's hard not to think that one of the biggest problems with Infowars is just overhead
Overhead I want to cut some Corners here but we got out we got to post a new video
I'm salty cracker you know if we got to post a new video
On the street
If you really stop and think about it maybe if the overhead wasn't so high they wouldn't have chased after so many of these false Flags
Story so hard to get money and then
Where would we be now keep a low profile
Good work
I don't think of that
Kohinoor Harrison will be getting back to more views of History podcast
100 grand
So Alex
Is what
One thing he's consist
That's not true
But he is consistently wrong
That is about story
And when he's wrong about something he likes to
Continue to be wrong about it
Talk to a little bit more about Paul Pelosi
The other huge
Economy news Russia War news
Wasn't attack
Nanbaka
It looks like
Another drug-fueled
All of that coming up
And more
You want somebody to take
The big media
We're doing
We are recognized by the globalist has
The biggest threats
So I know most a-listers get this but I want to really sneak into the mass
But never spread the word
Or never go buy a book
Or supplement or
Film
Or t-shirt
We don't have George Soros of the New World Order funding
We have negative a billion dollars
You know you got a sales pitch year that comes off the continuing the Paul Pelosi
I do like the idea that he's calling it an operation
Hey Heyday hammer
Drug orgy
Operation
You know what it is
I don't
They Hammer drug orgy operation
Classic
I don't know how to put those words together in a way that makes
More sense to you
I need you to work on it cuz I'm still confused
So Alex I've mostly kept a close pin for the operation word and then Alex weaving it into an adverb
Because I wanted to play this
I just thought this was silly
You need to experience
Text three most people alive
You do this
Picture in 15 minutes
Mental focus clarity
It's it's
Intellectual aphrodisiac
Just tell me it's okay
That's all I want to know
Very special formula nobody else got it
The Columbian
$6
Still sold out
Public comes in soon its 10
Godzilla
Why are you explaining your different kinds of speed
Sorry for you all right how long do you
I want the Haida last you want to be you want to be Speedy for 3 hours or do you want to rannosaurus Rex
A mess
It's so honey by God so back to Pelosi
I don't know
And the police intelligence until today that they found both men in their underwear
Paul Pelosi Nancy Pelosi bedroom
She was off
DC
Try guys
When the cat's away
The mice
The mice play
What's more more likes
Homosexual
Interlude
Or Ronde
F*** you
You
My issue
Websites
Wednesday
Leftist nudist
Big Democrats
Supporter on record
The website
Person
Are not true
Are you don't like the spin
No see this problem with the spin
Is that
They
United States media is not reporting
On a gay Hammer orgy situation
Operation
For sure
Ivy
That is so f****** awful they Hammer orgy drug-fueled operation
It is like I don't know how to be angrier you can just say like fussy
It looks like it was gay guess what now of we can still be terrorists
That's so f****** it doesn't even make sense if you're in if you're telling me there's a Hast
Situation and both men are in their underwear with hammers
I'm thinking that the guy who took hostages
Hazel weird guy who made him getting his underwear and then got his own underwear cuz they gave him a hammer
I think that would be an important thing to rule out before you jump to any other exception yeah
His hostage situation was just a regular situation gone wrong right this is a hostage situation going
I was going to go and I mean I think if you have misgivings about
Details and information that fits their
Hulk pump up baby
You know like
You know I think
Think you can
Bi-curious
Without
Doing what Alex is doing
You're like
Lamenting the spend well spinning so fast
Instantly homophobic
But he's f****** response
I forget also
Mirroring a victim of a violent crime
Not not the smearing part of it being like a gay thing it's a
The spirit habitat
He was a victim of such like
Walking
Crazy that you can override
People's brains that easily with being like Oh Sees
He's probably gay
Because it doesn't make any sense
I think that
There is a lot of that going around but I think Alex is kind of more focused on the hammer Park
And I guess that's a plus
Yeah sure okay
When Paul Pelosi called 911 reply that tape for
Anemometer
Still doesn't have that.
He said
No he knows a man
I don't know him
We figured out how that sounds
Completely made
The police
Yeah
Notoriously democratic
To release today
Pelosi is refusing to release surveillance
Paul Pelosi
What his underwear in
Call the police
Then come back
And join the man
Then it began to hit each other with hammers again
Again
Put your hammer down
I continue to try to attack
Pelosi
Some kind of weirdo stuff going on
This is come out
How
This is this is some classic weirdos.
F*** are you talking about we talked about this a little bit earlier I'm ashamed but I don't think there's a lot of hammer plague
What about the prospect of like.hot construction data
What about that idea that you could listen to a man say that out loud and not go
Well send him to Coyote land or something along those lines
What about Into the Wild
Alex isn't the weirdo they are the weirdos
Bitf and he went into the bathroom
Keep it together again
You don't get to hit multiple times with a
And somebody parts
Certainly not
It's usually one
Oh man
Yep Alex put the number on this
Cops didn't shoot them because they were like
This is the fourth Hammer f*** Weaver on.
This week it's just a weirdo stuff
The number on this
About his percent trance certainty
About his narrative
So what do you want to bet
Dish Network
Two men in their underwear
With hammers in a bedroom
But you've got to find
The police have guns on them
Boatman
Pelosi
What
In the hell
Is going on here
Nancy Pelosi
9% chance
This is some kind of weird wacko stuff going on
I can't
Find a way in my brain says jump
Like here's my jump if I if I break into a room and there's two men make every like wearing their underwear with
Both of them having handers hammers brandishing them towards each other
My thought is not like oh they're probably having some sort of sex game I thought is like this is like our five of some
Some sort of fight
Like a Family Guy cartoon fight that lasted over 6 settings
An overtime their clothes ripped off as time went on until they wound up here like
With hammers like that is the only thing that makes sense anymore reasonably wacko stuff
I also just I can't get over the fact that Alex keep saying two men in their underwear with hammers I think he's like
You do the math
Alex continues his streak of being completely wrong about things that gives a 99% chance of being right about
David the papers actually already he's been arrested he confessed to a crime and he's going to jail for a long time
He's charged with one count of assault on an immediate family member of Us official with the attempt
How we ate against the official on account of the performance
Of official duties which could land him
30 years
Yeah that's
That's a crime that government
It's like to take seriously.
For doing our job
Then there's the attempted kidnapping of a Us official to retaliate charges could add years
A real good fun time with this whole gay Hammer fetish
Thing he's doing but the serious stuff
Also I might last clip Alex said that they are refusing to turn over the security camera footage to the police and that's cool
We made up
I was just reporting based on some dumb s*** he's on social media but political political reach at the police and political
PolitiFact spoke to Pelosi spokesperson
And they both
He's wrong about everything every like every detail
Suspicions on it is wrong
Fictional
Please fiction you're not you're not even spinning a conspiracy with anything to it
No pathetic
It's a completely alternative reality
The unnamed person let in the police
I had to specs
If you studied the
What
We're going crazy doing god-knows-what to each other
The other one
Really
Really quick
You're called a conspiracy
All they do is lie to us
History of fraud
We would be insane if we didn't
Question
What's going on here
Oh my God. I want to start a war
So you might think that Alex is being homophobic by saying studying the lifestyles
Of these we will lead you to believe that they're on meth
So we're on coke
But would you understand starting with the lifestyles of
Hammer people I mean globalists
Like the hammer Brothers in the Mario Brothers
They were super in the bath
Find if you will study these lifetime sales
Give me one other example of a hammer
Sex fight
I just want an Icee Hammer MC Hammer
About turtles
Doris Day
MC Hammer vs Jim the Anvil Neidhart no that's a nay.
Whose nickname is the hammer in subsequent scarecrow ahead of movie called The Hampton
Adam Goldberg have the Hebrew hammer that's true all of these things could be there it is we're all at 4 now it's make
Making said I'm just pissed that I already use the hammer Brothers
He's questioning but this isn't questioning anything
This is Alex lying about misreported details and bulshit meme cc'ing on right-wing social media
Which has been laundering into being stuff that's been concretely reported by the police
It's fine to question things and retain an open mind until you hear more details about situations but that is not what Alex is doing
He's constructing an alternative reality based on nothing for his audience to live in so they don't have to realize
How much they have in common with the guy who tried to kidnap the Speaker of the House
It isn't good for business for Alex to let his audience realize how far
Down the extremist Road
He's taken them
You might wake up and be like oh
S***
Yo you might look around
Look to your left look to your right
Two of these people are Nazis
Pizza
They could be a crystallizing wake-up moment wearing an SS badge in your life
Elon Musk
Guy whose tree fruits will be determined at a later date
Descend upon him like a zombie
He did some stuff with this up Losi story
Picture
Elon Musk
About the truth stop that
Can I hear some of the memes
Paul Pelosi crimes
Hahaha meme
You almost didn't fact-check Hillary he posted a link to an article from a fake news Outlet called the Santa Monica Observer
Is a publication that has reported in the past that Hillary Clinton was dead but I can 2016 and the trumpet appointed Kanye West
Do a high-level Post in the department of the interior and also that Bill Gates caused polio
So they're just a few years earlier must go was understandably embarrassed when this stuff was pointed out about the
Do you think he would like
They didn't learn a single lesson
So
It's great having billionaires
Run everything
Friends rule the world
There's other news that's really important
Russia
They have proof that the United Kingdom blew up the pipeline that sounds right
Have the Russians official
Military
And there's a big bottle video
Whether it's about
Pushing its vaccinations remoting outshone
Kyrie Irving
Care about the impact of the word
He's just a wealthy and titled visual
2 oz
Tweeting
This video that I
Dozens of versions of millions of years
20 years ago
Club
Oh my God
Apologize
Posting
Instagram
Yeah so Russia has proof that the UK did that s*** with the pipelines but
More importantly
Basketball player talks about me and
Yeah yeah if you came
One of these guys who doesn't really care when he comes up in the media it doesn't care
It's not a big deal he's so used to people like in terms of interview my God so many unlike you
And he never likes to talk about himself like on the show he doesn't want to like you
Right
Kyrie Irving
Was really cool getting
Posted my thing in the people are mad at him
Committed explicit waraq
Towards Russia
But I mean we got to deal with the hearing now
That's like future news
Brighten the hearing now is I have a lot of views on my video exactly
31 West Club. Jordan cuz
You know whatever
They said trolls really stupid
But
Alex isn't the only thing making a return
On
He came back on Saturday
And on Sunday I'm very thrilled
See something that has been MIA
For a long time
Oh yeah
What the heck
Yeah you can
You can face me
We really going to do this.
Yeah you
You wish to have to
Never heard of them
Liberty
Raise you up
F*** that guy
God
Don't even s***
When the enemy
Scared of the Lord
Already Alyssa
Watch this
How much always true of his job
Yeah it always was nice to feel that Bop come back that was good I am shocked to say
How refreshing that felt real good
Not his best work
No you belong to the city but man oh man
Like a breath
Breath of that fresh Stuff You Belong To The City
No you got to you got to do some classic highwomen before you can really hit You Belong To The City
He's at the bar pretty high
Like some of those other You Belong To The Sopranos were like
He should not have
All the things that Alex
History for it I will give him some of those rants Over You Belong divided Beyond 100 interview
News in the past month mostly about Alex's Ransom
So yeah we check back in here and we see Alex come back from his work station
I'm a wise-ass off about Pelosi and a hammer operation
Android yeah that's what you'd expect
It's been forever since we talked about Allison presentation deprived of it because of his workation
I feel like
Sour grapes
A little bit
Will be back
Next week
Some episodes
I believe how we're going to end up doing it is we'll finish up the deposition stuff on Wednesday
Check back in contingency a little bit more about
Does present-day stuff see if we can catch up a little
The gap
But also I don't want to disappoint people because you know we talked about how there's 4 days of deposition
Them are not as
So there's really only going to be two episodes worth of
I've stopped and I hope no one
What is a hamburger that other more professional shows that would be like
Teething it out and advancing I like making it an event as opposed to
Just being like hey that thing that everybody loves we're just going to throw that out on our Wednesday episode for fun
Yeah that's not how we do it
Not a great business model but it is what it is
We do it I'll try. Com
We're also on Twitter
And oh my God I'm not doing it I know you are doing it but you also
Finally got
No followers happy happy to reply to 122 follower count
Tip of the spear
Emilio Emilio I'm dzx
Clark
You have a houseboat in my mind I like that a mine boat
This is no good I got to come up with a new bed
The sex robot
Alex
Christian color