Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge babe I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
Let's sit around worship at the altar
Alex Jones
My bright spot Jordan is you had a few video game bright spot
. had a surly
As of late
My bright spot started playing it
Months back
I got distracted by something else and put it down
But there's a bunch of news about it being released on the switch
And that was baby remember that I had it already on the PS4 until I decided
How to get the back into this something to give it a shot
See if I can get back into it
They got back into it
Quite quite hard
Deep
Getting back into it I don't know
Yeah it's a lot of fun it is a good sensibility fun story good
Mechanics I like it
I'm enjoying a quite a bit
I want to play a little bit it's it's very much up my alley I'm going to get on 280
I'm a little scared of it because I feel like I'm going to spend a lot of time in there good
It's quite easy to palaces at this point and
It's just shocking even having played a bit of it before
Like I made it through a palace and a half
The first timer
I'm still shocked
How long
It's wild but it is
It is a lot of it's a very Charming
Game
Got an offer like that
Yeah yeah yeah
It's very good fun to look at
And if you enjoy it there is a also a Persona 5
Sort of
Politely
Is Warriors
Type game
It's not exactly like
But there's a little bit of a
Can Flash kind of things a little bit of a merging of
Potoo
My bright spot Dan is weird
The Al Yankovic story
Ball my God
It is
It is like I've read that I've read some reviews about it that were really really terrible like
Whatever it was and it's like I want there to be a disclaimer on the movie that says
Sorry everybody
Specifically made for Jordan Holtz what I would want if
Al Al Yankovic made his own biopic that what it is
Yeah yeah
I
I had heard that it was
Going to going to happen I was really worried about it I don't know about it
Looks so good perfect
It is so good I did not okay but not remembered that it was out
So funny so good so good
I honestly say to you this
He kills it
It just does absolutely amazing job doing the thing that he was told specifically to do any
He just Nails it
The whole way through
Great and his abs are unreal
Love it's like the Weird Al in real life
One thing you know by Weird Al
Swallow washboard
Touchback on something
Well I know that I have mentioned
That Bray Wyatt is
What is happen
The word is very hard now well I'm I got a
Cuz I know that we got to stay on
Most of the audience
I'm worried
I'm a little bit worried you're worried about it well there's
There's this person in a mask
Who keeps interrupting his promos with these videos
Andy the guy named Uncle Howard
I'm a little worried I'm a little hope
I
It's
It's trouble
I had such high hopes
Send a WhatsApp Uncle howdy
I'm your uncle how they
Oh no what is that what you're going to tell me
I need the threatening Uncle howdy
Dino's Secret
Sawed-off out-of-body walks over
Do you know part and parcel of
Of some of Braves.
He was also the guy doing a children's show Firefly fun house
Children shows can be uncanny because they are inherently of
Sir do I have the children's mind if you're taking that you're taking this children show host and adding a bed
Anna Stuart
Uncle how do you being something that you had a menace
2 is not really unfamiliar territory
I agree
Still worried
Totally I'm just saying that if you're going to do Uncle howdy
And you're going to elevate it into something that the legitimately scary
You give him the child
Koverman blood that's the combination that you got to go down if it's Uncle howdy Maybe
Maybe
I don't know
The thing that
The troubles me is
That like when break came back with the Firefly Funhouse
For quite a while
It was just
Fuses goofy children show host now
Concerned about that
Is well I'm not sure that it really
Felt like hey this is a good idea the moment
Maybe
But
We've already kind of done that that's an issue and now I'm I'm worried again
I don't know it'll take it'll take
An amazing swing to make me feel comfortable the WWE quite nice
Actually would saying we've done that before and I'm worried again
Yeah
I'll go howdy Ono Ono
Oh no
You know
Sometimes you just got to say we'll see
We'll see what happens
That's it that's what somebody says before being eaten by a Tyrannosaurus Rex
Jurassic Park
You know what maybe it'll work out this time
Anyway we're going to be talking about November 3rd 2022
Thursday of last week
And
I don't know I don't know if
It's just Uncle howdy or something but I forgot
The midterm for a man
I'll tell you a minute I forgot and I listen to Alex
To show that I remember
Yeah this show has
This is a lot
Does it
No Kohl's
So that's not easier that'll be fun we'll talk about it before
A little moment to say howdy on Golden Boulevard.
I'll tell you A life ain't easy for a boy named Squad
Text Raymond
Peter ink thank you so much you're now policy walk
Thank you very much this is a birthday messages out of months late
Did send them
The timely fashion Okay Lego
And Blissful prick
Happy birthday to you all you're not bother walk
Happy May birthday Andrew thank you so much
Juvenile policy wonk
Thank you very much
Agitprop
Thank you so much
Thank you very much let's Trudy goody fresh and fruity hear Rusty just calling to
Election fraud give me a ring back when you can play
How your nail polish
Pitbulls are the secret dynastic Family behind the Council of twelve
Thank you so much
So we're going to get down to business on this
Very dumb episode of Alex
Very very stupid
Before we do here is not a context drop
From one of Alex's collar
Just wanted to make
Point and share Battle Royale with you
Yeah
I'm sorry what
See the battle Roar
But it's for a commercial
Specifically for a commercial
Cut is he saying Alex I want to cut a promo for you know not even bro
Hate you need to splice it in somewhere later
Kind of takes away the sincerity of the battle Roar if you're going into it with a you can use the truck commercial
Yeah that's kind of
That's kind of not good thing I like those colors
Familiar enough to be okay what's up
I'm going to do a yell at you and then I know you'll put it into a commercial I'm going to yell So Good Year to make money off it
What a weird you know like there's a lot to unpack if you get deep in there as to how can
Can you possibly have
Created an audience that's like
You know what he needs
Me to call in and yell at him for me
You know you know what though there's really not that much to unpack you just did
So there's a lot of news
Live news
Climate change
Story that just will not go away
The Pelosi's don't want the footage
Under surveillance cameras
The Congressional
Police
Baby spend all the surroundings
Want the footage released latest gentleman they just don't want to talk about two men in their underwear
With hammers
Enable
It just gets
Crazier and crazier
LeBron James
Dayal
3 hours
Yahoo does want to talk about you guys hamburgers in a bad one
Sure seems like him
Wow I did not know that the story wouldn't go away I feel like I stopped paying attention
Yeah I mean I felt like the story
Bully went away there and then it was gone
We were talking about his show on like Saturday and Sunday
That's about the last we'll have to hear about the Pelosi s***
Still talking about it at the end of the week I'm sorry I have a limited amount of attention and sympathy for any
Anybody with over 100 million dollars I just kinda don't care
For somebody who is the victim of a home invasion assault with a hammer
Life does go on
Recovering he's in the hospital he's got better insurance and we did a guy who did it got arrested the keys in custody
I don't know how much
Too much
It certainly
Maybe something
To consider about the vulnerability of politicians and people were both hoping to violently Richard
Certainly that's a conversation
But holyshit
This story is still relevant to the Infowars
Tiny bit about
His court
Some issues
He could have made them all go away apparently yeah
You know that's what
Democratic Party
I told me
Airlab
I mean you'll be nice to me you only gross lawyers
I am happier and more live
We're being attacked
Be
So I reached out to Bill to get a comment
He said that he told Alex if he turned on the Second Amendment goddamnit
I did not get a comment from him
He said they do not do this
Damn
So yeah it's a it's a it seems incredibly unlikely that anybody
Okay listen up Ally
I bet maybe one of Alex's lawyer said that to him
Probably just say that you don't like guns anymore maybe they'll drop all this
I could see that being like
Message that was conveyed from Alex's lawyer that never
Came from anywhere else
Right
I mean you know it in in terms of jobs
Normally I think whenever I've lied to my bosses
About something that happened I felt bad about it and they might not believe me
You know those types
Thanks I mean if your work
Looking for Alex Jones and you got your ass kicked in a in a law situation you can just lie to him and I'll be like
That sounds more true than that we got our ass kicked for lying all the time how could we possibly
Obviously we're in the right so clearly it must be some kind of demonic
They sent me one of my own daughters
Toes that's what
And that's why we lost
They sent me one of my ponytails
So
But we had talked about that Pelosi s*** out
We're not releasing while we're too naked
Underwear
Lammers
Diana bedroom
Pelosi said he knew and was a friend named David
On the Paul baloche attack
He woke him up
We wanted to try them up
He selling ended up using a hammer
The smash Falls skull
Thankfully by the grace of God
Paul survived
All this happened after the assault
And it just
Hard even say
After the sailing enter the home asking
Where's Nancy
Those are the very same words used by the mob when they storm the United States capitol
On January 6th
Footage
See that
Chance.
They had that guy
Drugged up
You know he wasn't. He's part of evolution
Pedophilia is
Girlfriends
In prison for
Behavior
What does downgraded this from a ninety-nine percent chance
Conspiracy to a 95% chance which would be relevant if the words
These that have any meaning
He just making up his conclusions and proclamations as he goes along so he probably doesn't even realize that what he's saying is that it's become
I'm more likely that the Pelosi home invasion was a real of that since the last time you put a number on
If you're paying attention to his show that's what he saying
No David
Wasn't part of a hallucinogenic
Cult any more than Joe Rogan
I would bet that he did do some drugs during his time living with some San Francisco nude
Distance from a hallucinogen called
What's your member valances audience
Then you'll actually believe that cities are burning and demons walk the streets of every urban center tackling and threatening any
Conservative or Dare show their face
That audience might be naive enough to buy that s***
But it's a small
Select group
Yeah am I also in my experience I mean I got to say a hallucinogenic called is usually pretty chill it's the
Organized around like money or power all those
That's going to f*** you
What happened
Some people take a hard turn on hallucinogenics
Trout
So Alex mentioned
The papes girlfriend there which is a reference to the high-profile nudism activists
Sent a Cisco
Gypsy Taub
Is her name
Okay. But she wasn't it okay
Probably not
It should be pointed out that she wasn't a nudist activists in the 70
Which is kind of where your mind goes
Closer to the 90s and early 2000s
She was a local character and actually has a ton in common with Alex
Princeton
She was a huge 9-11 truther
Public Access show call about 911 called uncensored 911
Which eventually became a show called my naked truth
Where she would host a talk show naked
I guess Alex didn't do his show naked but he got his start in public access and he was super into 9/11
Conspiracy so him and Todd would probably have lots of bond over
You may notice that Alex says that she's in jail for
Coach pedophile Behavior
Yeah that's
Typically this would be Alex using suggestive language to implant ideas in his audiences hatch
In this case however he just doesn't actually know anybody
Details of the case but he feels like he heard something that was like that maybe
With pedophilic but he wants to keep it vague.
Just in case change things up
Tom is in jail for stalking and harassing a former friend of her son
Who she sent messages
Is expressing her love for and who she made actions towards attempting to kid
He was in the ninth grade at the time and her actions are represents
Wow
There's no indication that the paper had any involvement with that stuff though because
Split in 20
2015 and she said that even at that point he was less a romantic partner
I'm more of a roommate and someone who took care of the kids
Who maybe his kids as well
It reported that he's the father of her children but this whole thing
Chaotic and I have no idea what's what
20 year old named James Smith in 2013 and to pay pay a loss
Contract contact a little bit after that point
She told the San Francisco Chronicle that she assumed he'd quote
Completely lost his mind
After that point
Does make some interesting points
Inasmuch as
She felt that the paper wasn't really a trump guy or a right-winger which mites
Stream True to her on the surface
The nature of this conspiracy world that's so prominent now involves the denial about the actual political under
Meaning of the
Conspiracy beliefs
But U-Haul
You may think
But you're just supposed to the Deep state
Cabal or something and have no connection
It all to the ways with
Conspiracy belief is used
Invalidate an attack any kind of federal bureaucracy
In your mind you're against
Demon to drink children's blood
But the real-world implications of your belief serves only explicitly right-wing political goals
You might notice that no one arrives at left-leaning politic
By obsessing about Soros
Sir Klaus Schwab
Some for that
Two dynamic
B built-in you don't read
You're not supposed to realize how all this
This conspiracy is geared towards
Funneling you towards the extreme right-wing political
ASAP
But you don't identify as
Extreme right well I mean
Because people don't talk about it
Totality
For the most part you know people aren't saying you know like
Once these
Far-right billionaires in such get into power
They slowly or quickly a road all of the safeguards of society
The conspiracy person I like
Societies falling apart well just because of the people that you are accidentally
Maintain their power and its
You give them more power
They make Society crumbled more you get more invested in your bowl
Bulshit and isn't nasty Circle
Sure everything about this
This kind of dynamic you know you have like this like
Complete opposition
Too deep
State bureaucracy
And what have you
And like
Yeah where the rubber meets
The road in reality is like oh okay
You know end up getting a bunch of Republicans in office and they want to get rid of Social Security what is that if not
Emblematic of
Deep state bureaucracy and there's so much
I hope that that is where the like
Conservative and right-wing politics
Are the end result of
The obsession that they've gotten YouTube
Think isn't political
And then I mean you know and the
Circumstances being
Because of what they
They do
It reinforces your distrust
Best of
Except for not them because they're the ones
You trust
Cuz they blame the other
Until you're told to label them a rhino or something and then
Too late anyway
Toby's clearly unwell as his depaepe
But they currently aren't
A couple and haven't been for even to touch
For about 7
Chuze charged in 2019 so there's no connection
Between the paper and her crimes and no evidence that
She was running a hallucinogen
This is just all like Alex talking
S*** because it's easier than focusing on anything of substance in the Run
The midterms
And why not
Socket
Yeah I know but that's a really interesting story
I would want to know more about
That whole
Circumstance or anime
You know I mean if you want to know
Inelegant instead of Vista
Dude shows up at a hit with a hammer now it's two naked dudes a f***
Can you nope right and that but with hammers like literal hammers
And then instead of you know this
This person with a rich insane history
But we're just going to be like out pedophile Behavior whatever it is like no Manuel I made it does show
Sound like
Curiosity on Alex's Park
Yeah
This is way more interesting than
Anything else he talks about what's interesting to me is that like Alex could
Probably cast
A lot more suspicion on the story if he knew details better job
Conspiracy theory Rising if he actually cared to do his job
To help him
So Alex makes an announcement
And like
We were recording this on Sunday
I might have a really bad week ahead of
He's tempting me to get back on my b******* a little bit
McCall's
Battleground States
So we're going to be here
Tuesday Wednesday Thursday Friday
What's happening
Always talked about violence
An imminent Republican violence
False flag
Provocateur operation
The government's use all over the place they got to demonize me
Popularized
Russia
Plane
No one cares by popularizing the term false flag attack
Say everything is a false flag with no evidence and it's just meaningless to you
Whatever Putlocker
How do I resist
You have
Why why
He's not going to follow through with it probably not and it'll just be his Junior Varsity Squad
These are going to be there he's going to you're just listening to him say I'm going to force my employees work till it work
Yeah
I know the only thing that's stopping me from EX
Really doing it is but there's nothing
Less compelling than watching me watch
Infowars health so I can't really do it as a stream of no real point to do that
Small facial changes
Yeah I Rob
It's not good content otherwise I probably would do it I would probably
Stream myself responding to be out of a job
I mean
Not a good laugh or not a good responder
Yeah probably not going to do it
Alex has some thoughts about the the
Some ideas of
I don't remember who it was it wasn't buying but there was another show that he plays where
He's sorta
Crazy world
Political
Fringe
Labeled
The minority
They're a minority group
Okay people who have this ideology
He does not like
I am so he starts ranting about how they've almost taken over the GOP
You go to any Republican or any Rally or get any statistical number
Percent of Republicans are now
Populist Anton newworldorder phone
A globalist give Infowars noorani InstaCredit
White people Optical radicalization
What do you like Trump or not he did a great job
Energizer
We've almost taken
The Republican party over
The power structure is in
Total complete
We're not the minority
Diverse majority
Republican voters
Identifying what's wrong
Those white men and women
I'm on your criminal
You fell
All you people quotes
But you're going down and you can feel it in your dirty
Globalist bones
Your bones are dirty
Yeah I know I'm still writing
The queen on my checks to
I don't even think he was trying to say Prince Charles I think he just couldn't come up with a third person
Prince Charles
You know this will come
This will be important later in this episode but that is a smooth 026
For Alex
I'm alright I'm alright alright
And you get like
I don't know why
But it makes
Alex 08 Snapchat
The Hulk My secret is I'm always angry
That's why this this this transition from normal talking to screaming
Has like a dozen
It would if I wasn't coming it
Commenting on it it wouldn't even be like noticeable
No it's not
Slowly it set it comes up sell fake right right been in this make a note of that cuz this is going to be important later
Can meet somebody else who does this poorly
And it's a takes a while to
It's cause he said he was going to get to the media
It's not
And Australia
And Alex is obsessed with the idea that covid lockdowns are coming back
And what have you color
Apparently in Wuhan they had a small lockdown
Just trying to have zero covid policy and a couple times
Periodically over the last year
It'll show up and then everybody's locked-in yeah and then
But Alex
Is obsessed with like this is going to
Come back it's going everywhere
Victus color brings that up and he's like yeah
Alright I'm enjoying I'm enjoying this covid
Fierst
Ohio
You enjoying the Lord
Thank you so much
Started out putting them in years. That's going to be your wife
Restrictions
Judges are involved in
And drugs and I think it's
Agencies as well
Visine youth crime
Violin
Cityscape
Islands in South Philly weather
Vacuum
Exactly
Primary election
Tell me about all these things I said
Beyblade
Clearly technology.
Note of this planet and we have no business
Very interesting
What is a backlash in Australia when I see the people getting really angry at way
Alright I guess nuclear testing has caused
Flying things that are alien technology to be about it we should not deal with any kind of nuclear
Technology because it's not of this Earth
Long pause
Very interesting very interesting
This is exactly like
Most conversations I've had in the line waiting to get into a show
Concert of some sort
Like if I'm waiting
To see Sylvan Esso somebody's going to have a nice little conversation with you to be like this is great I am enjoying this
Aliens are coming for you
Damn it we're just going to stand here in silence for the rest of the night
Makes me it makes me think of that that exchange I had when we were in Hawaii I saw a guy who
He was complaining about Democratic politicians
I normally I would just be like
I don't know why I just ignored it but I like
Like I was in such a good mood is going to the beach
Alright
This guy talked about how these nuclear weapons are creating flying things that are not of this Earth
Alex has to understand that a lot of his collars
Not kept
To a very short amount of time to reveal some kind of a position or idea that they have
That makes their other positions
To hear about look a little silly
Alright you keep him on a short leash
Keep him on a short
So another caller calls in he wants to talk a little bit about the
Does Pelosi situation that everybody's talk
Everybody can't stop talking
First-time caller
One-dimensional
QuickBooks Online
42 years old
It looks like he's a pretty happy guy and I just think it's kind of laughable that they would put
Feeble
82 year old alcoholic
Somebody like that off
That would be able to
Conspiracy theory
I was just making sure. By the police report here
But this color is confused because the media
He's consuming is full of s*** right
It would be confusing to imagine that Paul Pelosi could take the paper in a fight
But that isn't really relevant because they weren't fighting
Wasn't there to attack or kill Paul he was perfectly fine waiting around with him until Nancy return
Paulding have to fight off the paper which is why the situation really isn't that confusing and he just
Get back
Alcanfor evidence
Isn't the new conspiracy theory but it is really fun that crnkovich is still a name that people like Alex say without feeling
Intense shame
What certificates describing is the same old game 2
Conspiracy theorist
I've always played
Essentially goes like this
There's an event that you desperately don't want people to accept his real because it's super threatening to your political project or
Propaganda business mod
You don't really have any direct means of invalidating the event and you can't really claim that it didn't happen so what
You do is you make
Ridiculous demand in
This pitted suspicious
Is that your demand isn't being met
Has no right to the surveillance video from the Pelosi household in the police have already said that the claim that they've refused to turn it
It over to the authorities his fault
But through repetition and an insistence that you
Totally believe the story they just made that video public
You can convince your audience that it's a reasonable demand and that it makes no sense of the Pelosi's wooden
Release the footage
Wouldn't they want to put that out cuz it would silence the dissenters
It's suspicious that they're not
So hoping there's a tried-and-true game
Gets played
Pretty much every time with
Conspiracies to some degree or another and it's a scam
Cernovich and Alex don't
Actually want any footage to be released
Because they know damn well that it wouldn't prove anything that they want proven
All they wanted the ability to use the fact that it's not really
Please do some kind of a mean
Introduce suspicion and doubt
In Their audience
You can see clearly that it work
And if it is really still be like all this
This is attitude and give us the uncut video
Not sincere what you're saying is is what would happen it would either be like
There's something that it in this
It's not really release that deep for me. Give it on to some other demand for information that suspicious
They haven't released
You know it's the it's the Obama birth certificate no we need the long-form
That's all just gone down this too many times
This is not how I wanted to find out that Ray Romano is an Infowars
I'll tell you that right now
You didn't hear that voice
Maybe I was just
I don't know
What was his knife his wife's name on Everybody Loves Raymond
It's not ball
Get another get another call and
One of the things that's really a through line throughout this episode is Biden gave a speech
Amy talked about how
There's going to be
You're we may not have an answer for all of the midterm elections on Election night you know there's going to be some balance now
May take a while
Preparing People in
Like reminding people that that's the case
This is proof
Is telling people
About to steal it
So that's that's sort of the game that Alex is playing on here
That's what this color has
Thoughts about that
Speechless
Philadelphia
Which was so badly received
With this speech last night
Free calendar
Awesome hey it's
It's going to take us some time to count the votes okay
Unless you knew you were going to have
Stealing place
He was everybody not to question the steel
That's what he said
Nothing about how the country is going
Badly things are going
Not one word about that
Everything is
Paul Pelosi
Underwear with a hammer
I don't believe that and I'm just because like with the
There's no way that would have
Why
That just
Polaroid that script
Oh my God I guess I guess there's two ways you can really interpret that that would be that there was a script
For the attack
Part of this group was
Du Pape saying where is Nancy so they could connect it to January 6th
Or the other way I guess you can read this is Alex saying that the media coverage of it
Has the script where the paper didn't actually say where
Everybody is just saying that
So they could
Can I go January 6th
Except
The pavement is interview said that that's what you was doing
Is there
They asked where Nancy was in advance
Right to be that it was all fake
I meant to pay
Interview with the police
After he was arrested was also
PostScript
Really really important to keep this in mind
Because if this conspiracy is true
That means that when Alex is asked
Why were they
They found in the in their underwear with a grip
Well I mean was it
Cuz if it's not
That's a question that I need to know about how did we get to naked hammering I will say that if there is a
Play that I'm
Auditioning for and part of it involves getting hit with a hammer I'm not taking that role
Scripts are they right Northern like all right now
While you wait
Listen
I get it you're going to be bored
You did it the other night where that be I we all got together at Langley or whatever it is they're going to DIA
A f****** Is On The Rise by man what are you talk
Yeah it's a little bit strange I don't I don't know
You just that Alex says is that callers also don't ask follow-up questions
And so it could just sort of lay there as there was a script
And it doesn't really mean
Appreciate that somehow Biden
I'm saying it takes a while to count
What is not immediately off
Proof about to steal I feel like most of these people who are claiming that the conspiracy
Should really wreck
Recognize that it does take
Relatable facts
I have
A vampire puppet
But that I'd like to introduce them
So we are in a little bit for this guy and the other contacts drop
But here it is
Mr. Battle Royale
Just wanted to make
Commercial
But that looks like with all these narrative
A craft
People like you and people like me who want to build Meredith
Going straight
I want to bleeder 8U with my
Ideas for my speech embarrass you
The other wife
Okay no violin
None of that
We don't need that
I think I know how it feels I think I got it
I find it very sad
When I hear something like that I mean person of all
The way that the artificial growling
And stuff
It's a bummer but ya sattar is
Feeling that he's expressing that like we don't believe in narrative
Right
Shut up in order to
Storytown
I don't know what you're talkin
It must be comforting to feel like
That isn't how you engaged
Information
But it's not true
Anybody listen to Alex
Is a dick
Tannerite I mean it's always
Is everything is from a movie of course you're addicted to narrative and honestly I don't I don't think that narratives themselves
As a way to experience a lot of stuff
Is bad
It's just when they're the way most people
Strobe
You know narratives that are built on
Completely fraudulent information
Direct you towards
Really dangerous and negative conclusion
That's
You should probably recognize
Your
Not special
Your mind thinks in stories
Come on bro
Man I just
It's just so hard you know you want to think that you're an individual iconoclast
That acts like everybody else wish
She's they could and then
Someone listening to Alex Jones
You know I feel about that
I hope he uses it in a commercial
So Alex talked a little bit about his belief in electoralism
Which is weird
I'm sorry what
Well
That there's a reason that you should vote
Did little Democrats
They're going to do it
Being elected
Elections office
Steal it and do all this crap
He's doing the front of us
Nothing we can really do or what happens
We both need to steal it again
Do they have to use the names of dead people
And they have to use the next door to move out of state
Play have a limited pool
But they've got that's why they're picking
I'm sorry what
Angie Battleground
A massive tsunami
Here's a dumbass as simple as saying
A 350 million Americans
Voting age
Why why would you say that
Call voting Republican
They couldn't statistically say Republicans lost
That's basically what's happening Jared love you
Yeah
Yeah I think about it
All right so every
Single time
You don't vote Republican
Looking the Democrats
Use your name to vote Democrat
Only if your dad
This is one of the
Weaker defenses of electoralism that I've heard in awhile
Democrats couldn't say that the election was stolen or something
Also why do the people rigging the election need to use the names of dead people are people who moved out of state
If this is such an elaborate plot that they're engaged in why couldn't they create
Fake identities can't just make up names plus if the whole scheme relies on fraudulent
What's in dead people's names
Where are the examples of that happening in 2020
I don't seem to believe it's a rock-solid case that that's what they are doing and what they
I plan to do
13 weird that I don't think I've ever heard him site
One example of it happening
There is that
Did you know that if you cast an absentee ballot but you die before election day that they will invalidate your ballot
That happened to 3400
69 voters in Michigan alone
I wonder what Alex thinks about that and I'll continue wondering because he's never mentioned it
Also PolitiFact reviewed news reports of instances where people cast ballots on behalf of dead people and found that quote
A more often the perpetrators
And this isn't always a malicious form
Brought either
Sometimes it's one of the cases where someone dies after casting an absentee ballot in the system doesn't catch
That does happen
Sometimes
Or in many cases it could be a relative or a loved one of the
This person who felt like Castor devoting their name would have been in
In line with their wishes
Still fraud but maybe it's not as rooted in evil or malice as it might you might assume
Whatever the case the frequency of people voting a dead people's names he's so small as
To be a relative
Is argue
Alex has
Is pathetic and meaningless but
That's because he actually doesn't want
Really think
The people should vote
He doesn't really
Uno's that if
That's his position there like that voting is meaningless and then nothing will ever change to that system a whole lot of his listeners will take
That is a sign that it's time to take a bar
Probably doesn't want to like
Fully endorse that publicly either
He wants a
Trickling of Chaos
The full-on unintended consequences version where
Right one goes out and kills all the police
Place and then storm is over guy home invading the Pelosi's
Cool can you get to make jokes about house
Difficult
But it worked out okay we can profit off that
I'm still being busy
Did notion of like
A bunch of Alex's audien
It's taking up arms or something and like it will never solve
This through the system right.
That's sad that's too much
Yeah I mean ironically that might be the only way to save them
Is if they were to actually take up arms everybody would be like maybe this problem is
Too big to ignore for now
Instead we're going to be like and I will just let him do it for another few years and then we'll live in packs
I don't agree with your position
No no no
Timeless
Thank you
Stop
Anybody
And I believe that
We will win the election by
Seahawks
Stop
We need that meal watches out there
Music
Case of a nuclear war
Is that Ray Romano
PhD but he likes the mule Watchers get to later
And also he's saving his X3 a case of a nuclear war
Man that is an interesting PhD
I doubt it's a PhD in the effects of radiation on the human body
I will say that
Sure or voter intimidation
So we have another color is fun
Gyro in Georgia
What's going on my brother how you doing today
The New World Order
I'm trying to tell you look
Spoke to you about a week ago and I don't know if you remember or not
Bonaire
What about
Baby doing
Spiritual
I told you I'm
16-year listener
Panther to you about three times this is
And today is my birthday
On top of that
What beautiful brotherly DeSoto prayer
So I'll get it I get a haircut of prayers, man
Yeah dude
I love this though a week ago this guy called
Special collars off the air
Animal
Yeah I think
I think that's
If Alex
Had been doing this kind of stuff
Like back in the 9/11 days and like
I call this
His career would not have gone the same way as it would because a lot of those people who were like
Ostensibly
Skepta cleaning and kind of atheist but also have
I'm leaning towards
Conspiracy they would see him for the religious zealot that he actually did
And I don't think that he would have had any traction
Outside of the
The extreme-right militia Folks at
The Christian identity folks
And I think that I think that would have been a better reality let me know that
Yeah I mean that I think most people do I think that's that's one of the things that we all I guess just
To paper over is how many of these benign beliefs are
I also how you doing some sort of like a
Passive
Acceptance believe so you know like
Hey listen
That's not what this is
You know that's not what this
No no this is a little bit different
Passive this is not passive
So are we going to call her
They can steal it
Based on this Joe Biden
Daddy loves you Cincinnati Ohio
Red Wave coming and
Feelings about the elections even though
Get away with it
And
Well I can't wait to see what they do
Before Interruption on the open
We're going to make them Steel in front of us again
That's going to cause that even bigger Awakening
I think the Deep Staters are going to let the Republicans win the house
But they're going to mitigate this massive realignment just happen
No Stealing tuna rolls too much
Beautiful
Because
Yes
Everybody is so fat
I can see everybody just Etna Street
I mean
Crazy
Everybody's awake
Read Alex Jones
T-shirt
Store
They know what's going on
Sentence for fact
I'm more mob than ever end
Financial support that's
They hate you
Bad time to get cut off by the brake
Are you giving me money
LKQ you can give me a ride
Yeah man
That's
Breast
Confused as to why we don't just make
Voting mandatory
If that if we're going to have to fight all of this
Every every election is stolen then just make voting mandatory everybody has to vote
Steal the election
If that were to
Be something they were done then you'd have to also come up with a lot of ways to make
It more accessible
So I made her want to do that
Yeah but I think if you go that route then you'd have to add a lot of other steps along the way to
I mean obviously they don't want to
To solve the problem they want the problem
Going to be there so they
You can blame it
Whenever they
Obviously it's not a problem they want to
The electoral system is
Much of the same as demanding the Pelosi's
Exaggerating
Complained
But they have
In order to just
Justify their own police
The notion that
They can't steal two-in-a-row is silly
First of all if you believe that there stealing
These elections
Then why not oh no they wouldn't do that we wouldn't buy it the second
What are you talkin about you
Assholes stormed the capitol
The capital
What are you going to CC
We know you don't believe that elections are real right know that I mean it's it's legit just
A way of
Really antagonizing the audience
And the space
To be hostile and very angry anytime Democrats
Well it's a and it's also a little bit like
You know when you will
We talked about voter fraud that kind of stuff
It happens more often because Republicans do it then Democrats that kind of
And that's parts
We just psychologic
You know like it happens more by Axel
The point
Is there priming them to say that the Democrats steal election
And if you do that
Then that means that it's morally okay for you to steal elections because they're already doing it maybe
That's the way that they're their process works is they they bring it into a situation where it's like
Obviously
They're stealing election so there's no reason we shouldn't
Stupid for us not to because then we're not even playing with fire
Yes we have to steal the election
You may you may you may have something there I think
It's more just a way to always feel like you were the righteous party
There a lot of good reasons to do evil
Sure
So
My man
This next caller blue my mind
I believe you I don't know I still don't know what to
I like to YouTube
I like to donate to your
And I like to do
Because I have actually
I like to donate to your legal
We call this fella back and talk to his we need to fund
That would be beautiful brother
I don't believe this necessarily
I'm going to guess you guys like replicas or something
He's asking or offering here is a
Ridiculous
You can't truly believe that he's offering up
Both an original and original put Caso and in original world
The cheapest of Picasso's paintings still sell for over $100,000 and some more valued in the tens of
In order for this guy to have this
Someone would have had to pay a shitload for it
If you're in the position to pay for a piece of art like that
You could just donate money to Alex instead of partying with a
Piece of history that
It's only going to appreciate in value
I think it should be illegal to give Art to Alex
The value of Colby's has a bit more variable
His Maryland paint
Sold earlier this year for 195 million dollars but there are a bunch
Books that are substantially cheaper than that
If this is real and I have misgivings about that it represented
Deeply fanatical and unhealthy attachment
Making sure Alex stays wealthy
Whatever amount you can possibly get from selling these artworks will absolutely not make an impact on his ability to carry out his legal case
And honestly I wouldn't be surprised if Alex
Big Y.
Are going that's an investment like you have a Picasso
There's not going to be more of them shouldn't be at
You can't act
No one can let Alex have art. M just a just against
Said no sculptures no aren't Jordan consider this
That Maryland painting is the most expensive
Peace made by either of these are
And if Alex Guthrie
Yeah it's Alex got the full value from selling it he's still need like
800 million dollars to cover
Viskase Sandy Hook
So I don't know I would
If I were this color
Hard to believe
Do people think Warhol was good at stuff
That's the weird thing to me
Letter that Marilyn paint
Thing is very iconic
I mean
Whatever
Whatever art world
What's next
Skull crystal skull
No okay
Yeah. I guess
The mostest
I got really self-conscious about this cuz you were like
Square has not expensive Guernica is
Priceless you know like we're not talking about the same kind
Something that's sold at been sold
Article from 2015 here saying that
The women of Algiers
Painting of Picasso's is the most
Expensive is that sold
It was 174
So
There are there is a chance of their Picasso's that will never sell a Tartan Museum
That makes Morse
Can human treasure you know it's not like
You could sell that I mean I suppose you
You could because we live in 2022 plot twist
Guys off right now
We gave the fake to the Musial fund the info War
So anyway Alex gets really excited about this idea of people giving him valuable.
Want to donate we should create like a donated infowars.com
Will you can send us emails of what you want to do now
Do you got my pleasure
My truck
You donate
Painting
A hundred percent
Will do to find this operate
I agreed to a deal I'll just be honest and listeners
Currently getting paid
$40,000 a month
To work here
Live off that
A bunch of
Truck car in nice
Deep house
It won't pull the back and I just Suburban guy
B
Pay 40% of legal bills
Associate
I wonder if Alex realizes it forty thousand a month is super
Spiritually higher than almost everyone in his audience
I mean unreal
It was saying that it's like a modest living is pretty wild and saying it in the same breath or he's asking people to donate
The Cars album pay his legal fees is
Amazing
Barry out at auction listen I'm salaried at half a million dollars a year now obviously the fact that I only
The company and keep muscle
The more money offshore and then Bitcoin and stuff so don't worry about that
Sell your own s***
Yeah give me five grand to pay part of his legal expenses
He's being sued and he owns a hundred percent of the company that's being sued with him
I'd be willing to bet that he'll be able to offload
All of that on to the company by Betty Assam language in his corporate policies
There he doesn't cover legal expenses for employees something along those lines
Don't sell your truck
And give the proceeds to Alex
If you're one of those nurses listen to this somehow
A f****** Picasso can't save them 8000000 a Bitcoin couldn't save him and your Used F150
He is going to do anything
Other than get a few bucks
Jackson Alex's pocket
Save it
Keep it give it to your kids
Do something do anything at the kars4kids
Light it on fire would be better for the world
Metallic
You can maybe do that is an art
Installation maybe make a little cash
Video of you lighting your car on fire new Guernica
Silas complains about money
60% off on all these
Money onto the products
Okay
Buy something
We're dealing with
Maidana
Jackson with the money to find this place
What doing what
Insolvent we were a year ago
The money came and I'll provide again
God's plan
I'll never quit but I'll keep fighting as hard as I can
Decides
That I'm not supposed to
If you decide
God working for you
That means you
If you decide to take me out of the game
Supposed to have
Lady Gaga
I don't want stop fighting
Tell you that
We need to go to infowarsstore.com and and get Alex's war or get endgame
DVD to get a buck
And I don't like coming on here
And just give me money give me money
Worse than me Dubai
Yeah
Yeah I dis is this guy's torture
Yeah that makes sense
There is
No chance
That 60% off is like him taking a loss on somebody's dumb pills
I appreciate this cuz I thought occurred
That you know we had a lot of situations where
You could take Alex Jones clips from his shows
And play them in the school setting and you can learn a lot
You know for lawyers
If you want to become a better lawyer you can place him Alex Jones clips
You know what not to do
You know how to not be a bad lawyer
That also
Accounts for business I forgot about that you could get an NBA
By not doing what Alex tells you to do on it hurt says he's doing on his jump
Would be a good life
Anti marketing
Example
If you wanted to teach somebody how not
To get a truck that last one
Play
This is like a richdadpoordad kind of situation
Listen though
Alex
Feel sometimes like
He can't ask for money
Anymore he's just run out of it was just run out of juice
He digs. He's got it in him
I can
I don't want
I hate being on my business and my business guy
I'll give into the new world order the ATL
Please give me money
Okay
Okay alright
Give me money
Convincing
Wow
I mean I don't know if I've ever seen an argument board distilled down into the
The things that he does believe
News clippings but involves Alex yelling on the phone with another caller show
We're losing which again
Joshua makes them dangerous I'm worried
About a false flag the next 5 days what do you think
Is real I think I definitely want to Gin up a bottle violence they want to say how dangerous
I want to run this country
Republicans built it
Republicans do all the damn work
We all know it
And they're everywhere
Everybody knows real business people real hard-working people
Republican party over we've almost done
I appreciate your
This guy is above the left-right paradigm
Republicans built this country and they do everything
Alright
This guy should read and ran
You know what's crazy
I'm confused as to why they still think that false flags are,
Well I thought mine was supposed to be dead by now
Yeah but like we saw what happened
Somebody made a harebrained attempt to assassinate the speaker of the house or the very least
Hold hostage and everybody was like
It was a good day
People are concerned about it one guy went to prison
Alex has done a whole season about Hammer f******
Yeah Yeahs sweets
I don't know if you make a good point
That
Seems
It seems like
Anything happening probably wouldn't make all that much of an impact you really feel like at this point everybody's kind of
Everybody just expect political violence and now and if it happens will be like
Well that's part of the game I guess
Honestly
Isn't that where we are
I don't think it's where we should be no a 3-week statement of
How
Lackadaisical
He's got enough power
We'll get back to this here in a little bit this discussion with the mule watch
And stuff like that is also even like
Another lackadaisical approach
Should be one of the most seriously taking things
Yeah yeah but
You know
I mean maybe what if instead we should lower taxes for rich people
That's an interesting idea I think I got to pitch for the Democrat
I just got a text from my friend Marty DeRosa Hammer Time with Alex was a wild ride
From somebody
That's alright I should
Come up with
Another person that was Greg The Hammer Valentine another wrestler but I was distracted by Jim the Anvil
I never came up with that one issue that correction in apology
Hammer
Uncle Howard
Ellison
Does next caller
My God my God why this Ole Boy
To be as how this starts
Awesome I want more of this on Infowars
Horseshoe
Talk to Arizona
You the man
Phone World idea here
You guys are in
Louisiana Tech
Louisiana
Hysterical nonsense is going on about
Seamless production to stop
Doodoo butt
Far as I know
So so explain what's causing the bottleneck
Windfall
I agree that
Inflation
Bob inviting occasionally tells the truth he says I'm going to go out the door companies
Definitely globalist
And they're definitely part of the whole problem
First of all
Wow
Lovett I've refused
To hear that one time and then not not acknowledge nobody acknowledged
That's the only thing I want to talk about
There's a payoff is that you just have to pump the brakes
Okay but
He brings up
Appoint
And that is that
Diesel isn't going to run out unless they stop production
You got this wrong and Ralph has to come up with a way to like
Kind of hold on to
Is diesel fuel
Oil companies are globalist
But this does
Doesn't work
This is going to play
His family is part of oil companies or whatever it is
A good first
Attempt and then as they keep talking these like oh no wait I can do this
Reduction of
Diesel has
Austin
Any new diesel at all
If you do the app
The numbers
Planes out to
Not you have any new supplies
Behind schedule in major shortages
Starting in like 12 days
Crazy
Because
Wide shut down the biggest diesel refineries
They shut down the system
Yeah they're there are
Applied problems
I talked to Oil Company folks that work at every level of it at most
A lot of my family works at every let
Roughnecks
Answers to unit delivery companies
The last four years under the lockdowns in control
Oil well
Equipment
Plants are breaking down
Yeah yeah
It kind of makes me want to scream like my
Screaming goat
Call brother
No
No no.
Okay little shoehorned a moto Force what do we got here
I mean does he have what I want to know is mechanics now I want to know what requipment
Probably like on a app on his phone or something what you've got
What is somebody who's on house phone but has a cell phone that has a soundboard app
That's my guess maybe
Casio keyboard
You can have one of those little keyboards it's got all the screaming goat
In there who hasn't
Spent the day programming a screaming goat into their keyboards
You might be right but it doesn't matter
Alex is trying to find a way for his
Conspiracy to make sense by making
Things up as he goes along and it's
Really good way if you want to do the
That's a good way to do it is to make up personal stories from random people that you know to defend your point
Anecdotal evidence
Yeah
These are compelling things for his audience these anecdotal stories
Because other narrative-driven people
And Alex knows this week and manipulate them was storytelling regardless of what that passed College sets
Repurpose that guy's unfortunately delusional
Reality they're benign oil refineries that have been shut down or scaled back soon
Pensacola Dam
Pandemic began and most of them happened under Trump
Presidency
Another was damaged in Hurricane Ida and what had an explosion
In 2019
Still limiting its
Capacity
There's a confluent two variables that are affecting the situation with diesel but it's not going to run out in the middle of
December and as time goes on the price will stabilize
Imprint downward
Note to self Alexandra's any connection to reality and if
The did he wouldn't spend so much of his time covering this dumb Paul Pelosi story and you have no patience for screaming goats
Inclimate horn
Although that goes my favorite color in a long time
It's ambitious
It's somebody having
Fun
God damn it is like
It is
A
That he said
I am going to play this when I call
He wasn't like
Last minute you know it wasn't like a game-time decision like
His fingers on the button and he has a moment of
CertainTeed screen lock my screen screaming goat
You know it yeah
Cuz you didn't have it wasn't a revised
He didn't have other screaming things or another he's just got
Call Doran and screaming goat Andy bevere didn't have to say it makes me want to scream
But that wasn't a necessary, but I can made that comment so we can play the song
Perfect love it
Love it
Guest
One of my good friends
Journalist
He still able to break through I think he's probably had
50 million views of his reports the last
Hernandez a little bit in the past he's one of the people I've collectively referred to as the baby reporters
Sutro upon imports from time to time
Along with like survey Savannah Hernandez and Patrick Howley
They're people who give me a distinct Vibe of angry immaturity that's being enabled and boosted by Raelynn
Media Outlets like Alex
For Drew and Savannah that use Turning Point USA as well
How we probably isn't welcome at
Tpusa because of his moreover
America First Association that almost
Comical anti-semitism
Who tried to start off his career with a veneer of respectability in journalist
Pretense presenting himself as an undercover journalist and investigative reporter
This was all dropped
Pretty quick
Became clear that he was just trying to go out and get footage of protest that he could use to make a antifa bait for the right-wing meme
Stock and trade
This culminated in him being a defense witness in the Kyle Rittenhouse trial which is a little bit weird
Considering he was on the payroll
Of the right-wing media Outlet right real America's voice
Set the time
And you didn't actually see the shootings
He testified that the BLM and antifa people riding and then a few hours later he went on Tucker Carlson show to talk about
Being a witness on the trial
Just pretty classy
I can't believe the people don't trust the America
So weird
Drew is essentially somebody who saw this success and profitability of what Andino was doing and got into the same Lane
His work is meaningless and it's just meant to incite based on distorting reality with Selective editing and telling have stories
Further he's intensely boring
And he's not good at talking
When I heard his name come up I almost turned this episode off but I decided to keep going only because Alex was still allegedly
Taking calls and some of these weirdos are worth the time baby somebody else
Where you're coming from
And so
What kind of assholes
Looks at Andy now and it's like I can be a piece of s*** to
Like that's crazy
Thinking about
How difficult to work is
Maybe you get a milkshake thrown at you
Or something
And you get to make hay out of that.
I'm saying easy work
Lots of money
It's hard to say no
It's actually pretty attractive really I can't believe so many people get into like multi-level marketing
6 games whenever what you could do is just be a giant piece of s*** online
Yeah yeah
Here's the problem
There's only so many spots
Really in that world true
The bar for entry is really low like in terms of what requirements are necessary that
Talent is not really all that important
You don't have to really know much
Right in a lot of people can do that so these pots are easy to
To fill
But
There's a finite about a time on Tucker
True people
Getting called up to Carson's couch
Great
And it doesn't you know without the monoculture you don't get catapulted into stardom overnight any
Hot stuff
It's tough I get it
But they're still like even if you can't make yourself into like a really high level
Person in this game a lot of money to be made on that
Back on
Yeah yeah yeah just getting on the talking point
Turning Point USA the rotations
Play Alexandra mad about alike
Probably
States of America a superpower
For now
Not conducting election
Fairly and securely in
Single day
Central and Paramount
Biden said last night
We've always done it always takes days or longer
No one know that didn't happen
Machine
Obvious
That none of that's true.
Full of s*** but also like doesn't through sound like a baby
He really does
He really does sound like he is a very annoying
Is that reporting a suits
Just a little too big
Phenomenon
What is feeling
And it's because of the way I mean it's at least eight
Partially
Contributed to by social media the way that everybody's
Clamoring for information
And the way that the media now covers these elections like
Kinds of influences make it
Feel like we should have things immediately
And it distorts your
Memories of how things were in the past
Pretty regular for elections
To not really be fully counted until the next day or days later
Nothing to do with
That the electronic Mists of it
Because if you're if you're going to make that argument
We saw Brazil
Just head doing an election overnight
Right so if you're complaining about that then just say
Let's change it to do what somebody else does
Instead of being like
Wow this country is over I think we should do fast
Sure
I guess I was going to say hostile party
Partisanship also plays a role but that exists in Brazil to
Why we can't do that now because hostile partisan
Gunship wasn't
Bad enough whenever they started the that you don't put on chip was
But former dictator
Back then so yeah
Hear it like
You have tons of people who just like you can't concede any
Like races that would probably been conceded 30 years ago
Or never concede it now
There is such
Polarisation
Many races are fairly close
Yeah and
These things to contribute to how
Voting ghost
Also
Apps
70 ballot
Hi there can be certification of those or no
There's three there's a lot of stuff that aren't real
Factors
It's just a way of invalidating
And I mean literally the only time in my lifetime that I
The only time I can think of it
The past hundred years that election was actually stolen it was
The same way that the other election
Since I've been sold which is
The Supreme Court or a bunch of rich white dude got together and we're like here's what we'll do. This time how about you get
One and I get one and we called today took a long time
Took a long time
To steal that election
Thanks Rodger
Anyway Drew
So they
Talk a little bit more about Dubai
Comments about how it will take awhile
Account
Andrew gets pretty mad about this
How do we stop their surroundings and I put a sold in Hernandez
I mean in the purse
Propaganda right number one
Is higher more intellectual
These people come out and they say what they're going to do before they do it
Because number one for the sake of
Ganda
Because they need to put
Narrative
Literally jailing the true
Behind the movie
Poster geo-tracking
What was going on during 2020
How convenient
They're shutting them down
Turn all kinds of people on social media while at the same time
Geniusly
People to accept
Midterm is going to take days
To come to a conclusion because they need to
Because there are millions of people in this country not the viewers
Idiot
Who
They say is Gospel number one
Number two
Because they view themselves more powerful more greater
Their word is literally God
Call James
Whatever they say
Goes in the future
Disguise one of the best talk show host that is your addition I'm sending you back to the mine
You know ya like that
You're not good at getting angry I see some potential there
You know
Hazlet
Confidence
That's true and that takes that's more than you can't teach that you really can't
I know it is I'm in Alex
Position I find that a little admirable
But yeah he's swinging
Is bad
He doesn't have a good arm
Sounds like an angry baby can't run for s***
Yeah I don't think
Picking up like half of the word
Finger though it's
These guys are doing things it doesn't feel rooted in any prints
Sapore meaning
It's really weird because he's whiffing a lot of words and whipping a lot of like
Phrasing
But it doesn't feel like nerves
It's not like hey I'm in the big leagues here or anything
Now you just doesn't have it
I mean you know baby if he has another 10 years to work on s*** but but maybe
He's just a
Exhausted from doing a lot of hard work
It discusses
Barack Obama's rally last night in Phoenix
Before I trolled him
One thing that I heard continually
Instantly throughout all the
Candidates
You're making mail-in voting some kind of trendy thing
Cringe
The same time because
This is so stupid
IQ
Just believe whatever they say
He's made a mail-in voting like some kind of new tech
Trendy thing
Just be apart of in doing
It's really weird how they've done that
Cute pools about that can grab a manipulator
I know exactly what they're doing
Play
On people's laziness
Play on people's
Low IQ because they're naive
Could you didn't roll Obama
That Obama's speaking at an Arizona any wouldn't stop yelling while speaking
We got kicked out of the event
While Obama told him he needed to be polite and that if you wanted to speak so bad he's
Should set up his own rally
You got some attention for that but unfortunately didn't get invited to go on Tucker to talk about how his Free Speech was stifled and that proves that Obama
But better luck next time maybe it'll work out is this
Is what we called journalist
Dummy text
That's just this
Business model
You know
That's what he does he goes to it like an event it like
Basically
If This Were the past
He would have been the person who is in Alex's
Yo Bill Clinton's a rapist Toronto
Yep you know that
That's the that's the level of work that he's doing
Sedalia Kansas
Amanda
It is what it is
Hi
Just
You can't be a you can't be enough
TNT cringe
You can't be a Nazi and be like
It's very cringe like now you're a fascist
Come on man
Stop this
I think
That it sounds a little cringey to call things
Like voting
I understand that
Aged out
Of slang
It's hard for me to judge
Too much but he's from another generation
I understand but I can't handle Tik Tok face
Can't do this like you're going to have to dances
I don't want anybody being like Oh
Oligarchies on fleek like I don't need any of this s*** you know I can't we have them use my b
Come on
Sorry was the first word that popped into my head
Should I reveal
This is private I don't know if it'll put you on blast here
You do respond to some tax
Should I send you with cool beans I do I love say cool beans till I die
That'll never go out of style my man
I thought cool beans all the way back from
Simpsons in the 90s bad
I remember people at
K-life
When I was in church saying cool beans
When I was like 14 minutes are all I know
Could be from the
Morty's
So do I pull Watchers
The mule
Come back up
And Alex Andrew love
The narrative
Because it's going to become a mainstream narrative things here and there
The kind of test it out
The public
Stupid people in the Mindless
To believe this stuff
And I'm telling you
Force
This will be coming in on Monday
Jailed indicted
Canceled
Target
Three-letter agencies declared a domestic
Chrissy
It doesn't matter
Whether you're on the right or the left this is what the left doesn't understand
Care about your voter process
And you show up watching a ballet
Accuse you of being Adam
Democracy
It's not about left or right
Control all of us
Globalist and Satanist
Real
How to control elections
Because they want to control the pain
We have no democracy
Democracy democracy democracy democracy
What about Bill Gates
Making decisions on behalf of the United States of America in
On foreign soil what about that is that Democratic
All these Democrats are in
Globalist
Some right-wing rhinos are as well
Right
Economics
Public right now
It needs to be a
.
Oh man so that's that's an example of the like you can't
You can't do the yelling
Saying yeah it's
Alex
It's like aha
It's false
But at the same time feels right this dude yelling
If you want to respond to like calm down
Call Mom Dad
Call Bella
This'll pass
He's just having a little bit of a flourish when you try
I feel like he is sitting on top of another him
Wearing a trench
And that's how they're doing this year
Baby reporter has a really good illustration of why I called this guy babe
Alice's the situation of the relationship between the world economic forum and the government is non-existent is known as
He knows he's supposed to be mad about this
Stopping at these people because that's what the right-wing media audience
Eats up so he does it
It's performative outrage and there's nothing really behind it
Even tripped himself up about the whole idea that we have no democracy at the end there because he knows that he needs to direct
This exciting Outburst into partisan
It's not that there's no democracy in the country it's that the Democrats and the Republicans that I don't like her puppets of the world economic forum
This kind of destroy the whole premise that there's no democracy because if you were able to get this
Support you could unseat those Democrats and bad Republicans
And only elect people who are hostile to Klaus Schwab
It doesn't matter that he's basically contradicting himself in the course of a minute
The actual things he's saying don't really mean any
It's about a listening animotion
No response and then directing those emotions into negative feelings towards your political Adam
It's something Alex does a bit better and less transparently than Drew
Which was young and also has no discernible conviction
Past getting attention so it makes sense that Alex would be better at
Yeah
Also poll watching is totally fine
There tons of people Watchers who operate within accepted
Guidelines
What's not okay is voter intimidation
Which is what Drew and Alex are Defender
This is become popular
Analysis crewsense at least 2015
But wasn't much of an issue before that because he didn't really have strong convictions about presidential candidate
Never made it out of a primary so it never really was an issue
In the lead-up to the 2016 election Larry Nichols was on the show stressing the need for armed groups to be outside every polling play
Place any effort organized around this
Id2020 these ideas continue to circulate heavily and write with median Rodger Stone made
Some pushes and back
The original stop this
Steal ideas
Hello
Clearly these were not attempt
To defend Alexa
Integrity
They were spindly disguised motivation
How to make people scared to vote
The cycle because of course it is
Hit Mesa Arizona armed individuals with their faces covered we're seeing patrolling
Leading to a humpback group called clean elections USA being ordered by the court to stay at least 75
From drop boxes
And ordered not to follow or
Speak to voters
This is because they were doing
Reuters reported people watching them from hiding in bushes
People watching
Binoculars
And even taking photos of Voters lice
Templates
One voter reported to the doj quote
I've never been more intimidated in my life
Trying to vote
This is the behavior that Alexandra running
Cover for it
This is what they want to see more of
And here's the thing
I totally understand the Vigilantes doing this voter intimidation
If they truly believe the b******* that folks like Alex and Drew yellow but day after day why wouldn't they harass people at the
Pools in Ballard
They have to believe that the election is being stolen
To not do something like what they're doing would be to let that
Happen
These people are wrong and what they're doing is
Is horrible but it's the natural conclusion of the rhetoric italics in Tucker use everyday
You believe the things that these demagogue say
These actions make total sense
This is the problem
If you believe that say somebody a Super Evil
Acting without any cons
And there's no one who will hold them account
Maybe you think the only way to do it is to go to their house
And smash their f****** kneecap
You know like these are things that make
Sense
It's just insane
It's just in
Senior
Because I grew bored of
This baby
Two calls for a while and by that time the
The charm of the guy with the
Clown horn to head kind of worn off
Yeah listening to him wine is really taking the the sales out of that
Clown horn about the devil
Controlled demolition from with
Of our society and the number one
Democracy or a constitutional republic or anything
Functioning
A group of
People on planet Earth
Money is a
Voice of the people
And when you begin to stop
Is taking away the voice of the people
These people know that
This is how it works
Countries that are communist
They know that the only way to truly take away power from the people
Is the take away their vote
Also voice
Censorship
Election meddling
Go hand and hand
Totalitarian regime
Because those two things
Need to be
In order to have a
Healthy Society or
A healthy group of people here on play
Globalist these people
They know this
Because they're all energized by
Satan and Lucifer
What I mean by that
Is Lucifer
Has been around longer than us
For a very long
Chicago Behavior
Study
Manipulate human emotion
Study how to manipulate Society
To do his bidding to get into the palm of his hand
Human beings
To do what he wants
This is why we see the same reoccurring agenda
Text Jordan you look a little bit frustrated and I don't understand why cuz this guy is spitting Hot Fire
You understand
Set the devil
It's been around for a long time
You been studying people
And what he's come to the conclusion
Is that an order to destroy Society
You have to get rid of Elections
And kick people off so I just
I just have never heard someone that dumb you know what the really work
Shadowbanned
Ask you a question
If you've got an ultimate Evil
Alright
Strongest evil
Second only to God and Lucifer Unholy Duo
Holy Trinity
Beelzebub
Wife
Yeah I don't I don't idiot are you
I don't
Oh man
I feel
It wouldn't take that long if you're the devil to figure out like how to push buttons
In early Humanity the devil was like hey maybe if I give people candy they'll do what
The devil was still formulating a lot of these ideas because social media didn't exist
I'm so
If his argument is that the only way social media could exist as if there was the devil
I might believe that was not the argument
Self is good but shadowbanning is the work of the town
I am definitely going to include Uncle howdy
Uncle howdy
This dude is a disaster
Alex wanting to hire him
But he already has a thing with Turning Point
Feel like
I can't see him
Attaching himself to Alec
Anything other than
Like greater attention
Amazon here is good for him cuz he's just like I'll get the word out or whatever
Tucker's not calling
But
Actually it's
It's weird to think he's actually probably
Better situated than Alex right now
Yeah
Yeah in terms of like longevity
Yeah yeah people to sell their f****** cars for it
That is a good point
Azure Pointe Sienna
Cider do Wolf Blitzer
Guys I'm sorry
There is a show is going to get canceled
Get you to sell your
Car and give it to him I need unrelatable
Sell your boat
In order to keep neon are alright
Xl-3 we got to go
Stelter is asking for 8 million in Bitcoin
Today
3 parallel
Text did not necessarily ask for that
For that specifically
At least not on are sitting at episodes
For the midterms
False Flags
Still, there are we still doing the midterms
Episode comes out on Monday Tuesday is is the election
You know please
Think about your vote
There's important
Maybe we'll not Usher in the devil but
In-N-Out there's a lot of
La divaza
The difference
Between the Republican
At the end of the day
I guess we're going to keep our eye out
For false flags and abiding
Assassination which Alex's promise to
Just going to happen I'm assuming Chicago's get
That's my that's my retirement plan
And Alex is going to be right about one thing we're overdue we're elderly on a number of
New Kings
But maybe Alex knows that that is a work of aliens
Cincinnati should go anywhere near
True know the radiation
Australia
Write all coming together
That really was a breath of fresh air
Live webcam DVD
I've seen you tweet hi now it's terrible it's mornings I get angry
If you're up in the a.m. checkout Jordan on Twitter
You have to go do a mortgage loan
Baby
But for now
Have until then how many oh I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
I have a cardboard box
Very well-situated igloo
Who igloos not bad egg lose the way to go
A wigwam
Still just a name okay
I'm done I'm done I'm coming up with something else name
Huh
Anyway
Next time
Alexandra Thurston color
I love you