College bike I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy or the bad guy
Money
So Alex
Dot-com
Little bit about Alex
My bright spot today Jordan as well we're recording this on Tuesday and that means that as we were
Recording I don't have to be watching Alex his livestream that I am drawn to like a moth to a flame
No but seriously my right spot is cereal again I mentioned
Sing into cereals
Some that have been a little bit off the wall the frosty cereal the Wendy's frosty cereal brands
Yeah
That's pretty good
Really that's amazing I think a free
Frosted Flakes strawberry milkshake flavor cheesus Christ not good out of control
Flavors are out of control until I got one that was a Prix
But it's like I guess sort of Jurassic Park theme there something special marshmallows
Okay it's tricks but with marshmallows that are also dinosaurs
Is putting marshmallows in their cereal anyway there's inappropriate
I'm waiting for like
I don't know
Kicks through marshmallows in or Smacks
King vitamin
Just won't stop putting marshmallows in the granola aisle next week and there's going to be Uncharted are leaving everything
Yeah you're probably right I couldn't resist trying this I'd forgotten the trick sucks
It's not a good cereal even in that fruit to the world better
Also
I was
Thinking about it
I hate tricks
I hate the idea of an abusive cereal the whole marketing campaign is it
But excluding this water rabbit feel like
You are accidentally proving beyond a shadow of a doubt that Trix are for kids
Right because you're you're an adult man and you find them wrong I find it orally
If I do not get to think about yes
To f*** a trick sucks tricks aren't even making that pronouncement
Now honeycomb but with marshmallows the f*** out of here
My bright spot is I got to hang out and see my old friend Leah bourbon last
Last night and we were talking and
Catching up
Oh old old timey style I found out two things
One Kelly Clarkson has a TV show into Lieberman was on it baby
Right on Twitter or something
I mean I already knew Kelly Clarkson had a show I did not know that but yeah I saw that she and some other folks were on it
Fantastic hanging out with
F****** Leno is 8000 years old now I mean a used to be salt
I'm pepper and now his face is white you know like the whole thing
Taken care of
But isn't that really cool yeah it's really cool I was trying to think of a Kelly Clarkson song
A Moment Like That
Kelly Clarkson
Behind These Hazel Eyes live a great song man
Jordan's Pizza is Captain II Capitan
Thought you were the one
Open up deep inside but you don't get to see the tears I cry alright
Hazel eyes
Damn that was Kelly Clarkson so I don't hook up
Willmar Kelly Clarkson when did your 90s hit
Hip-hop turn into 2000 regular pop
I love the a lot of Pop along with my hip hop stop
Fun fact about Kelly Clarkson what that for kids yeah I watched one episode of the first season of American Idol
I turned it on so I Kelly Clarkson like that's the winter baby I was right
That's nice call Liz ice
I think I am not sure I watched one episode of another season I think I might have called that one
One of the later run
Bo Bice remove remember watching it but yeah Kelly Clarkson was clearly the person
Who had like
That thing whatever you know what it is
Yeah that's like
Their star power Star Quality quality
From Justin to Kelly
I think two or three times in the theater
What you were working at the theater
I watch I want you to I also smoke a lot of weed back
Maybe laugh our asses off that
Today will be singing the greatest hits of the 90s and 2000's course
Taking a break from Alex I'm just going to a cappella going to be finishing up some Alex's
Position stop
So we're back in the Connecticut deposition here
3 + 40 some stuff in there but this is enough for an episode of quite frankly
We left off Alex was under oath
And the
Having to wrestle with the fact that he sent a dondi to Newtown and was pretending that
Schenectady
I thought it was terrible
But Avenue
Complimenting the reporting
On-air brawl summary
He did not have a good first day like like you know when you have a first day at a new job you make some mistake
People are training you but that's
Par for the course right so he's had his first day
He's really f***** it up and now coming back for the second day to really buckle down and do his job right yeah
Yeah you know like the first day was off on a bad foot
Second day is coming in as Miss Independent absolutely nailed it
Carl barks the policy chonk
Thank you very much mr. and mrs. Dean and games
Policy walk
Text hey ryguy I'm a freaking policy walk thank you so much
Thank you very much
Journal policy walk
7-year anniversary to my walking partner Natalie
From corn dogs thank you so much
Very much
Gift wise
Is that the was at the plastic University copper or wool
Modern they've a modern version of the updated
This is like a thumb drive anniversary it's close it's a desk set
That's weird that is that is straight but that's coming off of last year's modern gift for
Sixth anniversary objects
The General
That should be one of the traditional ones
Cuz of the 5th anniversary traditionally is wood
Okay
Okay now here's my problem
Who is decided
Well the traditional ones I think have been like long time
Franklin Farmers Almanac
And now yeah they've the modern
One kind of dumb
I think actually desksite is the front like we may have lucked out 7th anniversary might be the best one in terms of
Apna Bazar GIF disappointing I feel like it's it should be weird text stuff as it goes on
Modern times I think obviously your 20th anniversary is like
The dildo anniversary where you're like working at experiment you know it's getting weird anniversary
That's when it's not nice Platinum
Fair enough unless you want to go traditional then it's China
Gun to my head I don't know what
Desks at is
Multiple gas
For your employees if its employees
Will do technocrat and make sure so raw pole supports a technocracy that keeps the human horror out of
These people's eyes technocrat
Start until you're brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Has a Caribbean
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Thank you very much
This takes place the next day I was incorrect the they regroup
I would like ketchup for the deposition Thursday 3 after Alex has gone on vacation
I got that mixed up I thought it was between day one and two but these are actually back-to-back days
And
I have a couple of out-of-context drops because I couldn't pick one
So here's the first one
Okay okay okay
What a fun weird resigned like
Okay like that back at me like all right
Thoroughbred ambulance
Is the other one
Wow you really ought to
You have now
Oh my God It's My Life by the WikiLeaks
Structure of it there the characters and you're like that guy's great
Alright so we start off sort of catching up from something happened today before which of course was the
Bloomberg email Alex had discussed this you did not have it there bringing it today I thought maybe
But it turns out he didn't do anything even to try to find it
JoJo's you were called during your testimony yesterday you
Email that you claim
Mike Bloomberg
Young People Get Ready
Can you call that
Did you do anything last night
No I didn't
And your call Tess
Yesterday
Kissing videos
Love yourself cleaning
That you had
Records
Emails showing
Closed
Articles and Sundry play some type of analytics but I can't remember the exact thing if I'd like to correct something
By the way
You need to correct anything
I'm asking you
Specifically about the
Records and emails
You claimed that you had
Showing
Sandy Hook
Elementary School
Who's clothes party
Shooting
Did you do anything to locate either those emails
Or those record
Position reference
But I get on the bus 706 Austin
It's 6 Central right
Where your team is in Texas
Now that make it home about 6 we had time to make a video yet
Yesterday about your deposition didn't you do that but you didn't have time to go and look at the
Record in email showing at the
Sandy Hook school
Adoption video
In the parking lot at the hotel is right
And
And then you arranged
For that to be
Sliced and broadcasting your website right
Hopefully the color splicing
Okay well this is just like a guy falling down
Like a hill and getting every Rock on the way down
Yeah I guess it is
Your team is right they could have looked it up I do they all went home you time to shoot a video didn't you
I guess I did at that right
Created I appreciated his
Commitment to not letting up
Like not one second is it just going to be
Fight milk
Note you explain every moment of your day yesterday and when you lie to me I'm going to tell you what I saw I was there
If you're Alex you can't Reliant
Question 1 you know right here you can't you can't get on your back foot because then if you do
Do you open up kicking his ass and then he knows I'm not going to
Have a good day
Video together because he had to camera people with him
Your two cameramen
Shooting at
Wtsb us who were they
It was a
RAB do
And it was a race
Why'd you bring Rob do with you
Consultant
And
If you just said something sometime for this Radu was another one of your employees who
Claimed that senior
The hoax correct yes
And you cast rod do
About those emails and record showing
Schools closed
Did you ask him
Even make any effort at all to get those
Record email
I actually did a little bit myself. We were able to find some of the stuff you asked for but not that particular thing
Are you claiming that you yourself personally did something
Locate the emails and records showing that Cindy
Schools closed
Yes what did you do
I
Center at dinner
With the Robin and I
Didn't got to locate that we did some long Michaels around confided in late like last time
Yeah that's that's quite a bit of work he did
I sat there a dinner and I told Rob Leslie happiness we got to get this done buddy
This is got to happen alright it's fascinating to see this kind of like the way he's articulating it's because he's
Put any effort into finding a cuz he knows that this doesn't exist
Isn't a real thing again so why waste your time with that Beast
He still has to pretend like we put it to work drive by it's a real thing
It is it is a bit like
You know that his childhood was different because I remember if I was trying to lie about how I didn't do something
Second grade teacher
They saw me coming to my way
Because I was 7 years old right
And he is still seven years old and somehow he's just going to keep going
You don't like what I was trying to line second-grade eventually I'll be like you know what
Well I think a teacher has a little bit more limited time until one of us all day
Position cuz you're going to end up saying
Something that contradicts yourself or he went from teacher the principal de psychiatrist
So we know that Rob do long for the trip Rob to Uncle also
Was in Newtown for that Wolfgang halbig press conference went to
Alex is asked whether or not he actually spoke to Rob dudes uncle
And it's weird he seems to not know for sure do not know I don't know
I want to
Go back
The video that we
Today
The end of the day
The video that you titled retired FBI agent
It investigates
Sandy Hook Megan
Remember that
Yes
In
That retired FBI agent
Was John dueker I guess you never spoken
I may have talked to Mother phone before
You just wanted you don't know whether to remember
And you don't
Any idea
What is anything he did to investigate Sandy Hook other than showing up at that
Freedom of Information commission hearing
Correct
Yes
And you had no further conversations with Rob do
About
What is Uncle may or may not have done related to Sandy Hook
I have a conversation with you
You have
Went with Osiris
Over the years again last night I was
Are you asking about a we ought to try to get
Talk to him about what
Tallahassee more about what specifically said
Repeat the same thing
They never seen
Government people so tight-lipped
And it's so not willing to talk about anything
This is what robbed you said to you last night
That his uncle I said to him
Spokane news
As of today
A recent
Did Rob do lesbians
He actually said he recently talked to him
About Cindy
No he just said oh yeah I just talked to him today he's doing great
Did he indicate
That
My office had reached out to him
No
So that that Radu to
Didn't share with you
No you just said how is your uncle and said he's fine just talked to me today
So if you're Alex you got to be a little bit confused by that because
They reached out to Rob dudes Uncle communicated by Rob to Ally
This could mean
That the plaintiff's office had spoken
To Uncle do or it could mean Uncle do is avoided Fab
And Alex should probably say I don't know I haven't talked to you in awhile I don't have no information about this
Either either Prospect isn't really great
Optically here be like
Episode about this
People of course I can't remember
The last time I talked to Rob buza Uncle because last night I said
Hey guys
Let's Pretend he doesn't exist and get him out of the country you can't talk to anybody
Why would I tell you that I'm committing witness tampering
Rob his uncle actually only speak Klingon now so I am not going to be able to listen
We're the ones who are really hurt by him only speaking Klingon remember the last time we got together for a family dinner didn't
Said a word about anything so you think you're mad
So the questions obviously at towards the end of day one head to do
A Dandy
You know the Kraken is really Central to a lot of this
A time so this is explored a little bit more here like
Let's get let's get into some of the Dynamics of how batondy was doing what he did
In the next month in July 2015
To be with mr. Hale
Call the Great
I know he wanted for some I don't remember when or how
But I'm saying you know that after that June hearing that we saw yesterday
You then set him up to Connecticut again
To report for Infowars correct or whatever
Enterprise near me
So to clarify just really quick
The hearing month prior that is being referred to is the one where robbed is uncle
Was there and where he was yelling at people in Alex
And they wanted his testimony said I saw that and f*** this right
No more so this is a month after that
We pull up exhibit number
You see this email from Rob due to dhanbad on D
Send July 8th 2015
Yes.
You can tell from this email can you not that Mr do
Was actually telling dammit.
There is more
Would you like to see the rest
After good luck do good
Yep I said thank you
Okay
Sushi there mister do
Telling dhanbad on D2 live stream
Is coverage of the album hearing to The Alex Jones
Channel
And of course
Mystery
YouTube channels
Unless he was reporting for Infowars right
Yes
I told you I remember when and how I was following this Robin's running
And we just saw not putting any responsibility off on a ride I was telling you I don't remember all this right
Right but at least we can agree having seen this email that as of this time mr. Metate
Was still working as a reporter friend for trade you showed me this yesterday I would have said that that that all my God I now cannot deny this
I do feel like
I do feel like a dinner we've clearly discuss the strategy of skipping from the like
I'll just deny something and then watch them play the video to Alex being like I don't remember are you going to play the video
There are a couple points where does that but he does have the same like
X words
Maddie is using
Very specific terms and if you're Alex and you hear those terms
And the way the crescents being phrases like I'm just about to get hit with the video of me saying that,
He doesn't seem to see it coming sometimes
So if you ask him did you say something like
Crazy aliens are coming to kill everybody and he's like never heard of that with an obviously you're going to play the clip of him saying
Crazy alien everybody
You just came to smell those traps sometimes
So Alex tries to play a little wiggle game here with Abaddon D and the timing of firing him
Does not work of course.
Padatti to go up there on your behalf
Earlier I guess it is your news director did here
Right on it was a sometime I saw him yelling at people
And I said that's horrible and I don't like that and tell him stop
Then I don't use them anymore and I just that's what I remember
Recording
He's doing better or whatever that's my bad memory
I'm being honest with you
Remember
I just want to make sure I understand this is
Are you
You seem to be saying
On the one hand you're speculating
On the other hand
You know you have a vague memory of it
Cuz I think you're anticipating me and I appreciate it
I take it that your testimony is
That although at some point
You believe you instructed people who work for you
The damn bar.
Should no longer be used
You don't know when you do
Is that fair
Yes
And you don't know why you did
No I do I told you it's because of what he was doing
Vanessa Rob said last night I said when did I say
Stop using it
They said when he went to those events
All the people
That's what he remembers as well and are you going to talk to him he can tell you about it but that's that's what the best I remember okay
Robinwood Dental he's exactly the same thing that I
I do like all the documents and all the evidence has gone for Alex to just being like
Rob do agreed with me at dinner last night yeah that's
Do you need more proof
You know in my culture dinner is sworn testimony
Create Community you cannot lie a dinner break bread with them and you share salt
You cannot lie to him
File case closed
So Alex seems to be trying to
I don't know if it's intentional or if he just doesn't understand
The video that was streamed on Alex's channel was the second time
Pictures after the video of badani yelling at people
Alex seems to want to make it the first one because it looks better
Left guilty several years difference does not look good and took Maddie is trying to
To explain to him this is the second one you didn't I don't know if he'll just picking up on it
We have text message
I'm going to show you shortly
In 2016
In which your staff is
At that time
Going dammit.
Daddy should no longer rap
A dead himself
In 2016
I don't want on for awhile well
It seems as though
You had the footage from a month before this hearing in July in which Mr bidani was a costing peep
Slater
You have permission to livestream
Similar hearing over your YouTube channel
So it probably wasn't after you saw that footage right
No I never I was saying remember getting upset that he still kept
Popping up there and then I remember
Rob said he's not officially working with us now
You know he's just adjust Paisley phone sorry for him
It's not good I've already said that
You gave damn bhadoti access to livestream material to millions of people over your YouTube channel
Felt sorry for him.
By this time I'm reserved
Like I said I thought Rob you was that event that's how my memory is all messed up on this
Testify under oath if your memories all messed up
So
Alex is trying to sort of change the subject I didn't like I need to correct something about that I said about Rob being there
Is a good tactic
I think if you're if you're sitting there and you know I think I think that every lawyer kind of
Has different
Things sure have I said something and Maddie responded with well I'd be f*****
Alright alright but the handcuffs off
You like the explanation of their business. It's exactly like Banks you know you know how when you fire a bank teller they have to run
The bank for a day before they can leave
Later year later they just show back up
Before you do it by that's what they do.
So we get to talk in a little bit about Alex's payment and how much money he made
In certain years until the year 2015 comes up and here's Alex's monetary situation
Fell in 2015 you yourself had a another Goodyear you drew
8.3 million in compensation from
Your company right
To see the document exhibit 25
15U see your draw
In 2015 with 8.3 million dollars
Yes Bank
And you took a salary
On top of that of 97
Thousand dollars right
Yes all right
And then in addition to that you received a distribution
As a result of your interest in tlj are correct
I don't know
We talked a little bit about PLJ are you
And I think
Your testimony yesterday was you weren't quite sure what it was
But let me ask you a few more questions
About that
So there'll be some questions about this but you're sort of the brief version of it is
Free Speech systems is a company that Infowars is actually the name of the actual come
Company presumably
And so they sell supplements that are so old
From pqp are which is owned by like Alex and his parents
Then plgr is another company on top of that vittone's pqp are right
Alex and his mom okay and then there's a EJ trust which has like a large interest
Holding 8dl Jr
It sure basically all of it is just this nesting doll thing
Alex and his family
Sort of the brief version of it is it is like
The dumbest way of doing a Cayman Islands tax.
It cuz it feels like you're doing this to hide who owns it
But it took like five minutes to be like what will you own this send you on this and the owners of this
Yeah it's your initials
You might as well have called it picnic texting LLC
Oh you know we we found at that
We we got all chests use money because it was his initials on the goddamn account
I just imagine him going till the kids account no being like mesar
That's not how this works
Put my money where the Nazi gold is
Alex has an accountant
Name Lydia Hernandez and she is somebody who is kind of an all-purpose player
Infowars
Quite a stretch of their business time
An email from her comes up as it relates to plgr
It's so weird how Alex
Seems very reluctant to praise her
You see
This email
From
Lydia Hernandez to your father
Dr. Jones
Yeah yes
She says dr. Jones I printed out some of the
Reports
And place them on your desk in an envelope marked personal and confidential
And you see that attached to this email
Isn't it spreadsheet
That'll 2015-2 current distribution work
Yes
The Lydia
Hernandez is your former
Repeat systems account
Correct
Shell said a number of other job she did
Some HR work rate
She was kind of an all-round troubleshooter correct
Yes for the best you ever had
Amazing
Right remember that okay
What you degree
Should I play
What
Is there some reason you don't want it
Acknowledge that
At some point at least you thought that you was amazing employee
Genuinely don't know why I don't know I don't like really,
Potato good as an account in case I need to throw under a bus later yeah I don't know exactly where the
These questions are going and I might have tried think about it if you're asking me to confirm that I
I think she's amazing that suggests to me that there's some sort of crime that I need to blame on her
Seems like since she's come up
This is an this is going to be a great opportunity to buspirone
The day is long
Play nice lady criminals can be nice
Everybody knows that.
So Alex doesn't know anything about any of these numbers and
He does
And we're going to go to the tab of this
Spreadsheet that says
Distribution
And
You see here
Mr. Jones
On the column A it was two thousand and
15 and then column see it shows
Dates of distributions
8 out of p q p r
And
Those distributions
Went to
Other entities jlj rapelje are correct
I think so
Are you familiar with
This
Distribution scheme you have here where
Pqp are
Is making distributions of it
Proceeds
Do corporate entities
One of which you control
CPA David so
Okay
That seems just impossible to believe
You do like most
Business owners he's not really interested in whether or not there's money here
Are there somebody else's problem text me everyday asking for sales.
Flower really all that impossible
Has no idea what these companies even are better like if he god-like
If that were true which it's not if it were true he would be the perfect mark
Just take him for everything
It would be so easy if you had no idea what all of this structure
Existed for holyshit frankly if this were true
Then Lydia Hernandez should have
Taken several hundred million dollars
Would not have been difficult in La Trust
Yeah I think that if
Alex didn't actually understand any of this or didn't know any of this
This lawsuit was going on and his lawyers we're meeting with him
It would be an emergency
Total it would be like a understand
That's it this is setup
And it wouldn't all be set up entirely to that big Zacks perfect
Structure for him
Try to be sneaky
But if you look at this spreadsheet
You'll see that
According to this
The distributions from
Pqp RNs
The company that
You claim
So
The supplements on your website
Bad
Dale Jr
Is
Has two members David and Carol Wright those your parents
Npl Jr has two members
Alex and Carol that you and your mom
Right
And you have a 90%
The timing matters
In 2016 because that's
Reflected on this
2015 20
And
According to this
Spreadsheet
As a result of your
Percent interest in plgr
You received
In 2015
80% of the total
Apqp are distributions of 3
24 million right
Jackson
Alright
And so that's 3.4 million
Distribution on top of the 8.3 million that you drew down
Right
The accountant
Some of it pays the other thing in backing
Advertising
This has nothing to do this spreadsheet you don't see anything on here about advertise
Right
I don't understand all these numbers
Okay
I don't know numbers
Baffled I made like 12 million dollars but I don't know anything about anyting it was an accident honestly I just
Around and accidentally over $10
Falling into several hundred pounds of money
I mean it's silly
It's silly
We've all been there trip there's a bag filled with money
When your mind
When you think of the Common Man
Do you think of
What comes to mind for you
Hey tomorrow I just think it's on average everybody makes about 10 million a year I think that's I think Alex
Common man I do represent the Everyman
Stinger video yesterday
If he post about this
Position that you told
And in which you later published on your website that you
Told your audience that your Common Man
Right
Yep
You said that
Connecticut is really a bedroom community for all the riches
Is people in New York right
No billionaires
The country for trillions yeah
But you're the kind of man
Right
Damn, where did you fly into
Exactly
It wasn't
Kennedy year LaGuardia or Bradley
Commercial
North Little Rock blank privately
Because I also saw in your
Video that you put out yesterday that you were kind of saying you never seen so many private planes in your life when you landed right
And
Recent rainbow flying
Small private planes
Because
You earned over 11 million dollars in 2015 right
We had to do that that was for that
Call Michelle Jones
You just finished testifying that you have no idea what these numbers mean
Go to do with a wife of Jackson
Oh that's rough every time he's like
Know if I offer up this information
It will make more sense yeah this is exculpatory I figured out
That is kind of
One of the things that's really interesting if you watch these deposition that really do get a sense that one of Alex
Innate traits
The he cannot stop himself from
He's trying to make explanations to wiggle around and find the
The way that this works out in his best interest
So a previously that money was I don't know anything about this right then he comes up with like
Had to buy my wife out of the business that's why there's so much money totally hit so he offers that up not realizing this country
Predicts the idiots I previously and it doesn't really help
It raises more questions than it answers like a grotesque
Example of that towards the end of this episode put like
It's just
It's just his psychology
It is it is like those those shows are or you know like the cop shows
Where there's the criminal mastermind who's also a psychopath who can
Just getting on the witness stand and I'll just charm and be so you know those things
Like
It is kind of funny because they never choose a really incompetent psychopath who lost a billion dollars
Who knows I like just saw Alex like in the Connecticut
He probably thought that's who he was like I can get my way out of it hahaha
Can call this a struggle session and then everything will be fine it's amazing it is amazing
Insanity required
Soyumi course of the trial itself we learned that the Bitcoin donations that
Alex got the millions you know it wasn't
Play save Infowars type of advertising and of course Alex says that
All that money went to the legal defense for Uno's
I'm but asking some of these questions about other donations and such that go to be legal
Wishy-washy
You separately raise money
From your audience
For your own
Would you play me
Defensive
Infowars right okay
And
People can
Give to that
Users
Pacific ring for that the Infowars legal defense
Doctors website
There's a specific website
And when people give to that website
Where does it go
It is a cute aesthetic put in account and accounted for in
It's a free speech systems
It's accounted for adding account
Play Lydia
Thriller I just bought
When tonight's that's putting The Ledger is that then
Last time I checked I think it's been spent
When was last time check
I checked it to the last week
Okay and your sworn testimony here is that
Every penny
That was deposited into
The account you just described for me
Went to
Your lawyers
I would definitely counting myself but that's that that's my general but believe that's what the moneys for and there's also a
Lincoln on your website just for people
Donate right
And that money just goes right into the 33 system Channel
The war fun are you at war with somebody
What their crime crime syndicate
It's
It sounds better on his show it really does he really does there aren't there are too many sarcastic
Fun is silly outside of the context of his performances
Do you understand that we're human beings in the world
And not fictional we're fighting a war situation
You and me real people just trying to get answers yet girl reactions
Question comes up Alex's at war with his global
Who are the
Well are the parents of these children
What's nasty
Or my clients
Globalist
Sandy Hook parents
The ones you have are your using them
Nhb earlier times as well Global's conglomerate to try to silence
Populist voices
Anderson
They're just being used as pawns by you
So
Did the Sandy Hook families
That
Have decided to sue you are just Pawns
In a much larger
Battle that were saying about I'm not going to speak for them in my view they're being used by you
Senator Blumenthal and others
Response
Okay by me there lawyer
Ambulance Chaser Democrat anti-free speech anti-gun Tyron
So I need to be
ShopRite people understand
Dad
That that that that America is going to stand firm Against The Bullying the censorship
Do you want somebody biting in all of it and we're never going to stop resisting
So I
But I'm I'm you just refer to me
The family's lawyer as a toy
Preferred to me yesterday
As if it's filing fraudulent documents on purpose about financial
Ridiculous
A couple times
Shut the fuk up no reason to be talking right now
I swear like listening to some of this
Like if it's available to the jury
Yeah
I don't think there's a billion he's lucky I know it is kind of like
It's kind of like I understand why we had to have a trial with a jury there and we did the whole thing it was very satisfying
But there is a part of me that's like you could have just played the deposition for the jurors and they've been like 1 billion let's get Avenue
May have had access to it in the chambers a room but it's
4 days of depositions you know they're not good weed they didn't watch obviously they didn't watch for days of deposition
Play the transcript true true I don't know
Really it it's bad
They're pawns your Tyrone
Justin
Yeah I will say if they skimmed it they would have gotten more than enough
Yeah yeah for sure I don't think anybody needs to 12% masochist in our audience who have now
I'll decide if they want to watch
Depositions but other than me I don't I don't know if anybody needs to subject themselves to play a game
With these depositions where we just fast-forward and then click play on a certain
Spa and just see what the next 10 seconds are
Some of it some of it might that might be fruitful there I mean look there long stretches where
A lot of the same stuff that we've we've heard and talk about a bunch of times before
There's a long stretch in this episode or is that deposition about
Are all the various
Anomalies in quotes and we've talked about that a hundred times it's just basically him Maddie pointing out to Alex
MaxPreps was wrong wrong
It is you could if you just randomly dropped in it could be that
Could be gold could never know
It is it is him
You know I do think that hitting his mind calling them ambulance Chasers
Is a good is a good thing because it
It draws the image of a about the lawyer who's got somebody
Engage in the arm in a sling that's actually fine
And I get that
But that's kind of the problem
A lot of the times that ambulance Chaser does have to be using somebody who doesn't really have
Have that much of a problem we've never been like
That ambulance Chaser representing
The families of victims of the children of one of the worst massacres in the history of the United States price
Yeah that's a little bit different if you truly ambulance Chaser there it makes you look like a
It's embedded in there anyway that Alex I don't take recognizes it's just
Like Shifting the accusation onto the lawyer is really just the way that Alex is trying to take
He's trying to deny it without denying to take agency away from the parents while attack
Like all of this sucks all this is fake retro the poor parents they weren't being busy
These lawyers
Which makes no sense
No yeah no
And it's a shity
Yep
So
The discussion of the child exploitation material that was in the email I sent
To the plaintiffs attorneys by Alex's lawyers comes up
And here's a little conversation about it that ends with
Probably unfortunate
Moment for Alex
I'm a timer
I'm
Because I represent
Senior families in this plot against
Right
Can your overall Democrat Party plot against America
Right well where you are
Why do you
You talked about me and
Pastime show
You put a a million-dollar
Bounty on
Me for having my head on a pike right now
Shut the Charlotte Hornets very clear photo did you pound
Can you order offering that bounty
Your photos are like a cut to Hawaii shot of that
The camera got on
My photo and then pounded my picture
Right
You know you do we need to show the video
Talk about the fact that I was suspicious
Anti Alex Jones
Sandy Hook email sent with embedded c********* we never opened
And them headlines the news are Alex Jones child horns
Somebody sent me an email that you got it you went to scanned it
Using your system for whatever
Steven I was there
And then ran headlines seem to know
Deceptive and Notch Road
Clarify
Here for you
The
Child pronography that you're
Your lawyers
Transmitted
My office
Was
Found by
Third-party
Yeah I don't know I'll get to
Mr. Jones
Who is the first person
To ever
Publicizing anyway
That
Your lawyers
Headset
Material
Continue trial
Pornography
Who is the first person
And everything
Mr. Jones
You don't remember who the first person was
To State publicly
That
This whole issue with child pronography and your company providing it to your lawyers and then sending it to us
With you
Objection
Company-provided unopened email it wasn't opening
Cowboy
Poor Alex boy doesn't realize that he did this to himself by trying to get out ahead of a stripper
Alex drunk hanging out with Norm this happened cuz I got to get out of this
Boy got on air started screaming about it
There's no during headlines that we're being put out by nefarious globalist
Self know which was what college was saying the headlines of you put out
Did this man that's one of those things that I really I really just hate
Number of billion reasons
I hate that happened
Not least of which just because it muddied so much it's just like
It doesn't
Do anyone any good
You know it's just awful all doll around anytime you know
It's bad yeah it in terms of this
Are you dude
Think that is Alex hadn't done what he did
Then this would have been handled quite differently
Like no one would have gotten sanctioned over this either wouldn't have been any kind of
Like charges brought against the lawyers or Alex it would be very easily understood
This was something that was sent to them it wasn't opened
Alex made a much bigger deal out of this by trying to make a narrative out of that everything something
To accuse these lawyers of setting him up right every every article every headline that he had
Embedded his
I'm saying these things true it's not like they
It's crazy
So Alex Rambles quite a bit
Finally gets to just stating directly that
He believes that the families are Pawns
In a plot against a smart
Getting back to my point Bell
My questions
What you see
He has
A really kind of life-and-death struggle
Between
You
Your audience
That supports you
And
This
Movement 2
School Bus movement
Right
You consider
The plaintiff
The unwitting Pawns in that attack against you
There's no doubt the corporate media the system is using the lawsuit to try to get rid of the First Amendment for the general public they admit that
I think what you're testifying
That you consider Mike
Alliance
The unwitting Pawns
In
The plot against
What I see it is
Is that
Misrepresentation when I've apologized
Claims that I'm going after people when I wasn't
I just seen
Really a lot of
Sad people that watch for children
Using
Me to keep story of her children in the news and gun-control Munoz
Accusations by you guys
MLS Playoffs Antioch when I know I did
Social media was exploding then
Began
Was around 2012 or three getting any everybody grew with it
And Barack Obama grew all the conservative media just fine
Liberal media I know that it's well-known
You're staying here and there Sandy Hook
Do you consider
Mike line
Now
Unwitting
Overarching
Accuracy
You and the freeway
Absolutely okay thank you
Tracy thousands of articles I mean I mean thank you for your wow wow
Wrong answer
Boy
Ono if you just couldn't couldn't not
Notes could not know
But like the well
In a in a situation like this if you give an answer and then the lawyer says thank you for your answer
You just
Really screwed yourself you're f*****
If you should be really worried
So the question comes up about whether or not Alex contacted any of the
And whether he ever was in touch with anybody
Either you ever had some sort of background report on anybody that nobody seems to know
But this is this is just a nice set-up
And Spike
If you ever
Pokemon theme
Not that I remember
Have you ever spoken
With
Any
And remember
No we've invited them on the show
You've never personally
I know
Nobody on your behalf
As far as you know
Have you ever sent letters to
To any
Remembers
Anybody
Sandy Hook
I will follow back
Lettering
Leaving to email Disney movie back
On the show you that when you say we you're talking about sugar
Watching
Alicia
But other than this repository Universe in
Letter Danny
Family members
No
And she killed in Iraq
Doesn't seem like you want to compare yourself to
Madeleine Albright
My hero
Mr. Jones
This is a
Video that was
Produce To Us by
Free Speech systems
In 2018
89 Edgecliff
Anti-slapp Provisions for attorneys fees and damages
Mike Shinoda my lawyers last week
They shoot potato manipulated
Verizon.com
Boston
Or your audience that you have been
Seven letters and getting on the phone with
No I don't know the context of this
What
Talking Dead
But I can't remember the times but I told myself that it wasn't true
Well you just testified completely off
So which is true I barely remember deposit
I don't know
I don't remember this man that is maybe the best example of how
Holding two contradictory ideas inside your head at the same time and Alex is a master of doing that
I will give him that
It's when nothing is real it is quite then you know
Certain there's a certain place that I get I guess
I mean look
It's fun to talk s*** on your show and being like we've talked to these people and they're all dropping
The suit it's great it just
You shouldn't
Things are recorded
F****** them running not be there later
Man
We should really destroy every episode of something immediately after do I get no evidence of anything ever
So embarrassing
The discussion
Pretty long discussion about Alex's video of his final statement on Sandy Hook
Conversations around
The various anomalies
That are incorrect
So I'm going to play a ton of that here is one click of the discussion about the Bloomberg email
And the reason I kept this in his just because
It's so funny to hear Alex talk about his own ideas this way
And I'll ask you to pause it
Intermittently
You're just us a number one
On the day before the shooting an email sent out by Bloomberg's anti-gun group
You pull up on the screen as you're staying that and Infowars article
Correct
Yes okay
And that enforced headlines exposed how Bloomberg
And it's dated March 13th 2013
Correct
Yes my are dykes right
Yes he was a writer of yours
Okay
Can you pull up this article
As evidence of the fact that mr. Bloomberg's organization had in fact send out an email
The day before the shooting as you just said correct but that's why you put it there
I guess I mean nobody spontaneously decided to do that
Know a lot of times they just put stuff up on the show but I don't know
Are you claiming that
This was not published in the middle of your statement as evidence
For your claim
But the biggest
So
You said that
America Center email the day before the shooting saying prepare for a big of a
Right
Right and we talked about that yesterday is being evidence.
For your claim at Sandy Hook was a hoax because Mr Bloomberg
Would have foreknowledge of the event,
Right
The used
But
You said he jumped the gun
Meaning that
You release that email early
Intending to send it after the fact
Knowing it
If there was going to be home
Looks correct
That's what I people Earth
You can imply that you'd agree with me that
That's what you meant
And you said blue me
You jumped the gun
You sent this email out early knowing that
There was going to be a hoax right
The yes mr. Jones
I'm yes thank you
A possible interpretation of my thoughts at was a rollercoaster ride of one clip
That was insane likes to scribble
My mind went from being a desk situation very much like you and I right now to being Alex
As one of those children who just had a traumatic event sitting there with the cops with a crayon scribbling down as the
Cops ask question
About what happened that's what's going on here
Yeah my mind even goes to like a kid at a desk
Like one of those desks that has like the pocket under that put all your supplies
Is a little bit too small for Alex but he's sitting there not paying attention in class drawings @s
I could do that
This is another thing that comes up pretty repeatedly in terms of Alex's of Asians and that is
Someone put that email or that story up on like an editing or something most
Yeah and no that's not the right thing supposed to be there is evidence of the claims that I'm making but something
Buddy else put this together and it's not the right thing you know what I'm not mad at
Write the story of this deficit that ends up being an excuse for at least a couple things
Could imply that is
Add amazing
Misdirect from a thing you were imply
I was applying it but you could imply that I was implying you couldn't play with this is a claim that I made you could
What a dork anyway Alex just like he's he's in deflection mode he's just
Hey what about the behavior they make mistakes buddy
Fine
You don't
I've heard you say several times
This morning
And yesterday that he got things wrong made mistakes
Right
And I appreciate you saying that like the New York Times
I'm sure they're liberal they're good
Give you an opportunity here
And
You're not going to get any debate for me that
Media makes mistakes all the time
Lassonde have
Grievous cough
But
Acknowledge
That
What you claim Army
Mistakes that you made
Regarding
The worst school shooting
Where you claimed
That it was a
Oaks
In order to
As part of a
What
To disarm the public
Real concert
The people who you claimed were part of the
Adam Lanza killer children
No you didn't
That's a shitt response yeah
You recognize that the mistakes and things that you were engaged in surrounding this have
People
Tell the guy to kill anybody
He's dad
Yeah it is it is very much
It is very much you can you can just
Like
Something something I read Trump said the other day was
If
The candidates that I support win
That all of the
Glory should go to me
They lose
No one should blame me for anything and it is so like that's just encapsulated in what Alex does
No it does make sense
What is responsibility if it's not just claiming credit for things as credit
Alex
Ask about this idea that the audience comes to him for truth
This is weird
He is a weird response there's a little bit of grandstanding okay
I just want to see
If you understand
When you tell
Your audience
Comes to you
Or the truth
Because that's what you tell them you're giving up
Run like the Supreme Court nominee I can stay with a woman as yes
You're Expecting
Oh my God
I don't want to play games with you
I'm talking about my client I don't give a
Relax people you guys
You trying to do right now
Distracting the question mask
So I just want you to answer my
Okay
I didn't think it was going to be hard for you acknowledge
That you your audience comes through for the
Would you just agree with me on that
Can you make mistakes
Are you and I can disagree all day long about whether you make me
You lied on her
Alright
What the
You agree with me that a minimum
You were right
Industv
Since you made it outside
No I believe I believe they were real anomalies and I was and I was wrong I said that years ago
Injection
A video yet
Yesterday you said you were Reckless
Do we have to clip
You responded to exactly what I think is like the most important under like it just ate today
There is
I wasn't paying attention amazing
Is
Dark astonishing it's it's such a blip
11 terms of buildings that are said in this deposition
But to me it's so important because it is just like Alex thinks he can
Absolve himself of this wrongdoing and the pain that he causes people because they
I was even paying attention
Like no dude that stopped betters Greenwald interview and he said like he was drunk
I was just drunk when I was this better when I hit your son with the car I was
Drunk and I wasn't paying attention so leave me alone
Well that's actually a really good sort of
I wait to look at it it's like
I ran over your kid
But I was drunk when I did it
So I'm not a bad person I didn't mean to hit your kids
You did decide to drink and drive which is something that maybe make
Makes you less of a good person
The decision point was earlier I wasn't paying attention when I made all this b******* up
Threw it around about these grieving parents
No no no
The act of saying the thing you're trying to absolve yourself is irrelevant the decision to behave in
That way and operate your news Outlet writing like you're a drunk driver either the problem and that does make you a bad person
When you
Made the decision to drive drunk
You said something and that was I don't particularly know that this is a possibility maybe
Maybe even a high possibility and I don't
Care and if your kid dies
I know that could happen but it's less valuable to me it said just getting home without taking a tour Expedia
Weird for me to drive drunk and for Alex it's more expedient to make sure it up because it's
Sensational
And his audience enjoys it did you not hear that I made 11 million dollars of course I wasn't paying attention when I was
Lying about that lot of money
So
This makes it really got me
Thinking
I don't believe a good bit of this
But there's a interesting level of false introspection that's going on
So how old were you in Sandy Hook
P38
Broadcast
Screenshot the number
Jackson
She'll eventually if I don't want to believe
I have free speech.
What what is a gun owner I'm being blamed for something people then
Basically have a baby form of resistance to that just didn't believe no it didn't happen because it's a terrible thing
People then start
I'm so the mind then
Start finding ways to
Absolutely then vilify the media on the group's they're saying and doing that
Well
Myself and I
Therapy of Earth actually end
Call therapist.
I think
Be commended for that
But I also want to say
I also want to ask you whether in that
Reflection
You come to realize
That the statement you made
Wrong
You play more mistakes
Jackson
Just like the judge lying and saying we get any false documents and you lie in court is hurting
Liberal in Lubbock
Dr.
And what you say
You don't speak
That
The family
Quaver actor
Suffered
As a result
I don't think
Do you level a pain I went through losing their children being a father myself for children
Having four natural daughter I don't think going to that level of pain are the worst thing happen
Even comes in any
Harrison
Things I did
In my
Mistakes in my own delusion
I think it's really admirable of Maddie to not take the bait
That Alex was throwing out there with all the liberal and loving both much you know because what he's doing is trying to do
Derail the the point of attention which is threatening to him which is you did
Cause this pain and hurt to these people and he says like oh yeah
Just like this
And if you just ignore that you like yeah fine
But you dare just like that then
You're agreeing with
Like muddy The Waters by bringing in outside grievances that you have
But focusing it it just straight on what we're talking about your answer is yes absolutely
Jerk know what you tried to do was agree with me and then throw keys off into the corn
Springfield to be like
Don't you want to know obviously some of the keys that he throws are repulsive
I know they they are things that
You know you'd walked
The corrector be like hey hold on now
I'll bet in a setting like this it's ghetto key just to stay on point and that that'll be difficult to do with it distraction
An artist like Alex absolutely end it is such an endurance test you know like
Only as as I'm listening to this you know this one in the last one it's like
I could not do this
If the Judgment was in doubt
You know what I'm saying like now that it's over and I know that he loses and all the stuff then I could listen to
Him in this deposition tell me these things cuz I've got a big smile in the back of my mind
But in this situation
Where you don't know yet you know you're going to you've already won and all that stuff but you don't know if it's going to go the way you
Really wanted to yet like the idea that he can just say that s*** to you and then not get
Consequences
Terrifying endurance of not like
Because of what Alex does he gives you as much emotion as he can to override your ability to think
Or try Melissa that emotion in you to do get you off the rack
But also I think this clip offers a really good insight into Alex's mind and how these conspiracies work because
If you look at it's basically exactly what we say pretty regularly as what he's articulating
He's season of that that's threatening to his ideology and he knows that he has no actual argument about it and that the people on
The other side of the issue have points
He cannot in any way we're but
Instead of recognizing that and working on strengthening his arguments or attempt to find a compromise solution
Alex takes a shortcut of saying that this threatening event didn't happen
When there's a mass shooting all gun owners aren't blame for it but Alex feels like they are because to him discussion of gun
Regulation isn't a matter of making better public policy it's something that's being done to punish people who have guns
This is obviously an accurate but it serves as a launching pad for Alex to make the leap to where he wants to go which is to say that the
Shooting itself is fake
So there's no reason to punish gun owners which is would not happening to begin with
If I was at the counter the actual argument people who proposed gun regulation or making he would fall flat
He showed all he has what he went on Piers Morgan show like it's just a bunch of yelling and aggressive statements but there's no
Actual substance there
This is all just intellectual cowardice
Alex can't stand up to the actual ideas in the arena like he likes to think he can
So he takes the shortcut of taking world events personally and then insisting they didn't happen
The event didn't happen because the globalist were really just trying to punish me to begin with so they think this event in order to give them
Justification to do it
You can easily see how this allows Alex to sidestep any actual policy discussions cuz he's not equipped to have them
Also no therapist would allow this kind of justification to stand without further exploration
Clear projection and rationalization that you have to have a normal level therapist in order to accept
And move passage that's outrageous
I know that Alex has gone to some therapist just because of court-ordered stuff with his
Divorce and custody stuff but putting a poor therapist through this
This is this is the one time where there's just not enough money
What reboot of The Sopranos
You have to have a gun to the therapist had to pull that we reboot doctor cat okay all looks awesome. LOL
Call Alex
Rodger Stone personalities
And we could get Louis c.k. back
Cuz he's also
I feel like I feel like we could be onto something
Don't tell anyone
So Maddie points out here it's very important and that is that like if you believe that the
These people are actors and do know they've just pulled off this fake thing in order to take everyone's guns
You should expose them
That would be the right thing to do right
If you have somebody
Who's faith
Death is part of a political issue
Disarm the American
Those people
Some of the some of the parents
Advocacy
Spell became political operative
The political Arena
I move to strike the colloquy Council
Home
Change calculated to Mario
Directions to one we wait until the end of the break and you can make your objection
So Alex is basically saying exactly what
Maddie would hope he'd say because they have entered the political Arena
Just kind of making the argument that they're fair game
And so
This turns into B chaos and correctly what are you saying
Is if you survive or experienced a massive tragedy and tell people about it
Then it is fine to abused you yes unless you tell people about it in a way they
That Alex like a monster
Nah
So yeah chaos man
Directions to why we wait until the end of the break and you can make your objection
I said 1330 objection you know that you are a
Antagonizing
It's terrible on
They had it coming
Now that's a terrible
How dare you say the parents Atacama
You just said that didn't you harass them right now
I think you know what I meant this
You just said
Have you no decency Republican Lena and so they got what they got right
Is Ronnie Parker
He did and I think you should keep mayonnaise anti-gun agenda
Millet
Use for an anti-gun agenda
Never said a word about guns
Objection
Noah
No I'm sorry for any any pain that I might others caused me to Parker
Are we done here
The website are you jacking his answer no more.
Yes this is chaos
I don't like your tone
Yeah I get I get where you felt and I think a lot of the objections that are flying around not necessarily in this club
Throughout some of this early like
Things that are being said as state
That's right you know or at least appear to be saying being cited statements correctly
I mean obviously I don't understand correctly but if I bought I think if I understand is that these depositions
The transcripts
That go to the jury
If the objection is sustained then that section is cut out right
So so it is possible that the transcripts from the jury none of this section was in what they got
I would assume that most of it
Is I mean of course I think
I don't think a lot of these objections are
I think a lot of them are just sort of like what I'm saying is that a lot of people have asked likewise
Is he still answering questions after objection if there's no kind of thing and it's because that's an after-the-fact right
You know everybody would determine the alexwood and there are a couple of instances where this happens
Here one or two of them where Norbit like I'm advising you not to answer it and that's when Alex doesn't answer
Objections that are like
Roll the dice do appreciate the attempt to to bring like the lawyer
Here's town is a problem I appreciate that the lawyers on Alex's side
I totally would probably do the same thing
Question of Rob Jacobson comes up a longtime employee who
Testified in this case key that had a deposition about his time
Working there and Adan Salazar has said
Also Underoath
That Rob said hey
Should be covering Sandy Hook when all this stuff right
And so
Alex said some pretty
Shity things to say about Rob Jacobson
Eli
To say that I made
More than 1% of the money even in the times I hold shows I covered Sandy Hook
If I got a lot of heat from friends and family and folks to the office
Ariana end and when Watson threatened to quit
Image stop covering it
At times we did
When did he die
Remember a conversation with
Rob Jacobson work
He told you that
You shouldn't be covered
In the case of Rob
He is
I know he's claimed that and it's the office that he was the guy that believe Sandy Hook was he
Use lying about
Warning you
Against
Covington
Man
Just I just absolutely line because you know that you're
Your employer down Salazar
Acknowledge that heater covers
I know later.
Throughout most of it
He was the one bringing up saying you thought it was staged
And I do remember it on saying later
He bought that he also talked to David Knight
Was a alien reptile
And I had really serious breakdown and I'm really sad for Rob and the tax is being exploited by you guys just
Disgusting
It's not familiar
Do you know that you know what happened to that position
Very sad
I really I just
I don't want to
Come back for a third day
About 11
So are they end up getting steaks but I cannot watch the Rob Jacobson deposition yet
I don't have that one but hopefully
Will be able to cover that in the future but his lawyers got sanctioned
Because of their behavior in that deposition
He was ruled to be abusive
And they were really really shity yes yes
Usevs yes and got sacked
Because of their behavior
I with Rob and I think Alex is referring to that but as a whole
Objective eyes look at that the deposition is a real bad thing for Alex is gay
Yeah
That sounds right but Alex is a viewing it as as a while we showed it we showed you that it's something
That's amazing to to look at it you're not in a glass-half-full way like that
So Alex is the real victim
When you really think about it and I don't know if that's true what do you think about the whole Sandy Hook thing
Alex is the victim
Dad and and and then was my being wrong about things Purple People absolutely
It was not done consciously and I apologize for that
I have learned that by becoming very very famous
When you do have power
And
The same time I have suffered by being deplatformed
Demonize threatened attacked
What I said about Sandy Hook and I have been punished a lot
And that's why I'm not even
This whole Fiasco with trial and Anna and all the media stuff
Is is is is your to me not to because already for the families
You sure like to be from for me
It'll make a nice HBO documentary for everybody so
Do you own
You feel better
Ura
A victim
That you've been unfairly
Victimized
As a result
You've made
Let's just say this I wish that I
Knew what I know now
I was younger respected for me
Honest
Say like don't tell them you were delusional
I really believe all that stuff
Other I was saying I would and I was wrong about that
Because so much others have been proven and documented
And any other you start thinking everything's a lie and I've explained that
And and
Alex won't own his position if he views himself as like the woe-is-me
Person in this whole circumstance I've been kicked off social media been marginalized and all these people
To me that made me say these things and
How the media tricked me with being wrong all the time and so I thought everything was fake and look at me eat
Won't you think of the poor Alex Jones is really just a s******* he was wrong on a lot of
Accountant
But most especially it was
Cathartic
Turns out I think so yeah it was quite cathartic
In a lot of ways how he would think it wouldn't be he's like well I lost so nobody should be happy right
In his he's required to have a position that they're not really that upset about that it's true
So he would think that whatever catharsis
With a Advil would be fake yeah it's not real
Wouldn't be that big a deal I do like how you accidentally or you're delusional
Something which is like
Clearly this was a conversation what you had with your lawyers about how to lie to what if I said I was crazy
Do you think that would work I believe temporary insanity gears so that's going to be tough
So Megyn Kelly came to interview Alex sure and he presumably
And he definitely claimed this on are a number of times that he had like
The whole thing recorded he was secretly
Got all of it remember when we covered that he made that very clear turns out that never was true
And there's a funny reason
I want to show you a
Video
Published
June 2017
You recalled it
This was around the time
You didn't interview with Megan
Kelly
Yes
And you had a lot
Complaints about
How she
Presented
That interview
Yes correct
Yes
It was unfair
Yes remember
Water jump cuts
I told her I thought Sandy Hook a banshee
So
Then it's me look he's he's denying it again
And and
I hope you can get that rocktape from her
Because
I can talk about Sandy Hook when I come all the stuff
They're all day long and then to the Manor View at night
How about Sandy Hook
Dee Dum
DIA
Have You Ever Seen The Lost Village from that interview know and I told one of my crew of course the
Course they did to somebody called her phone minutes into it
And stop recording is Ice-T
What happened to that a
They don't wander
It was
With my sister
Mileage
The minions episode
Despicable Me
He's like the minions
Oh boy
I just
I just you know everytime you think that there's going to be just a very simple explanation for something
Affordable occurs it Alex lives a permanent Force
Door he goes out a different room you know
Who was screwed up a recording they're no longer
Trying to throw someone out of the bus until he remembered it was his
Sister yeah probably
Supervillain minions wafer Villas
They are evil
Anyway
Remember this game up a little bit on the day one
The notion that
Koskoff firm
Are the mafia
Write this comes back up
Is really wanting Alex to shut up
And this is called
Sandy Hook vampires
Remember that
Yes can you title that video
Buy vampire
You're referring to
People who you claim
Get
Energy
And Goodwill as a result of being associated with
Tragedy Coronavirus
And I suspect you put my law firm in that category
Yes
So what's go head and now this is obviously before any
Lawsuit was filed so you could have been referring
Then right
Are you now
He'll disputed the families have a right to
To hire a lawyer if they choose
Correct
Are your thoroughbred ambulance Chaser.. Volume a
From Sandy Hook
Just because I'm a lawyer
You know
Mafia around here
Are okay
So in addition to being an ambulance Chasers where the mafia
I was once told that by member
Confidentiality cribriform I tried to discuss this with you use their ad like an opportunity to do so off the record for a moment you have account
Eventually green with my firm at 2
I'd like to discuss it with
I am the way it was with Josh there was a
Context in which we met and agreed not to discuss thing
This is coming from
Opportunity
For 1 minute
Hernandez
Important setting at your word never when you can talk about
For any questions about what took place at their reviews
Alright so Norm called you guys the bafia that is an issue that maybe
Yeah they could be
Or conversely
Yeah the converse side of this is not to not realistic I don't think
Then Alex would know if he signed something there was a confidentiality
I am the beat like it so he saying that Josh koskoff
Sign this confidentiality thing
Think that they would know about this
Have you heard a very firm it team on this case and this is all bulshit but
Jumping up to back up later like course
Norm being like we want to strike all of this of the mafia stuff
You know I think I think Chris is doing a fantastic job
Hair but that one moment I really feel like I want Bill to tag in and just sit there and chew on it
Gummy worm as Norm keeps being like Josh
Let's go ahead and do that right now
So what are those things I think Chris is really good with his being serious about unserious things like the who is it
Vampire
She wanted to know if the judge is a vampire here
Give her a vampire
And your vampire
Objection
I know that we didn't provide fraudulent financials and I know he's my brother gave you has everything you said you have nothing
Do to consider the judge
Empire
Same where you consider
A vampire category
Do
Probably demon rap
What category is families who lost
Loved ones
Sandy Hook
Don't have a right
To seek relief
Through the lawyer
No I think that did that the media and other media and the people that they're actually always hyping it up
Claiming that high
Not true
That they're the vampires so if you become successful off
Danny Gokey
Yourself
Diorite
I know you're misrepresenting that I did I know that it was a small part of what we did and then
My opposition to Barack Obama during that. It's what exploded show
If it's very weird
Conclude
Actually you did
Garner audience
Revenue as a result of
Your lies.
Sandy Hook
Yourself
We are with negligible Revenue not really Bill discover almost
Seems like $300 off articles or something
No way that I can tell you the Sandy Hook was not
A revenue generator for us in fact
One of our lizard iguana to the time was very
Controversial deep question
And I still did things like that if I got a 911 I've explained that to you
Audience members
Of yours who
Harassed
My client
They they like
There have been claims that those are my listeners and and much of that some people that I saw on the news that did
Go around some people are not my listeners even though the media center
No true Scotsman
I mean no listener of mine would harass live for
How to get no true Scotsman vampire
Stop and be like
How did you do that cuz you made my words turn back on me and I don't I don't know how to do that to people never say
Bill made
Has the definition of gone solar I don't understand
Edwards work
They do not
So Alex gets to talk in a year and getting asked a question about Owens video
He defamed Neil heslin relied on the Zero Hedge article
Seem to understand what the issue is there
Now I I don't have to play the the full video for you mister Jones I may just ask you some questions about it see what your call
Of the broadcast for mister
Destroyer clean
That contrary to what your husband said during his interview with Megyn Kelly is not possible
Rachel's healthy
Sun
Chipotle yes
Yeah Shirley characterized would only said on that video he was reading this article
Okay you think that that claim came from zerohedge hat article
Reading is your 100 only talked about it
And and
I dropped him off at school with bookbag picked him up in a body bag
And the people said she wasn't picked up the body back that day so technically that was
Hyperbole
Wish I was like yeah there's nothing at all
I have to Domino's located
Supporters claim
That
It was not
Do it held his son
His arm
After sun
Murder
You recall him saying
In the context of the body backstory
What's this lady
So Alex seems to be wanting to make the point
Like or the argument that it was exaggeration Owen was accusing them of exaggeration that too
The issue is he wasn't technically a body bag that's the whole thing I'm just trying to clear up the record I just got to make sure every
Nobody knows this is all a big misunderstanding that's very weird because if that's Alex's understanding
You can't possibly be
No. It maybe is something that sounds like maybe this'll make make us all sounds less malicious
Zerohedge article I won't say that it doesn't matter what he was reading because he said things that weren't true
Edward in the article
So they played some of this and then it comes up that shortly after this
This video that I made got taken off YouTube
Rosenstreich on it
And Alex has asked whether or not that freaked him out
Maybe should be assigned as did that freak you out
Do you think the lawyer says
Freak me out all the time generally Dracula
Now on July 20th
Of 2017
So
A little over 3 weeks
From
Owens
Broadcast there
Do a call that
YouTube remove that video
You refresh my memory of it
Okay and that freaks you out right
No
You are perfectly
Text
Okay
But you know you won't freak out
Okay well why don't we pull up exhibit number 107
I will represent you mr. Jones that this
I has been produced to us as a text
Message exchange between Raju and Nico Acosta
That
Nico
On July 20th
Text
Mister jius
AJ freaking out about the YouTube stream tri-strike what's your ETA to the off
You see that
Okay does that refresh your memory about
What your reaction was to this
No I just know I told me when I talk about Sandy Hook so I'm sure I did say what the hell you doing
Oh you think you were upset about
Owen
Publishing that video remember I told you that
Do you know that you rebroadcast
Personally
Broadcast YouTube instructions
Going to be mad angry right
Directions
I can't know what you're talkin about this is yeah there's really no
No answer for me here vividly remember so many mr. Magoo cartoons because of the the
Manner in which it was almost a Rube Goldberg that wasn't working you know everything wondered through without being
What if he was dead and just got beaten by Styx for an H mattioda
I'd like to introduce you to my lovely wife a coat rack
What the hell is going on I only mr. Magoo joke
Cuz I can't see very well that right that's kind of Vegas shooting comes up
Now
Strap it in
Oh boy alex is a conspiracy about that Scott know the deadliest mass shooting in US history
Correct
Not sure everyone
U-Haul at 6
People were killed
111 wound
Initially
Masa
Death
On that day
Just as you done with Sandy Hook
Indicated that it
Are the government
Yesterday before it happened I said runty the Michelle I said they'll probably
Rock concert or something
Bryson
You said before the shooting you
What happened
Build your audience
Globalist
They predict it
The Sunday show
Until the show
He predicted it
Yes
And then because you had predicted it you knew that
Actually
Stage 5
American dolls
Working in an Indian with one of the other side effects of the Civil War
American government
Criminal almost American government
We're working with Saudi Arabia
In which
Department
Well
Fashion
I'm sorry
Actions
I had the station
Going to CIA
Yes which one
Four factions
Different clandestine Splinter groups what are their name
Osaka restaurant
Splinter groups within the CIA and
You don't know their names you know that they were
Involved in staging the murder of 60 people at a concert in Las Vegas
Scipio
American
For what purpose
Embarrassed Trump
Atascadero N2
Basically
Want to cover US invasion with South Saudi allies
Who sang what
Check out the government
They took out the Saudi government took out the large faction
And he did that
In response
And your source for this is what now
This was just a lot of this came out pieces that is also do people involved
That was involved forces
Things like that
Ashley
Call you weren't thermostat.
Well okay I guess we're going to have to move to
Until you
It disclosed I'll see you for stores
For this
Oroville
Crime committed by the United States government this
Describes
Pieces of information that identity
It will move to compel that
There's there's not going to be an ass I'm going to be
Disappointment
So then what's going on here is it Alex's combining the Las Vegas shooting
Being and when MBS took power Saudi Arabia when he
Help people at the Ritz-Carlton named yeah
There was that Purge in the in the government so Alex has turned the Las Vegas shooting into a Prelude
Said that
And then Trump orchestrated I guess a regime change in Saudi Arabia
I mean somebody who has I was his political sat in his beliefs
He should be totally cool with that he should be totally fine with Trump secretly installing it
Different governments share is a sovereign country
Yeah
And it's worked out really well for the like things that Alex values in a free Society
So it all is for the good
I don't know
If I can get over
Some of these groups have no name
Delivery of solid the best
Way to answer that question
There's no other answer cuz you you're either going to make up a name drive or you're just going to say I don't know
But coming in with
They have no names like f****** Batman why would they have known you're a fool
Fool yourself sound dumb ask him if
Name the Trump installed a new Saturday regime because he was practicing to do
I know that I heard Alexei some of that stuff like on his show and what has he written deposition
It feels
Like he really thinks that's how it happened
That is a thing he believes his tone has like more of a like I think you're actually saying this
I've been a lot of his other clients on comfortable ground
And he say he has the tone that he feels proud that he knows it
Poor guy
So he is the topic of pizzagate comes up short and Alex discusses this tiny bit
And then is a little bit wishy-washy about whether or not that shooting actually even happened at the pizzeria
You familiar with
The gentleman
In Edgar Madison
Justin Welch
No
Quit refresh your recollection
I told you that
That's the gentleman
Open fire
On
Pizzeria in Washington
You said that was his name
Will you covered
That fairly extensive
Yes
And
But you
Add broadcast
Over many
Chose
Your claims that
Restaurant
Ping pong in Washington
AC
Was actually being used by
High level
Democrats
As a site for
Sexual trafficking
I covered the news covering it
Was nowhere near creating a story
Did you ever assert to your audience that that wasn't the
Prove it
Comet Ping Pong
Was he fat
And you
I do location
No I did
Talk about some of people there
Like Tony podesta
Other stepdaughter
Nerf
Taste of Texas
How was the restaurant
Connected to that
Add fundraisers there there was a lot of Art
Weird
Stories that weren't true
About basements and all the rest of that stuff
We picked up and cover solo stories were first on 4chan hm and picked up by the mainstream is
Whelen debating cupboard weather
That was true or not and
Wild
Whether or not that that place was being used
For the child trafficking
That is discussed in a regulation in your testimony is that you never
Stated that it was in fact being used for that
We we did reports on it and then read the reports I'm just asking you
Waiter
What your testimony is are you
Testifying today that
You never
Started on your show
That the Comet Ping Pong
Was a child
Sex traffic
I I never said
Myself
But that was certainly happening
Wow
You said
When you say you never said it was certainly happen
Did you ever say what's happening
But
A gentleman named Edgar Maddison Welch
When shut off.
Pizzeria correct
And are you
You have doubts about that
A shot up
Open fire in the pizza
You read that
No I don't want to shop
I think those stinky like shot into a
Bores a wall
Okay see you agree that he shot in the restaurant
Restaurant before.
An open fire
Okay and you believe that be true
It's very bizarre
That's a strange
Level of just need your
Dial that one's just complete like I just refused to agree with you on princess
Yeah it's Defiance for its own sake
I'm Alex Jones I'm not just going to say this happen
You're going to need to really fight me
Before I will just be like yes yeah I've walked into too many rakes today
Jammed up a little so no it didn't happen interest me
Interest me what he said debates is because I I do feel like
The more I hear them continually talk about it the more I think that they believe
They were having debates
Not on the show
But baby leave their show is in conversation with the rest of the mainstream media that's interesting you know what I'm saying
I
I wonder if you're over reading it
That is an interesting way to look at it from an outside perspective
That it that is an argument that he could make
It would be bad for him still not a good idea know if you viewed himself as being in Dubai
Play with
The mainstream Media or whatever his perception of the mainstream
Then that's fine
But it doesn't excuse or absolve him of his his actions even in the slightest
No
And it also is really surreal to have like his him saying that like I was reporting on things
That
4chan and eight Chan were saying that the mainstream media reported on the couch
New York Times was using 4chan as a source
Big try not to do that yeah good idea
But that is his perception of like the mainstream media I guess
Yeah it is a fascinating thing to me because he really does you know it in normally it wouldn't
Big sense but I do think he thinks he's talking to the TV
You are correct I think that you have an interesting like sort of textual analysis
How's that
Pressing it I think he's really just trying to evade responsibility for the things he's saying by pretending
That they were just talking about how is this possible
Well I'm sure he's trying to think of more like
You know we had climate debates where we had at expert who said this and then we said this
Kind of just the standard evasion of like
And all sides deeper inside their brains can you believe the people should all rest for having
Reviews conversation
Rogan talking to Matt Walsh just leave out the part where there's other ideas
They're being so tired we lose debate so we have debates without the other side that's the way we do it
Two really interesting line of discussion comes up and that is whether or not Alex's audience should trust
Tim and
I agree with Alex here
I want to just
See if you can
You want your audience
You know I just get up there and say what I think
I really actually don't try to get the glove mirror
Hayden area that I just took
If you get on the truck
No I'm not a question
Got a creeper Banner I'll give you the trust me I'm just I'm just out there
All my guns at once and try to explode the specs
Wow
So you don't care
No I really don't I really just try to be truthful
What I do is
Find Saugus at tires
News
Angry rage
Real
So
I guess then
Junior audience
Or should they not
Trust me
I'm trying to tell the truth
I die I think that is already and shouldn't trust him I agree
Iib mutable yeah yeah
Now this introduces an interesting problem for Alex
It's so wet
This is just a great question for the lawyer to be asking
Should your audience trust you and if you say yes they should trust me then that you're telling them
These people are actors and you know they should just take you at your word at this you're misleading people and
But if you say no
Then it becomes a they will you were saying these people are actors if they don't trust you but you want them to look
Came to this stuff
Where does that lead us realizes he's at
Right Sogo
Verify when I'm
When you say go
Consciously
I do say that
So I should go be mean to somebody but that was even really correcting peep
Play some Cartier
Your narrative essay with investigating Sandy Hook
You aren't telling them the best
That's ridiculous. You're right
My clients were crisis actors and they
What are you unmask them for being involved
I mean there's been a lot of examples of stuff you guys have said about me on the news and I know it's not true and it's meant to make people hate me
Play some crazy person
Is
That person in their actions it's up to them
Or your neighbor does something wrong to you go to jail too
Mostly peaceful protest go out and confront people
If twins we're not going to accept it and don't Republicans do it it's the worst thing ever
But Democrats at the whole thing about it you'll get it
Everyone knows I got problems
Because they know it's a train wreck sometimes but it's real
I know I've got problems
Logical female the mammal species
You're not crazy
Acolyte
Thank you
This all spiraled out of control because Alex realizes that no matter where you go with the question
Turn of trust
Especially when he was saying trust but verify at least it's don't matter what
Angle he takes
He's f*****
It leads down the road where the lawyer is going to have him pinned down on something he does not want to
Be involved in so he starts throwing around the what is a woman thing
You'll because that is meant to elicit an emotional response in the person that he's talking to before it generally he can get
Get out of any of these tight situations with that SHINee key it just doesn't work
I mean it if he might as well have screamed free Charles Manson
Like it is Alexis what I told somebody to do something and then they did it that's not my fault
Well by some logic Irene it eat his it is so funny cuz he does suddenly realize like
So if they trust me
I said that they weren't real they were crisis actors and then they went and behave that way
And if they didn't trust me
They went to investigate because I told them that they were crisis actors I told people that we should look into this
We have to invade trust but verify how do you verify
Screwed
So they take a break
And turns out that Alex shot a little video during the break
They'll need to get some feeling back if you know like he's got it
Something
During lunch break
Video
Tubi
Broadcast over your website
No
Say what
Did you make another video
No
Did you give an interview
Meet the Press
During that interview
With press
You
Stated that
The planets today
I figured episode
I just thought it wasn't talked about the devastation
Just what you mean of you
Animal correct that you said
That
The plaintiffs that ass
At your death
I just know you guys had asked for deposition is to be accomplished lemon told that before not talk about their position
I haven't designated your
Deposition
You can talk about that with your Warner
Why do you want the deposition be confidential
I know you guys will take Snippets out of it
Carpet bombing campaign to biosignature E
I like to be on trial
Like pieces of it
Well
Why don't you
Publishing entire
Banana Kong YouTube edited version
Well mr. Jones
Yesterday you discussed your
To your audience
But I discussed the fact that you were like the Niners New World Order
Okay
All right you've been claiming
To your audience
For years that
This litigation is part of an F
Yes
But when you have an opportunity to
Testimony
Defend yourself
You want to keep that
Federal cancel trial
We can ask
You know about that
Patachou
Also I think I was talking about us
100%
Boy alex heavily from
Peace about himself in Rolling Stone for his bio
As she is reading out Alex's bio
And there's something else in that Rolling Stone article that maybe
Alex
Should not
Know about
Read that Rolling Stone article
And so you're aware that that article also
Described
A gentleman named Byron Williams
Who was arrested following a gun battle
California police
And was
Hey Abbott
Listener of yours your call that I don't remember
So you don't remember that the article described Mr Williams
As a devotee of yours
Who was arrested when he was on his way to shoot up
An organization called the
Tides Foundation
Sorry about that
Well that's this is Geodon on your website
You probably wouldn't have featured
Is going to shoot up
The tides Foundation
Session
I don't see that part
It's not on your website
Can you show me the quote
I don't have the article as an exhibit
I'm saying you don't remember that part of the article
Glenn Beck thing
Foundation
He is bad at this totally off-the-hook though because his conspiracy stuff feeds into back
Ampex whole thing about the tides Foundation traced back to being another Soros Puppet Master narrative
So basically the same s*** with slightly different labels
Is also a reader of Infowars
And his jailhouse confession he said quote
I'm actually mad at Fox
I'm mad at them because they go on to something else
It's like they drop the issue and it lands on a shelf somewhere to collect dust
And that's what's happening to the truth
It's going around collecting dust
How do you say you're not going to let these people get away with this stuff you can't let them get away with it so this was my
Play action because of foxes neglect
This isn't an insane perspective
Is it a logical endpoint of the narrative the people like Alex and Beck disseminate
This guy is expressing an understandable disappointment that these people who claim to have uncovered the truth of these grandkids
Didn't move on to some other topic and they never actually do anything's weird doesn't it obviously it's not rational.
Shoot up a foundation but it makes total sense for someone who believes in someone like Alex or back to get to the point where they've had in
Enough with the inaction
Why isn't anybody doing anything it's that tension State Alex Glenn Beck propaganda
Is meant to keep people are
Some people will inevitably
Break under that to that that amount of tension right it's designed that feature you're essentially telling me the
The only way to save the world is to do something and then the next day you're moving on to a different thing
How is that possible
Yeah and it's like well yeah he's the problem is
He's making rational choices within a framework of insanity yeah yeah yeah
Yeah
Somebody brings up Matthew Mills the guy who Alex had on his show and then ended up harassing people at
Episode of Family Memorial Run
And Alex failing to answer if he knew that Matthew Mills was a listener
Movie show
I don't remember all this
The transmission
That's what you meant.
That he was a listener I don't remember this remember vague amount that was hard to see it
Well
So you doodling Wellness
No I want to see it I'd like you just pay attention
Just I'm relaxing listen to you
I get the feeling that you're not taking this very seriously if you're doodling throughout the question
Distraction
It doesn't take much brain power do
So I'd like you to focus me off when I get brain power
Tell me what you meant
When you said
He is a listener of the transmission
Don't take much brainpower to doodle
I mean honestly in in my in my understanding I think it is him being he's been
Better able to answer your questions I think if he is doodling at the same time he had his blanket
100%
I meant think about like some of this other stuff I've been I don't really know how to articulate it exactly but there's this
Trim that I see
Where is so much stuff is about like
They say were bad people
Or I didn't say to be mean to him the articulation and the way that Alex labels people is
People harassing victims families is being mean to them
A very childish prism that he looks through I don't exactly know
I don't know how to phrase it any better than that or give any more depth to it it's pretty consistent
This Doodlebug is just
Just another amped-up version of it really I really think if you had like a you know that
The Pediatrics who who like have the stages of growth you know Alexa
About right the 98th percentile in scores from 6 to 8 or something like that
You could cause you can flat Alex into the 628
Easy
I think an argument could be made
So
YouTube. Where Alex is being made to read things
And how's it going
It's actually reads better than you would have expected
But this is going to be there's a little bit of like
Some stuff that's kind of amusing and then this will lead into something that is pretty tough
I'll give a warning before we get to that because we're Alex's reading from
The first responder EMTs report normally probably wouldn't put it
I think that there is a value to it closer to it for now Alex Reid
A comment from his website which he understandably does not wanted imagine
You see that comment left 5
Fastest speaker 2.0
Yes
Can you read that for me please
You want me to read random, so the internet now so it's in my voice range Bo
Well I think it's not a random comedy Internet it's a comment on your website
But I mean you can go to YouTube and find some of this right now
What ligouri the storms of this works
Publix.
The rules
Can only a check
Is it necessary to read it aloud
Dear Daddy
But I mean this is somebody why you want me to say bad things somebody around, so that's not that's that's just dirty
Can you
But I'm not the witness not anymore
So Alex goes on to read it and listen to this is amazing
Sandy Hooks 2-year anniversary
Primitive postings
Mary Hoke Smith Newtown residents
Experts are really enjoying
Your house must give house number Alex Jones and outrageously I didn't rape you
The three found nobody yet Lenny
Trying using Kevin for your certainty start HBO show this
Founding over yet Lenny trying using Kevin for your search engine name
He's not a Talbots
Or also hope all your anus round around Walker's have found your way home
If I brought Emily a new dress yet Robbie
Can I drive to Cersei this
This is not my idea that
Who's the same thing in the first day of deposition so he wouldn't say people's names presumably because
Because he thought they would edit it it was covering for him not knowing anybody's name
Time it does feel like he's like
They're going to make me say these things and then this will be a Sizzle reel
Which is bizarre
It is it is indicative of how he would have let you know like he's Young
Telling you this is what I would do to you a hundred percent
He's like this is the way it's done
How do I know that
I do it
That's what he said that's what he's doing he's like what you don't understand the business
Write it because of the tiny clip of Robbie Parker that I showed over and over again
Yep yeah that's probably part of his mental process
So here is where we're going to get to the the difficult part
If you have
You know sensitivity about
Graphic depictions are imagery about the
Aftermath of the shooting and Skip forward
Hello maybe 20 minutes it's this is a long clip but there's a reason
Could something happens throughout it that I think it's critical to to keep track of and understand
Matt is the as Alex's reading this
Pay attention
Because you can see him trying to come up with conspiracies
As he's reading the EMTs report
It's fascinating but also really the juxtaposition of
Alex's voice reading this is really dark and grotesque yeah
There's another added element of like
It's really difficult to escape from
The awareness of like this is what he lies about yeah you know like
Hearing these details and just recognizing that this is Ban
Yeah
It would take an event like this
And and lie about it is just really dark
Skip ahead if you need to go to the bathroom
Beginning with
This paragraph
I do not recall this
H4h
You don't recall if we regroup
For proper seating
Before proceeding but my next memory is entering roommate
Turn clockwise and did not see anything getting some distance around around
Ravenna Ohio
Shopping centers around
The bodies
Two adult females Lyle floor
Tyrone
RC Open Door
A corner of the room
Initially thought
This was closet
Bookstore I was actually able to
Copperhead when I was
What time does Palais de Reynosa Facebook little boy on top of pile
Space I was looking at a profile of Bluffs I was face
Top of his head to the West
Position the body of them again realize there was
Sexy politics shoulder
Disable recall civic images but I recalled
Terrific injuries
Other than the two dead adult females
Was no obvious signs of blood or tissue around the room
First Impressions with the children have been
Elsword hit
Thanks little boy
Recalls on the blacktop
Is the room also that my handgun was Whole Foods times
Well
Stepping out roommate observe the rooms in the east
Evacuated
Police officers both directions I decided that my services were but she was not working EMS capacity
Dakota building
But actually a rescue Association of eilistraee BMT
19 years
He read this
When this report
Came out in late 2000
I think I even
Hunting
Darren Stouffer
Somewhere
Fraudulent
What
Just basically framing
That's where more of though young
That's why it's normal to Tequesta
You're saying that
You you read this
Is it the time in question
I don't remember I send you
That you read this report Bill Cario at this
Because you
Disrespect
Dad
This was
Further evidence of there being a hoax because
You did not report
The presence of blood
I know I'm asking a question
Defied
Just now as you were reading
This
Isn't that weird
And you said that
You were surprised he said he was surprised
You're saying that
And what you just read
Curio
So that he was surprised about what
Katsuya
He says
I am unable to recall
Cific images
But I recall
The mini had
Injuries
Other than the two adult
Two dead adult females
There was no obvious signs of blood or tissue around the room
And my first impression
Children
Elsewhere
And hitting in the bath
So he says other than where the two adult females were
MC button that area correct
You know where the children were
And that's where you'd expect are you suggesting here in reading this
Are you still trying to maintain some reason
That you think
This
Report
Is further Evidence
Suspicion
Because
You think that Sergeant curio didn't adequately
Describe the presence of blood
He said he was surprised
That's what a lot of people
Discuss vaguely
That that that
That's it.
People search
He said he was surprised
I'm sorry I'm sorry
Surprise or what
People have giant holes on a Brother killed their there's blood all over the place
Maybe there is the kind of stuff people cherry-pick
Navigate to people's houses being honest
Being honest when you read this
That Sergeant Carrillo was an EMT and
Was working as an EMT in the building
When after you claimed that there were no infusing buildings that on us
Objection
I'm just about I'm confused I was going off earlier reports
That no emc's weren't allowed in the building right
You Groove me that there were
Correction
Surprised
Why the children
Carrie was surprised
Children have been placed
Senator John
His first impression was that the
The children had been
Elsewhere
That would be way better
Is a killed elsewhere they have to replace there
Tire Denver
I want to know this is just can stay
I'm not tired
I moved
I mean
Answer questions about to get here
Alex is
Just
Constantly trying to find ways to rationalize his action
He's
Find he's finding something that he thinks it looks like it one of his quote-unquote anomalies in he
Here that he can use to be as the basis of like this is why it's reasonable for me to have
I've done the b******* that I've done and
I don't understand how somebody can
Click here
This description
Much less be reading it and that is where their brain is no I mean it did verify sounded to me
Like when he heard when he read there was no blood
He was like
I wish I had known that
Right that would have been really good for my back in the day that would have f******
Can killed
As a conspiracy about this stuff
If only I had done any part of my job
Yeah this is the this is the disgusting version of that his brain never stops trying to find his angle
It's it
It's so clear like you can
You can you can
Feel him thinking
Oh yeah absolutely and not just that but it is it is so much like
He is
Revealing that he didn't
Read this
Yes you know
And by doing this
I mean
Involves reading do it of course but it is it is just like you shouldn't
You should read this
I need to rivet the Revelation that he knows well it looking into the reality of something is bad
Business
It's the same thing earlier
I wasn't paying attention I didn't care enough to talk s***
Care enough to read this why is anyone holding me responsible for talkingshit
Right
So Alex has crafted this in his mind as this reason for suspicion reason for why it's
Justified all of his actions look there's no blood ballet by mean Immortal words
Doesn't jive right until you read a little bit further
Western 360
Pictures of mr. carriers report that we just been reading
Paragraph beginning my next Rec
Next memories
My next recollect
My next recollection
Is it when I return to the school I went back to roommate I believe
Lieutenant
Follow me and I returned what I thought was a closet but we arrived bathroom I believe there was one more gunshot
Splattered on the walls
Children actually been shot in the bathroom not in there
I also recognize
Add to check
Possible survivors
What type of furniture
TFC kickers
Riding me with some software
Or someone from the room t f c
Car logo
420 had entered the room and was diagnosed
I asked if anyone had access to phone
Talk to you
Anyone have access to phone with a camera
I was about to
Crime scene
Call the TSC Guerra
Took my phone
There was grass
IPhone
There was some confusion
And I did not I later learned that TSC Guerra took some photographs I started moving bodies like
Images of
Thank you children the bathroom or not clear
Call the T side of the polishing was unimaginable
Summit children a terrific injuries
I know that because
Began to systematically Schecter lifesigns
Remember calling
Calling into
Call Eula Paul
Survivor would answer
Watching an open-sea movement
All the children out of the pot with my one
I did some place their bodies on the floor
Jobs in classroom
Nearest a bathroom place to children in the rolling towards entry door
Kenosha City memory
Michelle Ramos
DC
Certain Carrillo comment on the presence of
Blood spatter in that fortunate
Dumb
Yeah
You have you have
Alex
Grasping at straws as he reads
The beginning portion of this trying to find
Things that he can present is anomalies not realizing that
A little bit later I like
The things that he doesn't comprehend
Are perfectly explained
A man
And horrifying
I mean he just will he'd rather make a cherry-picked anomaly out of it because
That's how he works well if it if he had read it
He would have stopped
When he saw when he got what he needed exactly what is
Beset that FBI says no one knows killed
I got what I wanted
Get out
OMG it's dark it's B really f****** dark
Even in this setting his brain can work that way
And that is just such a primary objective it is
I meant I just I mean I know it's
Awful and it's really hard to hear and hard to listen to
But there is a part of it is that this is the this is
In reality the event
That Alex lies about
This
This is
The image of it is Unthinkable like it that get the EMT saying it's on it's on imagine
Ana Belen NM
Instead of
Instead of dealing with reality Alex decided to lie and and exploit the whole time
He was reading that I couldn't stop thinking about Jesse Lewis and Scarlett's testimony whenever she was
Relating the story of him
Saving f****** lives you know
Keeping people away from this story
You know keeping them away from that yeah and it's just like
To really
Hear him read it
So blase
So looking for something that exculpatory that
Yep you know
Yep and it's just like it it really f**** me up
What is Aries like
Setting records of cowardice a reasonable person looks at that
Listen to that just goes to a billion dollars
You know like this guy this guy needs to be stopped
Yeah cuz he's not going to learn
It's not going to be he's not going to learn no I mean that's true and I mean I watched
The sanctions hearing
That they had nothing should leave punitive damages hearing
That's Norm
And Maddie did earlier this week
Normal almost making your argument
Like a billion dollars isn't going to stop him
Get a trillion dollars isn't going to stop
He needs to be stopped what amount of money like but he was making that argument for like the fine should be lower
No amount of money is going to stop at this person from acting the way he does his brain
This is what he does he can't stop himself he cannot he's reading this
And he does not give a f*** you disconnected from the humanity and the reality of it that's just
Need the committee's disconnected from Humanity in reality
.
You know
Hard not to hit see it that way
So we have a little bit of content to your left a little bit of
Stuff to get through but this is the end of the the grotesque portion
Yeah and the deposition day wraps up
With a little bit of an argument about whether or not they should
Keep going
To Maddy's questions end and then the Alex's lawyer and the guy who I believe is a lawyer for
Genesis Communications opportunity to ask Alex
Day until like they need to regroup
Or decide to keep going and Maddie doesn't want to break
I am come back another day unless there's a guarantee that Alex will appear for that
Absolute so this becomes a little bit of an issue and Norm has a standing appointment somewhere at 6 that day
I am so
Students with that but before that
Maddie asks Alex shows pictures of the family members
Plaintiff
And asked Alex if he knows who they are
And then asked if he feels
Any responsibility for the pain that they've experienced because of his actions
And Alex gets progressively more and more belligerent and hostile
He would have to admit you know
Responsibility for something
And so this is a begins with a Alex just denying any responsibility for anything
You accept
Any responsibility
Jones
Or
Suffering you caused
Experiencing
No I doubt it's it's apples and oranges I didn't I didn't kill her until any children
And I
Iraq Iraq
Apologize to time and I am
Not the Sandy Hook man
Coronavirus
Do you recognize
Photographs
No
You accept any responsibility for the suffering you caused
Mark and Jackie Barden
As a result of
Eliza
Concerning Sandy Hook
In the aftermath
Objection
Binocular child and I don't I did not
Feeling person against them
I thought it was like the wmd in Iraq thing
So what
Respect to the line
Utah
Set the new response
Story for the suffering
Objection Jackie
Eli you have to know it's incorrect and I didn't tell
The things I was wrong about on purpose
You accepting your
Suffering that you are
Incorrect statement
About
Playing baseball
Jack and Mark
Jack
Jackie and Mark Barden
Yeah
Public events
And freeze peaches man because of my hurt somebody's feelings were not in America anymore
Change the channel
Bacon
They can come out and say I'm wrong they other free speech
Well
Channel Win
People who are inspired by you
Threatening harassment
Schoolboy
I just can't lick
I don't know it's hard to it's hard to listen to this all and just think like
How does Alex not think this has gone terribly
This is gone as badly as possible
I hate that it is it is
Looking at
How is it possible
You know
This
Motherfuker
To steamroll your life
You know just
Out of
He can choose
To steamroll your f****** life
If it makes him money
And then he'll say it was an accident and it shouldn't be a problem well I mean
That is great until he has to pay a billion dollars we need to get him
I feel I feel like
Optically
Philosophically even from Alex's own perspective none of this plays well
It really is a is a terrible look of a petulant baby
Who refuses to Greeley
Own up and be
At all an adult about how about his own actions
So are you gets a little hostile here towards the idea of taking responsibility
You recognize any of
Photograph
No
Accept any personal responsibility
The suffering you caused
Matthew Carly and Julian Soto
As a result
Statements you made concerning the San Diego
Never said her name
Enjoying your family I never 7X
Casino
I refuse the false guilt you're going to put on the basis for the First Amendment
Wow
He he the one thing that he doesn't understand
And I understand I can make sense because if you've never experienced the consequences or something
And you always get what you want
Why would you assume
That
Your deflections and your attempts to get out of stuff
Make you look
Wayward
Right then if you just said yes or no and you know it is you can you can tell
Like he's he's always gotten away with it yeah he can just wiggle out he can get you a motional and then
Then he gets rewarded for it in what world would he think that it's a bad mood
It always worked he can't recognize that in this circle
Stamps
Even from a crash
Cynical Alex is on personal motivations perspective even
For him sticking to his guns or whatever
Acknowledging the people's pain
And saying I am I am sorry for my part in that
It doesn't hurt him at all. Then it only helps
What I mean
Very literally if it in this
Deposition
Heated actually expressed remorse and responsibilities they could sublet maybe it would have been five
100 million-dollar
I mean who knows but I may well see here's the thing
For him to do that
He would need to have a completely different mindset and having a completely different mindset might have made it five hundred million dollars
This solak probably wouldn't make that big of a difference would it be indicative of a
Whole different paradox
Fort Myers Club here and it's
He showed a picture of Robbie Parker and he does recognize him
So that's a little bit of a twist
Recognize anybody
What exhibit
Make it in this photograph
Yes.i'd Robbie Parker and his daughter
Do you accept
Any
First Response
Story for the suffering
Upaws Robbie Parker as a result
Statements you made
The aftermath
Sandy Hook shooting
I did not personally made him any harm but I am sad for his loss in his painting
And I'm sorry if
You're a badass questions in this country would get them hurt him but they cannot kill his daughter
And
That's why I cannot accept it
Possibility that you guys are created while you're out there giggling and laughing celebrating
In the hallway about all the attention you're getting
Are you coming here and talk also often
We manipulate people that have hearts and souls out there
Cold-blooded political apparatus
Buy into the
Fraud
Do you
Agree
That your condo
The aftermath
No I didn't even break the story or pointed out at first I didn't cover it
So it's just a just a refusal of of anything even in line with things that he said
He said earlier is this very episode that we are recording
I'm sorry for any pain that was caused to Robbie Parker
He's a good man do you know like this
This is just Alex recognizing the gravity of the moment
The Varian at this point of the end of the line of questioning
And him sort of feeling like he's got to be a defiant
Colonel Travis
Bandits
It's misguided it's disrespectful
It sucks
Ms Alex
Yeah
I mean
I just
How
How it's possible
You know so many people to have read in so many different Outlets Uno
Alex finally apologized for what he did or anything like that you know it's like
There are the only thing that an apology is is taking responsibility for your actions
And then working to correct that
That's the that's the foundation of what apology
Yeah should be and he fundamentally cannot do that absolutely not not a possible thing
Note for him to apologize
No because
All you need to really know about the penitent or lack thereof with him is when he
He reads
EMTs account of being there he's trying to find
Rationalizations for his own actions for his own lies that you told about Sandy Hook what makes
What about this helps me justify myself
And that's
That's that's sucks he sucks it is
We don't we don't talk about him in the same way that we do serial killers
Of any murders that he's done since childhood in the context of
Like murdering somebody but it is
If you are
Read a story about a serial killer
They're not going to be like
And then he was like oh serial killing is wrong I got it now I'm really sorry about that
Everybody kind of gets the idea that if you're already on
If your on body number five
Reimburse is probably not for you
And I genuinely feel like that's where we are with Alex you know it's like
Where where he didn't kill anybody
And obviously the
But
But it is
He's
He's a serial killer what you mean there is there is not
Cecilia point where he's going to suddenly realize that oh no the error of my ways
He is probably In Too Deep for any kind of Moment of clarity like that
Of course that is what he needs to do to try to make a Redemption Arc
Only way he could be stay relevant right pull a Glenn Beck
Put on a sweater talk to Samantha Bee put it down for a couple of years and then get right back at it right
Maybe if there is a other motivation he could appear
In some way to have had a I had a moment
Even even in this same deposition episode he's lying about like
Breakthroughs he's hiding therapy at stuff so like
Dinos
He knows that he can he can baby use that as some kind of a
I'm serious card or whatever but supposed to have a when you have a breakthrough in therapy
Everybody's like 10 this guy's change and said it appears that he was like
You're right
I am right about everything and I should never take responsibility for my actions
It's good call therapist
So we come to the end of day 2 of Alex's depositions and we may do
Like another episode cleaning up
ID3 and for pretty minor as a whole
And after how this date
Fireworks Amor Lake
Yeah
It's too heavy app
And so yeah will do that and I know probably Friday will check back in to see how the
Stream went maybe I will see I don't know who knows I don't know at all
Tell Rebecca we have website
Hey dude if you read the Wikileaks you got a reader bro you got to read out
And now here comes with the sex robot
Alex