Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for knowledge B
Sick of them posing
Need need money
Knowledge fight
Acknowledge
The altar of Celine and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
My brakes today Jordan is
So I've been lover of books
My life I was a Avid Reader when I was younger
Booze to Wonder Years
Choose to read when your eyes are blurry
Some of those after college Years might have been a little bit hazy around that front chair
But I always had a
Pretty
Decent collection of book
Growing up I always I like to have the bookshelf with
Even if
Just to look
Read the books but it's fun to look at
And I realize that I've not done that
I've been dead
The reason is because
How like
8 years ago or so nine years ago I had a house fire and my house burned down
And I lost
A giant collection of books
But I had
And I just
Kind of felt like after that point like what
What's the point of having these physical Shore
They can all be gone
Yeah and I guess
It's taken that long for me to get back on the horse because I've decided that I'm starting a new library
But it'll be a specifically anti-communist literature and Alex Jones adjacent Library
And I was a child
I did childish things act like but when I became a man
Right back on the horse of collecting books
And so actually today just in the mail I've got my I got my
First couple things that I'd ordered
Copies of the American opinion
Society magazines from the 60s
It's antiques baby let's open it up to a random page nope too many underwear why don't you look at
Page 27
Thank you sir little Gary Allan.
It uses the word
Do you expect
So yeah I'm excited to put this together and also has a little bit self-serving but I wanted to put out the the message
Did you folks
Better
If you have any John Birch Society materials that are kicking around your house and you feel like
Hey I don't need this maybe Dan would like it I guarantee you I would
So if you want to contact us that would be very nice I would enjoy any contributions to the
The library of those regular old people and I know you and I have both been there you know your wandering around here
Your house in like what am I doing with all this antique communist literature from the 1940s maybe your parents have it though
Others others all kinds of possibilities
Android
I think it would go to a good that good home
I take care of it
Totally I mean it's funny that I made the joke because honestly I think our audience probably does hi mean
Audience is more likely to have this in any other worlds
Episodes
Vhs's Public Access
I think this is a little bit more likely to have somebody who's sitting on something
Slightly less specific
Think I think there's more opportunity
Is that
There's a certain fella named Hayao Miyazaki
All right now
He makes some
Pretty good movies
I don't know if you've ever heard of Studio Ghibli
I don't know
About that but I've heard his name before Princess Mononoke Spirited Away
Porco Rosso
Spirited Away in Princess Mononoke everywhere
What
He tweeted out
Or something
Aries picture
From him
A little statue
Of Grogan
Oh boy do you know what that mean
Here's what I'm thinking
Was this one of these Elon Musk a fake Twitter account
Him ogogo
Hellboy
Official Studio Ghibli
Weymouth
So he is going to make a Star Wars movie I thought maybe he was going to be in the man
Mandalorian next season I don't know if it's a Star Wars movie or whatever it's going to be
Being in
Convention a little bit would do that he's not that kind of guy but anyways
The people responsible for maybe five of my top 10 films
I'm making one together
Incredible I hope you're not let down
I will let you enjoy
This brightness and excitement without my sentence
I was only let down by Studio Ghibli one time
All right and that
Because
It's not just Miyazaki
You know there's another director there who's also an incredible director
And he's really really good but he makes less magical stuff and more grounded and realism stuff
And we just stopped
Studio Ghibli was the same
When I was 19 my friends and I all got
Together
Get some pizza and we wanted to watch Grave of the fireflies Studio Ghibli movies
That movie is about two children following the firebombing of Tokyo
Adidas
The saddest f****** anyone had ever watch and I got shot
How about this
What Studio Ghibli
Man we got to do that
Episode to go over and is coming out a little bit late
We were guarding this on Friday morning
And one of the reasons for that everybody thought it
It's the
Additional half a billion dollars Alex has to pay and punitive damages self
Stop
It's not that
Although
Fun off the lights
One point
5 billion almost at this point I mean if I'm if I'm the judge
You know I am writing that number out I'm writing the Fire or the four and then the other phone
For and then I'm thinking of that time that Alex put a picture of me with flames in my eyes
And then I'm writing
Yeah it's it's quite an amount
I am interested to see where this goes but that is not why we needed to delay things because today we're covering Alex's
Star-studded midterm Alfred know it was not star-studded
All the stars were there
I'm waiting for him to get Chris Pratt I feel like we're not far away.
Today is the day
How did this get made
No today it's a bunch
Bunch of dorks complaining about them
Will enjoy that and watch that go down
But man it yeah it's a
Who
It was long but we're only at soccer
About the beginning of the covering and then the time that Alex is there cuz Alex checks out goes home
Alexander and Owen Shroyer
Post and take calls out man MMA just replay Alex's show from earlier in the day
Interview with David Icke
And a hookah
But we went out of business on this
Let's say hello
Thank you very much
Grim Reaper thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Wilfred snipple Pitbull gnome artificer of Clan crippled people thank you so much
Thank you very much. Joining the marathon knowledge fight at Mile 25 thank you so much
Thank you very much
You are now policy walk
Very much and Miguel
Thank you very much so
Hey guys
Just woke up from a five-month coma how many mustards are we at thank you so much
Rude
Adam you're the best brother Richard could ever ask for but Jordan and I love you very much thank you so much
You are now what time
I have
Risen above
A little breaking for me
And then we're going
Comeback
And I'm going to
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for
The end of the day
F*** you in your new world order
She rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
And you never see me again
I never want to come
That's what Adam he is not better tomorrow Alex is not better he sucks
He's not great yeah you know I really figured this was the time for him to step up if he was going to
The mint
Midterm
Marathon
Alex 4 months has been saying is going to be a false flag
Before the midterm
Midterm coverage and I mean we're now on the other side of it so we know that it was not
Very eventful even
No as a midterm
There's obviously Democrats over performed or the GOP underperformed however you want
Want to look at it maybe both maybe combination of both
Which leads to
A smaller GOP Victory than would have been
Expected in a midterm election such as this where
The Democrats
Goodwin the previous general election
And that's not very exciting no I mean it did feel like the American electorate
Sounding
Keep doing the exact same thing
Yeah it's
It was a
Knock things not great maybe we're not super
Satisfied with the way the Democratic party is operating but also not
Pissed off enough
The gop's going to gain ground yeah I think what it really shows his everybody's mad at both parties
Nobody wants
Anyone doing any more presents the population generally as a whole is more mad at Trump
That world is a positive sign
When you get there at least you got
It's a positive sign that you're not needed see like an overwhelming
Cascade of like
All of these
Like Fringe as candidate
Rising into positions of Marjorie Taylor Greene did win
I know that we talked a little bit about the possibility that she could have a competitive race check look like there wasn't
Possibilities both in the primary and in the general but you know
I thought I didn't come to pass
Democrat underperformed it was a giant
Pro Republic
Can District
It's not the biggest surprise in the world
Certainly unfortunate
But
I do like that our future Speaker of the House can only really Screech
More than
I don't think she's going to be this week
What are the Dynamics
That goes sort of unexplored on
On Infowars is that the lesser the margin of
Like
I ate like
Power
Univivi fewer people they have above 50%
The greater the power of people like Margie
Become
And that's because there's ignored entirely and Infowars analysis
Maybe they do maybe they don't certainly it's not
Rodger Stone has been very clear about
He said in the past like you don't want a
Giant Republican
You want a small win
And specifically the people that we know are crazy
We wanted them to win
Cuz then they'll hold greater amounts power but that message seems to have not gotten through
Do like Alex and Owen the best example of this maybe history is the Democrats
We're very very excited
The two have won the Senate
And then immediately they discovered that
They did not do anything even sort of close to that be
Because Joe manchin has more power than
Anyone in America
Dynamic is
Real
That's the fact that Alex has had to like
Do this show after screaming for months about like a false flag that never came
Is unfortunate
And then the second thing is this boring
Boring
It was a boring night
But what you'd expect at least be interesting on Infowars they wouldn't you would expect them to
To try
Acme in Harrison
In the info desk
Or whatever second Studio where they
Alex will throw it to Owen but I got talk about this County
If they have a map it should only be of the Confederate
Say it like that's what they're map should be like hey guess what Jefferson Davis is now though
Haha or a map of like
Hyrule
Over here in Tonto Village what they could have it it's like a five-person you know you have the five line
Mine's right and you have the little velcro faces that you attached to that and then we've got like
Soros weave
We've got
All those people in it like a horse race to see who's winning the most you know
I looks like Soros might have come out on top
I don't know who did but it is it's not us
Because here we go
Contacts dropped from Today Show
Ali you just
Mermaid swimming
The smart guy
I would say that olly Alexander is
Maybe the star
Cool
January 6th
He says it like this the first time in 15 years that he hasn't been involved in like campaign
Probably cuz of January 6th
But
I think that that
Is
Part of a desperation
That he has
I am so he's there the whole time
Oh no he's just lazy anchoring this this relay race
And Whispering I've got nowhere else to go underneath every
Not interested Charlie Kirk doesn't want me to lose
Not so the other right-wing f**** who are having the streams
This is about as good as it gets for Alexander at this point
So we start off and Alex is not there
Owen and Harrison
Are hosting the beginning of this cover it
We're back
Here
Infowars live
22 midterm
Election Harrison
Smith joins me in studio now at Harrison
I just had a little bit of
The belly laugh
Snooze
I should have waited for erda 212 no it is time now is the time. You haven't heard this get ready for a good laugh
Exact
Tweet
Are not broadcasting on his all-important election-night because unfortunately power is down in Los Angeles
How will we
Fill our cups
With their liberal tears
I don't know I it's it's a shame really I think
Everyone's being denied Irving Park
They're so excited for the liberal tears that are going to get to drink and now they've been deprived them
Because Young Turks
Not on air I do love
That American politics is absolutely completely devoid of any and all governments
And it's just like
Man
This election is going to be great cuz it'll make people feel bad
I want her to death so this is weird
Everything about Alex's world-building and Ameritas he's been selling for months
A power outage in the second largest city on in the US on Election night would probably be cause we're like this is a fall
Volkswagen accusation I'm willing to bet if it happened in an area that wasn't heavily blue at these Ding Dongs knew that
They had no chance of winning
This would be reported as proof of election fraud instead of some light-hearted news they're touching on to mock The Young Turks
They're reporting on a tweet The Young Turks posted that said quote slight delay with the start of Young Turks tonight
We'll create out here wants to show his live were experiencing a power outage but
The team is on it so we can deliver you the progressive perspective on midterms 2020
This was at 5:19 p.m. central
They plan to go live at
5 and they were up in broadcasting by around 6
Stuff happens as the crew of Infowars can clearly attack
And also by the way this is what we just listened to from Harrison is after set
So oh my God poor probably already live broad power outage in LA
Play that night is probably really local to their Studio maybe even just their build
It might have been some other Tech issue that they were calling a power outages shorthand to who knows
Anyway they did do their show there weren't a ton of liberal tears
40in and Harrison to mock but
Matt gaetz did show up to a painful interview where he tried to minimize his sexual assault allegations by saying that more
People that accused of biting than him which is a good.
No
How
That's a human response
Right from a human being
Murdered less people than that guy but I'm not really a murderer
Cool
So you see here this Glee that Owen and Harrison are putting out because they're convinced they're about to get ahead of their favorite drug
Which is seeing people they don't like in pain
Hey comes out really vividly every election and I do have to make it clear this isn't just some kind of joy and seeing that you have
Defeated your opponent
Political sadism
That's disgusting
So Owen
Is a guy
.
That's true
But if you want to describe him he's a guy who likes
To be thorough
With his investigation
He's not the kind of person who will take other people's words for things
He goes out and does his own exit polling
I don't know I feel like we have him sitting under oath that he's a puppet
No no puppet here when is an exit poll
Did you vote
Today
What was your experience
45 minutes waiting in line at went pretty smoothly it. No more conservative
Not
Probably went after you got off this morning
That's because I went
First thing in the morning
And I got in within 20 minutes
Experience
Free time I figured I'll me drive around and look at all the rest up
The polling location
I may or may not have made it to yours I think you might be just south
Technically
The areas I went to
Were you would vote in my disc
I think you might be in a
District
I was amazed at the low voter turnout
I was amazed
With the law
Voter turnout
It seemed like lines barely out the door
And the only places where I saw long lines
Where when I got
Traditionally more Conservative Republican areas
It did look like lines 100 200 300 people out the door but the Democrat
The Democrats are voting Republicans are all out in full force
Natalia
I drove around.
So convinced
Bet he's right and Harrison can look at somebody and tell how they're going to vote
If they look Democrat
What's good for the future is whenever fascist
Identify People based on looks
Classify them based on what we know that Alex can see demons in people see there we can look at the
Future future historians will say that they were not demons
Yes
Calls before Alex shows up from Oklahoma
The wind goes rushing to the plant that's what we do
Also it's a place where election
And fraud is happy
I want to take a quick call
Bill in Oklahoma
Build your own Infowars
Midterm election night coverage go ahead
Ariston
If you are
Receiving this
Transmission
Assistant
I'm in Oklahoma
1:45
Videos today
My experience
10:30 this morning
And the Machine
Already messing up
And I got it
Video
Woman
Machine
I've been messing up
Through early
Boarding and everything
And
The woman
Talk about what
What year
Balaton
Dropbox
That's kind of odd female song went back
Bet the machine tour
Still messy
Another video
Call worker
Editing
The woman
And she's like yeah
Nullify Ballot or change domain
Baba blah
Oklahoma
Are you putting it out
Social media
Fox News
Call
Don't have a lot of
FTP
Want to look up the video
Buy Rumble
What county is
W
Dirt
Rks
Took awhile to find this guy's account cuz he doesn't articulate his letters very well right but eventually I got it and I watch the tube
Videos you posted anything other than it was a humid
In Oklahoma
Which is part of what the poll worker told him was the cause of
The tabulation machines being down
I'm not even sure if I trust her expertise on it
Being the reason but who knows
Just one video that 20 and then the second video is where a poor worker is explaining to him that if a ballot
Through the reader and there's a
An error
The voter cam nullify that ballot in fill out a new one but they have to sign off on that process
The voter has
Decide that
The area that's most often picked up appears to be over voting
Where the machine doesn't read which candidate the voter pic in a certain rate
The poll worker has the ability to override this
With the voters
Consent
And the Machine wouldn't count all the other vote
Cast but in that race no vote will be tabula
And again
This is something that the voter has to sign off
This is a video of very kind and patient lady explaining to this caller how they deal with the tech at polling place
Discredit he doesn't act like an Infowars caller is pulling play some he's very polite
But he's also secretly recording these people for the purpose of accusing them of voter fraud on a national radio show
So you still kind of a piece of s***
Yeah so there's that also Oklahoma is an almost comically Republican state
And all of the elections he could possibly think these folks are trying to steal worth
Very safe.
There wasn't a voter fraud conspiracy but if there was one
It would not
Involve Oklahoma
I can guarantee that
How many ballots did after a f****** fraud
Make tube how suspicious it would be if
Some big race in Oklahoma everybody from f****** Northern Central Illinois
To Oklahoma
At once
Yeah yeah
It's
The humidity
According to this poll worker
Which might actually be another can
I mean do I have to pay
Pull up
The humidity numbers
On my app
AccuWeather deal here
I was prepared to cover all the numbers with the voting results
Coming in I didn't know I had to pull up
Humidity numbers here
This morning
This morning in my town
Where I live that
Bright
Okay
Mentioned earlier that
Cloud seeding
Cloudy
Call Aguirre till
Last night
I don't know if they were cloud-seeding last night they have been doing some of that lately but it was
I was hoping to see the eclipse
Pretty much
Didn't see anything after a
After about midnight
Facetious but this caller is not
If I understand correctly
This caller believes that there are weather weapons
Sunset were deployed specifically in his area of Oklahoma
To raise the dew point
Thereby causing voting machine error
So
That the GOP could win everything
But this is the level of discourse
We're seeing here on the known about how
How damaging it is to the voting system in all of this stuff to claim that there's so much for voter fraud
We know all of this but one thing we don't take into account
It's just how much
Time they have wasted of people
Who have good faith
Like he's like I'm going to there
Politely
I don't think he has good faith
He's he has good faith in terms of investigating the thing that they've told him
The problem
Good faith
In communicating
Is because
Who's he
The dewpoint and then came up with a
Conspiracy explanation
For why the dew point was I that really is crazy
Define
No matter what piece of information and you end up
Cyclic
The person at the pool her explanation of the like the humidity causes them
Machines to act up a little bit
It makes the paper softer or whatever right
If he was investigating that you would have found the dewpoint been like that it's cute
Then his next step would have been seeing if the machines actually are affected by humidity or if there is something there
There
Baseless nonsense about Chinese weather weapons making it humid
How would you not go immediately to that that was my fur
First.
You might have more in common with old bills and
Viewpoint today in Illinois
Sure whether weapons
How's that related to the election
So like I said this is an All-Star star-studded affair
Oh my God
Pulling out the big guns are we going to see the new judge the dude is not in play
We met Laura Loomer on the line with us
And
Probably around 7
Central hour
With other great gas Steve Bannon more will start to get the numbers in I'll be going to the big board
As well
Again folks
What's the numbers coming in for Warnock
Lock in the Atlanta Tri-County area
I think it's what we expected to happen there in Georgia we're going to be monitoring that close
But
I think it's going to be
Florida I don't think the Democrats around
Unfortunately they like to try to
Cheap Laura Loomer out
Being involved
In congress with all the cheating they do there
But I think they're going to
Sit this one out
I think they're going to let De Santa
Just win big on Xavier
Who's going to win big
Laura Loomer joins us now though
Laura what's the vibe in Florida
Who got Laura Loomer on the ground
When you want
Incisive
Insight
Reporting
From the ground
Pull out all the stops
You get yourself
One of the Marquee reporter
Somebody who has
Never
Spent money
Trying to cover the Las Vegas shooting
As a can
Conspiracy
What someone who has never
Handcuff yourself to the door of Twitter
Cuz she got kicked off Twitter
And forgot to handcuff yourself to the other door
As your on-the-scene reporter
Laura f****** Loomer Jesus
You know you do
I just got to get the loom
And she weaves it together the way you need it
Alright
I I I mean I get it
There aren't other options
There were a lot of right-wing Charlie Kirk
Bannon
Crowder
So they were there was a there were a lot of people who are probably already booked
Places
Rodger stone is supposed to be on here and I don't think he even shows up he was over with the Lyndell
Ron Frank's beat is getting more money on
See me the any money
He will take
Any money video with Laura Loomer Ally Alexander
Steve Bannon I'll legitly
I will see you at plays out
I'm at Alex not even there for the first hour cowboy
But he does show up
I got a little bit of low energy when he shows up
Call the same in every key Battle Ground area of the country Italy seventh day
Shutdowns and stuff Dallas
Infowars
That's what you got you doesn't demonstrate any of those things either the machines breaking down or
Stuffed ballot
He doesn't he just says that that's happening there aren't examples of
Prove any of this
It's just taken as gospel you just say it and it is Drew
Wild
For him though is that all of his Goods
Stuff happens
Before the midterm
It's not the actual Alexa
Forehead mean
It's not the who wins or loses
Is that interesting on Infowars
It's what they're going to do to stop it
It's the Schrodinger's midterm
It happens it's kind of a letdown the ballot boxes like we knew they were going to your argument
Already pre-loaded and like your coverage is kind of predetermined same arguments from 2020
Arguments from 2018
26 that we've been here you think they seal Alexa
Because you're a loser
I get it
Sewing a little bit of a little Grassroots
Guess what
So did Alex
Confirming each other's results
All right what we know is that
And I don't just go out to Paul's the numbers Nebraska
CC
I went home and
Took my wife and daughter out to dinner. Mom that a restaurant
By Lesnar
Agreed
Nothing but love
Was Mom
Like I was Elvis
Stop bragging
Samsung powerful guy
Is the Black Sea
The rebel
Nothing but love in Liberal
Austin Texas
Take me from
My house
About
Appointment
The office
50 minutes
Traffic
Oh and I forgot
Before that
This afternoon I went to vote
Student line
5 minutes
As well I've never seen line five.
And almost everybody I talk to
Was voting
Republican and
If you were loading libertarian
Very few are voting Democrat
That's a leftist
Austin TX
I mean even ABC and news and others
Tried to go
The place is like Miami there
60 + percent Democrat
Couldn't find anybody in exit polls
Political Bloodbath
This is a
Political realignment
At 7
Certainly Alex is Riding High on these expectations of a political Bloodbath
Oh that's not going to be good
I don't want to get anyone's hopes up it doesn't leave till like a freak out or anything it's just
Motivate
Coasting downward
And like Alexander is if nothing else
A self-styled political analyst
She knows everything about the
These district courts and all of this
Answer when he is on the show he's talking numbers
He's talkin aquinos candidates named simile of actual election coverage
Bores the s*** out of out course it does
Election coverage
So it's
Like to see this just like
This is a an attempt to be like a actual news outlet and Alex is
He might as well be asleep
Does does
30000 mail-in ballots were just officially counted in the exit polling suggests that almost
60% of them what Democrats how exciting with that
Well it's demon
Yeah that's where I was
That's where I want to be
Be honestly
Is it the analysis desk he's over by the Big Mac
And
So here is
Owens first attempt at being a big boy election Journal
He sucks at this
Let's go.
Pennsylvania
Determinism
Philadelphia County
We know what goes on in Philadelphia
2%
You never see
A number line
I want to elaborate
I'm seeing massive red waves
Just in the numbers were
Saying
Republican
Block the boat you know that's
Strategy in the mail in
What
What are you looking for
Just like with bolsonaro in
Brazil to correctly use they are clearly stepping it
And I'm going against
What's the poll number show up
What are you saying are you saying Republicans
Not take the house and send it tonight
Steal the house
Because
You have all these different
District
Why
What you were just a
Is date
In Philadelphia
So this is the kind of thing you hear when you have an idiot like onfe voting analysis test
He's a person has absolutely no interest in or knowledge about historical voting patterns so he couldn't even credibly say wow
Whether or not fetterman getting over 90% of the vote in Philadelphia county is in line
With past election
In reality Philadelphia County contains two
Congressional district
Pennsylvania second and third District
The second district is a Democrat + 25 district and went 72.9% to Clinton and 24
4.9% to Trump
In 2016
And the spread was even wider
For obama-romney
However the Third District is Democrat + 41 District
A+ and neither Romney nor Trump even got over 10% of the vote there
Pennsylvania's 3rd District has won the most democratic voting district in the country in cooked
Partisan index their latest analysis they were only behind Maryland
Which is just outside DC
In California's 12th which includes Oakland and Berkeley
Pennsylvania third is a more strongly Democrat area
San Francisco
Chicago and pretty much all of LA and New York
Owen doesn't know these things that he doesn't know that
It seems early returns like the ones he's talking about Jimmy totally
Expect it
Because he's stupid and uninformed
You take this very normal phenomenon
And translates it into a
Conspiracy
Also fetterman didn't end up with that high of a share of the vote in Philadelphia County
Have the time that I Was preparing this is when was only at
What about 82.1%
Which actually represented over performance there by dr. Oz
Notice how I'm commenting on how others got more votes than one might have expected but somehow I'm not implying that that's the result of an
Various conspiracy
Crazy
I wish that we
Had this
On MS
Just
Just somebody who's completely uninformed
What everybody's
Everybody else is
Very aware what's going on and this person just shows up
And they're like
A republican is winning in Oklahoma
These Liars what's this
They split Dakota into North and South
Attitude just to get more representative something is up
South Dakota
Going to North Dakota or is it like it is it like the northern Irish wall
Is that what we're dealing with here so it has no idea what he's talking about as it relates to Philadelphia County
That it becomes a focal point of all of his coverage throughout the entire night
To facilitate that he just has to make s*** up
Can you talk at Philadelphia County
Obviously Philadelphia
And normally you looking
Weather radar
You're looking at about a 6
To 70%
Maybe
Clipping
60 probably
16 presidential
2020 presidential
About a 90% clip
In Philadelphia County
Pittsburgh
Owens is making s*** up like he's lying to the audience because he wants to pretend
He's just like the adults on the news channel actually read up on these things
All windows facts and Trends but they're just made up
Philadelphia County went for Biden 81 points
4%
The trumps 17.9
The senate race results are exactly in line with what you would expect there from past historical patterns but Owens invested in
Constructing a voter fraud narrative
That he's willing is willing to make sure it up
To strengthen his clients that's how desperate he is to
Create his false reality
To Overlay real real
Right there aren't even details to fudge
Come up this whole cloth
Yeah 60% is the most
Based on all the stuff that I have read which is not nothing
Stuff I think about
My mind is Alex
So that means in the intervening time. I must have Reese
Search that
Clearly
Why would I just make something up that seems absurd
Show
Ally shows up
Call Holly Alexander the house album
Until the wee hours
Is a great political analyst Uno
Pandora Jewelry stop running today
Communist
Giveashare
Yuan
The anomaly
Numbers you're saying
What year
Analysis
Right now it's too early to tell but
Holly Alexander thanks for being there
Thanks for having me out
Starrcast I'm really excited
Hiiraan
Infowars and I think they were going to be able to call Raisa
Before the rest of
All-star cast to be able to call races
Before everyone else is I don't know exactly if there before anyone else would they have a couple of things that are accurate
We believe that the Warnock
Herschel Walker race
Who's going to come down to a run
And I don't know if that was
Before other outlets
Speculated on that boat
He may have been before other people
It's really funny how this election livestream includes two of the three people who made that b******* documentary where they went to Mini
Minnesota to accuse ilhan Omar being married to her brother
Laura Loomer and Allie Alexandra reunites
I'm sure Jacob Wohl would have been there if he wasn't laying low after pleading guilty to a voter intimidation election fraud scheme
Lately just recently
Sitting this one out
Is probably his best
Also fun fact
That documentary where they went to Minnesota and Tuesday. Omar being married to her brother that documentary is produced buddy website cult
3tees
Which Ali was heavily involved
Incidentally was a producer of the bulshit documentary Alex's War which is definitely just a fair down the middle slice of
Life character study about an interesting guy
What Greenwald said
What a bunch of dork
Anyway Owen
Rambling
Talkingshit
And then something a little chaotic happen
And I want to know
Not just from Alex in Hollywood
What they think about the
This new breed of a
What do you see going on with Pennsylvania now
Mehmet Oz has a large statue
Alexander
About 15 minutes, cash right now
With Steve Bannon his live coverage of the election
Take his feet until he introduces me to his
Now
A five-point lead and it shows you
How great
Canada
Seiko watch
Shermag
Right
Enforcement
Virginia
Oh yeah cut oh and also we can just not be ready to have you on Alex
Where your producers manso Steve bannon's not going to be on the show
But they're going to have Alex interviewed on bannon's show and they're just going to play that is if Ben Amazon
Yeah
Very different
They're not really in a rush to have Alex off
65% of the vote in
Member of the January 6th
Is down
No rush to get to Alex
Killing time
Do they know that Alex is what they have to know Alex
Is waiting and broadcasting on his show actually there trying to go to him but Alex's speed is
Bucked up
Oh the irony irony
Play John Cena's Denver
Control can you guys send audio or something
No it's msnbc's problem
This is not good
How am I going to get my people in 1.5 billion dollars of debt tears
You know what am I going to do with their with their audios bad
I can't hear
Subway
So they try to get this worked out and the producer of band and show is audible on Alex
The Stream
And they're trying to get the video feed worked out yet Alex is feeding back the Bannon show feeds
And
Has Alex on
Alex Jones
Tell us what you're saying is you look at it look at here
Cross this
Battle map
A tickling in your beloved state of
Texas down there in the Rio Grande Valley
Bluff Texas
Absolutely I want to talk about Texas
Looks like it's going for Democrats what is tonight goes on
And we always have I gone rattly since the time
Dwight D Eisenhower back in the 19
Pimply butt
You said Steve
Is absolutely On Target we have the whole corporate
Media
Big tackle Democratic Party
The rhinos
The neocon
Bullying the American people
The last two years
Find the drivers
This is a referendum
Against the power structure
The ragtag
American people in red blood of a race color and Creed
Come together
Until we want America back
Republic
We don't want the leftist critical race theory of the transgenderism
The open borders in the wars
Despite all the fraud
Call
Google manipulation all the Facebook manipulation and all
Manipulation
The pendulum is swinging back in a mighty mighty way and no matter how much fraud they throw at us
They can't stop a red tsunami
So I think we're going to see a major major victory
Tonight
Alex trying to make the most of his limited time the ban is going to give him until you can hear him
Jamming everything I ever thought it was a red salami
Little chorizo in there
Just a couple minutes and it's just like catchphrases
Is man it's ridiculous
And that's what this
Directions about
Rising to the challenge
Just like we beat Great Britain
250 years ago
Cost of the beginning
The second American Revolution intellectual corporate
Individual free-market religious
A Spiritual Awakening that is Unstoppable Renaissance 2.0
7076 44
Elsiane infowars.com
Breath
Take a short commercial break Ed Henry Steven K Bannon
Tired
Yep so it's just a couple minutes there
Simulcast
It's just Alex appearing on Panic show
Alex
Stream power imbalances very clear
Stitches Alex
Throwing up NeverEnding run-on sentences about the Public's awake and
Globalstar the Run
How is meeting with platitudes
It's tough to listen to send it so clearly Alex trying to make the most of the very little time but he's being offered on a more relevant
Show them his own
Like he's hanging out with olly Alexander Laura Loomer and Owen Shroyer
Like this is not
It's clear
Yeah I mean
It is funny that we're dealing with tears so obviously you know like
Alex
This is clearly subordinate to ban in
Ali Alexander clearly subordinate to Alex
Harrison Smith is under the ground somewhere he went to bed
We're supposed to be Manning the big board
But I think that
Because Harrison had done his show in the morning he been up since like
For something like that but they like you can go to bed
You can only do so much
You're right
He doesn't show on Infowars against upwards of two thousand viewers
Irrelevant yeah he is not exist
But yeah
And you know there's there's an interesting thing to admit like
Tim pool has a stream what's going on
Alex not welcome on that
That's not even a that's not even a consideration
Maybe you would be but he's not
Is that somebody the pool
Azan
Steven Crowder he probably could be on that he's been on crowder show but he's not
Nope
It's not on there
Banning has him on for a couple minutes
Charlie Kirk
Not a person talk about nothing
Alex's he's where he is
Rogan
Not coming
Bougie
That's more analysis got to go back to the big board
Big boredom analysis
That is a blue Mirage
The only chance
Is going to have here
Overwhelming numbers
Talking about
In major cities
And you can see
In Philadelphia
I mean that that is
Presidential election
Let's just see exactly what we're dealing with here
I do believe we're going to be okay
To the 2020 election results
To see the numbers in Philadelphia
Tri-County
And then as well
On my side screen over here
Right now
So let me just going to come in
Molly Alexander will come back to you in the Harrison Smith
Ali for a really harsh wake-up call if he finds those numbers
I'm not sure what Owen means when he says that fetterman is dominating in the Northeast
In the Northwest specifically Erie County but most of the North
Counties in the state of Pennsylvania are pretty red District
Wayne County Susquehanna County in Pike County all-arounder over 60% of Dr.Oz
But Federman had a good showing along the southeast of the state
Including Philadelphia and then up the eastern border
To Allentown in a little bit further north
He did over perform
In a number of
Red counties but they all still one
Pretty strongly
Ethiopia
Right I mean I understand
Cuz of the world we existed
Why it seems absurd
For any candidate to get more than 90% of the vote right
Crazy
Within the context of
Now
But if you were to tell me that a TV Doctor Who Lies to people for money
Is
Racing against a
Guy who works for a living
Ewing literally anything
Guy who works for a living get 90%
Over that
Instead of saying World Herschel Walker doesn't go to a runoff
He does
How old the reasons
Possible that there were like more Democrat votes
Open Wayne and Pike County is early on Northeast of the state doesn't seem like that would have been like blowout number
A Lego Anna saying
I don't really know what's going on here I think you've got the North
The northwest
Next up
Maybe that makes
Except is there brand
Is
Dangerous territory trying to look up
2020 and 2016 numbers against all of the rules that we have given them don't look
For the truth come on
If the producers had any sway they'll be like don't do it don't do it don't do it. Look at the numbers don't look at the numbers
But unfortunately does find them
She has what we're looking for
In most of the areas
Actually in Pennsylvania
Including the counties outside of Philadelphia
But you're not talking about
Ridiculous
In the past
Adelphia County
Is the 2020 election results
Philadelphia
I can't
Now give me Philadelphia County
I don't know why I
I can't get the Philadelphia
Bad audio
The number
Percent okay 91% right now
Just ignore the rest of the County's
1%
County
If you believe those
Popular
It's pretty amazing what just happened they're like this is you really have to understand that
Slam dunk Point yoga for looking into it at all he pulled up a past election
Salt from Philadelphia County
Totally expecting them to be 60% or so Democrat win
Unfortunately Biden won the county with over 80% which makes the numbers that sediment is putting up not really look that weird
I want as essentially debunked his own argument so instead of just accepting reality and that he was
Totally wrong about everything he's been saying
Owen says that it was an 81% Biden win in 2020 be
Cuz there was three hundred thousand fake palette
It really was actually like a 60% win if there is
If there is any more perfect encapsulation perfect
It's just what it is
You're not going to argue out
Yeah why even use that
What's the point of bringing up accounts from past elections if you're just going to make up your own numbers anyway it doesn't matter
I understand and accept that other media Outlets have a lot of fair criticism heading their way for their election coverage but this isn't a
League
If someone
Provide analysis on the election made
The fumble like Owen just did and then they had to make s*** up to try and save the ship they would not have that job much longer
No divorce though no one even cares enough to try know it Infowars if you say there's a conspiracy and then Pro
Prove yourself wrong
Do you know what your answer to that is
I didn't know it was an even bigger conspiracy
Multi-year confusing it fired if you don't keep
Election coverage version of posting your way through
Is so funny to me about all of this is it
Doesn't get better for like voter fraud isn't real argument then
The status quo just staying
Exactly the same after an election you know like
Who is
Stealing elections to stay the same
Could not win
You know like what kind of equilibrium of everyone's feeling so many like I connect
Actually answered
So to you it seems like a homeostasis
Static it is
And maybe that is the case
Reason that they steal elections to keep things static is B
Because
Alex and his crew are trying to
To take over the country and restore Liberty
That would be a drastic thing that
Is actually preferable to to the globalist
Preferred
To steal elections in order to just keep things
Kind of going along humdrum
As opposed to liberty rising
Interesting
Idea for them
Yep it's a bad one
It's not a winning strategy
No no it's kind of it's it's
Something they would probably not want to articulate
Yeah because it's no sound
Really because it is beneath like a lot of their Theory know sometimes when people are like
The way we have
To win
Is Toulouse
And you're like
Maybe that's
I guess the plan
This time you're like
That's a really dumb
Sure
So so it looks a little bit more into the numbers coming out of Philly or Pennsylvania 3rd District
Right around there in Philadelphia County
I need to Claire's this
Impossible
I'm they were stopping right now gop's out
40 seats Democrats have
16 of 35 seats
Have been called so far so still some to go but
It looks like they were completely off
And what would you
Excited about something
Get this
Hero
In a in a district
White people
Explain what you just
I'm talking about
County
This is where the Democrat
In the morning
On the 2020 election night we all went
Why
Normally win by 6
In those
Directions
The Democrats.
And I believe
Spider-Man
And
Shapiro
Intense
Sylvania
Even though
A 90%
County
Is Ludacris
It's absurd
It's an impossible
Listen up
It's impossible
I don't understand
If his own
Is a normally Wendy's by 60 to 70%
Wipeout itself
Well because the Maga Republicans are to power
They're going to overcome that sixty-two 70% clip
Everyone likes to say until they have to they have to stuff the ballot in order to keep that
70% but if that were the case
Then they would have won by 60 to 70%
Maybe they overdid it
Beersy
Whoops guys we accidentally
Book stuff too many valves all stuff balance
Look up the mules were drunk
Play a little crazy
A big problem have
The North Korean boat
Finally got there
Maybe that's why Rodger wasn't on investigating a boat
So Alex's mother Gaston
I'm telling you a big gun
Hernandez in while you doing analysis
Your house in the next 5-10 minutes I'm going to rub you I want you to be able to lay out
What you're saying what you think's going on
Open Arizona
Arizona
Something we need to pay attention to
We still.
For all that
Patient begins
A mountain
All day
Arizona
Isn't embarrassed
We got Drew Hernandez the baby reporter
5 to 10 minutes
So at the time of my preparing this episode
Cinderseal votes
But there's only 71% about scouted so there could be some motion there
Three of the house seats are safely one by the GOP into by democrats with four that were still up to be called
Kari Lake a real dumb dumb is currently losing to Democrat Katie Hobbs
Who's in the governor's race which also is only a little over 70% of the ballots in
I think the baby reporter Drew Hernandez here is correct they should keep their eyes on Arizona and then claim all of them
Results are fake when they don't like what they see
Games being played here
Man it is all you got to do
All you got to do is be on TV for a while and then somebody's like yeah you could be in Congress
That's so it
That's all you need
You got to get on TV don't know I just don't know man I just don't know
So Alex is going to predict
Robots
Volkswagen
Surprise
Others red wine. Let's go back
False flag
They wouldn't have VIP are they wouldn't have the insurance
MSN
BC Crowell they wouldn't have seen anyone that make that
Tanger Republicans are violin
They're going to shoot and kill them both Step Up
When they lose
They wouldn't have sold that whole narrative
They weren't planning
The pre-programming in
I'll talk to Mike Adams about that the moment
Hernandez your take on that
It's either they will go forward
Something like that
Or they just leave it as a
Play a10e
They want ohyeah okay so maybe false flags are coming or maybe they're not but they could
It's the classic 50/50 chance would happen or it could not
Genius stop
Totally
Also like Adam
I'm coming up oh no what a f****** all-star cast
Can escape any one of these days everybody is there it's like Smash Brothers
It is the crossover event of the century
And Alex
Forgot wallet
I'm telling you right now you have no idea
Up next
Ash catcher
Well yeah
He's finally going to predict them
My next guest that big ham
I didn't play a lot of Smash Brothers I don't know any other names
Captain Falcon is joining us from Florida
That's a good one
You got it all right
The Ice Climbers
Climber's that was later on
Box
Starbucks
Kirby just walks
Kirby's another one
I don't know I don't think so
Kirby
Kirbyville
Circle yes
Oh yeah that's right
Oh wow I forgot about it one of the first off I remember the formica super early out of the the 64
Cuz you could never get rid of him cuz he could
Float no that was Jigglypuff
They're both in it
Now got a roll there I don't know anything anymore
I don't know anything anymore
I I want to we're going back to
The coverage here but I just remembered something that I meant to say the top of the show and
Big bears mentioning that is our last episode about Alex's deposition
Made fun of a little bit they doodling and
It's been brought to my attention the folks who have ADD
Search stay
Sometimes it doesn't help them Focus
Doodle and I did not mean to beep
Pejorative or make fun of folks who are who are in that
I mean to me but that's the case with Alex
That in a deposition and I like when I'm talking
To my with my wife
She's already she's drawing all the time and it helps our focus and she has ADHD
You did not mean to malign anybody
The case for that I just also don't think that's the case for Alex
And other childish behaviors that key and bodies also sort of factor into the way I was
Describing that anybody took that
And way that I did not intend that we were not denigrating
So now you're back to someone I do want to denigrate and I've known for
You want to tell people
She's about to go bad with love
And they're going to get crazy
Sure
You just got to keep your your steady
What the establishment and the American left
Is about to go through in this psychotic break
Is going to be in
Message would just be
When the American Life Starts have psychic
Across this country
And you stabbed
It can be very
And we maintain our steady
That balance
Because we are winning we are taking
The country in the planet back
Right now
Huge
Herschel Walker is now
Great news
Eoin
You know
I personally
Don't think that's running with the ball is
Government material
And in fact I would say this 20K in the in the 60s or whatever it was I don't remember
Isaac Newton was in Portland
Elected Isaac Newton to Parliament you know why
He's a famous genius
He was not a good legislator their skills
People who like play sports even professionally don't have
Potential leadership
Possibilities capabilities
It is it is entirely possible it doesn't
Is maybe not
Miracle part of the resume
But also Herschel Walker sucks
So any number of reasons
Yeah whether or not he was a football player
Anyway Mike Adams
Our guy
Is on
And he has a very ironic
Thing to say
If
Party were made up of rational reasonable
Humanity driven
And they were too
Suffering tonight
Engage in introspection
What's wrong with her message
That will not happen
Because there's
Sociopath
They love
To control you they love
To rule over
We are tyrants
They are child mutilators
Bears
You dumb f*** storm the capital don't know what else to say
Beyond
Talk for the last 2 years about the election being stolen
Andrew storm
The capital
And not just that but if you want to if you're sore losers these Democrat
Then what you were talking about was what happened
In 2008 after Obama won by such
Huge margin of Victory everyone on the Republic at all GOP operas or like we need to have a
Analysis of the selection of
Totally the whole thing and instead of being like we need to appeal to more people
They were like we should get more races
Best got Betty party shade is going to be really helpful
The sociopathic response
Right right
Yeah I just love
The idea that
When you lose an election
It is time to assess like we did in 2020 I mean just insane
Call Mike
So anyway there's another Mike that has been Vindicated
It is not Michael Jordan
Is that Michael B
Be Jordan
Is Mike Lindell
But you know if anybody tonight
It's Mike Mendel
Because
Voting machine coin
Because we've seen
Mail-in ballots and all that
Double back on the machines and sucker punches
Michael David indicated B
Because the machines get even if they're not
Maliciously programmed in any way whatsoever
Just the fact that they can be
There can be problems
Problems
So Michael and Bell is Vindicated because sometimes mushy
Beams don't work
I didn't listen to round with pillow
But maybe he's been Vindicated I don't know maybe it was a good pillows I've never I've never
Yeah I don't see how it could possibly be worthwhile Aztec not my pillow
I don't know if
A pillow could be comfortable enough
For me to look past
All of the other thing
Thanks I don't know if that's a possible
Yeah well I mean your sleep half your life
That's true
Maybe it's that important so Alex
Has the Beast Gaston
Hey does a crew of loser
But he looks at it
Corset
Alex
Alright I'm going to give
Are the smartest people I know these are all
Already had Mike Adams
Already add bananas on already had
Rodger Stone coming up
Comeback
Come back with Robert Barnes
Constitutional lawyer
I got a lawyer
Historian good friend of mine
All the smartest people Alex knows are idiots
I I mean
Wow
Damn
Barnes comes on
And he's a little Alex's dramatic
Coming back from break
I got to say Barnes
Pretty boring but reasonable take
Okay on the elect
The song it's great that's is boring
I expected
Exactly where I want to be in this fight
And I'm so proud of
Who are they
Bikers are proud of you
But you're informed involved
What historic day
A urinalysis
The way it is
The outages the bizarre behavior
What's happening you got the floor
I think our Republicans still have an excellent
Chance to take
The house tonight
Also take the Senate tonight
Also take that at least
Some governorship
Across the country that were in Democratic hands
Before tonight
Pretty boring but measured
Pretty just a Barnes coming in with
Hey here's the answer to your question
And I was given that whole speech over what would amount to like the supervillain
Music
Your ancestors are priority
That's car speed from The Lion King
The song We're choosing who will punish them for what they did to the hyenas
Whoopi Goldberg
And also if it's like
Keep saying all this stuff about like
These outrages and said what
Philadelphia County
Great
Barnes ism
Complaints
I still like the chances
Is Adam laxalt in Nevada
I still like the chi
Lakemaster
Actors in Arizona
I still think when the night is done and tomorrow
Counting ballots I guess until Saturday or Sunday apparently loved
M2
Harry Reid's Nevada.
Picture of a boating
Harry Reid died last
You're pretty sure he was dead
I don't know what you have to do with it
Yes I've been in Congress since like 2017
I don't know why because of Harry Reed's involvement in like some of that
He was a target of
Fire during the Bundy
Stop and so maybe it's just like
Lip service to talk about Nevada.
Battery lasted for like 30-40 years or something so yeah
He's tough.
Forgot he is dead
Yeah that's true
Probably has nothing to do with the counting the ballots this service cycle
Probably probably
Do we get another gas
Haha
Is pretty excited
Amazing let me just say something I noticed they just did The Joe Rogan
Shining blood coming out the elevators
Stanley Kubrick
And you're sorry what
The movies in
Work with her dad and she's an amazing rain
Another for about
14 years
13 years or so
She's making a long-term documentary
Whiter
See that down the road
A long-term documentary
Richard linklater
Calling the kids of their life
But she's here
I'm roping her in
Is done
Where to put the chair in interview Vivian Kubrick
What is the soundtrack
For Full Metal Jacket
And so much more
If she's making a long-term documentary that it all involves like being at Infowars Studio
I mean
It's going to have to be completely detached from reality
Like the
The stuff that you would have to have captured over the course of that time the
Complete change in perspectives the arguments falling
Copart the b*******
Did people really believe in that they pretend they didn't believe in like six months later
Like it's going to be
Like I really am
It's going to be an editing Channel
To make sense out of all of their life
Yeah 2001
What's she's actually going to do is prove that the moon landing was
She really resents that
Soundtrack to
She doesn't like it when people accuse her father of being involved in taking the moonlight.
People's voter fraud bucker
I don't know well I think that she does believe that but you might not make those direct accusation
On this episode
Becoming
The first
More bar
Critically along the way
Bet the
Tip of the spear
Entire process
The only thing that made
Any
Republican victories tonight possum
Only thing that made any resistant
To the warmest machine
The only thing that made
Any opposition
Another lockdown
The mask
School shutdowns
In the fourth vaccines and the dangerous gift Leavenworth hotels
Any resistance to it
Was people continuing
Support info
The massive loss
Being weights again
The only thing that is facilitated or enabled first of all any Republican victories in the midterms
Any opposition to any democratic
Label thing
You giving money to Alec
Yeah I think
Boring saw Alex's mood was like I bet if I give this guy a handjob he'll feel a little bit better
I think I enjoyed it a bit but
Not enough to keep him around much longer cuz I was going to bail your pretty soon
But before that there's a
Little bit of news
Alex's court case
He doesn't talk about himself much
Does not cover himself with no
He comes up in a new cycle he's the tip of the spirits about the Sphere not the
Right
That much
A judge said in court yesterday
Jazz.
Alex Jones
It'll be on the top of Google
Judd says it's
2 points
Trillian enough
Jupiter Jones
Bad things he's doing what's your all made-up insane
I watch that hearing
Knows because of norm
Play good no amount of money
Was trying to sort of
Facilitated by his own lawyer
He's he was basically daring them to
Give me to trillion
Not quite what he was doing the saying it shouldn't be really high because no amount of money would
The enough shut up Alex so why even make it really high
Albie Alex's barely
Whatever she's a little bit of a dare
If you say no amount of money will stop him
We'll see if yeah we'll find out what way
So
Alex is not
It really feeling this all too much he's going to bail here pretty soon
By the way Barnes you been successful for
Superstar now
Your little mean to me you're hard to get on these days so
Is the next few days
Come on at least for 30-40 minutes
With the aftermath of this exact tell the producers when you're coming on
Either Wednesday or Thursday or Friday
Cuz you better
Come on
And I love you.
Appreciate you
Your brother and you're so awesome
Thank you
Putting my Citizens Voice says it
We just are like insane
We love you
Come back on soon we're going to go
Owen Shroyer and olly Alexander
Vivian Kubrick
In studio
Straight ahead and then
I'm going to let all the
Callers on
Owen and Ollie's
As long as they want to go your life never took a ton of calls earlier
Your calls are coming up
We right back there with a Snickers bar
Better not take Atomic calls earlier and Alex's basically checked out because this is not been exciting for him and nothing's really
Happening
Get hubris kind of
Call energized
Is doing the Philadelphia County stuff early on
But that ran out of steam a bit
It was a fail but now he is kind of a celebrity and cube roots.
F*** this take calls
Why would you
There's no reason to be there
So but yeah I was trying to go to break here
But he he's caught off-guard by
Your calls are coming up
Alright
What
No no we're going to get to it
Came back
Plant before and after
All the judging Connecticut
And the lawyers
This is really really important
Let's go ahead and
Yesterday at the hearing with the judge
She said she's seizing all my ass
Worth it
I get it
Yep I got it
Nailed it any call Barnes a cutie pie
I don't think I don't know what that was in reference
Wants to I don't I don't know what that was
I've tried to I tried to let go back in like
Really isolated and I got
No idea
Maybe his wife or somebody is there I don't know
Maybe Harrison
Maybe Barnes Issaquah
But yeah that joke
He has used that
Joke a lot yet it is tired
He needs to shelve it
He keeps doing the same
Thing 2
Keep doing the Wicker
OMG
Clint plays
Allah
It gets into a
I think it even goes into another scene
Just because the players show me ways to go
You can go at home
Hocus Pocus powder Goodwin hocus-pocus
Yeah that's right
They can do without more modern Hocus Pocus
You could go with what's another which movie
Macbeth
Any episode of Sabrina the Teenage Witch that's a good one
Which Finders
Haha ghostwriters
Now I'm just naming
Childhood TV
Ghostwriter
Writer with a w
Ghostwriters
Apology
Yeah
Come on I watch that
So Alex has his big Marquis gas
Restaurant we've got Vivian Kubrick
Daughter of Stanley and Amanda million
Who was the director of that plot against
The president movie
Right which is a shity piece of trump propaganda
And I also little fun fact
That document or that plot against President
That was produced
By John Eisenman
And some of the other producers
Who made Alex
What is war
So
That's all that's all
It's all connected also if you forgot from earlier episode that guy John eisaman also I was involved in sending
The Galley Alexander Laura Loomer Jacob Wohl
Do I Minnesota to claim the Elon Omar was married to her brother
End
Just
F****** above the board
Straight
Fact-based
Unbiased
Dispassionate documentary film
If you're a producer who's on your fourth lie documentary
Sunnyway Theron
Comebacks you guys here in about 30 minutes
We're going to be also
Talking to a very very special guest
In studio
And Amanda Miller
Another special
Contact me where to come out about 30 minutes
She's a great filmmaker on right and her dad
Roatan help Meg
Apocalypse
Now Dirty Harry
John Miller
Wow wow
These daughters
These icons here
But I got to say who eclipses
John Ellis
Well Stanley Kubrick
We've got his daughter here who I drafted to come on
He's got her camera
You want to have it
Still alive and get the
Jarhead said everything else
And of course he is Vivian Kubrick
Who was the Protege of the greatest
Hands down
Stanley Kubrick
Great to have you here knowing you for
15 years or so
You're amazing
So a picture of Vivian Kubrick with her headlamp and giron
Went viral
Twitter Ben Collins
Treated at Andrews like things are going well over on Infowars
It is kind of a surreal image person with a head camera on but I think
It was unfair that context was absent
I'm from it that like
You know it make
Since it's not
Insane as it seems
Define shitpost
Stonebank calling
But I think it might have given the impression that things were like more out of
Control on Infowars than they really work
But that's in Fort Worth
You know how many makes
It's their fault that it's very easy to believe there was that time when I was at a llama
Find studio and
Things were a little out of control
Hatchet about it wasn't a pleasant a play I'm sorry once you get the hamburger
Now I'm lost now
Civilian
Big fan
Infowars
Thank you Alex
I have to say
Infowars
Set of a bit like a
It's seriously I've been so
What is down right now
Probably for 18 years now
And I would say that
Pedigree
You truly have been
So
Truthful
Correct
I'm on the bowl
And Far Beyond
Is ever reported on what
Actually got on this planet
Well I tried to be
Overall
I really appreciate
You
Just want to say that everyone here at Infowars
I mean I can tell you from being around here a little bit
Bring me dedicated to what they doing that
Amistad
As extreme is Alex in many ways
An education
Hangout
But I do want to really underlined
But you have to have Lyft
Listen to Alex
Liscio's
He said over the years
To really understand how much
He does so much
Small in space
So deeply about
Warren Way
Nicolas Cage
Beaches
The mainstream media
About him if he
There's no question about that
I'd say he's an imperfect
Messenger
What he has done
Is I would say this
I'm sure
Spearheaded
Patrice movement on this
TriNet
Wow
That's
I mean look
I do agree with her premise slightly the picture of Alex as a cartoon character who yells his
Is not accurate
But
I would say he's much
Worse and Dumber and more malicious than the character and she's saying that he's so insightful
Speaks to deep truths
Then I think that's horseshit
And I say that with the pedigree of somebody who's
Almost at 750 f****** long podcast episodes analyzing him
And almost six years of my life
Yeah it's been watching
Dumb s***
Yeah interesting Lee enough
You're far more like Stanley Kubrick than she is
Maybe I mean
Pluck I accuse sort of curmudgeonly right use a little bit of crank notorious perfectionist
And workaholic
I'm a workaholic I'm not sure I'm a perfectionist if I was I would not allow Alex to be involved in any of my work that's a very good point
Maybe it's an imperfect is a perv
Perfection I would say
Just from my perspective on having
This is anecdotal
I will say
But
Maybe society would be better off if we didn't give a f*** with the
The kids of talented people
Or did
Sort of Bona fides in her own creative
No I'm fine
Whatever I don't know enough really about her entire resume
The resume that is
Thrown around is all stuff that kind of involves her dad
You know is a composer and has
Made the score for some of these movies and
She has
And nepotism is always worked out in the past
Look I mean
I think the nepotism is a little bit
But at the same time
Just because you're the child of someone really artistic
Stickley brilliant doesn't mean
That you
Going to be artistically talented in your own right Nicolas Cage
Sure
I understand
But I would say that there's probably a lot more of the ones that didn't work out like
Yeah probably
Probably
It's it's fine to say that she
She does have artistic Merit of her own accord
I'm fairly comfortable saying that
Now is she on a level even
Quotes to Stanley Kubrick
I would say no
Yeah I've been imagining that she has
Any kind of Gravitas
Approaches that is a little bit
But silly I think she did use also
Broccoli
Xerath did she compose
Zarathustra
It wasn't $2,000 Full Metal Jacket
So
She thinks that where I were coming
Coming to the something big here
And and what do you make
Say that we are at
Biblical
Climax
Human history
And that when people should have
You think that
You know
Viewpoint
Say you're mine on everyone had I'll be pointed somehow
Extreme it's because
That's how much
Don't realize you
He's been mind-controlled
It breaks my heart
I want to manage
And right now we seem to have
True enemies
Real enemies
Humanity
Running
And whether it's
Extraterrestrials or whether it's
Just goddamn horrible psychopath
How do you get to
To say that it's probably a compressor also man
Think about it not going to Alex
Scolded someone to 2003 % damn God damn whole thing
The lord's name
In vain he's not going to like that Furious
So
One of the things that I've enjoyed is over the years Alex has mentioned
Knowing Stanley Kubrick's daughter and
Come inside Bass
About some of the
The cheese told him
Child about Kubrick
Xlife
This is so f****** funny
Talk about
Factory Connection
Loving
What about a book the library
Library somewhere
And it was talking about the CIA
Came to him
How do you know about
The code to the B-52's
Outside
What you told me 15 years ago or so
So why's your dad
But he was
He was a remote viewer
What time do we have the
Schedule
With you
Alex just took his own story from it
She's talking about dr. Strangelove
And the design of
The control room or whatever
And
The CIA did
Call or the government calls and asked like how did you come up with that
And he didn't
It was a
Someone else
The crew made the design of this has created
This entirely
Father story out of the theater remote we were initially psychically knew what the
Fukkk offf being like it's extraterrestrial in nature the government if
People trying to murder us and then being like hey let's calm it down about the
This story okay that'll do directly with a story about her dad probably would like to correct the record
He's not a remote viewer
So she is also into David Icke
Along with Alex
No really
You're going to resent him or the rest of this quote
Vivian
What
What do you make of the world today
And just
What's happening
What's happening is that
The spirit beings
A being solely test
And whether it's in order to learn
Lessons
As the Eternal being said I believe we are
The biggest test
That we've ever gone through
Because
Does every recent
Expect that week
Get trapped Aaron
I think we should all have ideas about
What could be happening but the main thing is we actually have
Push back the Braves
Bacillus
Because the people attacking us
Have courage be
Because I have money
And they have I'm sure
What was it like
Military guys
You know they've got people
Protect them Alex don't like us because he has a lot of money and a lot of mercenaries
Describing Alex
Courageous as a lot of money so much money and X Blackwater people who are on his payroll to protect
Just like I would love to show Vivian a picture of Alex outside the courthouse and Austin with I-10
Security guard
Yeah
Thinking so brave now
Amanda Milius is on and she's she's just there for like
2 minutes
She's on the phone
And she's with
A guy named Daniel who maybe her husband or something I don't know
But anyways he's involved to stop a steel pretty heavily
And it's cool because like
Her associations with the producers of Alec
What does war
Riot documentary just shows like
How aboveboard
And unbiased
Character study
Alex that documentary was
Possible for a group of
Tight-knit
People like that
To make something that wouldn't
Portray Alex in the
Correctly
Correct money corruption would not have
Anyway we're going to get past that a little bit
And just go to Alex
Samsung stupid
Rodger Stone coming up you're going to be covered with olly Alexander
Kitchen off
Tomorrow
Have Harrison Smith myself 11 a.m. you at 3 p.m.
They said this would take days
Weather
Make a tack
Balance
A real snake
Why is the voting
In all the key District
So what you see here is Alex articulating that they can
Conspiracy he primed his audience for didn't
Match the situation that was playing out
He was expecting for there to be a giant red tsunami as he said
No times on this stream
And that late in the evening or early morning the margins would narrow and he would then claim that it's the result of a ton of fake ballots being
Pumped into the box
Closely with the conspiracies laid out by Alex and folks like Mike Lindell about the 2020 election analysis
Preparing his listeners to watch this stream under the pretense that this was what they were going to see again
Yeah it was the 2020 election to
Where are the 2020
However
Bpop was underperforming
Even early in the night so this whole game just doesn't play
If Republicans are losing Arizona and so many of these races are really close to this early then the predetermined storyline
Isn't really going to fly
This is Alex thinking on his feet and coming up with a new framework for the audience to use to claim that the election
Beast Machines breaking down in key districts
That's to blame
Keep in mind that I was not proven in any way that machines are broken down in key districts nor is he even Illustrated it pours
The closest thing was that one caller from before Alex was even there that was those too much humidity in Oak
Oklahoma and no matter where he was in Oklahoma that was not a key disc
This is a good illustration of why fact-checking doesn't really matter in terms of opposing someone like Alex
He just made me factors whatever reality is most
Convenient for him and allows him to tell the stories he wants
Hospital will be most profitable to tell his audience
A respectful realities existence is a
Requirement for having your back
And I would still give a s*** about that
It's the same thing that same Dynamic it was a player
When trying to check the pasta results in Philadelphia County
It doesn't matter you're just going to come up with a new story
That under
Undergirds the point that you want to make
Because the the
Central idea that they're expressing is I'm right
And then if you come up with information that shows they're wrong
You just need to re-enter that information in a way that shows that I
Even more right than
Involves
Making something up entirely at the best way to do it
Argue with me I made it up
So Alex is going home and you sounds a little rough
And I'm out of my sports jacket
Said the terrorists Republicans are going to blow stuff up
Only election
False flag
They cannot
Lucia power
Sponsors
Battleground areas all shutdown
They have done again.
Dictatorship
So this isn't that much later than
Other stuff
You went from zero to drunk
Like real fast pronunciation
Wow
That happened quick
Got a lot of paper cups rolling around unless Solo cups hanging out underneath that death
I don't know what the deal is maybe he was thinking like I'm going to be in this for the Long Haul them things weren't working out Tuesday
How to get drunk go home
But whatever the case he sounds rough
Really fully know if Rodger Stone does show up after Alex left because I'm not going to watch 8 hours of
Taken
Call
Listen for a little bit longer to see what was going on and here's
Just our last clipper
The valley
Being real dumb
You know let me go into Claire this
Let me go and declare this
We live in a Banana Republic
I say that was
I say that with conviction
And I say that we can establish that is a matter of
We live
Banana Republic
Infowars
Was cranes years ago at the beginning of my career
And now I've liked
These are my ride or die Brothers
Call Bro
I'm glad I'm on this
Yeah
I understand the image of that Miley is trying to evoke with the term Banana Republic but I don't think he actually knows what that means
He just thinks
Place that subject to colonialism like to say that the Democrats
The colonize the us but that's not what a Banana Republic is
Very specifically at Banana Republic is characterized by being a country whose economy is solely dependent on
Exporting its own natural resources
Typically this involves a single resource That's the basis of the economy like of the bananas were in Central America
Guatemala when they were under the sway of giant America
Fruit company
You can make the argument that the way that those large
Corporations held so much political power based on their control over a single resource with those countries economy relied on
It's similar to how many of the giant companies in the US have outside political influence
Their involvement things like
The energy markets but I don't think that's a conversation Ali or anyone it informs really wants to have because
At the end of the day they're on the side of those big Corporation
Who sang makes no sense
Look I was just trying to have a big
Dramatic moment but
Comes off as a little bit crayon negro
Hang out with your ride or die LOL
Why are WeedMaps
Fascist can't use
Slang terms like that
Annoying
/
Uno
And I'm not even a fascist
I I just think it's a little dumb
Honest
Leslie
IWatch
A lot of
Infowars election night coverage of the debate night coverage
What time does La more fireworks
This was
Yeah it was
COA
Yeah it's it was I think that was a weird night then especially just because the polling like
The day before
Once you got to like
Here's everybody's pulling information
It was all like the margin of error is
Four Points
That could go either way
It is it was literally like okay
Tomorrow night the Dems might be up by 4 or the Republicans could have won everything everything started happening and we were like
This is going to be exactly
The same tomorrow
Forever
Yeah app
I think if Alex wasn't
On if you didn't need money and need to do a Telethon
And if you wasn't on bannon's thing like
I don't even understand the premise
Doing this
Like there was no one exciting on it and Alexander Laurel Uber Drew Hernandez
Jim cool
You had Mike Adams
Robert Barnes
Maybe Rodger showed up after Alex left
Look it's nothing it was what I felt like
It was going through the motions
Like they felt obligated to do a livestream
I agree with
Except
40in with the Big Mac
Okay that's fine
I'm really trying that really was
Trying really hard to give the appearance of try
I I meant I meant if it was his idea
If but it can't pause
Owen wasn't the one that was like let me go to app
Well maybe maybe
It's it's creating the appearance of being like a big boy show
Infowars
Cute and
And he's
So anyway we come to the end of this
Stand up
I don't know midterms did with a dad and Alex did what he did and who
It's great
Besito bar
Until then I mean
Clark
Do do do-do-do-do
If you read the WikiLeaks
The sex robot
Holding
Alex
Kristen color