Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for knowledge babe I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex Jones
Indeed we are.
Well I'd like to thank everybody who responded to the call for submissions
Do the anti-communism library more than you would have expected a few and I appreciate it start building
Hats and we'll see where that takes us
It's very exciting new project
It's not back to the 60
Me as well but we'll see
I want to try and create a a nice
Compendium of
Yamcha's almost
Literally want to always have
The documents at this point
Yeah you want them
Yeah man and there's something
So interesting about holding these like
Pieces of weirdo history like these American opinions and one of them is addressed
Some of them have address labels on them
One of them went to a guy in Monaco
Okay alright Diane Monica was reading a John Birch stuff and somehow that's ended up in my hands
Nuts yeah there is
There is a part of me that is like
I I walked in and I saw those and it was a little bit like catching you with dirty magazines like it felt a little bit
You shouldn't have those out
Plato
Is everywhere
And that also wanted to take this opportunity to say to folks
Your buttons are still coming out
They're still being sent
I hope to have it done by the end of the year
To give some just a little bit of an idea
I'm going
Through the
Baby email inbox from
First received two most recent
Andre 3000
I have no idea how many already
Yeah there is there is nothing about us only being two people
Yeah
And having
Really no situational awareness
Absolutely no concept of like I got an email from somebody who's like it we can help
You track your Lister Bezos I got to
With what magic why
What are you
What
It did we talk okay
See what
My bright spot is
I don't know if
You've heard of these two
Young up-and-coming
Gentleman Dave Anthony and Gareth Reynolds
I've spoken
You have Dave still not spoken to me I think that's on purpose
Is this point I think they would be willing to talk to you
Willing
I know they have a new show called The pastime
And it could not be more
It's like
Iat's my alley in a way that I
I can't even comprehend lights newspaper base
Completely different from the dollop see Dave read something
Ceguera to react to it
No but he picks a newspaper from a random
Place in the past or whatever
And just reads
To you and the reason that this hit
Me so hard is because
We listen to it I remember
That when I was growing up in my hometown
There is this historical society
Had all these microfiche
Newspapers and I f****** read
Constantly I love reading those
To the point where one cent
This is always stuck out not sentence like a little fragment is always stuck in my head which
She's just a
Another ham with Missy
Like I said it's like
I can't believe this
Get newspapers used to be a little different
The writing of it was a little different
It's snowing in LA
I did the days of hams going Michigan you miss it
Right right that's the message
It is it is so much
I was so angry too when I listen to it cuz I was like
That was my childhood and bait turned into a show goddamn going to have a show
No but it's great it's really really good I've not had a chance to check it out yet but I've heard from multiple people that is
It's a quite good
So Jordan today we have an episode to go over going to be talking about
Friday's show that November 11th 2022 okay this is
Post midterms
Post Alex having a another half billion dollars tax Yahoo
Is she at
Post having his assets somewhat Frozen until there's a hearing in
Early December I believe
Either way
But actually I ate you would not know it by just listening to this episode
I ended up spending
Way too much f****** time on something that is
Completely pointless
And we'll discuss it when we get to it
Do you mean one of our highlights
So let's say hello
Arguments Ace associate Morgan Stringer
Very much next Jordans laugh is everything and I know because I'm a Jordan
I do think it's about you and how about we walk
Gorilla with us watch Bass
Vector robot
I don't know why I couldn't
I could not read that in these heroes in a Half-Shell rhythm
I think I just
The man the myth and now the Policy Journal policy walk
Next Kiki's Brightspot delivery service
Very much
I appreciate it Alyssa pants
Picture of Jordan
So I thank you so much to Jackson Mississippi doesn't have running water and no one seems to care please send help
We are not the sort of people to
Don't send emergency messages
Timely message
Oh no
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone
Sodomites
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much
Souderton
Not all the return
Time to come in
And so they're still little bit of optimism
Here
And this time they might still win the Senate that's what we're talkin about
/
Friday
So they lost both
Yeah
Hope Springs Eternal on Friday
And they have not had to turn this into a voter fraud
Conspiracy
Yeah it is kind of funny how they like
If they
Ben went if the Democrats have been waiting by more
The Republicans almost would have been in no more
Comfortable position to claim that it was fraud
As opposed to having like a lead for so long that they're like
Well we can't call it Friday yet
You know that
Don't say fraud until you see the whites of their eyes
So Alex is a news story that has nothing to do with the political
Sweetheart
Really really shity
What are the big news Ruby getting
Baby used mRNA
Technology in hundreds of studies
With Vaughn
Not just here but around 1 a.m. quino
Everyday
Portion
Of the individuals that have a tested on them die
Horribly painful.
Livers
Coagulate
And it's happened again
New York man dies while they
Editing technology Chris
What do you think they just did
Where the MRNA shots
Do hundreds and hundreds and
I'm over a million people.
So Alex is not in any way establish that mRNA technology used in tests in the past has killed a ton of people
I would fact check this but he's not being
Specific about what test
He's talking about so he's not even really making a claim worth being taken seriously
If you have some examples I'd be happy to engage with them at that point
But this is just talkingshit
What else is it isn't true
And that's why he has no specific
Well based upon what he saying the
Action of the symptoms that he's described
Brain rot has happened liver time before that I can recall and that was
At a certain point
The Arc of
The Covenant was open
Sure
Exactly
And if you don't avert your eyes from the MRNA guess what happened
MRN Ark
There we go New York man Alex doesn't have any of the information on this that's worth reporting like there's nothing
But he knows that brings us to the level of it being perfect
To be on his show
This is about twenty-seven year-old Terry Horton
Who suffered from a very rare form of muscular dystrophy
His brother Richard was the head of a nonprofit called cure rare disease
Would you let a push
Exploring gene-editing therapy possibilities
Four conditions like the one his brother hat
Terry was going to get a tailor-made treatment
And it's signed up for it but he passed
According to statmuse quote it's unclear when or even if he received the experimental
In reality this is a rare condition that is
Pretty commonly fatal
It's been estimated that between the ages of 20 and 25 86
6 out of 1,000 patients with this condition would die
And past the age of 40 that number goes up to 336 out of 1000
Every year
The median survival age of someone born in the year that Terry was with his condition is 28.1 years
Which is close to 27 which was the age of that Year's
We don't know if he even got the treatment and even if he did we have no idea if it was connected to his passing
YouTube we do find out that it was
Connected to the treatment it wasn't an mRNA treatment and it has nothing to do with covid
I was just a monster trying to capitalize on this young man's death and exploit him
So he can be used as a prop
The push anti-vax bulshit
It's disgraceful and if I were this guy's brother I would probably think about suing a
Yeah I mean this
Leave this one alone I feel like this is a situation
If I understand correctly
Where there's a non-profit
Like
Geared towards people who have
Diseases that are
Everywhere
Impossible for a pharmacy company or anything to think what we need to develop a therapy
I wouldn't be within their profit motive
So you're not going to wind up getting all of the trials and everything you need to develop any therapy within any kind of reasonable
Length of time through the FDA or all of those
Possible channels if you go through all these tests and all that stuff
Something along those lines where it is
Hey we got this rare disease
We've got
People who are in a situation where it's like hey
Oh my God
This hasn't been tested enough
Who f****** cares man I don't know another would have looked into it enough to know so I don't want to sign off on your
Said sum
Vitro
I'm not saying they're like
Hey we found something in the woods I don't think it I don't think it is like that but
I do I do think there is something to the
The snow just the reality that some of these larger pharmaceutical companies wouldn't
Explorer
It wouldn't be in their interest to explore some of these things so that's
Some of the work that's left to smaller nonprofit
That's more my description
It is that they would
Have any reason cuz they were about
Getting old this this is sad
No matter what no matter what
Alex using it
For his own purposes
Sucks
Just leave everybody like that
So now back to Paula
So that's coming up as well
Call Diane boil bunch of globalism
Come out and help World Government we got that for you
Right in
Do all of the election news and boy
Suspected fraud Tuesday night
Now the evidence is overwhelming
Got the trumpet Santa Civil War kicked off by Trump
Got mixed feelings about that
But you do Civil Wars are supposed to work
Mixed feelings about home
I mean do you know when you're fighting brother against brother the point not ideological let's stop slavery part obviously
How much does a mixed feelings about V Civil War
Mixed feelings about this
To Alex's no concrete evidence
Anyway
Election fraud check but he is now definitively proven dead
Also every single episode
Not every episode episode 3 can go back through like
A decade ago 15 years ago and he has a piccolo blister announcing world government
Say finally come out and said it like
Wow
The blase nature of the way he
He describes it too as though it's another blind news-item coming up as I'd like it if there's a
Actually World Government announced
I'm going to hear about it
As more of a big deal 7-ounce world government and in other news
Squirrel water skiing exactly
Another ham stolen
Stolen by the EU
Exactly
So Alex
Does not like this
Idea the trumpet DeSantis are fighting I get it I understand
Also we're going to be looking at
What Trump said last
Night on the street social
Coming out and attacking
Governor DeSantis
Not a good idea
Corporate Media One
New York Times
Fox News
All of the established
Media
Other than a few exceptions like Erik Karlsson
Have come out
And have praised the Santas in attack
Trump
Trump the reason we didn't
When bigger in the midterms and all this made up garbage
To get us fighting with each other and
Trump with his ego
Big is the moon
Aztec in the bank know I love Trump
And come out attack
Pakistan has
Never
Attacked from
So now it's not about a stolen election
Captain Steel
Now some about buying me a tea and a geriatric patient up Federman
Mega Million
Destroyed
Giant
Zombie Goblin leader
It's not him that if
About Trump
Trump
Is the reason Republicans
Didn't win bigger
Total distraction
From reality
Waited
Straight in
Diane is attacking to Santa
I wish
Zombie Goblin leader
Struggling to land that's it
Hoobly
Do you can hear Alex Express in something in this clip that makes a lot of sense
He doesn't like the idea of trump into Santa's fighting because that's a
Repeating narrative from his own
And it's one that
He can't really profit from
Alex wants all the right-wing audience to be swept up in this stop this
Fuel type stuff for he could do another dumb Caravan tour and yell at rallies about how much proof he has of Alexa
Brought
That's great
Wait for Alex because he can make a lot of money off that never has to prove a damn thing
Conversely
Trump DeSantis is a dead end
That fight is
Is no good for Alex because neither choice is really that great for his bottom line and if the audience is forced to pick a side because there
Fighting Alex is expected to have a position
Alex is already done his whole I give Trump two weeks to come out against the vaccine or else I'll attack him and Trump didn't give a single
Bulshit
How much is already embarrassed himself with his concert
I swear I'm leaving this time for real
If he does actually decide that he doesn't want to be on Trump side anymore
It won't have any impact on the only result will be pissing off the members of his audience that still like Trump
Staying as things are and being on Trump's team again is also embarrassing
Because Alex made all these ultimatums
Trump didn't care which shows that Alex is a spineless coward
On the flip side
Going over to DeSantis has its own problem
Many of the listeners particularly long-term listeners have a little bit of Hero 4
They were sold a bill of goods about how Trump was going to change everything and he was the god appointed leader they needed to trust no matter what
What and what did it amount to
Basically nothing but chaos and an ego-driven a******
Picking fights
Haven't gone through all that it's understandable as many of the listeners aren't super Keen to adopt a new god-king
Once Bitten Twice Shy and all that
There's problems here with this fight
This is not the State of Affairs Alex wants to see
In a perfect world jump into Santa's work together or at very least they would be like kind of respecting opponents
So I wouldn't have to pick
Decide this early
This is clearly bad for his wallet
At this point
Yeah I mean
I feel like the
The the main issue for him
Is
He's kind of
Pot committed with
Trump
Less because of the Electoral body kind of
Situation
And more so just because of the
Personality
Connection to the two of them
He's not going to relate to
The Santa send a scientist is never going to give Alex
Probably not you never really would think
I've been surprised
True that's true
Santa's cookies
True but I mean it's the point that everybody is making about their fight
Is that people are tired of trump
And would rather have DeSantis someone who is less like Trump
It makes even
Way lessons for Ed DeSantis to be like
And now Alex is my buddy
What that loud bombastic a****** right around
Sort of lesson the appeal of the I'm not Trump thing
So I feel like I'm
Is right you're right that Alex is Sodapop committed with
Trump but I also don't think
He'd understand
And he should dumb
No just like our last episode Ali Alexandra saying that it forwards there is ride or dies
Right right I am the Galaxy
Stay to his word and be ride-or-die with here's what I say
Here's what I say
That they have
To-do list
The smart play for Alec
Exo-k
Say
I don't care which of them comes out on
Because whoever comes out on top is going to be the better
Candidates because they're going to
To fight each other so much harder than any Democrat
Could fight that all of their bullshiter be out and by the time that we're ready to play against the Democrats
Will be on
Unstoppable
I think iron sharpens iron that kind of like this
It doesn't work when it's Trump and decide to get so ugly
But they don't
No cuz you
You can't
Hold back
Wow it's getting ugly
Bright light
Let's see who comes out on top
That would be the fun thing that's what they that's what they what would drive money to Alex
Is non-stop fighting
Sure but you have to have
Your side
You can't have non-stop fighting and it being like what let's look at these two fight
Like
Trump and Hillary in 20
16 wooden
Has been
Valuable to Alex if he wasn't
I like into Trump and hated Hillary the interest of the audience
I'm so like if
It's two guys who you're but you're supposed to like both of them and they f****** hate each other
That's kind of difficult
But here's the thing
That people are discount
And that is that the way you get
Famous
Is you have
Rap battles man
I'm talking now hold on just a good idea
Rivaling you got to have fights going on and then ever
Everybody is like we got to pay attention to this that's the way you do it
DeSantis shows up and he's like
Do it absolutely
Alex is like
Yeah
Alex
Doesn't like Trump statement
Social
He also thinks it's
True
Great
Wish you would have come out against them
But overall
Bubbles take Trump more than anybody's Anti New World Order
He's obviously better the Democrats
We need to not be fighting with him
We need
Not be
Battling
With each other
Really is
That's simple
Statement by President Donald J Trump what is the president of States of America
Weboost
Santa should not him
For president Ann
He made the Santa
Santa says all these neocon
Fluttering around DVDs
Many ways which is true
I don't like Jeb Bush hanging around I don't like me
Ronnie hang around
You know what trumps hung out with all those guys
Statim in the back so
The jury's out on that
With the Santas and I'm not going to get in this house Bagent
Trump's better or DeSantis
Better Trump's words
And people need to stay focus
Contemplation
The open borders
Exploding crime
The war in Ukraine
Stop the poison shot
Outlet mall
Injections in lockdown
The future I'm a good luck trying to take some kind of a high road
Gossip show for the extreme-right like word start flying it's going to be like all out
Could talk about y'all be like
What do you think about this
It'll be
Conspicuous if he doesn't get in the mud and make it a beauty pageant absolutely zero people
I think that
0 people want
What's that
We all got to come together
Message from Al
Yeah you can have those with some people on the right walk though we should all come together maybe
Most of them aren't that but you're not going to Alex
To get it now but I also think that your
Maybe mischaracterizing what
He means by
Kumbaya here
Is more like we all got to get together with the narrative can't let this be the thing Everybody's Talkin about
Because if it is
I can
I got no roots
Play here
What you don't want Alex to be the guy saying don't fight
He's Alex
F****** Jones January 6th and was yelling in the bowl horny on everybody
School around hasn't gotten better since then has it
So
I don't know who is dating who
I don't know
Dallas making it
About the Democrats trying to steal the election in blunting the victory
Instead of making it
About how we need to get rid of the Republican neocon rhino
Corporatist leadership
Like Mitch McConnell than others
Instead of that
It's all about
DeSantis
And that's why the Republican establishment has weighed in with the liberal media
Try to create a trump
Shrimp
An old
I've taken the bait
Something take anybody
He's just an a****** people constantly
He feels like his position in the extreme right-wing Spears threatened by DeSantis because
It is so he's attacking him
It's honestly shocking the Trump waited until after the midterm 100% I guess that's a pretty good
But you don't want the Democrat to win the Florida governor race
Particularly because Trump lives in Florida
Bob so you wait till immediately after to attack because at this point it's about the 2020
4 general election
That is an amazing amount of restraint for someone like Trump to his house
I mean what I say goes back to what Alex said earlier of his like Trump attack
With a dentist Easton nobody attacked first
Yeah
What did you expect Trump to only attack in retaliation that's
It's the way you view him as a pacifist until you come at him he's not at all aggressive
Alright
So you some good news
Soccer news
It's kind of fun
Owen
It's still reporting from the bay
Big boy
I like to imagine that he hasn't life is tied with one ankle doing
He's got it
Necktie like I'm done these he's Haggard but he still
Needs a checking in on Arizona
Stan right now
I don't like what I'm seeing in Arizona
Despite the
Confidence
That Lake
In Masters
Still have
That these late
Night latch
Ballot dump
The favor that I'm
I'm just not seeing it
They're not getting the returns
Please.
They thought they were going to be getting about sick
60 even even
70 /
I'm some of these last-minute returns coming from work
Conservative areas
They're just not getting
They're just not
Katie Hobbs lead
Was actually
Send it
Last night
With the late night
Last minute ballot drops
And they say 82
Percent RN
So
This is going to be a miracle comeback
I think for Kari Lake
And then even farther behind
How is Blake Masters
To the incoming
Mark Kelly
Isle at that will take
America live
For master
To pull the
This one off I don't know how he does
The returns are not coming in favorable right now for
Republicans
And it
It's been shown that the
Incumbents did really well
There's a minute of Owen
Sort of covering the election results
Making it a conspiracy
Which I was surprised by what I'm hearing
It's it is what it is it's pretty much just kind of like here is that his numbers are coming in
I know what I'm here
You know like I know that I'm hearing Wolf Blitzer at the Boar
I'm
Frustrated
Wolf Blitzer isn't tied to the board to
Shirin 2
That it's
Elwyn doing this would happen
Think maybe that Owen
Kind of like
Experienced it
On midterm night
Let me let me give this another shot let me see if I can just say some information instead of
Some dumb b******* about Philadelphia County
Because I've got Alex giving me let's all come together
I do got Owen trying to be a journalist
This is busy
Is b*******
Does Dill say about the dumb s***
Yeah buddy
He's trying to be at
This was a three-headed monster
Sure if you will or a try
Act up
Of the new brand of
Conservative
The Fighter the one that takes on the media
The one that takes on the establishment
The one that's not afraid to back
Trump
And what we kind of weed
This could be a determining factor of what the
The future of the Republican Party looks like
If we have big wins in Arizona
This new breed of Republican
Didlake
And Masters
Olamide rep
Type of person to Republicans meiwah
Forward
Well they're not winning
Yeah
She's giving an assessment of your late did this was this new new idea this
These are our kind of candidates and they are all
We tried unqualified stupid a******
And we thought it was working really well there for a while but now it doesn't seem like it's working
Took the wrong message from 2020 maybe message was everything is stolen
Workout
Things Fall Apart
And in the run off with
Just be like
Gravy
For them if they
They can get that in Georgia
Sadly I kind of
In the Wind
This point I'm not
Not sure what the Republican
Plan is for Georgia
If they think going on get another abortion
Is the key
If they think going on Sean Hannity is
The key
Then they're going
Toulouse
.
That's it
End of sentence
They have no boots on the ground
They have no plan
Nothing from McConnell where is McConnell
By the way
Anybody heard from McConnell
These last couple days
No he's hiding in a hole
He's loving what he see
He wants to lose
The Senate
He want to lose Us in it so we can blame it on Donald Trump
Is number one
Initiative
From now
He's to get
Trump
No matter what you the voter thing
This is what it's all about this is the new battle for the GOP
This is a good
Conspiracy
Yeah they really is it is not
Too far to be it's not like
You're not you're not
After being overly ambitious
You are obviously there is a ton
Understandable and believable problem
And that is that Mitch McConnell is
Pissed off about Trump
Basically taking over the GOP
Indeed so in order to resolve this
You take the midterms
I thought you blame it on Trump right and just like that
You're out of the woods into your safe quite that simple
But it but it in terms of a conspiracy that you're going to make
About losing the midterms
Pretty good but I mean as far as the conspiracy goes I don't even think that's a conspiracy theory so much as it is like
Okay I think this might be a
Fairly workable plan
That might work
You know I do
Macado's plans
Do for work
And I wouldn't put it past him to have a good plan I think that
It's staying the the majority leader is probably more important
Probably
But
B like it what year
You're saying is totally Act
Bigger is a
Like an A to B to C
The plan makes sense
You cannot mean it. I don't know if it works or works but it's
Things Fall Apart and stage 3 and magically everybody doesn't like
That part is going to be a little bit of a problem
Execution you can see that he's probably helping juice the media narrative go along and all that stuff but again
It's clearly
Getting yelled at by
The people that like Trump you know it's not like they he's he's tricked them into liking him more
It's just rare that you hear a conspiracy being thrown out by someone it in four words that like
Well at least has the grammar of a conspiracy
It is not
It's not
Out of
Resume
McConnell blocks out of
McConnell blocks the Supreme Court
You know like I said there's if there's a plan behind that it's not the clear like a 2B 2C like a fight
I do this then this will happen
We'll get Trump and then we'll fill that
Define late
There was always the possibility that Hillary was going to win
And they were going to have to
To fill it
He's the one who orchestrated that whole idea is a long shot
And giving him this is a long shot why not
You know
I don't know if it is
Happens this way at all
It's reasonable to think that he might have tried.
Hear me out okay
Alright I don't think that this is I don't think this happened I think
It's probably agree with you on that
Yes yes
Now
10 years from now if someone writes a book and it's a towel where Mitch McConnell says
I threw those midterms already get Trump out of my hair
I don't think I'd be that surprised that's what I'm saying I also don't think it happened I don't think there's any
I agree with that
20K
So anyway the Trump decide this thing is babe
You are absolutely right and that's why we
Cannot
Take the bait
I got to do this DeSantis versus Trump
Trump versus Sanders garbage in Trump
Really digging the baby
And I'm even care about Trump but your answer right we need to focus on the Republican leadership
Election fraud and on issues we've got
To get that talking point out our Millions delicious right now and viewers
Can do that f***
Don't take the bait
Tropicana's garbage
Stay on McConnell
Kevin McCarthy
We got to stay
Army's Alexis we got to stay on the issue
There is no bait
It's Trump being an a******
I don't know I mean that
The irony of course
Verses that
They have no
Governing
Ability policy
Ideas
Anything
No such issues are tough I can't believe they're all saying that like they haven't
Very clearly been removing anyone with ideas
As a matter of Prince
We have to stick
To the policy conversations policy
Lock her up the last time you heard of attack
Playing that was
Can I can I suggest
Lock her up
How about a 10% flat tax across those are issues are you talkin about 999
Herman Cain
So
You do the post-mortem here on the midterm
You're going to find a lot of places to place blame and Alex has an interesting one
Overconfidence
3D
But we know there was the same
Play Book of fraud
Battleground States
The Unexplained fallet Rob's
In Georgia and
Michigan
Pennsylvania and Nevada
Colorado
Is is real
Everything is the globalist
Even your feelings are just a result of the globalist
Tricking you into feeling that way
That's crazy
So I guess
The GOP overconfidence was part of why they didn't win the midterm
And that was caused by the globalist to the media or saying that the GOP was going to Wynwood
Ken's to stay home
And not vote
Which is stupid
I'm not sure that many of the voters Alex's talkin about
Take their voting cues from the mainstream media but an even bigger problem is that Alex was
Constantly talking about how the midterm was going to be over
Red tsunami in a bloodbath
If reporting that the GOP was going to win big is actually a psyop to lower GOP voting
Then Alex's meat
Guiltiest party of that
Also Alex is presented literally nothing to support his claims of voter fraud
And irregularity
This is just something you can assert with no evidence and it's
Accepted as proven by the audience at this point
They've been taught.
People that everything that they don't win has been stolen from them so no proof is necessary to defend this playing
That they feel as deeply true
Yeah
Yeah it is it is funny I was talking
Talking to
And I
There is
They're not election voter fraud like they're stealing election so much as they're like
Well I mean obviously they steal election
Everybody steals elec
Like there's no
Fair Alexa
Can you know if Democrats are stealing elections Republicans
There's never there's that there's an equilibrium
Simultaneous with the real one where do but he's doing
Voter fraud
They just
Moved it over 10
You know it's like it's like a switch
Weird Bizarro world
Dark Universe
But also everybody stole the same amount of votes that other people stole so it all kind of washes out
This isn't this isn't going to get better
AR we got to guess
May or may not have shown up on
Midterm Eve
I don't know cuz he was hanging out with Mike lindow
We still don't know who won the US Senate race
Nevada
We still we're going to a sudden death
Runoff
I think
In Georgia
Right now what I'd like to
Shane all honesty is
She's got 150 million dollars in his
Federal
She sending the Herschel Walker
Donald Trump has got tens of millions of dollars in his
Federal Pact
How much is he sending
Herschel Walker
We're hearing almost nothing
And meanwhile Raphael Warnock
Who's an extremely
The guy who ran over his wife
For the car
I'm sorry
Uses of Herschel Walker beam
Unbalanced
50 million
Dollars
Yeah that's just something to Rogers repeating from Attack ad put out by the Walker
Her campaign
They allege that in a fight during their divorce Warnock hit his now ex-wife with a
In reality she who claimed that he had run over her foot but there's a little bit of trouble with the story
Bruce Lee Warnock was the one who called the police to his ex-wife
Home to report that she had accused him of running over her foot
The police came and found that you was quote a reluctant to show her foot
To an officer
And the police report said that
I do not see any signs of Miss Aloha Foot was run over
Not able to locate any swelling redness or bruising or broken bones on the left foot
It's entirely possible that he could have run over her foot but not left any of those signs
It's not likely but it is possible it could happen
If this is what Rodger has to attack Warnock with compared to the very clear and verifiable dirt that walkers got
Going against him this dozen
Feel very
Compelling
I know that Rodger is an attack only kind of guy and he needs to use whatever ammunitions available to him but this
Feels pretty weak
Makes me feel like the Dems are probably going to hold onto Georgia
We'll see we will
Who knows
You know
It is it's like
What we
We saw that there is tons
Is of narratives but it feels like what we saw I was
Just old people and Young
People tied
You know but Rodger is the voice of the attacking old person does not feel very
Strong good
Yeah
So look here is where things
Spell Bart
When I was
Burbank
Hours
Perhaps what did Rodger
Well
It's more something Alex okay
Couple years ago
Oh no
It almost killed
It happened again
Going
A big event
Frank Speech TV
That's out
Crazy
This is getting
Rodger just
Keeps getting T-boned
The middle of nowhere
Rodger keeps getting T-Bone
So what about the polonium poisoning
If you are
Continually T-boned
In the middle of nowhere
That is a
And I could be wrong
I could be wrong
But
It seems more likely to be T-boned in an area where there are more cars
That's just math
In my head
Yeah maybe I don't know I wonder if it's my perception
I don't know this based on the Institute
But it's my perception that people are a little bit looser with driving drunk in the middle of nowhere
You been the case in my
Growing up in the middle of nowhere for my time in Central Missouri
Center of Allstate
Now that being said I also know a lot of people who drive drunk in Chicago
But they're also comedian so that is a fair at the confounding variable
Anyway
The car into accident that Rodger had in Florida
That was really weird one of the t-boning
This happened back in 2017 in the circumstances of that one we're really bizarre
Rodger was apparently in the car
In there was supposedly a hit-and-run
The police are called but for some reason they don't show up until 70 minutes later and when they get their Rogers nowhere
He apparently waited
30 minutes and got into Burr
Leaving the scene of his alleged assassination attempt
Take me out kind of thing
So he was just in another car accident in Memphis
That's her just outside my
Baptist this is what I've seen pictures of the car
Cuz they they posted the pictures it looks like a bad crash
I don't know if there's any evidence that it was done intentionally but that car was backed up
Crash
Itself happened in German
Intown tennis
And their police department has a Twitter account where they have the habit of giving people updates on things like traffic situation
Instance
On October 21st they tweeted quote
Our officers are working
A motor vehicle crash in the area of Poplar Avenue in Brockton Avenue
Currently we have traffic
Big shot down consider using an alternate route
4 on September 9th they tweeted quote
Car vehicle crash at Poplar and Germantown Road
East travel lanes are blocked
Please use an alternate route
On November
Right around when Rogers accident would have happened they tweeted quote
Officers are on the scene of a crash where utility pole was struck and damaged on Wolf River Boulevard near river
Westbound Lanes on Wolf River or being diverted causing delays in the area
There's no other tweets about car accidents or traffic issues since
October 24th
I don't think this was Rodger
Because I found another route news report about this accident the person driving the car was taken to the hospital
But
Here's how I ended up wasting so much time stood to know
I saw a picture of the car
Oh no I'm heading upward Angle now and I saw a bridge
Oh my God you didn't geolocate did you I was trying to locate my God
Everything all around so I can locate anything playing that one
Game there probably was a better way I could have done this but
Anyway I wasted a lot of time skills is just memorizing
The world
You should try that okay
So the Germantown Police Department also has a Facebook page
Is there more active on
They have a Daily Post where they list the crimes that they responded to that day understand that
Rogers accident occurred on either the 9th
Or the 10th
November I'm not entirely sure I believe it was the 9th. But there's also a story that would came out on
On the 11th
Implies that it was yesterday
So the 9th or the 10th
Let's just say that in
Proper
Stone fashion
The details
Yes
On the 9th police responded to a report of someone being a
In possession of a stolen vehicle and quote
An unknown suspect
Started a small fire in a trash can
That's a bad Night's Alright
Then other for crimes
On the tap
Missing ham what was two people fighting
Too involved reports of forged checks and the last one was botakin
Complaint reporting the theft of a catalytic converter
Conclusion I can come to after spending
Way too much time on this is that if Rodger really believe that he been the target of like an assassination attempt
By way of this car accident
Strange they didn't call the police
That is as the keeps a very suspect
I'm it does not appear that they are called the police about this maybe even if it was just a hit-and-run or
Even if it's just an accident
You called the police
To have the police report for your insurance claim or whatever
I'm based on everything I can find
About the Germantown Police Department
Transparency and their social media that does not appear that
Rodger called
Interesting
Yep the plot
I mean it just comes a little bit murkier than usual
It's still Rodger
Could have been hit by stop by a polonium poisoning
Driving a
Sure like that's what it's come to no conclusions other than
This is sucks
Car is not
In perfect shape
That is what we can
Can conclusively
I will I will give Rodger credit because
He doesn't think that this was an assassination
I'm fine
There's no reason to believe
A political motive
Guy wasn't wearing a black lives
Matter t-shirt
In find a copy.
I was longer than that
Another words
Whatever struck the car didn't do so much damage to their own car
Backup and pull away in the local
Beliefs were
Never able
Identify who had done that
So it remains
Unsolved
Weird
So I applaud
Rodger for not
Thinking that this is a political hit
Kind of shity that he kind of still thinks wanted 2017 was yeah but here's another problem with what
What you just said
She said
This wasn't political end
He's basing that on the person not wearing a black lives matter shirt
Well I mean Beyond just being dumb
Implies that he saw the driver
Call the police
He's with hole
Information about a hit-and-run driver
I don't know
I will buy it
I don't buy it either
Just don't
Might have hit a pole
That's what makes sense to me
That's just what I got
It's infuriating it's not like I'm going to trust Rodger as a default
Sure
Lbry
Some more analysis here and I think that this is
Really sad
I think you just is trying to struggle with
The fact that there are more people in cities
And they people in cities tend to be more liberal
What the hell is going on in Atlanta
What the hell is going on in Phoenix
What the hell is going on in these major cities
Chicago you name it
We're Democrats
Percent 80% sometimes in New York
90% of the vote
Address
And try to mitigate
With these margins
Do they Trust
The results
Is that just because
Abandoned
Is it election fraud
And so they never have a chance
Enemies State elections
They just get overwhelmed I mean New York is a
If you take out New York City
The state of New York is red
Absolutely Owen Shroyer
What a great Point disenfranchised the largest city in the United
Fitness state is red
It is it is absolutely not possible to consider
That perhaps
When large groups of
Different different
People
Get together
Recognize how very very very similar they are and live in the same Community together they don't think
That is all black people's fault
He had you lived in the middle of nowhere in a small town with nothing but white people
It sure seems easy to say it's all black
I feel like the messaging
Especially the current
GOP
Love you
Frenzy ice weirdos like Alex and Owen Wright
They're messaging does not ring
True to folks who live in cities and have broader life
Experience
I'm and I do think that I wanted people in the GOP will have a difficult time
I'm winning elections if they can
Make any kind of an
Appeal to people who live in cities
And I think one of the things that they should think about changing the f****** message
Instead it's all voter fraud why won't they investigate this
You spent the last
Computers
Screaming about there's a people having investigations that go nowhere
Come on man
Yeah I mean
Itzy it does seem silly
If what it seems like is true
That old people and young people tied
I mean I wouldn't want to be on the side of old people
For the future
You know what I'm saying that's not a winning strategy if we're like let's choose the Dead one
As time goes on it becomes worse and worse option
New
Of a guy
He doesn't say who he is and
The financial guy
And I don't know I didn't look into who this person was either because it was just really clear that Alex
Doesn't understand what he's saying
And all this
Actually matters for Nate
As well
Gandalf
Again I want to
Talk about value One More Time
Because the southern
Part of the world
Has value
Are greater than large
Elements of the northern
And we start
About
On water
Intrigued
I'm biodiversity
Refined
Where does that say
I'm doing a lot of work out of Asia and I say that my next door neighbor
Indonesia is the left lung of the world
And obviously Brazil's a right
And Africa
Absolutely
Critical
And we need there
Natural
As a
Some based
World more than we need
That 66
Billiard weave
Got sitting in the basement of the bank of England
So how do we and I'm hoping this
Discussion today at least from a central Banker
Point of view
And how do we start
Tokenizing how do we start
System
That actually create
Down the volume
Transfer that
Value around the world
Oh yes
Elder transferring my the third world
I control
Liana World Bank
Wow
Wei Ramen
Animals they vote for them you don't have a vote anymore
Admitted plan
Really bizarre he does not have comprehension skills like really basic
Comprehension
Yeah yeah what crazy is that that's actually a really terrifying things to hear a central Banker say
You know I felt the scary thing but he just said and Alex's like all the IMF I think it's
Depends on exactly what the intentions are because there's a way to hear that
That has more of ascent
That
The things
Is like
These rainforest
Kristen Brazil
Yeah they have
A value
That is
Is greater
To the system of the world
Then anything that we can really put a monetary value on like in a logging industry or
Whatever
Forces are there that are concrete
That would lead to deforestation
It's so
System
I should be
Conceived of
That allows for the tokenization of these beings
Existing
Right you know right
And I do think it's kind of scary
But at the same time
It's
Claimed
Closer
To conservation
Right here's a mountain in a similar way to Rodger
And my default is not going to be believed
Right
A central Banker
A central Banker talking about natural resources
Is the most
Terrifying thing that can happen
That's in my head
Because their Winn-Dixie when you say tokenized
What I'm hearing from them is
Okay
Alright
We've been owning this the wrong way
We've been strip-mining
What we need to do with own it the right way
And gross stuff that we own
I can I can see I can see why
Back
Impression comes to mind
And I'm not saying that's not what he was saying I think that there are ways to look at
Like the implications of what
So that kind of very
Agree on what he's saying
Yes and that is different than what Alex Alex has her.
Idea what he said
He just thinks that all we're going to take all the money from the bank of England and give it to the side
Weigh-off
So you just heard the bank of England I say where the transfer all the wealth
Out of the North
Control take your money and enslave them
And now by bumbling around
At the new
Paris agreement 2.0
Promising all this
For our wealth to the global
Lockdown for years
Yeah it's just
Stop to
Here
Kamban think like
People take this
He has just basic
Inability to
Heatkeep respond
Cool two things
He does
And that's kind of trouble
Yeah I mean a lot of the times you can see him
Get enough of it
I'm being emotional enough about
The right
Part of it that you can
Can kind of skip over that he doesn't understand most of it
Right in this regard I mean I I can't see anybody
He who knows less about what they're talkin about flounder more trying to look
Like they know what they're talking
Yeah it's terrible I mean if you listen to as much of it as I do so I can hear that a lot more
Points not always talk about
Maybe I just needed to find something
To fill in this episode because
This is maybe shorter
For a couple reasons
First
My side attempt
The geo-locating a bridge
I thought it was so fun if I could coming by.
They would have been a great risk like blocking a Supreme Court Justice
Yeah it doesn't always play and play out in your favor
And whatever and the second reason is this
Have the sensors trying to silence us cat McGinnis
Is our guest with a bouncy hour to talk about the midterms
Between
Trump and DeSantis
Open borders
And Ukraine the insanity going on
He is the house
TV
The founder of Vice
And so much more needs introduction
Gavin thank you so much for being on with my friend
We didn't talk before you came on I threw out kind of a
Plethora of things to Hitman
What's Rent-A-Center for you my friend
A new phenomenon I'm calling
Terrorism
It's tearing from a chair
I had a show in Rutherford New Jersey last night
And antifa found out about it
They just terrorized
Thumbs
The venue owner
The chief of police
The mayor
And
To show up
Left her chair for any of this
The mayor got
Spooked he called the chief of police
Who told the venue to shut it down
And they did
What's
First and foremost on Gavin McInnes his mind is as yet a show cat
Yeah the midterms
I mean I had five
All of these important
World events
We got to get into all of them but first
I had a show camp
Most importantly
Let's think about the true victim
Okay which is of course then you had a to drink
Oh my gosh they lost a lot on that okay
That's bulshit
Unthinkable genuinely thought he was
Who's in jail I thought for some reason like a couple months ago what happened
Why would I pay attention past it's fun that you didn't
Because the reason that it came out that he faked it was because Owen Benjamin who is
Of course before swelling Nazi used to host the fourth hour for Alex
He
Leaked texts between himself and Gavin twitch
I mean it speaks
To the fact that him and Gavin are still on friendly terms you know he's a forest dweller
Yeah okay
He
A couple months back
On his show he faked like a raise
Yeah and then disappeared in the middle of the show and it was all just like
Oh my God he was faking getting arrested
He still touring as a cop
Yeah he had a couple of shows canceled one was like him and Alex
Steinbeck
Troll guy
Yeah the two of them are apparently doing some like Duke
Wow
Can't believe it
Not good
Spending a lot of time trying to geolocate Rogers
Car and then Gavin McGinnis being on the show
What's a real bummer
Kind of makes it so like
I don't know we have
I have clips that I caught
Gavin
Talkin and as I'm sitting here
He just says offensive things
Trying to bait reaction
Any of his analysis or the things that he says are worthwhile like
A hit 120 says that his prediction is that Biden
Is going to beat Trump in 2024 because women are too emotional
Like I don't know
What what's the point
Here's a what
Hearing okay
His show should have been
Canceled
Because he
He thought that terrorist was funny
And that means
That the shows are. That's your opener but terrorism
Strong
Wow is that bad and he came out with it like this is
Is my this is
B
Get in there
I'm trying to see if there's anything even if these clips
It's worth talking about and I don't think there is
Although I was sad to see him up
Pure
I don't I don't know what
I don't I don't know why
Yuri
I thought he was a thing of the past
By everybody and we just moved on from him
Existing well I mean
That never really happens with Infowars comes back
Constantly
He's always around
Now I'm I guess I wouldn't really be
Like
Gavin belongs in that part of my brain with Mike cernovich inject
Sobec
These people that like
I don't really see
I guess Jack Pacific was on not too long ago
Cernovich I don't think has been on Infowars in a long time
Lauren Southern
These kinds of people who like
I've been on in this Lake
Other.
Premium download
Feel-Rite
Yeah
But it's enough
His role is supposed to be like during 2016 he says offensive stuff tonight
Fun on this show trolling the libs are eventive stuff
Kind of tired now
Bad I don't know if I like his shows getting cancelled now that I know that he
The comic
Cuz I kind of want him and people don't know though
Isaac
Bye
Is that
Well yes
Canceling his shows might hit his wallet
And all of that stuff real bad
I think it would really hurt him though is to live through a lot of those shows that I've lived through
Where you got 15 people who showed up and 12 of moron free ticket
No I don't think so because he has a
Gang
Oh no
The proud boys
That's right they all f****** love him yeah
And also it might not hurt his wallet so much
Because he claims that he's going to sue the city of Rutherford New Jersey good luck
Just have fun at their headquarters
With like a boombox
And I Allie Alexander
Hanging out with him
Everything is cool
Bad guy
Hatem
Hitam anyway
So this is going to be a shorter
They don't have to sit through 20 minutes of us being like
Gavin McInnes
Not funny
Yeah I don't really have much commentary about him other than his position suck
And I think he's just saying awful things in order to get a rise out of people
Alex has a new story
Cover
Monticello
Footage
A
Shop teacher
Wearing
Giants
Brass
Asian bizarre behavior
In Ontario
School board rules to allow male teacher
4 giant prosthetic bras
It's meant to make
A whole system
Joke
Be clear about something
I don't know enough about that whole story when it happened I just saw people I don't care about complaining about
So I decided to sit I don't know what the circumstances of his teacher RI
Anythink
By Alex is lying
The school board reviewed their standards to see if there was anything that they could do in terms of imposing a dress code and found that he could
Could raise human rights concerns and also have implications in terms of Labor rights
And employment law
But the board didn't
Make any position or change on this
Because they can't right now
The superintendent of human resources for the school board sorry Taha said quote
Even if we are to consider a workplace rules in that sense
We can't do that
This is because they're currently in the middle of collect
The bargaining and the board isn't permitted to make rule changes in the middle of that process right
It's right say make a good point though that even a good faith rule about dress code or grooming
Standards could
Easily end up being applied and discriminatory fashion
But the larger point is that their intellect
So they can't even consider Rule King
It's probably just a headline like the one in the National Post that says quote
School Board
Concluded can't Implement dress code after teacher wears giant fake breasts
And then he wrote his own story about it without looking into it any further and realizing that the reason that the headline says that they
They concluded they can't Implement a dress code is
Because every collective bargaining
There is a decent chance that they might not even if they weren't
Yeah no I mean
The reason they can't
Is because I can't write they physically in the universe we inhabit
They can't make a
Anyway
I lied there's a third reason that this episode shower another gas
City of the balance book
Bacelar presidential takedown
And also talked about the midterms what we're witnessing attorney science teacher
And two-time New York Times best seller he's best known as
Author of The Pledge series plague flag
Corruption and ending play with.
It just goes on from there
We really appreciate him coming on with us today and
He didn't want to talk about this morning. About it
Cut it down a lot more books on it
But you really
Help me write the great reset
We've been off and on the number one
I bet
Showers bended I saw that they were times ignored that
Find a bug
Store.com
Congratulations
Good to meet you in
Personnel afford having on many times
I applaud Alex for giving a full disclosure on that again but yeah he's the guy who wrote Alex's book
He's just a big old anti-vaxxer
So he has
Large
Stretch of his career writing books
With Judy mikovich
The person who is behind plandemic
Best documentary quote on quote
And so he has a long career
As a big-time anti-vaxxer
Tom and in 2017 he ended up being denied entry into Australia
Because of it
Because they he was just going to do a bunch of anti-vax rally rally like no
At that point he had Brandon himself quote the world's number-one anti-vaxxer
I'm so
Kind of gets rid of the the arguments to do was trying to make when he was denied entry into Australia's he was like
Raising concerns and asking questions and stuff
And also
When he was told you
Couldn't come
He sent a letter to the Australian government that was
Taunting Malcolm
Turn Bolt the the prime minister
Here's a passage from the
Love it
If you wish to greet me at the airport when I land I would be amenable to such a
An effort or if you think our meeting should be at the lodge the primary residence of the Prime Minister I would
Except that as well
After all I will be a guest in your country
Please don't make too much of a fuss over my efforts but if you would like to give me an award in recognition of my work deliberate Austria
Really from the grip of
The pharmaceutical industry
I like the sound of the order of Australia officer of the order
Maybe it's the imperialist in me but it just sounds so Regal
Yeah I can't I can't
I like talkingshit to governments to I can't argue with that
That's pretty funny
I don't know it another Circle
Constantin has a kind of Socrates ish
You know you're just
Poking your thumb in the eye of government you know
You cannot do this thing with like I only can I use it toward my car
What's that song
Interviews boring but he hero.
Foxes book
Great I like the idea that they will work.
Together
Please resume interviews okay alright that I'm working on a little
Coverage of his buck I will say that
Alex is fingerprints are all over
Maybe some like idea thing though I mean he put it
It's fingerprints on there because
Confirms that he wrote Abraham like
Chocolate sauce
Yes they were like
Assigning the cookies with Hershey syrup
Yeah Alex Goodman some of the syntax and if there's like there's no way that Alex
Alex doesn't know about whom
Doesn't know about like a dependent clause in a note
In apostrophe D at the end of this year
He thinks that you're grounded grounded
Ebel
Yeah
That's Alex
Who's on the phone for that one
You got to have some little
Maybe you should have like little fun fact sex
Santino like let the guy write the book
And then have Alex's little comments
I like in a little
Textbook it out also I want to see this
It's going to be a little while until I'm done
With coverage of his book
Any proof
Will be born from that
Berryville tree
I want to give a little bit of a
Short
Synopsis
It sucks
The bad book
Bad book
Hickenlooper did a terrible job
No not a good I don't even think this is right
The name it can't he can live like that
Kent heckenlively
Did a bad job
Also
I don't think
He wanted
People to know the
That he wrote the book make
Or something because he's not acknowledged in any way until the back
Back of the book
Thank you
It's not that it doesn't say it on the spine Alex and it doesn't take ghostwritten by nope
In the acknowledgments at the beginning there's no like
Nothing
Yeah either he didn't want to have credit
Or
Alex wanted to have all of
Yeah Alex wanted most of it to look like a
Why did he bring it up
When Kent City
Talk about that
Asian Cajun
Why is it going on the shop
Although he's going on this is another Patrol shows several weeks after that
The heat on Alex's book is
He would have if he wanted to be part of the book you have been part of
Heat part right he has another book that he's promoting he's on the show
On the show because you did Alex asalatu wrote his book for
Otherwise I don't think this guy is the world's number one
Exer
If I never met him in person from what I can understand
I am
I'm seeing that
He was a far thinker
And said sure I'll write your shity book
So that I can always promote my books later on
Yeah
Pretty clear that your audience
Would be into the kind of
Direct that I put out
Stuff
Good stuff all around
I did look responding to the midterms
Quite well
Yeah they're taking
Oh oh so I forgot to mention this
Hick and Lively also runs the outlet called
Great Awakening books
Might be a little signal to qanon
They also sell barbecue in on books
The part in
In the great reset because and I respected
For it alright in this one
Unlike certain adaptations
They left Tom Bombadil in
And that's what you want out of it you know Glenn Beck took it out to come out
Have that in your book if you don't I'm pissed
Right frankly
I take it up with the blaze
So anyway we come to the end of this stand
Yeah what a what a
F***
The fuc
Indeed
Between be wasting so much time on Google Maps
Gavin McInnes being on the show
What an awful f***
Anyway we'll be back with another episode
Sprite.com
Mdzs
Clark Gable
Bye-bye bye-bye bye-bye
Have you
You never read the WikiLeaks
The sex robot
Holding
Alex