Air Jordan sweater
I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge
Need
Knowledge fight
Acknowledge
Dot-com
The altar of spleen.
Alex golden
Windy we are Danny Jordan
Euphoria
Today Jordan is I don't know if
It's because winter is upon us it went from
7230 in a week
Religion of Italy was like 70 degrees last Wednesday
Baby was
It was on seasonably warm that day
40 degrees
Anyway I've been a little down
Do you have been mental health of days people will
Do you wrestle with
Some precious metal happen
Do do you have sometime today is
Things that I have done
Traditionally
I need to make a
I need to make some kind of a change
In order to
Myself out of the funk
A little bit you know sometimes
I meant I wanted one of my old habits was a shave my head
And I decided maybe that those days should be behind me
And I should get haircuts
And probably wise good with her hair for your age my man you got a
You got a rocket while you can
Yeah but so I decided
Sure
And so I got a back shaver naturally I have never shaved my
My back before in my 38 years of life
Here's the thing
I thought it would be super easy with one of those arms
The things those long razors that you can put behind your back
Why would you think it would be easy because it's a tool
It's like we have got this tool because we've made it this far at some point someone should have met
Play daytime easy-to-use vaccinate figured they had it covered
It's hard to shave your back
We have constructed a problem in order to make it easy we have
Got this weird thing
No it is not easy I don't like I did a good job at the only result
Experience because of it is it feels a little bit different and weird when I put a shirt on
Hey new experiences right now I'm struggling
That you know of
Obviously I love you you're my best friend you're my partner I really don't know if I've got it in me to shave your back for you
I just don't know I didn't ask
I know you didn't ask if that's why I'm saying this up front so we don't get into any aqua
Awkward situation preciate
I did take it anyway
I did a little late you know I did a little work on it and ran like
A couple hours later maybe I came back in a little bit
But anyway
I don't know I don't know what I'm going to do is probably because I shaved my arm
Arms in anticipation of getting that tattoo right that I didn't end up getting kicked off
I am so now I know my first my first like piece I got my entire like upper thigh
Whole thing done
And they shave the whole thing
Swear to God for another year at
Just kept shaving and it felt really good to me
Smooth I just kept on going I was like why stop now he knows it from like when I have shaved my head being in the shower and water
Hitting your bald head really great
Like there's something to that
Bi we'll see we'll see what happens
Anyway
I feel a little better
How about you
My bright spot is my wonderful my part my perfect wife she had
Both her covid booster and her flu booster yesterday
So this is a break for flu B
Yeah that functions as a psa2 everybody get your booster shots and all that stuff
I hear this season's flu is quite bad both from the CDC and anecdotally from
I would second that
Well I am happy for her luckily I am immune to all infectious
Diseases so I don't have to worry about it
It's nice that is one of the advantages
I had sort of prepared that we were going to
You know maybe go
Repast
Things are real boring
In 2003 I'm going to skip ahead for our next
It's time we go back to the past but
Unfortunately report back to
The present
Very important
That is the Trump announce
Yeah I took today we will be talking about
The aftermath of this on November
16th 2022
See how Alec wrestles with
The reality that he's going to have to make a choice
A huge Groundswell of excitement from what I'm hearing
Everyone
Apparently heard this and God God he's just trying to get out of jail
Weather
We did this dance already
Some people are saying God God God
But Alex is going to get down to
Really the the the nuts and bolts of it
He's going to talk about
His feelings
About this announcement
Play all the relevant coverage in the footage
Trump Trump's announcement
Do 1st June who got one
So it'd be wild if they didn't pick up a policy wonk at some point
I'm a policy wonk very much I got to say this brings up an important point and that is I think that
At least one of these other b y button
Might have got lost in the mail
How you may need to make some more because
I know that one has an out and I haven't heard back from anybody that it arrived
Just went out so there may actually
I think I might bump it up to 5
Okay I think that's what I might do all right I don't know I got to figure this out because it's really unsatisfied Stampy special
Lost
Happy birthday this is from Brenna but it is also back on
September 10th we are a little bit late but Happy birthday to your boss
Thank you very much
This is a different than from Chicago p.d. also a traitor and I support this message thank you so much and I apologize
Irritator Dan
Elliot from Melbourne the real Melbourne in Australia not that b******* one in Florida that keeps on getting my pass
Packages thank you so much
Melvin Melvin
Bebe
Text Buffa palooza in Burger flipping squashes thank you so much and I hope all is well
Thank you very much and early Alex Jones sounds like a man with a Perpetual mouthful of
Thank you so much
You're not a policy wonk
Next
We have a technocrat Jordan
This is it this is a fairly special London old old buddy of mine's
Dirty Laundry truck secrets are buried
You're now a tech
Start don't get mad until you're brilliant someone
Sodomites
I don't want
Jesus Christ old old buddy of mine
One of his nicknames would actually dachshund
It also goes by sweet butter
Is sweet butter on the streets
Sweet butter on the
Okay
He was one of the four people who lived in a house they were all year older than me will work
Movie theater together
And they lived at this house
I dropped out of high school until I was just over at their house all the time getting drunk
I haven't having a blast
Freedom in the irresponsible way
One day I don't know exactly what it was it might have been a party we had over the house it might have just been
Another night of me Chuck and booze
But iPad
Passed out on the front lawn and
I guess because it's a residential neighborhood and people didn't want for them
Frowned upon
Generally speaking
Lower property values
You can do it in one night in my favorite property value were
Looks by while your other The Lawns
Lehman everybody loses the grand on their value so I wake up the next morning
Unin on Direct
To someone kicking me
And a car horn honking and open up the tarp and it
So Mike has little brother
Antebellum that was not my finest hour
Anyway thank you sweet butter
Infused if you do see a man underneath the tarp your first thought is that body right your first thought is dead body
And that raises a lot of a lot more property valuation
What's the buy my bike has little brother
That's not a terrible idea if you were dead body
Not respectful
That's fair anyway we start here on the 6th
Steve and Alex
Straight into the Trump
Because there is other
Broadcast
Today
I told you probably
Show
Research
Shut up
So Alex is obsessed with bragging about how he had a knee-jerk announced
Vet the
Missile that had hit
Poland
Was probably a surface-to-air missile
Defense from Ukraine
Right now the signs are pointing to that being the case
And so you got something right accidentally and he is so excited right by virtue of knee-jerk.
Defending anything rush it does he may have inadvertently
Translate you got it right until you play with
The clip of himself
Saying this
On a previous show of course he does over and over again
Leaving the show okay
It was right if I was
Potentially right about topic
This is exactly like if he was in his office
Any like just
Threw a ball of paper all the way across into a into a garbage can
And nobody saw it but it was recorded so he's like I'm just
I'm going to play this over
You guys see this
I nailed it right in the Gazette right in the bed good job good job
Is Rodger Stone on a plate
Turbo Clips early go to Rodger this is Trump last night making them in an ounce
Running is running
2024 we told you
Months ago that
He had told people very close
The show
He was running
Today yet again you're not Vindicated
You said you was going to do it on the 4th of July to bility was roughly five months ago right
I mean like that's not fair it's not fair
Negative
I think just about anybody
Like
Could have ended predict Trump was going to run again
I think I think that's not like though the wildest tomorrow's news today kind of s***
You set to announce
Predicting that it was a
Ukraine anti defense missile
It was in the next war that I got it now it wasn't this world okay but 10 years from now it's the next door that I mailed
About 1
I think he could probably gained a little bit of like haha
I wasn't far off
If Trump announced on July 7th
So Alex
Here's one of them
Says we will take America back
We will put a
Stop
Electronic systems immediately
Voter IDs same-day voting and only paper ballots
I hear is the present announcing it
Night announcing my candidacy for president of the United States
We will do whatever it takes
To bring back on
In
Our
Eliminate
I will a meeting
Play the band voter-id
Esteemed a voting
Only paper ballots
Alex plays a few clips
Trump speech
But he doesn't play some of them that I think we're a really troubling
I think he's maybe should have commented on was when he called cities in America cesspools of blood
Sure cesspools of blood
I don't know if that even makes gramatik sense
He said they were going to go to Mars base on Mars
What's happening
There was a period where he got lost in the term quarters of
Sure we're going to take the quarters back
He clearly was all scripted just like I want those quarters
Important thing I think
Event Alex needs to Rabat
Hear or talk about is
Trump went on a
White protracted rant about how you need to kill drug deal
Dealers in China they have
Quick trials
Where they would to catch a drug dealer and then have a quick trial and then that night baby x
Executed and that's what we've got to do here in America
And he even said
It's the only way
What
80% of the people I have ever met have dealt
Drugs at one point or another
Tell me baby all dead
Yeah I
I think that's a little bit unhinged
I think it's a
Terrifying
I would say almost
A large portion of the country is leaning
Much much more towards decriminalization
More States
Are legalizing recreational use of marijuana at roses like
This is your drug dealer
Is that I would have expected
I mean it's
Listen far be it for me to not have my pulse on the the modern voter
But I don't think you can go from paper ballots is
The Hallmark of my campaign ad also
Murder on a daily base
I mean it would be
Outrageous the amount of murder you would be doing as the state
Listen to this
Fatburgers so offensive to him
To hear has a libertarian
Oh yeah yeah
And then to Trump is talking about this as like something that he talked to she about in like
This is something that's trying to does well that's how it should be offended by the idea of taking policy decisions
From communist China
Yai
Wondering
If conservatives are aware so far
That's from their tea party beginning
They have
Conservative them
Selves all the way into thinking Sharia law is actually pretty great
As long as we don't call it that we call it Christian law put a little bit of a different branding
Why not have a dictatorship and murder people all the time
Right
Do you want to do on a dime sack real smaller stuff here is Alyssa
He can't be
We got to kill him we got to kill
40% of America right now
It's
I mean look that obviously was
Baby drop going a little off script
His prepared remarks
A lot of it was so boring cuz you just reading like reading a prepared thing
Contrite
That part was
Deeply upsetting
Based on
Like Alex's respond
Especially like
I question whether Alex watch the full hour or two
Right I imagine he might not have
And second if he has them I would say that the
Goal or the
Do you know the move is just like well
That's bad
Let's pretend you didn't say that
Go let's just go around the side of it
Yeah I feel like that
Seems to be the main move for just about
At this point let's just pretend you didn't say any
Let's just get out of really really troubling thing
So Alex
Now that Trump is announced
Has a feeling about
I've been on the fence about Trump
Santa
Extraction
But she called omio khonjin the Democrats in the Deep state
And Ivanka and Jared come out again
Call Dad
Really makes
Text me like Trump more
And watching entire media pylon
Really likes
Really makes me
How much
Power structure
That's
This is so annoying
The more this boat runs into this iceberg
The more I think this Titanic is going to make
I think is if we keep reliving this Iceberg a little bit harder I know we're taking on water right
But I think we can
Through
Everybody hates this guy and I got to say
Like him
I got like that about it
Idiot family wishes murder Autumn what's that my highest list
So that you know he's good
So Rodger is on
Images
Also assign
You know like
If you're having Rodger on for the response that means you want Pro Trump cover
Rodger not only thinks
That the 2016 election they tried to
The 2020 election
Vastola
22 midterm was stolen but what about
Obviously challenging
History Alex only once in our
American
Asia president
Grover Cleveland
I was liking 1885
In 1888
It was stolen from him and
Disputed election
Where he clearly by-the-way got a majority the popular vote
And then he came by we caring about that now 9
The energy the room last
Remind me of 2050
15 + 20
60 it was
The old
Trump
Hie
Established
He was very
Brandi was very much
On message
That is not true you ranted about killing drug dealers
For a bit but you just said it was old Trump
Both
Percentage of the word share
Death of Grover Cleveland was robbed man I mean I do recall he won the popular vote and there was some shady
Backroom dealing but if it's important to remember
He won the popular vote
He did not
Lose the popular vote in all of his election then I was like I was robbed was robbed
Right
If the standard of like winning an election is the popular vote
Against
Use that you got to pretend that doesn't happen so you had to go back
240 years
Whatever
So if you're still in the Rica
Construction errors
It's been a tick
So Alex
People hate Trump
Like it I like it
I saw a Rupert Murdoch
Called Trump
Like he did
Six seven years ago instead
Continue to run I'm not going
Well I mean he did that
Flip flop
Good morning
Captain
He's got the established
Lined up against
Not good
Lined up for him
That does not bode well for
Rupert Murdoch hates Trump as a person and has for a long time before his 26
16 Rock
A big media figure and Burdock is in the public
Publishing business
Unfamiliar with each other at that point
Gradually Jared Kushner convince Murdock to sit down and talk with Trump and this led to Murdock realizing the Trump was actually
All signs pointed to him being the inevitable Republican nominee so he endorsed
I'm sure he would have preferred a different primary candidates who won the nomination but I don't
I think he was going to back
I think he would have
Just feeling I've
You don't like the
This guy
Alright fine he's running good
Important
To keep in mind as as people keep trying to throw narratives around people long before
Anything you been
Close to a presidential election is run
Is that hay
F*** all of these they're arguing bulshit at the end of the day they're going to get in line behind races
Is the most common
Okay I mean
16 should teach a lot of lessons
About the primary and how
Sort of humiliated
So many people were who were
Trying to take Trump out in
In the primary
They
Fell in line like that
Cowards and weaklings they are
So Alex is really just kind of trying to just
By supporting Trump basically I mean that's the overall Vibe you're getting here
It looks
Coming out more
Start coming out saying no mandate which is already done
And really hammers
Stay away from children
And now more more trumps doing that
In the right direction
I hear you was last night
I will get
Biden's radic
Take a left ideology
Out of our military and I did
I did and in the fridge
Executive
It was gone
We will abolish
Everybody
Didn't covid Band-Aid
And rehire every patriot who was fired
From our military
Weather Nepal
And fullback
Oh boy
What
What are we
Talking about
We're talking about hiring
Maxine
Deny our folk you didn't want to get a vaccine
Understand conservatives living wackadoodle world
And that's great
But I just didn't know that that was a thing that would get an Applause
I wouldn't somebody be like
Hey what about you
All of the other problems that were facing you're talking about like drug dealers living
I would have gone with a different policy thing again sounds like an insane person
Diary
You're not wrong so
You're not getting here is a visual
Thank God
So I'm going to allow
Trump live
Great
Photo up
Rodger
Live
You guys all look great
Schloss
2 lb or something
Dude looks good
Chess
Define
Find
Looks good crate
Great
Good look
Presidential
60 lb down
Okay
He's plump than usual
He's on his 10th bag of blood today
So Rodger has some feelings
What about the House of Representatives
So now that the GOP is going to be
Control
Bolin Wiki
Angel
Kevin McCarthy
Selected over Andre
Andrew Beggs
Is essentially meaningless
Make
McCarthy
Speaker the only
That makes him speaker
Is the vote of the Full House
In early January
Juncture
He has to have
At least 280
To become speaker
Publicly
Did he has
2 block
That elect
Alberta
The block that elect
And all I
Pretty good politics
I agree so what why
Why is Trump
Endorsing a
Fawning all over Kevin McCarthy
I find that problematic
Myself I've argued against it
Explain Trump
Force of Nature and
Sometimes he's wrong
That's the kind of guy you want in charge you know what I want somebody who won't listen to anybody and doesn't change his mind even
Even if he's wrong
Absolutely not become speaker of the house and if he does try to pull a power play he could f***
Ground because of really undesirable outcome
The only way that this
This works is if he holds the party hostage
If Gabe has like seven votes.
The commit to not
Not flipping no matter what
He could threaten to tank the GOP winning the speakership
In that situation I guess he could try to force the rest of the GOP reps to get in line with him or let a Democrat be speaker
But I don't
See that possibility happening
I think the best thing you can do and I mean this is kind of just decent politics
Is
Threatened to do this and then negotiate some kind of a concession
With McCarthy
Maybe some
Positions in
To be the speaker
McCarthy is going to be the speaker that is why Trump is being nice to him because they live in Rio
Reality I would say that Matt gaetz is probably smart enough to realize
That if his profile goes up any higher people are finally going to put him in jail where he belongs
I'm pretty sure he's a criminal of
Many different types I think he problem
It's me as the sort who would love
To be speaker in that role I didn't do what I think you would but
The the reality of these numbers
This just doesn't work for him he would have
Have to
Essentially and like
Really of the majority leader or the speaker in
Party leadership chat
About corralling boats
It's about
Getting people on the same
Pedro
And if you have seven people or whatever that you're holding the vote hostage for
Going to be very difficult for you to
To take all the leadership position of all those people you're just pissed off
Just yourself to be
In charge of it just
I don't I don't I know that Rodger knows though
Yeah yeah he's being a little bit
No it's it's what it's wiser to take a I mean a in any negotiating position
You start by saying I would like
100%
Of what it is that we're going to go for and they're like
How about we give you 10
And then you argue from there you know like Matt gaetz
I'm going to see you this week or that was instead
How about you get a nice chair and he's like
I like a nice
Yeah like that's how it work
You'll end up with a committee position or something and everybody will move on
So
Look
Rodger
Had some harsh words
For DeSantis
He's clearly now coming onto a more Trump
Position
Where he was kind of like
Both sides
Alex as a
DeSantis is better about the vaccine
Narrative
And Rodger wants Alex
Get off that
Go back to the point you made it the very top I want to be very clear about this
His position on
Auctionnation
Is it digital
If I need to bring you the video of Ron
Katie Michelle
It will protect you from infection
I can do them wrong
Been coming out against it more and I put in that good
Surgeon General that I would
I'm not a politician
Metronomy party
And so I want Trump
To really hurt
Operating on the issues
And I know you do as well
Political
Area
I don't Rodger
Today
Both of them
Oppose mandatory
Opposed
Vaccination
Oceans for those
In the military
Both of them opposed the mask
Their positions are again
Rhetorical
You're right the governor has been more
Aggressive about it
But
The end of the day their positions are denicol
It's interesting how Alex's just like I am
Issue guy
I hate vaccines right and if Trump will just
Do the thing that I want him to do I'll write a story where he's fine
I'll come up with a way to like convince myself that it's all good because
He's doing what I want him
Yeah right
That's about it cool
I do appreciate the I'm an issues guy and my issues are
If everyone including his family hates him
That makes me think he's pretty
A good pretty good guy for the job
I think that that's not an issue for me
Rodger wants to scientist to stay governor
I want
Continue the job he's doing
As governor
He's been very
42 years old
I said yet again
If he wants to run
It's his prerogative
I think
He clears the field
I'm not sure he
Sustain
Alarm
Conversation
He is very good
Controlled environment
He's very control is very good one he controls
Microphone
But in a wide-open free
Fighting debate
With a brawler
Like Donald Trump
Personality
He has he has presents
He's got some off and has itself
Deprecating
Humor
The governor's trying to
Charmless
In that regard
Trump has like
A lot of
Ways you could die
Describe his humor but self-deprecating isn't one of
His candidacy with
We are the greatest movement perhaps that has ever happened in the greatest country on Earth
Yeah we are we are
It is in a self-deprecating
You could read it that way because it's
So narcissistic that you think well there's no way a Riesling
Reasonable human being would be anything but
But cleverly sarcastic about bisque
Absurd thing to say even if he's
Operating in the realm of parity I don't think it's
It's still a self-deprecating absolutely appropriate
Play something like that about Ron DeSantis 2 days ago
I would say can handle itself accepted a control
Environment
Charisma Lacey at Rodger just said there was
Trump is going to make him mad and then DeSantis
This is going to ride up dropping all the Slayers that he does
Wednesday on the regular
The face is going to be a dick to him know how to handle it and it'll look like an idiot
Although I will say I was I was very confident that that was how it would go and we'll go
Up until I read the
Trump's insults Brandis sanctimonious
Garbage
Sauce
Garbage sauce first attempt
Yeah it's bad if that's what he's going to come with
I'm not worried about Ron DeSantis getting mad I don't think I don't think we're in the throwing hands phase of the
Just opening
Right right
We'll see how it goes all right
So I only
Say who you
Between trumpet DeSantis
Man I'm supporting
I think overall
Is the better choice in Rage assassin
System
They're totally scared of him and
I seen established
DeSantis
Makes my skin crawl but I don't
Okay so I'm not going to say who I'm in favor of but one game only gets a positive things about and then the other one was saying negative
Sing about
So you could decide
I am hedging my bets
In the least
Legible way
Hey I am going to bed at all 99% on this one
And then 1% on the other
So you know that I have not yet decided between the
Strategic flexibility
So Rodger has a x
Split Nation
For the midday
Okay now we remember
Boats
For North Korea I recall that they were involved in 2020 as game here
No he does not I mean
This is the wrong distinctive on Venus
Whether we nominate
Former President Donald Trump
Weather Menomonie
Governor
Santa Shore we nominate
If we can't have
Free
Fair
Honest
Transparent
Elections
What's just happened in Arizona
Is an abomination
Did the night before the election
Are the correct
19 in
Long
Election day
The paper ballots
That are sent to only Republican Precinct
20 inches long
Ethically made
Not
In one case election judge I spoke to said
A person tried to get
The tabulator
Received their ballot
Dean times and it was rejected
Why was rejected
Because the trays
Inside the
The calculator are not made
To take
This wasn't done
Biax
This was done willfully
So apparently the globalists know that they couldn't get away with election hacking fraud
This time and that too many people were out looking
Looking for the ballot mule
So they could
Stop do you know that
There's no good
So the only way they could think
To steal the election was sending ballots an inch too big
Republican polling places
Here's what I like
About their terrible play
Right all right one the globalist have terrible plans because these people have terrible plans and no imagination
Right
The thing about it is
There are diminishing returns that their best state
India is a bad
Plan
2 years ago
So now we're all the way down to Badland number 55
And globalism
Bad plan is
Haha
Add a niche you know how obvious this would be to trace back
Like in terms of the production orders of like
Who made it an inch bigger
It would be required in order to do this would leave such a huge part in the paper turn out
Very obvious
Investigation
This is based on the theory that was published in the Gateway pundit relying
Coolio the expertise of one person a guy named Ann Sundin
Have you ever this article in Gateway pundit there's a hat tip
Do David and Erin
Clements who presumably brought this all to the attention
Of Jim hoft twin brother
David Clements is a New Mexico State University Business School Professor who's been suspended from his position because of
Enid mask mandate
Backpack
Actually I ended with
Also he's got
Collect a salary while he's gone on tour around the country
Rally's about how the 2020 election was stolen among other various brightwing
Conspiracy topics
He's been on that reawakened America Tour
Clemens has been making interview videos on Rumble about election fraud nonsense since 2020 and he's
He's interviewed luminaries like Ron Watkins
Naturally damn Sundin
Associates in this election fraud stuff over
For the years unbiased
Expert to the Gateway pundit
I have no idea who Damn Sundin is other than that his resume is always written
Super vague
On all of these websites
He is an expert I know that all right I can tell you one thing about it
You've not the same damn Sundin who's on the FBI's most wanted list for cyber crimes
Because I watched a video interview with the guy from the election
Broadcast spiracy
Andy's look
Nothing like the FBI's Most Wanted flyer plastic surgery
Ramen you could age hide in plain sight
I'm I'm fairly convinced
100percentpure B.
Of course it is like
Unique enough name
That I was
Free
Since before and bolts in the field of
Like Technologies
Not not the
It's not the criminal right
Anyway Alex was right about this missile
Thing until Rodger needs to congratulate him about it
This is really quite extraordinary look how I got up late
Today cuz I was up
Celebrating the
Historic announcement of Ghana
And therefore
When I went
Too bad I heard
Russian missiles
Attack
Then when I came on your broadcast
I saw you
Laying out
The truth
Figuring it will everybody else
Probably be saying
Alex
Nobody
Other than Infowars by and large
Is reporting
The truth
This undermines
The important gym Infowars NY
They are so desperate
To take you down
Addition realize the importance
Infowars nyi
Show value
Form and
Forum
Because I know
Whenever there is a
Concerted effort
Propaganda regardless
Regardless what the
Weather
Donald Trump
Weather in Chicago
DeSantis or whether it's
The situation in Ukraine or whether it
What the red Chinese are up to
Used to go to find out what it is
Really going on
Fearlessly
And when the knowledge
Spiritual Theory
Streaming Stick
It's what always
Makes me laugh
White supremacist
Is Infowars
This is such b******* like these assholes Pat themselves on the back so hard every time one of the random denials they make
Make accidentally happened
The end up being accurate
Alex did say that he thought the missile that hit Poland was a surface-to-air missile from Ukraine
And it's now. That is the
But
So dishonest for him to pretend he was the only person talking about
A Newsweek article from a day before this episode was recorded said quote
The Associated Press initially cited an unnamed Cedar us intelligence confirming
That Russia was a
Indeed behind the cross-border strike
Hours later the same Outlet cited three us officials
Who said preliminary assessment suggests the missile was fired by Ukrainian forces
In an attempt to
To intercept
An incoming Russian missile
On the same day is this episode Business Insider published an article including quote
A statement
From the office
Poland's president said it was
Highly probable
That Ukraine had launched
The surface-to-air missile in response
Do the Russian barrage and that quote
We have no evidence at the moment
That the russian-made s-300 missile was fired by rushing for
There were a lot of people some random people on Twitter and Summit official position
For jumping the gun to blame Russia that is fair enough
But what Alex and Rodger doing is
Just as bad as any of those people
They're manufacturing a fake
Consensus that they stand in opposition
They're pretending
That everybody in the media everyone in Government powers
Establishment we're pushing the message
That Russia did this on purpose and the Article 5 should be info
And it was
Infowars
Steve wrongly maligned
Please write truth-tellers
Who had the courage to stand up and say that it looks like
Like it could be a surface-to-air missile
This is an illusion
They weren't the only ones to voice this kind of concern in this possibility
This is why
White supremacist outlet and they're constantly wrong about almost everything
Alex didn't think Putin was going to try and invade past the dawn boss
And said that zelensky was a double agent working for Putin
He said that Russia had paid off the Ukrainian Army so the war was only going to last a few days
He said the Putin was going to pump up probably nuke us tomorrow for like the last
2 months
Alex is full of s*** but every now and again
One of the things that he says out of a knee-jerk Defiance accidentally happen
And double look
Inaccurate
And you
You can tell how rare It Is by how excited he gets and how often he needs to bring these things up
He's played
Clip of him saying the missile was a surface-to-air missile three times on this episode I believe
I think
I think about every time he has to answer for how he's constantly wrong about everything he just yells jussie Smollett
Okay great yeah
How to make such a cantic deal out of these rare instances and pretend to be thousands of times he's been wrong never happen
And because this has the effect
Spectre subtly tricking the audience into thing
But he's right way more frequently than he actually is
It's a pretty simple and very intentional manipulation tagged
Is it going to guess it works
Yeah
The weird thing is this is probably the one spot where you could really kind of dig in with a conspiracy theory
They just did that
She's kind of
That kind of works either
Either way
You know like a
If you're saying to me
Take the conspiracy theory
Is all the governments involved in this except for the Ukrainian government
Have kind of correctly realize that if it is Russians
Missiles
They did fire them at even if it was an accident it did cross over into Poland
That's a real big problem
Right
If it's an accident
Maybe we all just say Ukraine baby accident and then it's less of a problem still a problem
But it's not the same problem now is it now if that what if we find out
60 years later they do the investigation and that's true
Fine that's great
It's just
Why are you saying that you got
This part right this is a boring part
I understand I understand what you're saying boring narrative
Conspiracy should be what you're saying
Can't
Because that would require him to say that Russia
Right but I mean then he also gets to say everybody on the way in the west is lying I mean I'd so confusing
Right but they're lying
Runaway that is advantageous
The Russia is angle would be
Actually attack a NATO country
I think I think you would have some problems spinning get drunk
If you were is you're talking about just like writing a
Conspiracy theory
You're right it is a dozen
More
Like intriguing Yarns
Yeah
So you got a
Support info
We know that
And there's a reason
And it's
He has a billion and a half dollars
Well that
That's the real reason
But there's a storytelling reason
Comedian makes fun of Rodger Stone
Challenge
Sign Stone
Yep
Films high quality
Supplements
And so please
You're not going to get the information we're not to cover next hour
Anywhere else
Euthanasia
Children has now begun
Starting here
What
I was reporting on
Yesterday
I'ma start the next hour on that
Oh boy
So yeah they're euthanizing children that's why you've got a
Supportive
So just what are they content warning
I guess I don't think anything is
To severe but there's a lot of conversation about like assisted suicide
In the in the coming clips
Some feelings
That's going to be a
Much like Raptors it will Factor heavily into this conversation
So here's that you know
Alex
We always love it when he
Tells us about how
We Belong
The city we do belong to
But sometimes
There's other songs
But he rants over we can belong to many places
If I'm like a judge I'm giving this 104.7
Evil force
In the history
They're covered operations have now been drawn out in the open
Process
Trying to break us
Their downfall
It has been foretold
And now
Beginning
Manifest
There's a mind of man
Envision
Overtime
You're able to rely
Ugliness
Gas obstruction
Kelly manifest
Copic
System Hollywood
Stretch
We will manage
God has given
And our stairway
Heaven
I want to do this
I'm going to Come Back Inn
Read the latest
Roll out
They've been baited
Government intimidated social
Suicide
Wow yeah
No I think
Pinkeye mostly gave it a 4.7 because I think it songs all right
Yeah I mean it doesn't have the timing right at the beginning you know he's talking over the wrong
Song parts
And they're just so you know there's just songs that have
It's just
You Belong To The City that makes it
Perfect for yelling not enough I don't know what it is but it sounds like something I could definitely
They have on in the background
Snow
I've started the crack the code
I think Alex really just like saying and now
He likes it who hasn't spent a couple of days getting into the La Fontaine for a little too long
Come on
You know world
J'adore
Ditto world
So here we go
Alex gets down to business
Incites these two stories
Already has
Regarding
Assisted suicide
Is it like that killing children euthanizing children pray and government social credit score
Blah blah blah
Together
Do all of this
We're going to be getting to
Shoulder that frown
It's one of the report's globalist push
Mass
Suicide
So these are the two stories that Alex is operating off of and I guess they proved that the government is trying to force people into being youth
Sure the first headline that he read is Canadian law it's just the title of a
The great race video those cribbing mostly from a Tucker Carlson segment
And that take me to self is reporting on an article that was posted on Barry Weiss's Subs
All of this just boils down to the Canadian Parliament passing the revision to their medical assistance in dying legislature
Also known as their maid maid legislation Sheriff about who is eligible
To receive that care
This revision was passed in March 2021
But it doesn't take effect
Until next year
In that revision they repealed the requirement that the patient's natural death
Was quote reasonably foreseeable
Which is to say that they opened up this kind of care to patients
2 or not immediately terminal
But might be living in
A terrible amount of pain that is
Treatable
The revision also specified quote
Person to Soul underlying medical condition is mental illness are not eligible
For medical assistance and died
That is something that is obscured by Tucker's coverage and then now Alex's
Just completely lying
Even if you take everything that Tucker says in his report as truth
Person who Keys Bass
His entire story on his 23 years old
So this is not a child
Yeah
The headline quotes globalist
Push mass suicide is just a video that was posted on Band. Video
It's a John bowne report just
A lot of it is
Covering similar territory and so Alex
And I'm talking about the globalist
The second headlines
Tubidy
The first one does bring up a
Fairly important conversation which is
Be sticky issues
Around assisted end-of-life care
Obviously I do support access to this guy care but there are cases where things can be a little bit complicated
I do think that these are things that people should be talking
Perspectives of folks Tucker and Alex are worth
They aren't dealing with the issues as they actually exist they're creating a fake version of the issue to use as a prop to attack their prey
Political enemies and keep their audiences in fear about how they're going to force your kids to be euthanized or whatever
And in reality
When we get this there is going to be going to play a little bit of the gray grease report
It is
Kind of a weird situation
Actually I have a suggested solution to a Malak
Whole crew
So anyway here's the intro
The gregorys report
Big Banks 2 the human is promoting
Government
Termination of
Physically disabled
Calling it liberal and trendy
Bill Gates
On steroids
There is a critical graduation
I'll give you the rest
Public Storage
First of all I can't believe that Alex doesn't call these Reese's Pieces
It's such a f****** missed opportunity
No happen instantly
Peace out peace from Reese himself
Aretha Aretha
Yeah you should watch out for
No they do Reese's Pieces would be so good
I don't think they get sued
When he goes to church
She's always talk about race
Jesus
Anyway this is a
Completely inaccurate description of the report the entire underlying story
But here is the beginning of the report
The film Soylent Green
Was made
In 1970s
NSAID
Topian world
In the year
Where the government is restoring the people food it was made of people
Cold
Pleasant experience
Estate
Assistance
Suicide
While government-run media
Is the idea
Cannibalism
Government assisted
Suicide
Is officially now a thing
Medicine
To keep you alive
What
For insurance
These days
The hospital seemed more likely to liquid
And they will help you kill your
I don't really want to die
Amir farsooda has applied for medically is
Assisted dying known as made
He lives in constant agony
Start the process
Because his rooming houses
For sale any can't find anywhere else
Live that he can afford
He barely survived Ontario Disability support
Hundred dollars a month
He doesn't want to die
But being homeless
It's not an option
I know in my
Present health condition I would
Survive it anyway
There is no answer in Alex's world for this problem other than to let pursued die on the street
They would be opposed to the government paying for his housing they will be opposed to the government providing with free healthcare so what the app
Actual answer
I'm not saying the pursued should go to assisted suicide because of the circle
Constanta is like
But I think that this
Situation does highlight a really sticky issue where the reality of what he's living through
Brings into Focus how cruel the system itself
We is
This video from the Canadian news is about a month
The old and five point Reese's making this video
Fursuit head actually launched a successful GoFundMe
I need raise $60,000 to secure his housing and he's gone public that he no longer is
Considering medically-assisted
Pursued has a really good perspective on the ethical issue about how his poverty
Was driving his thinking
From a Toronto City News article
Quote he said government
Should be focused
On fixing the issue causing poverty rather than the more RAM
Implications of those in poverty seeking made
I think the proper solution is
Do not have that problem is to alleviate what's causing
Problem
If Society is concerned about people like me and like
Million other people on
ODSP
PM property
Then bring them out of poverty
That's the obvious solution
If they were out of poverty and they had a roof over their head and food in their mouths I guarantee you made wouldn't be a
Consideration
The whole debate would become
Superfluous
I'm certain that Infowars will not follow up on the story and cover this comment from first food because
They aren't interested in this respect
They want to use him as a prop
To build up a fraudulent argument that the government is trying to force people to kill themselves
But they'd honestly be pretty fine with letting him die on the street
Especially if they knew like
But they could call him a communist
For his ideas
Or whatever you know like this but this is a little bit of a difficult
He has an underlying
A chronic
Health condition
There is miserable for him to live with without
Proper care and a place to live
Any poverty is threatening access to that medical
Care
To live
Obviously the solution isn't
Well
Vertically
Suicide
Hey buddy
Highlights how someone in that situation
Would look at that as like well I'm going to die on the street anyway
Let's start
The clear the Clear Point is almost kind of
Tusimple insofar as
Like
What is the point of the government
Of all of us together if we can't even basic
You can get them simple Maslow's hierarchy of needs handled you know
And if you're saying that I can't have
Eaccess
Food water or shelter
Consistently or or
Guaranteed
If I can't have guaranteed access to those
Then death is
Borderline a lateral move
Or at the very least I'm living right next to it every single day of my life
That's what he's expressing
Really what you're saying is that whoa whoa whoa whoa we want God to kill you
We don't want you to have control over anything
Yeah it end
I I just I think that Beyond this were bored being embarrassingly produced
Doesn't
It doesn't really touch
What the real issue
Who is here
Or what
The the subject of the stories perspective
And I think that that is
Dishonest
Ingenuous
Exploding people's discomfort with death
Using that same emotional trigger
Like they do with
Lgbtq or any number of those things that allows you to
Override
Here even ability to think
And really when you break this down this Amir fursuits
Story is about somebody who is
Facing the prospect
I'm living on the street with a chronic
Condition
Causes severe pain
And all this
Bambi
Because of that he's gay
Considering
End-of-life
Medical assistant
Right
That is
The story
It is about the poverty driving
This
With the underlying medical condition
And of course is not just his poverty bright
It's being reported on Infowars as an instance of the government wanting to
To kill you
Yeah and that's not
Correct
No
He's exploiting
This person's
Pain
Because
Quite frankly
If presented accurately
The audience would come to the conclusion
Too easily that the answer is the opposite of Alex's polity
I mean well the answer is in a in a certain sense
The government is killing him slowly
And that's why he's considered
That's the point
Is that if you're saying that the government is doing
Their job well right now
That is going to lead to this man's death you have sentenced him to death
And you sentence him to pain as he waits for it
So there's more to this report
Greg's analysis
I already did
According to the Canadian government
They are getting several requests
For suicide
From children
Do they refer to as
Mature minors
And they are seeking to amend the laws
So that these children can be euthanized
Without their
Parents consent
There are posts
On social media that suggest
This might be
Betru we shouldn't surprise anyone
It really concern any of Reese's viewers that he seems to be citing the Canadian government but also saying that post on social
Media seem to indicate
This is true
Like that's not good
And it should tell you the great did zero research on this subject
Social media Post in the government
So here are some things you need to keep in mind
Assisted dying for children has been legal in the Netherlands since 2002 and in the intervening 13 years
7 children deprived themselves of that care
Belgium made this it's kind of metal
Willcare legal in 2014 and three children sought that care
Between 20
16 + 27
It's something that has a precedent
And other countries experience tells us that it's something that's used by people including children who has severe medical condition
That are not treatable and caused a great deal of supper
Mature minor is a term that exists in Canadian and American law already
It's not something that's being used specifically in this case
Which is how Greg is
Definitely trying to make it sound
The Council of Canadian
Academies did a study
And their conclusion was that the law
Already exists that mature minors can make medical decisions
For themselves that involved
Informed consent
And that there isn't really a compelling reason that this should be any different
When it comes to medically-assisted
That the reason
Something that makes
This a different
Case from other informed consent
Surrounding
Mature minors
The only thing that makes it different
Friend is your discomfort with
You know scientifically automatically or whatever you know possibility in your mind
That maybe we will find a cure or something you know sure cold hard logic
Doesn't give you an excuse to be like I but this is different just because
The organization dying with dignity and suggested
Safeguard where informed consent
Apparel Guardian would be required for patients aged 12 to 15 and
Patient with a parent or Guardian would be required for people
860 + 7
Which seems like I mean it's not going
I without the parent's consent even for these mature minors we shouldn't have
The ability
Me to record
Recognize consent to
It's up in terms of their medical decisions
Even if you're 16 or 17 it would still require consultation with a parent or
Yeah I know I mean
The numbers themselves of already
Make something
Really clear which is black
If it's been
Available
Since 2002 or 2004 whatever
And in the intervening time a total of
7 people
The population cycle 30
40% of their body
Next Generation
Text Lee they got to start all over
It is a very small numbers
I think I think it is something that
We can
Trust people at 80 is it somebody is struggling with suicidal ideation and and of course
The Tempest
It is it is like
You can trust people too
To want to live
You know there are times when you don't
But at the end of the day if you're if you have to wait up
Month
You you're going to find a reason to go to let you want to live
You just want to
Honestly
Like
The the circumstances that these
Children and their parents are in
Art so difficult to imagine
I don't
No
I don't think
That the government certainly should ever be like hey you should kill your kid and I don't think that is happening
I don't think I've ever done that ever one time no
Think that if a parent and a doctor and the child are all
Kind of the mind of like
This suffering is never going
It's so hard
For the effect the child dozen
Want to continue to feel like the government
Really
It seems very cruel.
To not allow
Call option
There should be absolutely support a f***
This law
You know it's a hard complicated and emotionally heavy subject don't get why people have strong emotional wreck
Directions around these kinds of issues but from the bottom of my heart
I have to say
And continue to stress
The Alex and enforce contribution to this conversation
You worthless
And counterproductive
They aren't even living in reality
I don't
Just think
They should shut the fuk up I know
It's not helping there's so many things where it is like
Of All That Jazz
Stay out of this
You know like I'm mad at them for all alright but I'm mad at him for all of their bulshit but
Sometimes they just go places where it's like just
Just f****** stay away from the
Getaway
It's different for you and me probably the things that they have that reaction to
But I think I find it more offensive when there is a point
Again
The the Maybe
Everybody should have
Free access to end of universe
That is somewhere where there is
Conversation
You know he's
Is relevant and they're right
Prayer
They're making that conversation much more difficult to have in a sane and rational world
Right and I think that hurts the people who
Are most hurt already
Yeah you should let me know
A reasonable conversation include
Sissy for the people that this is
Panang 2
By themselves
Dealing with all this stuff
And instead it
People arguing about the government trying to kill you
So yesterday last clip for by great report this is f*****
Consume
And a motive for helping Canadians kill themselves
Is allegedly
To save the government money
Allegedly million-dollar
So
And that's like
Four missiles flying to Ukraine
The government has infinite money for
Refugees and for
You know foreign aid and for
Democratic campaigns and fur
Waging War in Ukraine
But no money.
Keep people alive
That's too expensive
Couple million foreigners every year put them on the
Free healthcare
What
Average Canadian
Sorry
It's time to Suicide it's time for death
After 6,000
+ 65
Individual
Committed suicide
With the help of made
Medical assistance
In dying
The Canadian government save
.9 million-dollar
About $13,000
Person
That's what an individual's life
Is worth
In Canada what
Running
Savings from made are so far negligent
What does suicide program
Should continue
Don't cost that much
Really
Wrapping this up
Maybe you could have people pay tickets like maybe
Maybe this is solution maybe in Canada
You pay like
10000 bucks and you get to kill somebody
This is the predictable outcome
Unbelievable
Totally predictable that's exactly what I was thinking
Stabbing chair
I think it was
The only evidence is being provided here that the government of Canada is motivated by saving money is Harrison Smith another in
Infowars employee saying so
This is not good report
In reality the number that Harrison is siding comes from an October 2020 report titled
Cost estimate for Bill c-7
Medical assistance in Dyer
Who conducted by the Parliamentary budget officer and it was prompted by the request
Cast of an unnamed senator
They looked at numbers
From the Netherlands and Belgium as guides and found that it would be about 90 million in medical
Expenses would be saved by the
Well basically what they're both sight and Greg and Harrison
However it's very clear this report when it says quote
Many Studies have shown that healthcare costs in the last year of Life Ardis
Proportionately High representing between
10 and 20% of Total Healthcare cost
Despite these patients representing about 1% of the population
Nevertheless
This report should in no way be interpreted as suggesting that made can be used to reduce
Healthcare costs
This is
How Harrison is interpreting the report and then Greg is using Harrison's
Fraudulent interpretation to the jet
Canadian government
Is motivated by Financial
Consideration
Do Opera assisted dying
Kancare does bulge
The actual report the Harrison is sighting
Includes this part
That he conveniently ignored
Include expanding access to maid will result in a net reduction and healthcare costs
For the provincial
However this reduction represents a negligible portion of the healthcare budgets of the province
Doctor
New saputro route
In 2017
We should strive to save on suffering and invest more in its
Jan which may in turn reduce
Request for medical Aid in dying
Infowars and everyone who work there are raft of liars
Their argument suck
They just make
Most of what they're saying up and the rest is based on them abusing primary sources
And misrepresenting them
And the solution to the problem they're pretending to be so upset about is the thing that they entirely don't support
Does more government spending on social welfare program
This is just a dead end of them
I'm complaining about something they don't care about the begin with
I mean living even he even says that the government says it's negligible it's almost like in the report that guys are like
Why are you make
I don't want to do the
Cost budget analysis for a
Why did I wake up today and have to
To do the cost budget analysis
Suicide
Harrison's
Like his whole thing is like all they have all this money to send things to Ukraine but not to keep people up
Oh so you want the government
Set
Priorities
The federal government
Bunch of f***************
Stop just tell me wait if you could point you old what you want then say it and back it up and then whenever you find out you're a f******
Idiot say I'm sorry for being an idiot
All right how am I God
So Alex
Finally gets
Calls he said at the beginning of this episode
Take all the
Please call Spectrum
Cuz we got to find out
What the temperature holding
Informal anecdotal
So here's the first caller
Alex
We need to have
I'd like to have a realtor
On Donald Trump
This subject
Really really bothering me
John don't forget
I'll get his name and number
We will do
How many gas do I have tomorrow
Will do
2 hours
I'm called on
Is Trump good
Or do people support
I have mixed feelings as well
Okay
Appreciate you
Did Charles back on tomorrow
That's what you're supposed to be doing nothing you said you were hungry and I made that unreal
Punt Pass
The whole thing is supposed to be taking calls what do you think about Trump and his announcement
So
So anyway
In Las Vegas Nevada
Go ahead
Going
What's going on
How in the world are you
When there's
Any children
Bodies
More and more
We shot
He's backing off
When I watch that
Interviewer podcast
Greatest
Achievement of his administration
That was
I don't think
Perfect
I'm just glad he's backing off of them
Do you take the Santa's better being back
Deep state
I think we need to get
Brand new
Say something
The RICO Act
Treason
Gold
For how long
We've gotten here B
Hey everybody
I'm having flashbacks
We're just never going to change
Oh yeah maybe
Let's do that again let's run it again everybody from the top
So this caller actually has a good point in terms of remembering Alex's rhetoric
Remember what Alex's says and then speak it back to him he goes oh at makes me feel how can you possibly
Be in favor of this person who has murdered a million children or whatever
Stacking up millions of bodies repair poisonous shot
Alyssa
I have some problem
Right haystacks
Except a lot of bodies
Short
Sure but who is going to trigger the lip
Screw
As no charisma
So Alex remembers that he made an ultimatum
The Trump about the vaccine do that
You still can't vote for a guy
Not
Being open
About these
From the shop
Adecco
That's why I'm very very torn about this
You shouldn't be this is actually this is an argument for you being Less store
About it because like
If you put the ultimatum out and Trump didn't care
That should tell you that you have no purchase here
Cuckoo
He doesn't give a s***
Look I made the ultimatum
He didn't listen and so I am not going to stick to my end of the ultimatum right
If there's one ultimatum that I think of when I think of my ultimatums I think of that time Obama gave that ultimatum and you know how
All that work
So is another color and
This is just
Annoying
You crunch the numbers
Hardcore
Jesus Lugo I'm hoping he comes around with the vaccine
I'm hoping
Cheap surround himself
Bristol Rodger Stone
Steve Bannon
Amgt in the restaurant
We will come around
The meantime we have to get behind Trump
Milanesa
You didn't say he was running
Trump will come around we got the numbers we got to win this that's this Wednesday I'll promise you this
We're not going to
Your calls and you're going to have a place to voice your opinion in millions of people
About what you think
Tomorrow
I'm going up the phones up for multiple hours
One topic tomorrow
Raise this issue
Alex did you want to take calls on this subject
You know when you live in the moment a lot of people don't really recognize
Nice what it means to live in the moment which is to forget everything that you said earlier and put it off till tomorrow
Blame it on other people
So Alex has Gaston
Instead of
Dealing with his
Callers Feelings by drop
This guy
It's only a few people out
Exposing New World Order
A greater level that idea
Before I decide about the credit
And it was
Steve Quayle and David
Pulse rate
Punchbowl
About living legends
We got a pile of Infowars
Steve's Man Steve kirsch's seem to fade into his sub stack background
Steve pieczenik is still
I got to be honest
I need proof of Life on Steve
I don't think I've
I tried to find some YouTube videos
Is channel seems dormant
I don't know Steve's on the Wind
I don't know
Maybe he's happy to be involved in this b*******
Didn't get subpoenaed
In the trial
That's so much to do with you really does have a lot to do with it
Getting away scot-free on this is pretty well I mean
Take a sexual invitation
NFL Tampa Bay
And you know it is it is interesting to think
Another day if
Steve does have health problems
Here I think much like our boy is just going to
We're going to be the only people who wreck
It's going to be worth the same two people we're going to be like to think I do Steve and Alex is going to forget it was a lie Alex brought
What up that Larry Nichols died like
Like a couple weeks after empath
We're the only people
Why are you hanging out with people like that we all know it
Damn anyway
Steve
Interesting thoughts
And by interesting I mean incredibly boring
And on hands
People are looking
For a political solution to a
Spiritual problem
It's Micah
Contention
Better
United States
Has declared the Democrats
Specifically and the
Logan horse
I've declared war
On God made
Declared war on
On everything that made our country great
They described him as a family
Destruction of
How about of a Grateful Nation versus
Basically wearing I raped
Lenders United
States has
I've been taking
Hey look at a ride
Wow
Weird to think of the United States
Do United
Raping and pillaging and plundering
Unthinkable
I got to say
It's fun
To say that everybody who you don't like us
Is declared war on God
It's fun it's just a great thing to do
Doesn't leave a lot of wiggle room in terms of negotiation
Conciliation or compromise
Be kind of
Difficult
Impossible well if you declare war on God God himself is usually pretty
Stringent about that
Yep dealer like War
This is dumb but I do appreciate the rhyming
And
I think that that
Steve Quayle
Loki
Is a little bit of a fanciful gentleman
I'm being told
Exclusive Teeter
Your top podcast a broadcast
Is the FAQ
That they're already setting up
Another
Crypto
But Alex watching
Do currencies turn into
Tonight
For the finance
Actual system
Yeah
That is the woke Insurance of crypto jugs right that he likes wordplay and I appreciate it
He could write a children's book
If he wasn't nuts
Icon
Not Las Vegas
I call it lost wages then come on now
Sustiva Rambles
So Steve Rambles a bit haha
Penchant for that
The great reset
Get rid of that Bravo Sierra
The greatest
Because again I want to say this Alex
Cop 2017
Your people don't under
But they rewrote
The ten
Do a better job then
Godnixon
The creation
Timer
They're doing stuff behind
The Common Man
Good private jets
You know 400 price
A jet
Going to
Mount Sinai by the way the one they all right,
A real one the real Mouse
Mount Sinai
Saudi Arabia
Anybody said this
Is publicly but I'm being told
People that know that
Interface
That world
That they've already decided
The coming world leader is
But this is the Christ
Prince Charles now King Charles
Referred to
At that Global Summit
Gentleman
All of this
The political
Distracted
Say something
Insanity
Okay so we have cop
They rewrote
At the climate conference conference
400 private jets
Flutamide Sinai but it's a fake mouse
There's a lot of pictures
Yeah
If you bring up the point that there are 400 private jets there
Talk to ya man of course
It's a very stupid thing to do if you're doing the climate conference
Real dumb
No I don't disagree
Not what we're talking about we're talking about this
Spiritual dimension on God
I thought the new Ten Commandments was the Georgia Guidestones
But then I guess someone blew him up now he is got to
Those are the old Ten Commandments ten command
Stop is the new new new new
Steve
Taxachusetts
Miss Rachel
More than any other one
How is it that the whole world
Goes into lockdown
At the same point how is it that the
Economy shut down at the
The same point
And the answer is that is
Lucy
Money Wars
Kia spirit
Espy Awards
You know people are having
All
Interaction
Strange creature
Sure
Incubus succubus
Cryptid lot of crickets
I called kleptodogs cuz they feel so much Dad
Boy
This is the State of Affairs that we find ourselves in
Steve Quayle warning us about chupacabras
There's just nothing that is
Let It Go
You can say it for anything
People come up to me and ask me all the time how is it
How is it that gas prices
All around the world can be so high at the same time and I say
Lucifer
Right I mean
This job because people wanted first of all countries didn't go into lockdown all at the same time
Some difference but
You could say all around the same time at
Because there was a global pandemic
I think
That
Is not Lucifer
Pretty easily explainable in terms of real-world condition
Non luciferian
Also though they brought up Spirit Wars they're just remind everyone
Spirit Wars where the two catchphrase ideas from reset Wars abandoned
Not really expanded upon a combination of his most important thing he's ever done
Which flopped and was really just a contract thing that he did for a weirdo get-rich-quick hypnotist a fella that Alex has
Mentioned he did a photoshoot Creek
So
Contributed quite a bit dog
The most important luxury Deanna Creek
So Cryptids
Chair out there
Cryptids during play
Sasquatch
The squatters
What are the Cryptids
Do you like another Mothman
Much as I love
I was always I was always
Mister myxlplyx what's the Abomination Abomination what's the Snowman
Yes
The yetis
Sure
It's just a different environment
How about you I don't like Cryptids much so I don't find them
Not a guy what are you what are you you like Messi
That's just because I feel like nothing is not coming out of the water between the two of you
A long-standing respect
4 things better in the water
Check domain
It's a different domain
Whatever you all are doing over there I respect you right in the water keep it in the water
Already be right right come in and out of the water
Don't trust the other ticket late
Sure
They're not hurting anybody that's fine
Toads are pretty cool
Yeah except for the ones that are poised
Right but you can lick some of the other ones
I'm not going to get into
I like to swim in the water
It's true I'm not going to I'm not going to bother
We are just I'm a traveler in the waters right I don't mind if
You're a guest
For a frog
Hops around
That's fine
You get like an alligator or something like that that's a dinosaur in the water
Water more than a million years old
Buckeye
I'm done
I think we'd get along
So we have one last one
Comeback
Situation in Russia
Little break
Don't do this a lot of prayer
So Steve has a little prayer
You know honestly
If God's the answer
By then why is
Steve answering all these
These questions with Lucy
Great question
I don't have an answer
That
Would still be blaming Russia even if it was a surface-to-air missile that was launched
Buy Ukraine that way is because they wouldn't
I've been watching that if Russia wasn't firing missiles so there is still an argument to be made that hey at the end of the day
Day Russia still bear some responsibility
Circumstance
But Alex doesn't care about that out for a joyride with our missile is just
We let's fire them willy-nilly into the sky know we're being attacked by a nation that
He's trying to kill us
With no interest in really fighting a war anymore that is the rationale there if you're curious out
Steve is so uncompelling that these are the clips that I have
Of him
The declare war on God Cryptids are out and about
Don't paper those should be good at all available everybody Cryptid
Except for sport play which is nice
I do I do appreciate that Alex
Has the Trump announces his can
Mediately starts waffling back
To like all right I support Trump
Yeah I know there's if there's a bear
Very clear indication of it
Except
To take calls about it
Can't handle having these conversations interview with Steve Quayle
Is just
Gross piece of s***
About medical leave
Suicide
If I'm Trump if I'm Trump if even on Infowars
Is my candidacy announcement goes over like
Make a fart
It's not good
It's not good no
Nono and the worst part is I cried about how he would die for you last time
He doesn't want to talk about it doesn't want to talk about it would rather hang out and pray with Steve Quayle
Here's what
Trump over the pain the pandemic
Everybody watch Great British baking
Michelle we prefer nice reality TV shows to shity reality TV shows now it's just how it were
Well I mean if you want to
Actually going to use the bank
I would say that his announcement speech was a little rough and ready
I like that flying too much
The British being able to use that
Yeah I do I do I just like to say rough puff pastry that's what I I just talked to him every time
Place a rough puff pastry oh my God so it's so it feels good rolling off the tongue
I am waiting the finale of
Oh yeah yeah
It is in Britain
But not in the United States oboy you would have to use some sort of
VPN
Yeah
Might have to look into that
The show I like Sandro Sandra
He's a big muscle is funny he smart
Damn my God what we are in love
With my pups jump up and
Not too much going on tour
He doesn't need this
What's the problem
Anyway
Jordan become to the end of this Earth to quote myself
Going to f*** the f***
I will be back for another episode
Yeah
I got excited there because I realize that Steve Quayle is the person who warns us about
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work