I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guy
Knowledge
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
Call Joseph
We are Damned
What are you doing
My bright spot Dan is that recently I I believe it might even be out
Today I was a guest on vgod pod
I feel like it.
The cult leader who prophesied
Currently living out like a Twilight Zone dream version of like hey man here's what you'll here's what will happen
You think he's going to talk to God
Wrong
He's going to go on the podcast
Video podcast
At the at the risk of sounding like the lead singer of Dishwalla
That was fun
Psyche and Satan into the literal Chris
Double was there as great as
Is good time
Check it out wherever podcasts are sold
V-neck Happy Meals I believe
What's the title of it Happy Wheels
Oh
The Godfather
Well that's a lot of fun
I'm glad you had a good time
Is Fanta
I will be damned
Because I didn't go on yes that is true that is true I would say that my my bright spot today Jordan age
Lee
Over in the UK just got a little dizzy
Package aha
Can be very very much appreciate it
And a giant thing of hobnob
Switch famously on the streets
My favorite of the British trade
I I will say that I don't know if I can
Can forgive them for this
12 months
Matured Christmas party at what happened when I opened the package month mature what happened what happened
He open the package and he said it is candy dumbass
Cuz it's labeled fragile
Obviously with candy and then you just handed me a 12 Church Christmas pudding
This one's for you and your wife
Andre Brandi mini pies I will
I will take one for the team and have all the candy
The 12-month matured
Oh boy
That's right up
Jordan
Today we are time-traveling I felt
The urge
To go back to the past
Every now and again you need a re-up
You need to go back
I can get a taste of what
What things used to be like
And like I mentioned on our last episode we I got bored
Of the August timeframe
The December
Strategic decision on my part
December 2000
3 is when Saddam Hussein at the beach
That's right and so I would love to see the lead up to that and how Alex
Respond
When Saddam
Because as we know Alec believes that he's in Belarus
With his kids and a bunch of gold very alive
He believes are there
So we will get to that way
Do that but for now weird
Checking in on
December 1st
Seeing what the path leads us to
3 +
I'm going to just
Give a little bit of a
It's not a warning but I'm going to be a little bit of
It was shorter episode
But the reality is something that we talked about it
I think is actually very
Cancel
I don't know we might hit an hour we might not
But I do think
That this is
Something that
Something that happens is definitely like
I can't believe this it's about
Quality of minute now
What we we've been doing for our episodes we've been doing all that stuff we got that under our belts now
It's about minutes
Quality right now
I talked about passing out on Direct
Condensing of Doubt or getting from efficiency that's Argo I don't know if you want me to put your business on the streets but I know that
Getting back into stand-up a little I didn't know if you have closely regarding that
I know that
A minute is a very important
That's what that is
That that I know that you're
Tracking rate
I've always
Permitted guy you know cuz I have those jokes that last two or three minutes with only one
Wayla
Play love under one under one is not a good last-minute I've been told that many a Time
I never really I never attract that and I never really understood like how do you gauge
Like what is and is not a successful laugh
Yeah like what if you get a couple people laughing in the audience but really hard
Just a good-sized laugh from everybody
Do the each count as one I mean who's got the meat the audio make the decibel meter has
I think it all every
Part of it became incredibly stupid to me after I listen to Dana Gould Black Dahlia B
That
5-minute long bed
With one
Punchline
Is so spectacular he's got you hanging on every word and then the final punch
Breaks everything open the whole place explodes
It's perfect for the Jon Glaser and Jon Benjamin
Forget about it
Hidden Siri has one joke with him twenty something
There was a by Jon Benjamin
Was the
David CrossFit that they did
The abortion doctor
No the comedians of Comedy Tour they did or not
I want they did a one-off. I don't remember what that bit was they both
Recorded this
Long thing where they started
Leaving the stage and then talking to a recording of the other ostensibly because they were at that's right
What are you doing back at the train
Forever the two of them had a bit on the invite them up
CD that was David Cross was a doctor who would put babies back inside
If it was interview him and fortified by the procedure
So good
Anyway
We have an episode to do but before that
Let's take a look
Happy early early birthday on this 12 raccoon
Thank you very much
Mike from Akron Davina loves you pronounced
Davido thank you so much
Very much
Next
Expelled
Caballo bahut it's hard not to think they're rubbing it in our face
! thank you so much you're now
Thank you very much okay
Next
This was actually inspired by today
Ironically they sent this in Pryor but it is actually in response
What's the today's episode
What do we want time travel what do we want it that's irrelevant thank you so much
Genetically Enhanced
Thank you so much
Thank you very much and we got a couple of Wranglers
Who worships at the altar of kudzu
And
George Soros in a hot tub we call that globalist warming thank you so much
You are now what time
I'm a policy wonk
I have
Risen above
My enemies
A little breaking for me
And then we're going to come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She wrote in on
And all your s***
Maybe later on West Broad
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
Everyone come back here again
Apologize to
Yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's not
Not even in the past December 2003 still not good not
Not good
Before we get to today's episode I wanted to touch on something from our last episode
And that is a we talked about Alex's coverage of the medical assistance in dying legislation in Canada
And I wanted to loop back in touch
Back on that here a little bit
Before we we launch
Directions to two
I don't believe that we said anything that I disagree with necessarily in hindsight but I did
Get the messages from listeners that have been really helpful in terms of illustrating ways that we could have discussed that issue better
And from a broader /
Perspective
1 points we could have done a better job of stressing is that there is an inadequate social safety net in terms of support
For people living with disabilities in Canada
And this is a very severe issue when it comes to the point where poverty ends up being a
A contributing factor towards someone wanting
SuperSU made
The case of Amir fursuit who we discussed on the last episode involved that Dynamic where his disability payments weren't enough
Keep him out of poverty and weren't enough to allow me to find a place to live
Which would leave him living with severe pain on house
We did talk about how his case illustrates the need for greater social welfare but
I wasn't really aware of the endemic problem that Advocates around disability-related issues have been raising around the intersection of
Poverty and disability
And how this makes the expansion of made to include people whose deaths
Reasonably imminent
Contribute towards a program that's
Dangerously close to
Eugenics
This is really important stuff
And I'd like to learn more about it and possibly talk to someone who knows more in the future
My coverage of Alex is content on the subject has attended
Z2 sometimes not see all of
The broader context
Implications of a story
Because I'm looking at what he
He's saying and then evaluating that
AB apologies for not stressing
Some of the more important aspect of what rational people's complaints about maydak
Actually are
There's a real critique
Critique
Kissing on the Alex
Critique and sometimes
That means
I don't
See
Some of the more reasonable criticism
Yeah it's hard to it's hard to
Completely view an issue in a rational perspective when somebody is also screaming like
You shouldn't do that I don't even understand how I'm supposed to
That's the challenge and some of that is just miss something
Things sometimes that being said I do think that
Some of our conversation was surrounding the question of how social safety
And Welfare programs
Would be a solution to some of the confounding factors
That that were discussed in these cases though
I think we could have done a better job of
Highlighting and and focus
Kissing in on
Some of those problem
Now the second problem which action think is a bit bigger is that there have been some reported cases of people with disabilities being off
Offered made
Has opposed to them pursuing
Further Canadian laws have not
Built-in oversight and regulations that many feel would be needed to make sure that that kind of care
His being applied responsibly
And that's a really big
Concern
I do think that Advocates and human rights experts have a valid point when they say that this Ledger
Translation does have the potential to have a d
Dehumanizing effect
People with disabilities
And in essence
Create a perception weather in the mind of the public or in the medical profession
That their lives are somehow less worth living
And that is definitely
The unacceptable
I'm not sure what the answer is but I'm going to read more up on this and try to listen
The folks with butter
Perspective
But I am confident in my opposition to Alex
This coverage of the story
The takeaway that I have is that there are more reason
Wants to take this seriously and that Alex Alex's coverage
The cartoonish version of
The problem
And exist in direct opposition to the
Most logical Elementary solution
To helping some parts of this
Is greater social investment didn't
Lifting people out of Pop
I Am So for anybody who took issue with some of our commentary I do apologize that there was a
A slice of this
Intersection of it that that way
And I hope to do better job of being mindful of a lot of that stuff in future insta
We do our best and then if we don't
Best we listen when people tell us we did
Drive to
Jordan
Today December
First is where we're starting
It's episodes
There's nothing going on
December 1st but it's the
First day of
December
There was so much going on
There was
The first hour of Left Behind
The first hour of the show is mostly just Alex being mad that bush went to Iraq
Back to give out
Do use for Thanksgiving
Oh yeah I remember that one but there's just a lot of that
That's the vibe you get
Water and complain about turkey
Yeah yeah
We think about all the Absurd
Things and insane things that Trump did
Because they were all so terrified on October towels
In a weird way
You know throwing up paper towels was condescending and f***** up and and Olaf
Infantilizing
Boys going to the place that he genocided and giving out turkeys for a genocide holiday
That's that's metaphorically more f***** up and I can take care of that's an onion of
So we have a
Couple clip
December
There's not much
To discuss here but
Go to check in every now and again see how Alex feels about
Various
Right-wing figures sure
You still hate Michael Savage
Also has a lot about people calling him and his friends.
Please and you shouldn't do that
Well I mean when it comes to Michael Savage
George Bush
Martial Law's good
Nazis and Michael Savage
On the hour every hour thing everybody has to go to a forced labor camp
There is the station check you got to do
Time is it
Time and temp for sure traffic traffic
I meant of course
You got to remind people that if you speak out against the government you split movie
What's his regular boarding zoocrew Michael Savage sucks
But even this is a little bit unfair to to the depictions of him
You alright man
It's just funny though because later on Alex will be like Michael Savage was a while Pioneer one of the first in this space and
Hero in a legend
Well and Alex Michael Savage started
I got a text either Legend
Yapto Alex a number of calls on this show and one of them is a very sad man
Who's handouts of Alex's
Apes
And I'm just trying to get
Facials
Everybody
Please help
Mr. Jones
We need walking
Constitution
Cheryl's
Appointment
Okay
Jordan 12
4000 copies in your area
My life
I'm moving to Paris
At the home phone
Police Department do I change that
Tell me about it
I made friends
Take my hand
And if they agree with
Stop
Bake a cake for a mother
Buy coffee
Well police
We found the
Alicia military
Criminal
Call Charles
So I suspect the cops are more affected by Alex's earlier documentaries because those films are kind of
Veiled threats against
The police
There's actually arguing that the police are the strong arm of the globalist and will be used
Enslave the population and thus will be the pay
Patriots anime
Unless they're explicitly on the side of
The Patriots
The message is essentially when things go bad we will kill you
You unless you're on our side
It's the same messaging in a ton of militiamen
Princeton
The book unintended consequences involved
The plot to assassinate law enforcement
Mike carried out by Patriots who had enough of gun-grabbing
This isn't necessarily will you call a direct
Sprint but it also definitely has an undertone in these materials
It might seem to help
Explain why they resonate so strongly with
The people in lawn
They're more or less telling any of you were a law enforcement that there is a war coming that the Patriots will win
And they need to decide if they want to be one of the good guys
Or they want to die as a v
You know it's a very emotional appeals is made in those documentaries 2
You could see
Your cop you might identify with people being labeled a villain
Sure
I mean
If it was
If I had a time machine
Right now I would go back and tell everybody to be like
Do you hear this
The cops like Alex Jones do you not understand what's going to happen soon
Cops like Alex Jones
Tampa
Problem with that is you listen to this and Alex
Is a liar
So it's really easy to like
Hear this
Just blowing smoke about cops loving his stuff
But maybe there was more truth to that Fender a surly
We're comfortable with
You know those documentaries
Isn't that way that he would
I don't know what it would be like to be a cop
Then getting this stuff
Cuz this is cuz he was sending those two cops
The guy was starting to send those to the cops
Around 1999 so this is
A decade after 9/11
Yeah pretty 911 but after OKC
Yeah so we're in that
Uncertainty zone of who the bad terrorists are
So the cops
I've got to be in this weird no-man's-land where they like we want to but they don't know who
So I assume this is how it goes bad
I ate it may be a contributing factor could be
December 1st
This is when we
Talked about
Alex is war
Glenn Greenwald interview I
Said on the episode
F****** liar his dad was in the John Birch Society
And like
Because in the film eat rice
Presenting self is just like oh I had some of these influences our round or whatever to know you
You're in a birch f****** household
Yeah and I got some pushback on Twitter even from some folks who have
Who aren't ramdump
People interested say and so I just want to play this just to reiterate that Alex's dad was in the jobbers
How you doing Alex
I want to dance
Your thoughts
John Birch
I know you said you
Your dad was on
Questions
Great membership
Great great so another thing that's in there is that
Alex thinks that
The John Birch Society isn't aggressive week-to-week they don't
They don't say it they don't go hard
This to me is so in line with
That
Illusion that people had about Alex not being right-wing cuz he criticizes bush
Diseases
To either communist
Criticized
The John Birch Society
That's very shiny know I'm putting together this Library I've been reading some of these materials
They're they're insanely aggressive
DIY grow
So anyway let's put that baby to bed go to December 2nd
Episode
Alex announces
Sometimes I think you're going to the pass just because somebody said that something happened on the past
Sitting here like
Walking Dead
I am in both the past and the present
So Alex has a
But he announces on the side
Listening without necessarily ring out
Talk to you but this
Is a f****** huge problem
Who has
So are costume and wrote a book
Book titled painful question
Jensen analysis of the September 11th
Attack which hasn't
Held up well as time
What's going on
Hey there's a theme with 9/11 conspiracy
Vista particularly from the
Early-stage
However this is not what I find interesting or troubling
About Eric Holcomb
As long as aggressive anti-semitism
Far more important
Oso a problem
Problem is not a crow
He's not to be pretty eyeglass pretty
Schmidt has a YouTube channel
Of his Public Access TV interviews and also a clip from the movie A Bug's Life
Which she claims is allegory
The Jews or in his room designer star the Grasshoppers and they non-jews are the ants
His description of the video reads
From the movie A Bug's Life the leader of the grasshoppers
Nazi scientist explain what happened at the stupid
Spread these goyim where to realize
But they don't have to be under the control of the grasshopper
For some reason around 2009 is channel shifted over to some recipes and cooking
Content and then two videos of bugs
I'm sort of curious about this but
It seems like
It's not a mystery worth solving
So I left it alone
He's a big
Time Zionist
Occupied government type
Conspiracist and that's his underlying theory about 9/11
I found a page under the name Erica Schmidt on the site Clippy
Which seemed like
There's some pretty offensive content on it but it wasn't sure if I was going to use it for this episode
On the off chance that it wasn't this guy's pay
Pager
However I was able to satisfy my own doubts by doing a little bit of crossword
Princeton
To the audio clips he's posted on that page
About Carly Fran
A woman who has made allegations about being ritualistically abused by the Masons
Incidentally on his own website
Huge questions.com
Eric routinely talk about France
And her allegation
Because I was able to find overlaps like this I'm pretty confident
The business is audio page actually know for sure it is
So that means
I'm going to play this anti-semitic trash
Cash for you for this because this is going to blow your mind
Choose headband
Nicely
We would love
It's their own fault
This song is over 5 minutes long but I think you get the idea there
That sounds like a
It's from the f******
Firefly unit like it you would cuz you would go into a
Spacebar I did they would be playing this propaganda theme song while you were gay Cantina
Yeah we're booked with in under a minute
He's growing into blood libel
Band that is so fun
Locked up
I feel like there is there is a
Who made
Did he
Did he do that himself I suspect you did cuz I have to the beginning is him
It continues throughout the song
Because of that I wanted to just
Include a few more things that he says of this song
Border on calling for genocide
The Jews are getting away with a lot of the times partly because most people can't believe
Maybe they're not the same
You claim to be A different race and they may be correct.
Suggestion that Jewish people are human
That's not good but Jordan
Gets worse
All throughout history is that every society treated use with decency and respect
Got tired of the abuse Prime murders
Horrible Behavior
Decided to refuse the German
And check out that box
What's the weather tomorrow
Claiming the Holocaust was the Jews fault
Covering a lot of bases here hopsmith II you know I saw the movie Clockwork Orange
Way2go
I was like
8 when I saw it
Cuz it was an accidental thing that was on TV late at night for some reason
And
You know that
Scene where he's got the Beethoven playing was got the horrific images and
That's horrific I can't imagine what that would feel like kind of like what the fuc
What you just played for me I finally am like all I got Clockwork Orange
Too far away for you to hit pause on it
Absolutely
Chords would rip out we.
Start all over I mean this is just
Bad
Horrendous
Yeah
We have to get to the
Crescendo's oh so here is the here's the last clip of his song
Let's imagine what the 20th century might have been like that the Jews have instigated all of these wars and
Terrorist attacks us imagine a world without these stuff disgusting
Actually suggesting that a world without Jews would be a better word
World and essentially he's making an argument in favor of extermination
This is one of the most blunt pieces of content I've seen one of Alex's gas
Produced
And the fact that it's
Delivered with a shity techno song just makes things
A little bit less
DJ Dan artinya
No
I even regret bringing up his name is Scott. I'm sorry I'm sorry
Anyway that's the guy who Alex has on his show to talk
Talk about 9/11
You may have noticed that the line 911
Just the start is in that really anti-semitic songs on Alex's part
Unless you trying to do a Nazi show in that case is a great call
Call good-looking welsey
The thing about Michael Savage
Is it was all the thought
What's Nazis Alex is going for the thought
Full Nazi riot
I'm going to hold the door open for you. Kind of nut
Also this episode December 2003 and by his earliest 2007
Schmidt it turned on Alex and decided that he was working for the Jewish cabal
In addition to being inoffensive and meritless gas
This is also something Alex should look back on with personal embarrassment
Here he is elevating the sapphire of a lunatic bigot who by his own devices probably tops out at about
Being interviewed on public access
Amanda is giving him
The credibility that he will do
Just be attacked with later
When Eric Schmidt finds out that Alex
His wife is Jewish
So
Pac-Man
Man man
Man
Ii-vi
Just me
I think
That
Once you
Thought your way into being like
Ocu be better if they're just weren't any of those
You're in a bad place
Totally here in a bad place totally except if you're talkin about Christmas pudding
But you unfortunately Napa
We can always
So you know I feel
I think that there's a lot of people
Who are under the notion
The Alex's show in
In the past used to not be as Extreme as it was as it maybe now or something
Easy perception to have because
There's a story if it's written about Alex
Pasta
It's a story that
The only people generally who have any awareness
It was like
Are people who love Alec
What's an arc going
Going to necessarily pushback on the narrative
And also
Because
I don't know maybe Eric hubschmitt knows what he's doing
He doesn't yell about the Jews on Alex's show
Crypto Alamance
Do the conversation that they're having about 9/11
And
If you just list
Listen to this uncritically
Then you just pick up this guy thing
Lakes that their buildings are blown up or whatever
When in reality what Alex is doing is
Mainstreaming elevating and normalizing somebody who's
Essentially blaming
Jewish be
People for 9/11
And
On the back of that
Rationalizing
Hey an argument for extermination
Delivered a techno song
So I
Think of this show is about as bad as a
Really in the past
Yeah it is it is
There's no way that he can't not know that he's
Got
Massive anti-Semitic
Let's let me know
Let's tease that out
Is it possible Maybe
He doesn't have that you okay
Maybe you'd possibly possible Alex doesn't know
That he wants to exterminate
Let's explore the possibility that Alex actually doesn't even know that this guy has
Is deeply a smell
So what does can't reveal it reviews
A complete application of responsibility to
Is that your gas egg
At bat
That's what we have
At best
Alex is
Platforming
And
I mean quite frankly
Advocating people
Support
Nothing
Because he didn't want to do his job and figure out who he's talk
And that's probably bad
Play Bad
No that's why that's why it's so
It was the first thought I had was like oh well that's why you
Your guests and then the problem was
I8
Whether or not they vetted him or not
Still could have gone either direction
You know they could have added him and being like hey
So long as you don't say the juice stuff
Will use you on their 911 episode for sure
Or they could have not better them and been like well let's just hope he doesn't
Reveal that he's a complete and total Nazi you know
But
Even as somebody who is an expert
And Alex Jones and his listen to all this s***
I can't really say for sure right
Like I think
The laziness argument is more compelling
After the fact
Yeah I think that at a certain point the
The argument for that
Laziness
Naivete or whatever
Kind of is more difficult
The support given the
The trends in the app
Aggressive support of
Hutton Gibson and
There's some problems
How come it would agree that
Message ABS didn't go far enough
A Synchro actually thanks for the
The JBS is partially run by
The Jewish cabal and their there
Paint on it along with Alex Jones and sharply and
Basically everyone he's just lonely
And he's watching his
That's why he's
Posted all this bug videos on YouTube now
We're going to talk about as long as it's here in a little bit
Yeah
So Alex intros
Bad
Computer programmer
Join Josh
Author
Waking up a lot of pee
The process
Waking them up
To what
Yeah
That is
Horton Quest
You question
So how Nazism is
That's what he's Wiki
No I don't I don't think he is I don't think so either
I think he's going to Public Access shows and
Now getting
Call up to the big leagues with Alex
Inevitably the
The waking up
Waking up is this
It's seen as this Universal good
Or whatever
And
Unfortunately
It's not
The waking up metaphor isn't good
It's not actually waking up
Shifting your
Active or something
You know what Alex is saying is this guy's waking people up and what he's actually saying is
He's shifting people
Point of reference
Right and that can't be a good or a bad thing
I am Alex walks
The presentation to be he's shifting people's perceptions
About 911 being an inside job
Right but in reality
If you
Explorer Eric Schmidt and you go to his website and you know take take it as material
Your perspective
Is going to
It'd be attempted to be shifted
To blaming Jews for everything
Yeah
Yeah you know it including
His own loneliness
What it reminds me of the way that you just described waking up is it in this context
Reminds me so much of the Sandman Comics at one point
He is ironic
Punishment is the guy is an eternal
He's eternally wake
So he's always living that nightmare where you wake up from the dream and you're like I was just a dream and then it's a nightmare
Wake up from the dream
And that is kind of what they're experiencing their you're always
He's being woken up
Again
To this new thing now you're walking up to this new thing right to be terrified blank pills
That pill you are awake 2911
Now you need to be awake to this now you need to be a never-ending Nightmare and I think
Who easily exploitable by Folk
Looks like Alex and it is hooks in this world because you know the tendency to believe in conspiracy
Series
It really does
Build upon itself
Believing in one thing makes you more likely to believe in another and then another
Answer when it when it's like hahaha let me reveal another thing to you
Yeah that's
Be that's the market
And part of that feedback is the excitement you get from waking up again
I'm so excited
You know like all over again instead you're
You're just consigning yourself to doing it all again the next
Stay forever and ever until you die
I don't think I'm really that interested in his
Is even about 9/11
Right now
Lahore
What you doing
Actually I got into it
In a roundabout kind of way be
I just about software for a living
After the
Towers went down I was
Embarrassing on the internet there's a lot of
People that were called
Conspiracy nut
Talking about how all we should
Trust this
Government to borrow something
Funny about this attack
And I was like most people I wasn't
Payment
Dismiss
But eventually they got through to me you know that
The constant
Complaining and I
Look up
Looking closely at
What happened
MattyB
That's when it occurred to me that those
Towers look like they were
Or blown up
Building 7 looks like it had explosives in it also
And I was thinking
First reaction
What is 2
Tell people about it.
Put some documents on the internet saying it looks like
Towers were blown up
Okay so
9/11 happen
And he's not that into
Not not paying that much attention
What you going to do okay
What about my life
Alright
That's New York
But when they started calling people weird
Rights
That's when I was like I got to go to the bottom of this
Everything exactly
No I mean a giant world-changing terrorists
Attack happen
Send look I got to do laundry
I got Ryan's going all right I'm not going to think about that and go oh well
The future of everything is a revocable changed
For the worse now
I could
I could pay attention to this
I got anti-semitic techno tonight
I can't figure out the
Yes I don't know I don't I don't think
I'm not impressed by his backs
No no no
Alex wants
Explain
What happened
A
Well it would it looks like it when you look
How these towers first of all when the planes
The towers
You cannot even
See in the video that the
Everyone has cameras all around it
And built ours didn't
Hardly move
They swallowed those planes up as if they were
Nothing I can
What shows house
Strong those Towers were to swallow a plane up at that
Highest speed
Without Really shaking or wobbling or crack
The plane
The plan is not damaged the building
All that much bases
Do the planes hit the
Hours
Shook a little bit
The power sway
But it was like
Strong winter
Storm
Adventure Tower
Extra backup
Again
And then settle down and then
Stood there perfectly motion
Is really dumb but it makes sense that this would be Eric's entry point into explaining how 9/11 was an inside job
Buildings like the Twin Towers are designed to sway because of the wind
Sky it otherwise
It'd be very dangerous
And you would never even notice that wobble even it goes like 6in
You wouldn't notice it if you were inside the building cuz you can subtly feel this way but you wouldn't notice it just watching a video
I used to work in Sears Tower
Willis
Stauer
Downtown and it sucks
It was really uncomfortable
Because I wasn't
Used to Amazon
So like it was
I was only there for a short. Time I never got to adjust
The feeling
Yeah it really freaked me out
But if you were
Just don't look at Willis Tower you never see it moving
Nobody's like all look at the way the Willis is shaking today
Can buckle is not enough for you to detect
It feels like you should be able to though so Eric's able to use this as like an introductory thing to throw out to blow so
Combined
Spider-Man really proving anything
Classic conspiracy drivel
Yeah
The Gulf
Between what seems like
Could be and should be true
And what is
Is so large
That there's so many places where it's like
You can't understand how everything works
You just can't
I can understand how giant buildings were
I can do my best
Play zingaat from not good at
Bora Bora
Schmidt is an incredibly boring gas
You know Alex just have an interview that dances around the general most
Common talking
Pointer at 9:11
Conspiracy theories and
Sucks
Naturally they don't get into any of
Eric's almost
Comical hatred of Jewish
People because Alex isn't trying to give the audience an accurate picture of the people he's presenting as expert
That they should serve
Don't make it too clear to them they're involved
Eric Schmidt sucks
And I've gone through a lot of his website to get a better sense of what he's all about
Everything is about the Jews
There's a lot of Holocaust Denial in the mix
There's one article that I thought might be interesting
As a break
From the rampant anti-Semitism right cuz it was
Interpretation
Of Katy Perry's video
California Gurls Katy Perry baited a Semitic video
Girls are undeniable Daisy Dukes
Amazon top
Pez have to say about
Katy Perry videos
Clumsy take on Candy Land that's
Intentionally
Campi in it
It's overt sexuality
It's a little bit much
Naturally Eric believes that it's an allegory for house
The Jews control pop stars as sex slaves
It's very boring and it only includes a surface layer analysis of my favorite lyric
Snoop Dogg's in
Entire career
Bikinis zucchinis martinis no weenies
The king and his Queen
Great life
That's just
Bikinis zucchinis
Louis I will tell you this
That would not go unappreciated by Lord Byron
He would he would very much of enjoyed that
I also love to imagine this party
Acrylic
Lord Byron would have been in one of those bars
Zucchini
Yeah like it's weed
So you got blunts
Keeney's
And the drink of choice is a martini
Party drinks
Negroni
I would like you would like a my time with the rhyme scheme no course not but a martini on the beach sounds
Terrible that does.
Straight gin and vermouth
Has not good but no weed
That's fine no losers
So apparently this is
Scription of an orgy
According to Eric
Which is better
There's an entire Saga about this woman who apparently has been emailing Eric and wanting to marry him
But he breaks off contact with her out of fear that you might be asleep
Jewish aging
Center possibly mentally ill is afraid that she might be mentally ill
He suspects and speculate
It's about how this could be a setup
One of the thoughts that passed through my mind is that Peggy could be used in a manner similar to Mark Chapa
Specifically the Jews may be pushing for her to meet with me and then the Jews will be able to
Kill both of us and make it
Appear as a murder and suicide by a mentally ill woman
So this is like I said
He tries to reassure himself
But you just can't quite
Peggy sent me her photo and she doesn't look
Jewish to me but I don't think it's possible to Identity
Identify every two simply by the way they look
Only some of them fit
The stereotype
Men are suckers for pretty women but if he emailed you is just as dangerous as a female shark
They're not our friend
Don't be fooled by their appearance
Control your stupid animal like emotions and look at the evidence
Through history and notice how the Jews have been
Treating us for thousands of years
They have never been anybody's friend
Oh so this is the guy they based 7 on
Disgusting stuff that is got to be the journals that has to be the Diaries of a f****** serial killer
It's really really f***** up f****** things
Likes hunting
High and low for an article about something
Didn't Trace back to a Jewish can
Conspiracy theory
There's a lot of stuff on this site
All of it
Is just
Somehow woven back to a complaint about
I like even though
This whole thing about this woman
Yeah it goes back again Isaiah 27 tell even even ramping a anti-semites at this point have to be like hey
Hey dude we think you just have a problem causing your problems like maybe we
We think that it's the Jews fault for everything
But not for you buddy
Size able to find one
And I will not read you some Pastor jobs
I refrain from giving good reviews to product
Because I've only used
Few of the thousands of products on the market
Is this where you got the back shaver
But I recently tried some underwear that is so much more comfortable than everything I've had in my life
But I thought I would mention it in case some of you have been irritated by your underwear also
Put in code anti-semite at biondes.
It is a pouch style made by David Archy
This underwear is extremely comfortable for standing sitting or walking
But if you have to do a lot of movements of your pelvic area such as
Is crawling around in a decorfix
Plumbing problems or doing exercise
Extreme movements can cause your penis
To be pulled out of the pouch
But it remains comfortable even when that happened
How do you feel
Citibank in Manteca
Put back in don't put that in a review put it back in before you put it in a review
Okay
Update February 1st 2020
That there's an update
Shorter version bikini version
I do not
Like the bikini version
Because after moving around a bit the material moves a slight bit off my scrotum allowing it to touch the skin of my leg
I am just
I
Just ghetto
People are more than just one
Bounds on this underwear for what
Seems like the length of a novella
It does seem to be going to want
Unfortunately modern societies have such a problem with sex
Scribes and sexual inhibition that these and underwear review the underwear of a word such as
Testicles
Send penis
The boys
What makes this underwear so nice
Is Betty
What I wondered what
Possible in a.
Document that I posted almost
Years ago of which is to provide
A pouch or are testicles
This underwear goes even further provides a pouch for our penis
Oh that's
Spats
8 years ago there's a hyperlink speculate about this eight years prior
Merry Maids
Wow
There are not a bunch of product reviews on this site and as far as I can tell this is the only one
He found some great underwear so he's got to talk about it at length on his ridiculously anti-semitic conspiracy theory site
What group did a free advertising for David Archy
Underwear they've got to be thrilled
You seem confused
What am I supposed to do with the existence of all of that
Simultaneous
How do you think of Siri
I don't know where this website now it's full of hate and then there's a f****** underwear reviewer he complains about the
Anyone
If he doesn't like the bikini-style he can't come to Snoop Dogg
Noah
Which means that those underwear wear your weenie pops out
Give me
But I think it's a metaphorical weenie in
Snoop song
I think he's a literal weidian this song
I wish he had a breakdown of all of
Katy Perry's videos
Last Friday Night the problem with this is that you can't be a rampant vicious anti-semite and then do a one-off
Product review
You know that's got to be like a new weekly segment
Product
Bicycle
It doesn't have it doesn't switch gears snow gear change
Solid ride
Stuck to my scrotum
Where is Vitas
URS Coronavirus
So it goes on and on about his various thoughts about this underwear
For reasons that escape me with this section which I will read to you in full
Since this document is probably going
To be considered a
Obscene by some people I may as well mention another issue that adults oughta be discussing without Hysteria
My God specifically some men believe in having a large
Floppy penis makes them better than the bed
You are not telling
This eventually goes on a small penis rat
Oh my God man believe it having a large floppy penis makes them better than the men have smaller penises or who have
Accordion type penis that compressors do a smaller-sized Growers and showers
Some people have been so convinced of is that they're stretching their penis to make it bigger such as Roberto Cabrera
Businesses are offering products
Penis stretcher
And one of the questions on the Amazon site
It sells the David Archy underwear is from man who's hoping that the underwear will make it
Penis look larger
The children who grow up in the USA
Could pick up the attitude that men should have giant penises
Hemet women should have dying breath
How many people actually wants such features and their spouse
Furthermore are those people quote normal
Or are they mentally ill
To quote
Normal women actually care whether a man has a large floppy penis
You know as a writer I will tell you this whenever you have certain little phrases
Can kind of gear us towards what your point of view or perspective that you're bringing in in
If you have repeated large floppy penis
That is something that you view is a negative my friend
Normal women actually care whether a man is a large floppy penis
I realize that women walked erect penis has to be a certain size and shape
But how many women care how long a penis is when it's limp
Just fact how many women even want to look at a man's limp
Who is this you Chris Rock
My opinion is that giant floppy penises are annoyed
My penis will compressed like an accordion when it's cold and I think that it is much more comfortable compared to
To wet it is warm and flopping around
Although this David Archy underwear is making that flopping problem just
Superior
Underwear review
Oh God oh my God right so I mean there's a cereality to this today
I feel like sometimes I want to
Be able
To allow people who are listening to our show.
Get a gun
Listening to Alex's show he introduces a guest you look into them a little bit you find this
Bordering on extermination ism
Type approach
Jewish people
Some of it mask
In a
Pretend opposition to Zionism some of it just mask
CNA
Ooki intific bulshit
You know that is
Unacceptable on on a hundred different
Levels
Then you poke around a little bit more in the
Can you find this
Ridiculous s*** like the Katy Perry video review being contextualized as
Jewish people having Popstar sex slaves whatever
This nonsense
And you're like this is
I just don't know what to do
Yeah
How do I not share this
This is what I'm saying
Yeah it is man
Cuz it cuz
Hate
Is what this guy is
Built this life
His entire life is geared around hate
. and ended his his
Focus of it
AZ is on Jewish people
For whatever reason
You know it's not obviously for anything that makes any sense
Then you would have to have an argument that it makes
Well I think
The way you can kind of make a little bit of sense of ease that so many historical can
Conspiracy theories have lead downhill towards antisemitism into a hateful
Conspiratorial mindview and you start exploring a ton of things odds are you will encounter material that
It takes you down that road
So I think it's more likely to lead to that vent to lead to other
Conclusion on the way I can make sense of it but in terms of the ideas make
Obviously
But
But it is
It is
AAA
Picture not of somebody with like some sort of
Mastermind dije
Dates that is is
Built around like trying to achieve something or or
Exploit something or anything along those lines
And it really does feel like this is a person who is
Isolated in I mean just
Insane
Indeed
In need of so many things
And it's also like f***** up
I think that a number of hints you could get from his website are
Definitely
Showing some needs not being met
Yeah for sure and no way does that excuse
The direction that it goes to
It also this big floppy penis
Underwear review
It highlights another thing that I think is is crucial
You start to see
And that is like with Alex he's a f****** monster who puts out
The hateful bigoted material
Often times
Crypto and nature sometimes
Hiding behind other rational
Those four things
But he also
Sings along with The Highwayman and he also talks Over You Belong To The City
See also
Like sci-fi to an unhealthy
The extant like there's other facets of his personality
Michael Savage came up earlier and I used to listen to a ton of Michael Savage's show
And he is a horse
Bigoted as well
But
Sometimes he tells a story
And he can leave an amazing yarn about old-time San Francisco Eatery
Like that like
There are other facets of these people's personalities they
But sometimes our
Are like
This is bizarre
People aren't only a bigger
And that is also part of what makes
Them
It makes
Some people
Distracted from their big
Bigotry
I think I think I'm
Not trying to excuse his head or provide an explanation
Course
I I take
I think it's like
With this
Particular situation there are Lanes of of big
Country that you can kind of
Push people down or classify people under you know you have people like
Tucker
Who is a virulent
Bigot who is smart enough to hide just enough of it to pass
Who is using it for evil as reading of gas
Friend editing
And he's doing all of this in service of
Money and
Power and all of this s***
And this guy is not that
You know
No he's a bigot
Something
Indifferent he's somebody who has a
Far more of a willingness then
Tucker or Ally
Likes to just be up
Front about the
8:30
Yeah and then simultaneously he's somebody who's like
A little bit
Too old
Experience blogging
You know what
That's the kind of sense that you get
A number of these articles
He's like somebody who
Discover is that blogs
Exist and think
That everybody needs to hear all their thoughts
About underwear
Or like this is going to be somehow a meeting full
Is a pouch
Underwear like
Like is that revolutionary at whatever point he's
Think so I don't know
I've never put as much thought into underwear as he put into I guess
The words big floppy penis
I have not put that much thought into underwear
Yeah the compound noun for for this fellow
So here's one last clip with Alex and
This is this is another thing that I think is important
2 hour
Video
Also
Full of I don't know
Over 100
Incredible
Powerful
The family up
Alex is taking his access to his audience
And using it
Funnel monetary support
To Eric and simultaneously he's selling his material so Alex is making
Big money
Getting the audience to support
And by Eric's
Materials
Now when we talk about Sandy Hook
Stuff
One of the
Things that is
Is really important
To consider
In terms of
A lot of people
Always wrong about something and then he apologized why is it so bad
But when you really look back
At this
.
And you look at the way that Alex was funneling his audience to support Wolfgang halbig
Facilitate his ability to carry out the harassment
To fight the legal battles
That he was in the way Alex
Directed
And
Advocated for his audience to give that money
Yeah and the way that Alex
Sold
Their stuff on his website
That is irrelevant piece of
The machine that Alex has built
And the audience
Trust
And
Access that he has
He has
Like given
Extreme people
Access to money
That they would not have otherwise
Wolfgang halbig didn't have access
Let's do a giant platform
Before Alex
Allowed that
Erica Schmidt was on public access interviews and s***
Like you didn't
Even Allison 2003 was probably a big
Big big forehead
This is
Of what Alex
Is and does
Without him
I mean nowadays
It's probably diminish
Somewhat cuz there's so many
Internet
Platforms that have large audiences have
I put a. Of time like this
Sand into the early 2010s
Like Alex was something that
Was able to be
A monetary
Victory
For these extremist
Able to be on Alex's show
LED tube
Reno
Probably access to a lot of stuff you wouldn't have access to otherwise.
And the way that it was spread
When there weren't those
Those million different outlets in million different internet
That's faces for a tutu
To grow the way that Alex said
Built Avenue can see all the guys
That we still see around now
You know like if it works for
The way that that was
Disseminated
A lot of guys wouldn't have quite
Like the same I have staying power though
Well that's fair I don't think Webster Tarpley is that big of a acre
Bright 20 still just hosting the fourth hour of that way
Didn't work out for everybody
Anyway we come to the end of this episode and like I said
Little bit shorter but you know what
Sometimes
The end up
Reading a lot of an assholes blog
I do think that it's
Really important to recognize this stuff
He's such a
Great illustration of
This
Sort of the Counterpoint to the argument that Alex's show tunes
That's of no it was baked in
It was there
The perception of it might not have been
As easily accessible
Buy a passive viewer
But it was there
I do I don't mind that this is shorter I feel like
With this guy has given me a lot to sit with
I'm going to be driving later just going like
F*** yeah f*** that f***
Cooking guy
What's a Big Papi
This is the sort of unsung emotional labor podcast
This struggling after the fact
To survive
It is it is like oh okay
Alright I'll touch that hot
All right but
How recording on Tuesday I learned a little bit
We will be
Reebok Jordan
Until then
We have website.com
Willoughby
But until then
Omniome Leo I'm dzx Clark
That was
I'm opening up my code what are you doing here did you read this
Have you read this
It is very chipper
The sex robots
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color