Soletic
I have great respect for knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guy
Collegeboard.com
Alex Jones
Quick question for you
What's up my bright spot today is
You know I know they were going into the thanks
Giving week lot of feelings about Thanksgiving
Of course but it's
It is
At best
Take away a lot of a trappings at the time to think about things that you're thankful for
Jordan Breanna audience and
Having a moment to think about these things and how how great and how many things we have to be thankful
For Eyes is very
Humbling and nice experience that I've had the last couple days
Yeah yeah you know I actually almost prefer when I had fewer things to be grateful for
Be grateful for it freaks me out
Weigh less than any of them
Give me 1/3 of 60
Yeah it's it's overwhelming but positive way and thank you all very
Very grateful
The jewelry that awarded 1.5 billion dollars baby
Another thing to be grateful for, thankful do played whatever small role in that as I did
We did
Bring up a f****** album or something
Sparletta
But more important for most of the world okay thanks giving
That would be the World Cup my friend I am enjoying it immensely you broken out your vuvuzelas
A decade's from
Million World Cup World Cup soccer
Grimm
Oh no it's really great so far everybody's fun the USA still terrible in soccer which is enjoyable
To Marcelo Balboa
Go back to Tony Meola tell that to
Alexi Lalas
Tell that to
Baba baba baba
Nope
Who's the who's the favorite you think
Well I think people were hoping for Argentina cuz it's nothing great historical soccer
Arizona now and then Messi this is my Lionel Messi's last World Cup
And here's the course the greatest footballer maybe that ever lived
So everybody's really hoping for them
Morning very morning
They lost in a surprise upset to Saudi Arabia tomorrow so now they're in a deep hole they're not there
They're fighting to get out of the group
Dangerous
Messi like messing with
Who else who else is looking good this year
I think England looking pretty good there probably going to come out of the group stages of the United States Liberty
Pretty fast
You know other teams other things are good chirp Netherlands
I know they're country lot of people have good feet that's true
Well
I am excited for you enjoy like I like hearing about the World Cup
Butter
I will talk about that before we do
Girl is more powerful realistic birds or globalist
Thank you so much
Thank you very much Alex has daughters abandonment issues
Thank you very much
Simed misunderstood the point of the fuk down in Illinois support group thank you so much you're now policy want
What inappropriate
Enraptured by raptures
Them try that again
Enraptured Raptors
That was it that was there is a trip up that was a spiked on the on the road that's what that was
Good about it
Until it came out of my mouth
Next PSL is the best semen thank you so much
Pumpkin spice latte
Wow that is a deep cut
Well done
I'm also Georgia this summer to send a message while back because we are to know the greatest
Boxes of mass this is a Veronica
If she's a policy wonk
And Ivan answering that is no you're not
You're not a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk I have
Risen above
My enemies
A list for me
And then we're going to come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty work for you
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f*** the horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
I apologize to the
Yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He probably isn't but we don't know the Jordan
Have Alex in the present-day on timeout because I feel like if it's Thanksgiving is one thing we should be thankful for
Matt is being able to
Say hey Alex
Go yellow about nonsense will be back
We are not beholden to your timetable lesson will catch up with you when it's a war on
Will get that we move it around speed
You know Linda mentioned certainly think
Can thinking about my family
What what better way
To celebrate Thanksgiving on
Then to enjoy the deposition of Alex's dad
So today we're going to be talking about
Did the Connecticut case
To trick you
Right right you know a lot of my normal mood I wasn't expecting the David Jones death
Position you had me on that one you've got me clean clean there yet
I'd like to know that I still got still got a few options and eyebrow fake a great part of our relationship
For still learning got to keep it fresh
AJ's dad
As we know Alex's Dad is he is a dentist by trade
He is somebody who is B6 smartest boy in Texas
Is variable
One of the smartest Boys in Texas and and so the globalist
Straight to recruit him into a program of eugenics
Orloff the population that he said no thank you notes and they just really like alright cool
No big deal why don't you tell your blowhard son about this in a few years because
View to you via I suppose very obvious means that we have a secret program before you would
Beyblade all at 4
World we're going to leave you alone
The guy who knows our plans that could possibly afford them by telling your blowhard son
The radio show with millions of listeners
He is the subject of fables
Yes on Infowars horseshoer
And at least definitely
Current Berkshire but we'll see any more pics and ideas
That didn't that didn't
End up stopping Society lecturer younger years
Yeah. There's a lot of that I know about him and
Facts
I know real facts
Whatever I know Alex fact about him but I don't know that much about him in general
I not really even seen pictures of him before the deposition
Not really heard his voice
I've never heard on Infowars Alex said he refuses to
Smart
And at least a fairly smart boy in Texas still
Snow in 2019
He sat for a deposition with Chris Maddie
And Norm is there
My friend Norm Pata source is representing him
And I think this is a shorter deposition as a whole
It's probably about an hour long all day
And
I think
That it still has some pretty interesting things being said Alex's dad
And maybe some things that
Help
Didn't help with Cato yeah
Brighton
With David
Can I ask you a quick question on Cone
Before we before we get before we get going and their actual tone is revealed I would like to know
Is this
Predicting he's going to be somewhat
Combative
Just kind of like a kind of like an aloof a******
Maybe a little aloof
I wouldn't say he's like super combative
He's not
Forthcoming okay alright alright
Bring up the the sort of tone
There is a something I'd like to point out
And you can take note of as we go along
America's debt
He
He's very like much smarter than Alex
Very good at not answering questions while answering them in a way that kind of has the
Appearance of an this going to be the first time that we are looking at somebody who is about to get trapped
Going
Oh well I know this is a trap
Maybe even a step before that
Dangerous
Starkiller with a discussion of his his coming to Infowars
When did you
I'll retire
From your career is a dent
I still
Have a life
But I retired from Act
Back to practice
2000 +
And is that when you became
Involved
In the operations
Capri's Pizza
That is when I became more
Formally
Involved
So we got it we got a text I'm here
My friend
Yeah he's got that he's got much more of a voice that you kind of expect for someone
That sort of Jones character
He's somebody who is not spent the first twenty years of his career doing a Rush Limbaugh
Impression right to destroy any chance at all of that accent any longer
I would say that if Alex sounded like this a little bit more of a I don't know if you could do
Who is delivery no this is yeah
Text boy draw
He's taking his time
So before he left his
Practice his Dentistry
In 2013 even before that he was part of the business as if it was a family business
This is something kind of weird here
What was your role before then
Justice being involved in
An advisory role essay
In a family business
So Alex would sometimes ask you for advice
About that
Occasion
Did your involvement
Anything other than
A Barbie house
Device
No
I'm in an
And
And what types of
Matters would he ask for your advice
Largely what am I
Perceptions were about things
We're going on in the world
Moral compass
So for example
Alex might be
Be considering covering
Turn story in the news
And would
Discuss that with you
Not so much it's like did you hear such a
Concession water
Best of
Now that's that's basic
Sickly what he would
Say to me and I was largely he wanted to know what I thought of
His expressions
And things but I don't know how much
Papaya papaya what do you think of fentanyl the Chinese dragon it's an interesting thing
David
To say that he is the moral compass
Yeah particularly because going to be starting in 2013 to be more involved with the business and this is around
Around the time that San Diego coverages
Is going on if indeed he is a moral compass then
You would hope that they would be
Plenty of evidence of him being like Alex
Stop this Alex may be listening or maybe not it's entirely possible that you could
Imagine a scenario where even though he is Alex's dad
But
I think I think presenting yourself in that way
Raise the expectation of like what did you do as the moral compass mean if if if if you were to describe
Tumi
If you are now if you were to say Jordan
Describe
What's the moral compass for Infowars looks like
I would say it is
Cracked
The glass is completely removed
The White and the red lines are exactly the same there just one color
It's spinning in all directions simultaneously
And somehow constantly being thrown out the window
Hindi
Ongoing active being thrown out the window thing is it's not if it wouldn't be used
I wouldn't lay claim to being one I wouldn't be like haha I know what my role is
Maybe doesn't have True North it doesn't
It doesn't seem to be functioning
He he gay
You can kind of see a little bit in there the way that there is a dancing around questions
I instantly
This is a man who understands the consequence of things
Like I don't know what he thinks the consequences are or any of that stuff but they are there
He's a person who knows.
A known almost scientific would like if I remove this tooth There Will Be Blood like an that kind of sense so if I save
Cause and effect
He's saying that he kind of like gave advice and like all this stuff and it's like okay
So you're saying that he would ask you about what stories to cover attic
Split pull that back
In 2013 he became more involved with the business
And at this point
He entered into what I would describe as a very bizarre Financial arrangement with Infowars
Right this doesn't last very long as they have for a year or so
For another Arrangement cakes input this is
This is why
In 2013 did you
I became indirectly an employee of
Okay
Why we didn't
I had a professional Corporation
Contracted
With large dental practice
This Management Group
And that Corporation lost its income when it lost
It's an employee
And so that Aunt
2K my professional Corporation
Spade lost opportunity fees
And it paid me
To be an employee of Alec
Townsend
Free Speech systems
Play paid
Your
The corporation that you can fold
Four lost lost off
Opportunities
As a result of
Retiring from your dental practice
And that Corporation
You can fold
Then paid you
A salary
In connection with your work for free speech system
Why was it arranged
Purpose of winding down in continuity
It was probably not impart
But it was a real
What employer
Yes
When was that
I believe that
What's the next year
That's
Weird
But I don't know if it's necessarily suspicious or anyting
It's not packed evasion but it's like
Hey if you do it this way there's 20% extra for something or other along the way.
Possible write-offs or something even less so to sneakily there could be situations
Visionware like he was the primary Center of that dental practice
And maybe transferring over to somebody else being bored like the center of the dental practice
Would take time
And so in order not to torpedo that other persons
Ability to practice maybe that's why but it is weird
And it's just
It just 1 and 100 examples of really bizarre Financial things surrounding Infowars
Unusual insofar as it's a
Clear evidence of somebody who knows the financial system is doing something to their
You know it seems like if it was like a practical issue about the dental practice itself maybe there be
Way to get up a buyout or something
I don't know anything but it just thought it was like
It's weird I don't think this one is nefarious
But I do think this is an evidentiary
That suggests there are
People at work with financial information that they are capable of
Bleeding in certain ways good
The line between legal and illegal maybe just a matter of who enforces what
You know England
Ghetto this is Alex's dad
So there is also the consideration of like having your dad come work for you was important
Enough that you
Didn't this Byzantine arrangement
Why is that what's
Like what purpose of this
I don't know it it's
It may not be shady as an arrangement about the surrounding circumstances of it make it feel quite
The moment Alex Jones is involved in shady as s***
That's fair enough
So David Jones as we know was the Human Resources Director
During that first year
Or thereabouts
Do you have
Title
Free speech
I was sort of a
The consultant in an HR Direct
But not really
There we go
Not really title or you want really those not really a title
Okay yeah they just are allergic to titles after Wars
They can't no one will own a title
I mean if you if you have a title that you are responsible for the thing that that title does right
That's legally dicey
Rob dues the news director and tell anyone ask him about it so much
He's just kind of a consultant at Large
What Alex on the company and tell her I don't
Company that he also owns
I find that
Again
To be Shady the title
I was genuinely excited because I was like finally
I get to know what H&R means in this context
And immediately the rug is Pulp
Madden really do that what
Not what you talkin about know he did do it now I know
But that wasn't a Time
So don't expect to buy.
And I take it that
From 2013 through the present day
Your responsibilities have evolved
Thursday
It's been a full-time engaged
But what you done during
In the sense that anyone
Job change
Overtime
There are vagaries
Alright bottom day today
Resultant
Challenges
I'm asking me and lie about your principles
What would I like to do then
There is two
Describe for me
From 2000s
In 13 going forward
What your
Responsibilities have been
Largely just to be sure we have a good environment for our employees
That where
Compliance
2 state and federal guidelines
Unsend that we do
Business properly
I do a little bit of this
That is the most non-answer you can get
But it but it feels like an answer sort of
Have your responsibilities change
Insofar as life brings change to us all
On a daily basis
Orange balls from the branch
Listen to poetry
Everybody call me
Yeah but it's it's it's tough to break
What do this what do you do
On a daily give our point out give me a rundown of your day I like
I got to make sure that our employees are in a good state
9:51 I make sure that
State of being h
I think this next clip sums up some of that stuff a little bit but also don't expect
So is that true generally of the other
Areas of the business day
You are awesome
Involved in
Solving problems as they arise
Our business
Is a
Single Talent business
The Distributing by one party
And I endeavor
To take care of some of
The delegate
It duties
It's not convenient
Should be done by the pro
Who do you report to
Airport
To Alex if anyone
Who else reports directly to Alex
Everyone
Okay
Alright so everyone reports to Alex
He is to be the sort of all roads lead to Alex Wright
And
So you you don't understand we were saying
Well I understand that what he was saying was you know AJ does everything and what he doesn't do I do
Is inconvenient for him
What do you do I get what you're saying
But right
You're forcing me to infer
So much of your responsibilities by saying you know he does everything and when he doesn't do something I pray
What is it exactly that is inconvenient for Alex to do
He's a single Talent
This is very annoying little frustrated
I'm screaming in my head didn't tell me what you do
So we may not find out exactly what they do or he does
But another thing we don't find out is how much he makes a that is because Norm is insisted he don't say
Are you currently employed by free speech
Yes
In the same capacity
And what's your salary
Necessary.
Everybody.
It's okay here's what I'd like to
I'd like to write it down
And give it to you
Borders at
Given the way
Read some of the depth
Have been publicized
So what I'd like to
I can write that number
Republic
This is agreed to am so his salary is written down on a piece of paper or something
It said it's not revealed
My instinct about that meat
Feels like it's probably a lot then right
Absolutely I don't think it would necessarily need to be something that is Fox to keep under
Raps if it's a normal salary
I mean
Let's go to the tape
How long how many zeros did he rig you can see the little swirly motion with his hand right how many zeros did he
Right on that I'll be the paper believe it was probably written down during the break while they were off the Record so it's not not on film
Yeah cuz they they go to a break after this request is made until the actual tape stops
Fix backup well if it's okay for us to find out that
Owen and Daria make an absurd amount of money for being shity
Then I'm I'm guessing David makes well over $1000000
I'm sure they pay him
An absurd amount
Being the fact that
You know he has the interest in pqp yard and like
He knows every
Everything
It just API feels like the whatever compensation he has got to be like
I mean obviously if I were normal probably like
Okay I definitely don't tell him that you got to
Massive bonus
Right before the deposition do not reveal that you received several million dollars
Hours before you walked into this courtroom
Get to talkin about
Employee handbook
Inexplicably it does and then there's a there's a revelation here
Free Speech systems has an employee handbook correct
When did that
How come you doing
It and its permutations
For a long time
4:40
We got there
Do you know who drafted it
Probably
Holman talvin
Doesn't
Holman
Taube
They merged
Waller
Okay
And then
McQ
Come on board
You said that employee handbook his head
Different permutation
We
As we became larger
When you have 50 or more employees
Is there other DDS you have
Open so we elect
Co employee Free Speech Electric
Medical employee with
ADP total
Okay
What
What does that mean
It means that
We
Have a partner in rhr
Development in
Administration
That is a division of ADP
That
Call employees are employed
Forgive me
What is ADP
The largest data processing company in the world
That does payroll
Okay
They provided a coffee
Dysfunctional process
Payroll for employment to help assure compliance
Swift
But did he leave
Employment handbook issues
Notice
And process do you have a
Point of contact
At ADP that you deal with
Yeah we have on
Corporate
Preventative and I don't remember what her
Her name is
Okay so you don't deal with it
So this
Is
I like what a human resources department would do
Yeah and they've outsourced that the ADP ADP basically does all of this stuff
Person there and the
Presumed HR person at Infowars Alex's dad doesn't know her name and hasn't talked to her in a while doesn't really
What is the human resource I really want to stress this
Mr. Jones
A great deal
What do you do
So much of what is been in my experience in places that I work what the HR department does your
Describing is ADP
You are
So you're telling me is that you don't have a job
Because you contract that job out to another company
And I'm just now finding this out and I've never heard of this other company before we're on year how many of us suing you
It sounds like that would be stuffing be inconvenient for Alex to do today
Staying in touch with ADP to be on top of the human resources
Stuff that they do that also be inconvenient for Alex Price
Very confusing what do you do sir
Not expect an answer I am shaking him by the shoulders
Until it had walked back and forth not going to help him
So will you talkin about marketing strategies
And this is B there's an interesting bit of phrasing work
It's done here
My correct sir that
You are
Personally
Familiar
With
Free Speech systems
Marketing and business policies
To the extent that they exist yet
And
What
Your
Personally familiar
With
Free Speech systems
Marking busy
Strategies
Correct
Free speech
SMS marketing
To the extent that
Today exist
So
I'm not saying that they exist but if they do I know about him
I mean
I I know about
The inner workings of elrond's council as well but it does not really exist no does it so I can't really be
Be held responsible for what elrond's council does contraire
Responsible
This seems like
Real nice and on answer answer again because the answer even if to the extent they exist is Acura
Even if that is an accurate answer than the answers
To the extent they exist exist in
Into your answers I think that is what are the policies
Do the extent that they exist suggest
Thing exists
Somewhere
What is it
Maybe what is the thing that exists
We won't know immediately but we do know that
There was a sworn
Statement
That David Jones sign
Had to do with elements
Of the marketing plan
That are confidential
Okay
Okay I'm so mad Maddie wants to know what about this
Is confidential and proprietary
And boy this is annoying
Don't you take a look at paragraph 11
Your declaration
Starting with that second Center
I am aware that plaintiff seek information in.
And occupy
Among other things
Related to the business and marketing plan
And I just want to skip to the end of the above entity
Right
So I want to focus specifically on business and marketing plans
Hell of the above entities
Some of those above entities down
That didn't really exist or have any marketing plan
Turn off I'll get to that
But I just want it
Make sure that we are
Operating with the same
You are where this time
That the police were seeking information
And documents
Related to free speech
Systems
Free Speech systems business and marketing
That's right
And
That information am I correct
You were tested with confidential and proprietary
Correct
It was my intent
Testify that some of that could be proprietary that there was confidential information such
People's names address
Two Social Security numbers
And thanks Cuz off and on our tips line
People would use that as a means of getting through to cuss
Customer service they thought it was
Quicker pipeline to effect
Listen often times there was information
That we were prohibited from sharing with people and it's my concern that was going to be scattered all over the known universe
Information would be contained in a business
World Market
Correct
Shouldn't be
Right
You were tested am I correct
That information
Regarding the business and marketing plans
A free speech systems with confidential and proprietary
Correct
That seems reasonable to me and highly valuable
Capri's Pizza
Correct
Well if you don't know how to do business
You can't do busy
Soap
So
Tell me what
The business
Plan
Or plans were
That you were referring to as confidential proprietary highly
Essentially our core philosophy
Sophie is what was
Jesus involved and I don't know that I really should have been concerned because it
It's probably not articulated
Ty perine
What the f*** is going on
So
Let me let me ask you what you took away from that and see see how you are processing information
Alright so here's our strategy
When a thing happened
We reacted make people mad
But if you write that down people be like that
That makes you sound like an evil person who's trying to make people angry so we keep it all in our heads buddy there's no no
Marketing strategy
Expensive just screaming at you maybe maybe
Your clothes
Something that's mildlyinfuriating about this back-and-forth and how this goes it's like
Are sworn declaration that you made here
It says that there are parts of the marketing and business plan
That are confidential and proprietary
What is that mean well you know some people use r or tipline as a put another put the credit card information
Has nothing to do with the business plan
Nope certainly not I guess it shouldn't be in there
Well
Look it's just an idea
It's just
And maybe it's not confidential maybe I
Yeah that's not even on paper and maybe it's just our core philosophy
That maybe it's not on paper
Is a misunderstanding of a business
No I recognized that perhaps they didn't go to a to a Traditional Bank
In order to get a small business loan
That's requiring it a a suite of business plan
Necessary to present in order to get that loan right under stand that
Alex's dad Baltimore show
Which is a nice way to do it if you
You can do it
But I'm pretty sure you still have to write down a business plan sooner or later
If you want
Well here is what this boils down to
The primary philosophy that may or may not be confidential
Essentially our core philosophy
What was
Jesus involved and I don't know that I really should have been concerned because it's
It's probably not articulated
Ty perine
But in reality it has to do with the fact that our customers are so loyal to us that they believe in what we're doing today
Such a degree
Did if we say something is good for you in as a good value they're going to buy it and buy a lot of
And you know you don't really
It's it's hard to articulate that but it's it let the core of the heart of things can
Can sometimes be very simple and very valuable
Understood
Pedigree
The business plan
Well I think what you just
Scribus
A component of the
But that there is no written
Business
Plan
Pertaining
There is a business plan but it's in Alex Jones is
Moosehead
Is there any written business
No probably not okay
So Alex has an idea of his head of how things are supposed to go and then it's never a reticulated
Put on paper anywhere
Find this believable I appreciate that what he essentially
Danced around there was like
We lie
We lied to that
Because
They believe what we say about other s***
Yeah then we lied to them about our products business plan is our audience will buy whatever we tell them
Exactly that's our business so captured them and trap them in an alternate reality that they view US
As a source
For all reliable information
Thereby making our bulshit products so much easier to sell them literally anyone else on this f******
Play Jim Jones didn't have a f****** business plan
So there's still the question of like what is confidential and proprietary
David will not be specific
You are also aware
That
The plaintiffs were seeking
Information and documents pertaining to the Free Speech systems
Marketing data
In sales
Analytics
And what
Yes
Would you
Described as competition
Proprietary
Cracked heels
What marketing data in particular
He's confident
Proprietary
That priest
The core
Facts of
What are prices are for things what it cost
Dubai
Materials
We sell per year
What stages we sell those to and things of that
Any any business
As trade secret
Okay
And you consider that to be
Marketing data
I probably would but I don't
I don't look at
I understand
And the
Different pricing what do you do
And
Profit margins do you consider that to be included within sales Analytics
I don't know
What the definition
Can-Am sales Analytics
It's like what it is
To cover a hole mole
Potato sand
It's hard to know what it may
Understood
And I also understand that
Perhaps you didn't
Prepare the first draft of this declaration but this is the term that you swore to
And you made me certain representations about in your declaration take
So
What I want to know is
When you swore this document
Did you understand sales Analytics
Include the things I just described for you
Pricing
Pricing trends
Profit margins
Dad of that nature
Not enough
Sterling
Okay not necessarily
Did you in fact
Consider that to be included within sales anywhere
When I'm asked
Jessica General Quest
Something's Express
In general terms I doesn't necessarily include the
Specifics
That's what I'm asking you is what in your mind
Was included in the term sales analytics when you included here
The reasonable connotations that a reasonable man would have
And you are reasonable man so you tell me
What is a
Included
I'm not going to
Norm
So why don't we
Take a brief break
Let's infuriate playing tennis against the drapes as they say
We
Frustrating as as a Daria
Deposition was
Because she was in many ways this she was trying to do this
Because she's
Weird evil psychopath
Yeah we came off like she was a weird evil psychopath who is like occasionally like I'm not going to answer that and then stepping into the Trap
Yeah he's just slippery enough he's annoying
It's not like
I'm soap I hate you it's more just like man
I swear to God that one more
There's only so much work I dare you to say that this isn't on me
Mrs. in front of God and the law there is only so much one man can take sir that I have
Have from the past couple questions and answers that I feel like I might be onto something here
So when David is talking about the things that are secret and proprietary Trade Secrets
I think he's specifically just talkin about the profit margins they make on things that they sell and how much money the business brings in
This is the information that he didn't ever wanted enforce desperately doesn't want to be made public because if it does that threaten
The stability of what David is described
Is the primary business plan the company has
Their entire marketing strategy relies on the audience
Trusting Alex
They've been suckered into believing that they exist in this false reality where the globalist are coming to get them and the only hope they have is this
Does Lombre voice in Texas
He's on a mission directly given to him by God against agents of the literal devil and God has granted Alex discern
Ornamented inside of the things
That are Beyond normal Mortals
So when Alex tells you that you need water filtration systems to combat the globalist
Trying to poison you with fluoride
The audience is likely to believe that
What Alex tells them that they need to take a special iodine to give themselves a higher IQ which is only lower because of global
Blister deprive them of iodine
The audience Buys in
Hippie audience's faith in Alex's shaken these propositions would start to sound dumb
So it's pretty critical to protect Alex's image at all cost
Certain things are acceptable to acknowledge like Alex's problem with alcohol because
He could use that to peel even more to the audience as an imperfect vessel doing the Lord's work
On the other hand
If you audience were to actually understand the financial underpinnings of enforcing Free Speech systems
And they realize the scam Alex has been running on them for over a decade
That's a bit harder to defend
Did the audience understood the millions of dollars Alex takes out of the business for himself if they saw his ridiculous houses and lavish
Lifestyle
If they know what he spent on luxury if they
New how high is profit margins were on the b******* placebos that he sells them
Vacaville High Chancellor Road in the trust that the audience is put in
It was out that there is no business
I think that this is
More or less
If you read between the lines kind of what David to say
I don't know I feel like it might be against
The law but it could not
Because we live in hellscape
But
If what I'm hearing is correct
He doesn't want to give the actual cost
That they spend on the stuff that actual profit margin was right Terry
Proprietary
But more importantly
Alex says that s*** on the show all the f****** times Drew so if that stuff is not true
If he's constantly repeating we're giving you the best prices on the Bubba blah
50% speak in specifics on there too
Question for the the Federal Trade Commission true
Would be it would be manipulative advertising false advertising perhaps advertising
Interesting question that again the FTC might have some thoughts about why the
Big crimes that caused all the problems aren't crimes except for they make all the money and then you can buy the government to make them legal
Yeah that's it that's all
The flaw in the system
So I think the
I think that this is the dynamic really that's going on is that like
If the audience understand that the business aspect of this
Is
Thought you manipulating and using them
Essentially
They lose faith in that
Then there is no more money coming in and this whole thing goes
Even if they believe us about the globalist in these like other things like even if that is retained
Then this whole thing collapses and the business the market of it
Is no longer workable
He's basically saying our business philosophy is fraud
Holy water
Is the church is that what you want to hear
So this next clip involves
Has played in the trial itself to say about
Ambulating spikes oh yeah I remember that were you aware weather
Free Speech systems
Collects data
Concerning
When during an Alex Jones broadcast it has
Ammo sales activity
Only in the sense
That if there have been days where we had extraordinary good sales
Someone will
Say what was Alex
Saying when that happen
And so we liked
Emulates
Spikes
And so that would be done on the Fly
But it's not done
By any Analytics
You would think Ivan
Terms of a
Right so that there's data that
Free Speech has available that show that can chew a spike in activity
And
Theoretically that would be pause
Possible to do if you need
Then someone who had access
To Analytics
To go in and
Determined
And on those
Occasions where there have been
Spikes in sales
As you said that's something that
Yes
Well that's unfortunate combined with
The clear data that exists that there was a gigantic Spike
You bet and sales after Wolfgang halbig was on and after they put that the day they posted that article
Call about the FBI
Saying that no one died at Sandy Hook
And so on
I mean those two things put together without from
I don't think anybody else it in fours would have said that
That
To this point it's
Fairly clear that David is baby kgs of them all
And he's capable of slippery slope in his early 20s flipping through a lot of little little
Cracks in the in the fist
But I don't know how he revealed may be the most important line
Many of these episode have a thought about that and I think that's because he didn't know what was in some of
The emails like turning over access
I still like Google analytics data and stuff like that and withholding certain things
But the snapshots
Like Google analytics reports that were
Are there
And so this doesn't seem like that threatening of a thing to say why wouldn't you
If you were doing a business why wouldn't you lean into the things that work basically
And if you assume that you're not getting the information on what exactly work
When
Then yeah you just say something that seems reasonable
Of course and unfortunately in concert with the the information that is available
This just
Literally says
Well of course
We would recreate because it was profitable
Yeah we are being what I'm saying to you is if something makes a lot of money I eat
Sandy Hook coverage
Then we would continue to do it there for making more money now
So part of the business is investment in supplements inasmuch as like you got to
Yeah I got to get a new formulation you've got to invest in the creation of the supplement
And sometimes they pay off sometimes they don't leaving aside the fact that
Most of the products that Alex ends up selling or just private labeling of
Already existing product
Yeah there isn't really that what they talking about we invest in
Product development I think if
I think what he's trying to say is centrally is that like
You know you maybe buy a lot in bulk and then sometime something doesn't sell
That's what he said
Yeah
You can parse this yourself
You you said
In
Paragraph 13
That
Free Speech systems had
Invested significant resources into into developing
Their business and marketing
Strategy so my question for you is
Can you describe the level of investment into those strategies and windows in Bessemer
Let's side developing
A new product
Cost two hundred
Thousand dollars
If it doesn't sell well you basically
Delete that are high
Sell it at wholesale
And so you learn the hard way certain things sell and certain things don't say
Right I see so
Free Speech systems actually
Pays to develop the product
Sales on a store
And those Investments have
Risen on the order of hundred thousand
Dollars
With respect sir
Products
Those would be the minimum
Minimum cost
Generally I mean no smallest thing you can do in bike cost
Effectively probably in
Thirty-two $50,000 category but it's hardly worth
Stafford to do it so they
Substantial
Amount of risk involved
Producing a product
If it doesn't
And Soto
The
Providing
Dad and information about those
Business and marketing strategies
What results in peeling
The wells invest
Yes that's true too
And I was hoping that you
I was hoping this time too
Prevent fungus
It sounds a little paranoid but
But there are
Certain
Political
Grapes
That
Have some in the
Anteater
Our
Platform which is primarily
Informational we radiologically driven and we want to
Promote a message
It has to do with
Traditional American values
And we believe that there are people that would like
To put us out of business
And we think that
Of the knowledge of
What are true
Financial
Condition is
Could be used for harm
Interested
So there's a couple of ways that you could interpret that that if people knew what their actual
Financial State was
Is it could lead to harm
You could think that means like well if people knew how poorly they were doing
They're in that they were that close to the edge
That it would hurt them
I don't think that makes
You could interpret it as if people knew how well they were doing it could hurt them because that could
To be used against them as a
Look at this pile of cash they have
And I think that's a possibility but actually
I think
Taking this as a thought that branches off of the supplement
Conversation and stuff
I think
That what he's actually saying is more to the effect of
If they knew who we private labeled from they could put pressure on them and they wouldn't allow us to sell the product
I think that that's more like what what we're going out here
Because Alex knows that you can't take sponsors and stuff because unless they're like Mike Lindell
Somebody who's like
Already
Superfriend gym and immune from
Any kind of push back that comes from it and I have to assume that some of these companies
If it were public
That he's private labeling their products and telling them they would terminate that agreement
As opposed to withstanding the kind of criticism
But they would get
I think that that's what David saying
In this
Yeah it can't be it can't be that he think obviously it's not people knew that we were doing poorly because
You combine that with the political thing
Then what would happen if she's describing people
Clowning on
You know they mock them that wouldn't be that wouldn't be damaging to them that I could be advantageous exact in some
Subway's because the audience would rally to the aid of
Of their Heroes
The only the only possibilities as far as this question is concerned is
If people knew what we were doing and how well we were doing
They would try and stop
So the less they know about what we're doing and how well we're doing
The less people bother us
It does it feels like it could be that whatever it is it's like a nice or something
So
The dynamic
Of covering things because they
Drive
Sales and stuff
Comes up the part of the crime
And are you aware that
Of circumstances were in those occasions
There was a spike in Revenue that
It was decided by Alex
Perhaps others
They would try to
Recreate that Spike by
Covering the same story or returning to the same story
No I'm not aware
Okay
That's just something that you into it
Would have happened
Just something I've observed
Wait
So you've observed it but you're not aware of it
In that regard
I've observed
For example if
People are being
Stressed out
About the idea of there being very dangerous flu thing
Things out there
And stuff and we
Found that there is a
Product it is
License PDF
FDA to be a good Surfer
Infection
And actually you can
Can make claims along those lines
If there is a
Headline that they
Disease Control Atlanta as Center Atlanta is saying
Please up five times
Send Wayside we have something that we believe will
Sport near me
And I personally use it as a hand sanitizer
You know that's kind of puff resale
Puffery Soule
Now this is interesting because this isn't 2019
It's right as before
We know from watching the way the covid is covered and the way that Alex tries to sell the sea
Silver product
It matches up very closely and very well with
This puffery
David Jones might say
And
I mean he's not saying that
But the way ilex did sell those products that you can make claims about
Was fraudulent
Yep he was mixing up his internally taken silver with the topical
Silver
In terms of its ability to protect or or ward off viruses
I have this
My friend
Not good
Wow that is that is
Just a vape
Could not be more
Clear
After watching there will only be alone survivors followed by
Call does it's all a lie you just need silver
It's like well it's your your take
Is
Money that's your take on things
That's what you need to do to get money
Saudia the subject of Gunn fear comes up the Alex talking about they're going to take your guns all the
Something that is
Helpful to drive sales
Write an interesting take on this shouldn't have
And you can see him double back on us to strike the record
And when
Alex
Discover stories
Stat
Amplify that
Concern
Has it been your experience that
That increases
Both traffic to the website
And people find byproduct
Counterintuitive but negative issues
Is that are depressing
Inara bummer
Tender Hearts
Hertz sales
We sell a lot better when Alex
Cheerful
And enthused about every
Everything and what winners we are when he's mad at the world because
Screwed up
We're losing our rights peep
People tend not to buy
And if you seen that borne out by the data
Yes you have
Best out of this maintained by
Prepuce not maintain
I would say it's anecdotal but I am pretty good on him
Anecdotal
Okay
Wow
That yes to the is there data is ago I f***** up obvious
So obviously what a fun little what a fun little trap
Okay all right those are good answer what are you doing
Just constant little
Sneaking in there and if you accidentally answer you revealed a lot more than you wanted
Have you seen the data sir oh yeah there's sheets of anecdotal stories
Dataprise
Talking about manhood smooth smooth also if people buy more when Alex's happy maybe you should try being happy more
Maybe they wouldn't be in such Financial Straits and wasn't screaming and threatening to go off pretty regularly
It would be better tomorrow
Maybe maybe
Subject of mda's comes up non-disclosure agreements
But everybody except Alex's dad apparently his hind
Antenor
Chimes in this play I want to talk a little bit about non-disclosure agreements
When did
Free Speech systems first start requiring employees to enter
Nda's
From the very beginning
Have you signed an NDA
Are there any other employees that you're aware of
I would not find an Indian
You the only one
Define idiom
When you say from the very beginning
What are you
What's the beginning for you
Well the beginning tomatoes
This when Alex moved out of his house
And on Demaree
And I don't know what year that was
Probably 2,000
Over 2,000
And your understanding is that from that time
He started requiring every employee hired by Prince
Set 2005
And that's a
Ballpark
Now that you could be two or three years
Before after
No I'm coming in with a I wasn't paying attention
Fell asleep again my bad my bad listen I just hope I don't fall asleep in the courtroom or nothing I'm I right
I'm on the ball
Wilkinson
So
So Andy are pretty important
When you don't want people talking s*** about how many fake stories you tell
Are you lie about everything there's another reason
Do you have an understanding yourself
Why
It is important to free speech systems to have
Their employees under non-disclosure agreements
It's a useful to communication tool
What
Particularly it is event
Twisted people are making
If people develop
Let's just say mental health issues
And one of the things that waiting to get it back
Offered
Jacobson was
Some psychological help.
Because we thought he was knocking
Congrat with reality
And ultimately his EEOC
Complaint was dismissed
Okay so if I understand what you're saying is that
One of the
Things that a non-disclosure agreement
Prevents is if somebody becomes mentally on
Stable
The company is protected from what they might say after they leave the company
Right
It's not too effective with people who aren't thinking well but if people are think
Working well
They can be aware that
Did they have DVDs
That could
Have concert
If they are improving
The badass
Just put it in basic terms isn't purpose of the nda's
Happy's pizza stones used
Prevent employees
Disseminating information
That is
Proprietary to free speech systems
Right
Yes
I could put it that way instead of saying in case somebody has a mental health crisis as it can't weird
Should about us later or something describing the reason
That is completely fallacious because you're saying that if somebody has like a mental break
Or whatever after they leave
Then NBA is helpful for
Getting them to not say bad things are not syncing correctly
It's just it's nonsense this is such a
I I mean I appreciate the true orwellian doublespeak of an NDA
Is good for communication
But I think it is
Because it's communicating
Very true
So the subject of customers comes up and this got to bum me out a little bit
Real sad
Some of these customers have been been around for a long time
Don't know
A percentage in mind of what percentage of
Free pizza
Revenues derived
From products tails
Infowars store
No
Give a ballpark
Possibly something like
80% problem
And then the remainder is comprised of
Donations
From processed through infowars.com
Used to be from
Description
Services
Some advertising
You know
The core customers are very important to us and one of the strange things that occurred
When we were deplatformed everybody thought we would go away
But many of those core of loyal
Customer
Mercer virus before they even knew what the internet was
Bicycle
So they either use
Telephone numbers are
New what iron
Email address was or whatever
I could do it
But
Deplatforming
It's hardest with
Acquisition
A new customer
Search engine
Not only
Don't send us they tell people they tell 2 billion people if you put link to Alex Jones run for
And don't say you're doing it says you want to criticize him we're going to
Take you down and kill you too
Exaggerating a little bit no not at all
Alright
So much because I
What he's saying is more or less like what I want deplatforming came around
Everybody Talks
We would go away but it turns out jokes on you
We have people trapped even more tightly than you even imagine
Why is all of our customers use
Phone right at 4
50 years yeah
But he does Express something that I have made a point of a lot and that is the financial impact
Of the deplatforming is largely going to be felt
In the acquisition of new customers
New people coming into his Revenue stream is hurt by the lack of Freedom frightened terms
Disseminating content
And these platforms
I'm just by their very nature if you're not growing you are
Drinking because there is a going to always
Be
A certain amount of people who get this illusion to turn right go on to hardcore stuff again sucked into
The Q or whatever
Your fanbase is never going to be static necessarily is if you are constantly adding new people in
That it will eventually be entropy
If you're going to lose
No I mean it's it is nice to hear in the deposition of Alex Jones's father that we are
The right to be so f******
Hard on everybody when they won't stop platforming and that's what that he's the one explaining that that's how they get new
You f****** people right that's why the criticism is particularly harsh about people like Rogan
Yep
Make these
Ill-advised
People who share that f****** Bon Iver
I'll do have f****** Cuban a doll thing
Yeah
He doesn't get new people anymore unless those
Do you do it
And you don't want to be one of those bags
Yep
Anyways anyway
I was watching this and it doesn't
Feel like Alex much
Jesus dad
Yeah and it doesn't feel like Alex
That much
His voice is much more measured Fairy look like
Pauses
Thoughtful long pauses supposed to confuse
He doesn't seem angry
Maybe he's better at controlling that maybe he's just an older person is more life experience
He seems aware of what questions are being asked to him and why they're being asked
For the most part
Yeah this doesn't
Feel like Alex but in this next clip I really saw I saw a
And so that Core group of customers
Some of which
Appreciate the internet and
I'm somewhat you developed before
But but it
Play predated
Social media influencer
You're trying to say
Before social media became someone
Audience
Which is the product
The product buying audience
It is critical to maintain
Obviously right
When he made that Al Gore joke which is
Something that Alex makes two
It's a bad joke
Yeah I'm laughing he's looking around for sort of validation on his joke told him there is a look on his face
That is like that I see Alex's face right here
And I'll try and get a screenshot of that and tweeted out but like
To be like
You're coming towards the end of this hour deposition
I get it yeah cic the the
The Alex
Any drones that is an interesting an interesting question you know that
How much
You know I like obviously I've noticed myself doing many of my father's mannerisms overtime sure especially
Age
Couldn't go the other direction is the question I have
Could David Jones
Have spent so much time with his a******* Sun
Now he can't help but be like
Elgin like Al Gore making the internet in my right guys at I'm pretty funny or how much of that Indian Alex is the
The influence of the moral compass of Infowars
31 West Olympia
They talked a bit about
Interaction that he has with Alex
Apparently they only talk business like once a month or something
Define difficult to believe and so did Maddie
But this is just
I mean
First of the month I put my gold coins into the into the safe and then we begin business meetings new business
Only comes after old business obviously this answer to the question and description here is like
It's okay characterizes everything for me
I want to see about your
Relationship with Alex
Can you describe it
Professional dynamic between the two of you
Mom
Business relationship with Alex
Just highly business-oriented he wants
That he's a big fan of George Washington
And he wants read a biography of George Washington where George Washington hired a friend of his to manage one of his Plantation
Hey wrote the guy letter saying just because you're my friend doesn't mean I'm not going to hold you to a very high standard
I'm going to hold you to a much higher standard than I do anybody else sucks
Expect you to do it
And I would say my range
Professional relationship is rigorous
So you have an anecdote from a founding father
Story that may or may not be
Allele
From a book that Alex allegedly wrote
Yeah but then also the other thing they're of my business relationship is business-oriented
I'd like that that has come to characterize what I feel when I think about David Jones Faz
Answer non-answer
There's nothing ironically like pulling teeth
It really is just give any specific areas like II
But after that question I'm like okay
Okay David
Great story
What do you do
What do you do what do you do if you are held to a higher standard
How your how do I understand her
What is the basis of that standard what are the standard
Spy with your judge
Thing you did that you were doing things that are inconvenient
I will not expect
I can't speculate about Thursday
Yeah yeah it's annoying
And we're not able to get Doctor Jones
Comeback for other deposition Explorer I think there's a lot of follow-up
Questions
Maybe wooden
Has been
As in there Mya the lawyers mines in 2019 that's certainly
Later down the road would have been
First thing to
I get to the bottom of butt
Apparently he wasn't
Responding to the request I think you need bill for this one I think
Could really cracking
I think David I think there's a point where David wood
He's if you feel coiled spring there's going to be a point
Where is you can get him there and he will explode on you
I don't think it's possible to imagine that there's someone in the Jones family that isn't like
Serta full of Summer Rae
Yeah I'm not saying that I'm not saying he's obviously he's not as easy to get a rise out of as Alex
Try to do anything to get Alaska
Write this it this is a nut that you would have to take some time to crack
Mary is a professional person who is like well I'm not going to
Purposefully
Try and infuriated person beyond all reason that's just wrong
Auto professional interior saying that the key is a gummy worm
I don't know we may never know if possible
So are we come to the end of this exploration of family time
Happy Thanksgiving to us all
Tualatin Heights
I thought this was Illuminating in some ways but also fairly Limited in.
The amount of time that they had
He was very clear that it was
Pretty tight
Because at the end
Norma's is saying I cry think this is about all
The time we're going to give
No it's okay
It couldn't have been as impactful as a lot of the other I like Alex depositions or the corporate reps wear
You're here for 2 days
I still think there's a lot to be to be to be said for this this is one that really for the first
Time
For the first time
I want to dig into what the f*** is going on with this dude brain
You know after this deposition
I I feel like
This is an Avenue where if I can understand
This guy
Then it will be much
Clear all that.
So apparently he won't answer the f****** question
That's where we are
That is true
But at the same time we still get the you know the answer about the spike strip
We're optimization about the confidential and proprietary
Elements of a marketing plan that may or may not exist call Susan Alex's head
Nonsense
Jordan will be back
In theory weather episode soon but until then
Babe what's up we are also
Will be back but until then
Emilio Emilio on dzx Clark
Gosh it
On your way home to go by the library for me
Things that I have checked out too long.
You actually read that you got to read this
The sex robot
Alex