Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for knowledge babe I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Need
What about Alex Jones
My brakes today Jordan as we continue the 2022 serial Adventures
Made aware
That's there's a new captain
Crotch
Out there all right when I heard about this
You're crazy for this one Captain Crunch
What is it you're out there
Caramel Captain Crunch
Yeah it's not go
No how could it be
Dads
It tastes bad and also it tears your mouth into shreds right
The concept of it is
Time for that
Tsar there's just like Cocoa Puffs and then I guess the
Captain Crunch pieces are like sort of caramel ish but they're not really bad and I realized as I was eating it if this was more
Karmaloop be worse
Oh yeah yeah yeah I bought it
So
It wasn't good anyway I appreciate the effort
It's almost like what they should have done if they were going to do that
It's almost like what they should have done is gone with a caramel corn
Kind of
Angela on some of them
You got maybe a little caramel coating on the others like a like a popcorn situation you don't then
Yeah and it feels maybe a little more I'll tell Manolo so maybe you have like more of a seasonal family
Yeah it will get suck
It's not good
I mean why not just make
Crab
That makes more sense captain crunch's of the Seas
Barnacle flavor
Go for it to take weirdos
Crab and crunchy water flavored
It makes her milk all salty and taste like Brian
I like it
My bright spot is
I found out
Some people texted me that Jordan Peele
Being Jordan Peele Fancher
You know the quality other Jordan
Right
Sheep
You show
Call The Quiet part loud
How far is that
It's a horror podcast
But it's a joke what's funny to me
Is cuz I didn't even think about that
Somebody texting me that and then the other two days ago
The thought occurred to me like oh
Oh
There had to have been
People who accidentally found my book
Based upon that all the Jordan and the name are the there had to have been so I met
He might be higher in search results way higher way higher
What's funny to me of
Alright is that I don't I didn't pay for the analects
I'm the Squarespace or whatever
But it does show you if there's been a huge bump in traffic or not
The day it was released
Huge spike in traffic with a bunch of people whether or not they
But it makes me laugh
Why do people say what is so funny to me is they looked at me like what the fuc
Is this
Wow this is going to
Turn pills going to sue this guy this guy on the ropes
Well congratulations on Backstreets traffic
But yes
All over
We do not upset on Friday although we
We did
Mean to we did attempt to
I'm in the situation was that Alex has been waiting for him to re-emerge
Right
TD special of some sort but now he was he stayed true to his word of not working
Proud of them
Took another vacation was at the studio all week
And left
Owen Shroyer in charge of the ship
Answer that made things a little bit tough
And now we arrive back here on Mondays episode and
Alex has still been out of studio and
I
Decided that what we should do is go back and look at a little bit of the stuff that happened
Over the course
Of the beginning of the week
And
See the response to the Club Q shooting
Colorado Springs
I feel like
That is worth
Seeing how they covered it
You know it wasn't Alex himself it was Owen Shroyer who is
Leading the charge
In the studio
And so yeah that's what we're going to look at here we're going to talk a bit about November 20th and 21st
First boy we're going to hear some Owen
Yep Troy dog
Alright
You're if you destroyed your your testicles to shrink as well still having Troy Dre
I'm about to
The first you are not nor will you ever be a policy walk nevertheless you are now a policy wonk
Next Alex's motherfuking positive sometimes make me think my Bluetooth speaker got unpair from my phone thank you so much right now
My apologies
Thank you very much appreciate the motherfuking I appreciate it was
It was interesting to work into the Rhythm next smelly we bucket of pooper thank you so much you are now policy want
To everyone in my name because I listen to you wow
Wow
I'm working out and end up giggling as much when I was wrong
Very much so your wife
Why is Easter
Weil funeral wailcester
Ritualistic barbecue sauce
Thank you you are now it's a crap I listen to 200 episode
Drop thank you so much you are now attacking
I'm a policy wonk
I have
Risen above
A little breaking for me
And then we're going
Comeback
And I'm going to
Start the show over
I got plenty of words
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
Horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just
And you never see me again
I never wanted
To the crew in the leicestershire
Bentley
So I'm going to start things off here with just a clip of the beginning of the November 20th
We don't talk a lot about Owen
Find him to be unpalatable to listen to
I think you sucks
Is bad
Kind of
A knockoff
Alex and he's doing the shotty imitation of this person
And he doesn't understand what makes Alex compelling as an orator
Or as somebody who's speaking
Galax
Those things that make Alex
Fascinating
A chaoticness to Alex
There's a confidence there's an unpredictability
Let make
What do you think things like
Someone brought in Donuts
Stop it
Yeah I appreciate that he's
A chaotic nephrite
Black
Fat
I mean at the very least Owen has no idiosyncrasies
There is nothing that makes Owen a unique in any kind of Truth
And if there is anything it feels very
Contrived
If there's anything that's idiosyncratic about him it feels like this is me signalling to
The right-wing troll base or whatever you know there's nothing there's nothing organically Owen
Other than like a man kind of snarky
Kind of generic in Alex impression
And so when you begin the show I mean this is really just
And how its impression this far as I
Unconcerned
Ladies and gentlemen here we are on November 20th
Global Journey
You're not an animal
10 things that Alex Goes constantly as he's dramatic
Monologues over the intro music and kind of
Are you sad that it's one of the only things that perhaps you could
Unqualifiedly say he's good at
He is good at ramping up some kind of an artificial sense of drama in the end now
I think Humanity stands poised
Like there is something that even though you know it's
Faking It
Domino's meaningless there's still something it's like there's a dramatic tension to that
Like there's nothing better than authenticity or whatever once you can fake that you've got it made
You know that kind of idea
And Alex can jump
Yeah probably anticipating and Owen is so
Transparently
Just like
But again even even in that faking the authenticity he's faking the fake
Version that Alex
Exactly
Just
Boring
Alright alright kid
Get your own style reminds me of when I'm when I was starting out in Inn, Dayton
Canaan Impressions Kyle Kinane there was a Mitch Hedberg
They're all those people who were starting out who were just doing impressions
There's a lot of people have distinctive deliveries and it's hard not to
Be your influences you get caught in that kind of vibe and then if you don't break out
You should stop forever you know it's that kind of thing if you don't develop your own voice
Quit there isn't there isn't a whole lot going on here
Outside of a Canaan impression metaphorically
So on the evening of November 19th through 22 year old named Anderson Aldridge interclub.
Q in lgbtq club in Colorado Springs and open fire
They killed 25 people and 25 others were injured in the attack
This story is first
Foremost a tragedy
In another sign of the rising tide of anti-lgbt
Violence in no small part facilitated and encouraged by modern right-wing media that accuses all members of that community
Good evening pedophiles who are out to groom your child
Alex some Ever Wanted Infowars is complicit in that trend
And and the natural endpoint of promoting and normalizing that mentality
Is it some people who internalize it and accepted as
May be inspired to take matters into their own hands
Beyond being the tragedy this
Case is also a complete f****** mess
The accused shooter Aldrich is the grandson of a right-wing California politician who supported the January
6th riot
And is the son of a very homophobic former pornstar who went by the name dick Delaware
Who also appeared on an episode of intervention because he was addicted to meth
To complicate matters even further Aldridge
Lawyers have claimed that Aldrich is non-binary and wants to be referred to with they them pronouns
Who just caused a lot of varying reactions for people
The prevailing attitude people
Seem to have is that this is a ploy to dodge potential hate crime penalties in the case
Since babe never spoken about this prior
And they were known to routinely use anti-lgbt
Peekyou slurs
People were very shocked
To see an interview with their dad where he expressed his surprise hearing his son was involved
A gay bar
Not because five people were murdered but because he was concerned that his son was gay
It's really awful to see but in the interview he also says that he hasn't been in aldrich's life for over a decade and
He doesn't come off as a very sober interview subject
Even though he hasn't been in his son's life
He does say that he raised his child to know that being gay is wrong and then fighting is the answer to confer
He seems like a s*** influence even though he's very clear that he's talking about hand-to-hand combat and that guns and
Murder are not good
Good distinction
Great
On top of all this Aldridge's mother called the police after Aldridge made a bomb threat targeted her
But too often the case charges were pressed
And Aldrich was able to keep his gun
I do believe that Aldrich could have made that bomb threat but also the mom is not a great source of information
Either
From an article in CNN
Quote
In 2009 Aldridge's mother received three years of probation for convictions of public intoxication and falsely
Reporting a crime to the police
The false report can Vicks
Since a May 2008 incident in Murrieta California in which police responded to a reported home invasion
And found voepel lying on her bed with her hands and legs bound with duct tape
Mobiles initially told police a man had put string around her neck boundary with tape and placed a knife on her chest
She admitted the following day however
That she had been under the influence of Narcotics
And fabricated the incident because
Quotes she was lonely and wanted attention of police reports
All of this just completely makes me feel ill
And at the end of the day I feel terrible for what Aldridge clearly had to live with growing up but that doesn't
Really matter anymore
People who have had more difficult challenges of some Advantage not to murder five people with
Clear intentions
To kill many more
I don't want to send
All the love and support I can to the survivors and friends and families of those lost
I call her in Colorado Springs
As well as that all of our lgbtq
YouTube family
Anyway
It was somewhat convenient that Alex was out of Studio last week because that meant that we didn't have to talk about his coverage
Of the shooting but I think
It's actually important to loop back and take a look at
My reasoning takes into account a few
The first is that it's relevant to understanding tours angle on this story
The second is something that I thought was a little bit more compelling which is that the right-wing media is coverage of this attack has been in.
In a way that I think does field
Different
For lot of folks
Then other times in the past
Princeton
Tim pool took
To Twitter to rationalize the shooting is the natural reaction
To the idea that cloak you had a quote grooming of that
Which is the way he characterized A Drag Brunch
The club was hosting
Get a sickening take that legislation needed to be passed in police needed to stop events like all aged Ragbrai
Crunches
But because that wasn't happening it only makes sense that people would try to solve the problem with violence
In this clip where he's trying to be like a piece of s*** troll
I noticed that he slipped a little
Now he's just trolling
As a whole with this question that he's
It's not a sincere question
But see if you can notice where he slips up a little bit
A bunch of goddamn pedophiles
Are grooming children
I'm when we're like
Hey stop associating
All lgbtq people with groomers
Y'all keep f***
Can do it
So you're laughing
If you claim
Drama refers to all
Lgbtq
Then you are calling
All lgbtq
See people groomers
And you are inciting violence
Stop inciting violence
Against
He knows damn well that right-wing figures use the term groomer as a catch-all for their anti-lgbtq big
It's cute game he's playing here but in order to take it seriously you'd have to imagine that Tim is never talk to or listen to any of the
People who come onto his show as gas
The slip-up I was talking about is that he says lgbtq p
He says that because he hangs out with a community of people who use that term to imply that pedophiles are inherent part of it
A distinct group within the lgbtq community
It's a hard slip-up to make too because it requires him to pronounce the P sound
Twice in a row
Which he did
To say lgbtq people
Yep it's a little bit taller
Matt Walsh has another figure that is decided to dip his toes into the Waters of justifying mass murder because of his own prejudice
You put a video on YouTube where he said quote
Is it that hard to not cross dress in front of kids
Is the compulsion that overwhelming
If it's causing this much chaos and violence
Why do you insist on continuing to do it
The trend among these figures is that they've decided to push the idea that the shooting while probably unfortunate is justice
Viable because Drag Brunch
Exist
They paint the picture that the Drag Brunch is what's causing the violin
Lgbtq folks would just agree to exist in the constricted boundaries
The right-wing extremist speakers in the media demand
Then the violence would stop
This behavior is legitimately
Very difficult for me to distinguish from making failed terrorist
It's all bulshit it's not even a sincere pointed someone like Matt Walsh is making
And it all makes me completely sick
The types of reactions that we see from these ostensibly more mainstream figures are the sort of things usually normally
Just here in places like Infowars
But now
Daily wire pundits and Tucker Carlson are walking all the way up to the Infowars line and debatably Crossing
Will be helpful to accurately get a sense of what Infowars coverage consisted of in the after
This episode that we're going to be covering here it starts with November 20th
The day after the shooting
When Owen was filling in for Alex
Who's the Sunday show so it begins at 4 p.m. central
There's no reason for them not to be aware of a lot of the primary details by the time Owen gets on there
You look mad
I don't know
By their own logic day then it's fine to murder them
Like I don't I don't even know how you can say that without recognizing
That if you are their self the cause of violence in lgbtq people
Can murder you based upon your own dumb f****** argument so I don't give a fuk
Alright I understand it's
It's important to recognize this into something or argue
I don't I mean I don't care
Images trying to not
No we're not I'm sorry
I don't mean to cut you off so I'm cutting you off so please continue that's on me that's on me
Do you think that
There is a hope that maybe some of the people in their audience would take this as a sincere argue
Argument that they want to commit to
Right because of the
Bad and stupid implications up
Just a deflection from taking any kind of stock
Of the kind of rhetoric that you are engaged putting out into the world and the consequences videos can have
Right and I say that
And I mean what you know
4 years ago I think I'm on your team
And now I don't think that what they say matters
Beyond
If you say it then you said it
Via I don't I think I don't care if they are genuine about it or not I don't think it matters
Clearly I think clearly the people who want to
Say that s*** and then whenever somebody challenges them walking back cuz I wasn't being serious I wasn't being super
I don't give a s***
You said it.
It Is by
Tim pool f****** argument
Farm to murder Tim
Well but that being said
His argument is bad
Yes absolutely I'm so it is not a justification to feel super hot to be totally clear
I agree with you in the sense that I do think the people if they're saying things and make an argument station
You know you want it now
Make that I mean I just don't care if you think your trolling or not that's over
For we used to have that trolling thing where you be like
Oh they don't mean it I don't f****** care if they mean it anymore their people's were saying that it's almost it's almost
Most irrelevant
Or if you mean something as much as the effect that what your have
Nope no more no more walking back no more pretending that you were trolling no more nothing you own that forever now
Temple can go f******
Tim pool
Fair enough
So Oma
The shooting
It says not enough first and foremost on his mind but it does have a guest coming
30 minutes
Surgery
Owen is not
Covering the shooting
Per se
But he's leaving the show talking about how he's having Alex Stein on
Because he has a video that he put out where he went and was being a dick
At drag queen story
So you can hear in there always engaging in the exact
Start of demonization
Campaigns at the right is just
Characterized
Yeah I know I mean at the end of the day
This needs to be a society white acceptance that
The far-right wants to kill gay people
Beyond
Daddy said he wants to
That we need to all agree on what to do with themselves
I mean again I really don't care
I just don't care I'm addicted
To being precise
Fair enough
So Owen talks about how they have a rifle
Symbol of rifles there there's a people who were protecting
The drag queen story time
It seems like they're not really like
Understand the dynamic
Have a good time
With Alex Stein
Yes there are people with
Rifles who are protecting a drag queen Story Time and apparently the story
Discovering is that there are more gay people who are turning against
Drag Brunch is the idea that
They would arm themselves
To protect themselves
Has not yet sunk in
To the right wing
They haven't that like the idea is like
So people have guns there
Meaning they're there to print
Text
Against other groomer showing up
As opposed to to protect
Those people inside
From Eufaula
Even if you take
The shooting
In Colorado Springs
Away
From
A2B
Fully
Fair
At the time that we're recording this episode
I don't think we know enough about a full motive
Or anything
Yeah you can make some pretty
Decent assumptions based on available information
But you know there is still a little bit of a leaping to a conclusion
About the precise mode
But even leaving that aside
If you don't want to get tangled up in that
You can still save it like
Proud boys are showing up and disrupting aggressively drag queen story times in various parts
To the country
A lot of times arm
Yelling about how there's
Pedophiles grooming children and hear the idea of armed security in response to that is even
Understandable
You know it even if
There hadn't been
Refusing it would make total sense
100%
But yeah
It's weird it's almost like
No just heard a punting on talking about the
Do the Elephant Room right now still covering these topics
That are adjacent to the subject
Find to be
Not the tip of the spear
No
No no
It's I suppose
Pretending that the worst thing that you are at fault for didn't happen so you can
Continue to make it
So we got to kill some time here sure why not
Show me Subway
I don't necessarily buy shut the fuk up you don't have anything
We don't we don't take cash anymore
Sorry
You're not up to date on your phone
The paranoid fantasy
Kind of getting in the way of enjoying the thing that I am fine with him
Inconvenient it is convenient to not take a boat across the Atlantic
You know I get it I appreciate it I like to get on the plane
And then you go from one
Country to another it's great houses paranoid fantasy what happens
Pterodactyl
Left
Right you don't even know which side the pterodactyls are on
Alright see you in the plane
Yeah
Where is it easier to Rob
Get out of the plane exactly
Run an improv show is another problem playing
Exactly they are trying to get you
Like accustomed to Flying because take it out of the plane so they can put on
So you'll be acclimated to bad improv shows no matter where you go also to Owens point
I mean I think
Babe and someone who's worked in a bar before
It's
Way more convenient to have tabs
It's substantially easier than making
Change for people
Especially if it's a busy bar in the second it's dangerous to be a high cash business
That you're at the end of the night you have tons of money you have you has the potential
Put yourself in a bit more of a dangerous situation
For robberies and such
I think that there's only positive
Stu
Bars if they choose to being cash
Non
Using bars
To Owens arguing
I say
When when when when when will stop whining
You whine
Ray's wine
Winding so about 20 minutes into the show
I want finally gets to talking about how there was a shooting
Club
Are you kidding me
Oh man
So you can see here is Owen begins to bring up the story of the shooting in the space of twenty-four seconds implants
Three separate suggestions
To distract the audience from the possibility that this was a mass shooting directed at a community
Did his show and his employer Target routinely with ridiculous Lander and
First on couches the conversation in terms of discussing the liberal media is a response
So the shooting because
That's more fertile territory for him
He doesn't have the chops
To actually discuss the shooting itself but yelling a bunch
Dumb s*** about random tweets he saw is basically the same thing on Infowars
2nd Owen says this is a quote supposed Gabe
He knows that if the target of a mass shooting was a gay club there's a high likelihood that a potential motive is homophobia or
Transphobia which are the primary drivers of Infowars contest
In order to create distance in the audiences mind between the possible motive for the shooting and the rhetoric they hear everyday
Owen tries to subtly suggest
But it's not actually a gay bar
If I want wanted to do it
Tiny bit of research e could have found their website and seeing that instead of
Serving aioli fries they have
Gail Lee fries
It's on their menu which is a subtle hint
Very subtle
He could have checked out their drink menu and seeing that quote cock shots are on the menu which are described as quote
Jello shots dispense through a white or brown cock shaped syringe
Check they also have a shot called the c******
Which is fire whiskey and Bailey's alright
I'm not into it
The Wayback machine has snapshots of their sight going back to 2000
For where they're described his quote at the premiere gay restaurant and Nightclub
Their phone number is 571
Gay
I say this with nothing but love and respect
This is not a supposed
Gay club
It's an Owens interest to muddy the waters though so he throws that into plant seeds of Suspicion in the listener
And actually
If this is more important than it may seem
An article about clubque was published in the Colorado Springs Indy in July 2020 with the headline quote
Colorado Springs last remaining gay bar Club Q changes with the time
That article is a fascinating tale of the queer history of Colorado Springs
And how it went from a severely anti-lgbtq environment to the 90s to Tabitha Vibrant Community in a bunch of Gabe
Bars to this point in 2020 where there was just this one gay bar left in town because has technology advanced
You didn't need to have a specific lgbtq bar for people to meet up
They could use apps and online dating
So many of the other bars became quote
Gay-friendly butt
Club Q that the owner Nick greska told the India bout a former bar they worked at quote
When people would call us and asked if we were at a bar I was instructed to say
We were a gay-friendly bar
Not explicitly gay bar
But that's not enough
Clubque was supposed to be explicitly gay and as greska put it quote
The whole idea of this place was to have a safe place to get a permanent one in the city
This is the place that only suggesting is maybe not actually a gay bar
Because he's an idiot
You just talk s*** and it doesn't know anything about the subjects he covers
The third thing he does is it gets all weird about the club being called clubque which he totally isn't saying is I'm going to do with you now
Ron stuff totally not
He's doing this because the audience is trying to associate things that are connected to the Q folks to be a globalist
Psyop
So that was one of yours one of the main defenses that Alex deployed about why January 6th wasn't actually the Patriots fault
I didn't call the shooting of false flag however if it's clubque I think you can put it
Together doing this to wink at the audio
Maybe they should think that it's a global Asylum
Again the club was named clubque I sent at least 2004 so unless qanon has been going on since their Joy
George W Bush Administration
And therefore it actually predates the Tea Party
If I had to guess
Because I can't really nail this down exactly
I would say that maybe the club was named after clubque the long-running dance party for queer women in San Francisco
The beginning like the mid-80s yeah that's just a guess but it's also worth noting that a lot of clear oriented things use the letter q
Yeah
Anyway as you can tell right out of the gate Owen is invested in throwing out distractions
To get away from the heart of the issue and I think that it's pretty f****** obvious why
And this is this is one of the reasons that I I find that argument about
The shooter's Identity or or whatever about it
In regards to the heinousness of
The crime being a hate crime
If you are attacking
A place that the
Illicitly safe
Forgave
People then it is by nature a n
Whitley homophobic crime
Regardless of motive or in
Tent broke because
I don't give a f*** what his brain but their brain
Suggest
Is the motive behind their attack
The attack itself
Is the motive
I agree I agree with you I do still think that there are important
Things to terms of the broader conversation those things are important
Particularly in terms of the way that this shooting
Connect to
The rhetoric that's being that that's deployed by
Checkers in the right-wing media
I think
That is where that intersection is important the motive in
I agree with you that the effect
Of it is is
It's an attack on the safety of all
Gay people
Simultaneous I don't disagree with that
Yeah I know I just don't I just wanted to make sure that I was given to the idea that the motive is not unimportant
What you're saying is that regards it is entirely possible I believe it's entirely
A possible for this person to have not listened to a single word that Tucker Carlson
Or Alex Jones have said it's entirely possible that this is unrelated
To the larger
Global rhetoric
Around the circumstances could be very personal but the attack itself
Tells you what the motive is
It's an attack on a safe space
Yeah and it's me it seems
Unlikely
From a lot of surrounding contacts
Text that
That Daddy doesn't
Exist with
In the larger context
Right of
Of so much of this right-wing media weather be on social media or
You know these people's actual shows
But
The extent that there is a Clear Connection
That is something that is a little bit March
That I can respect
So Owen
Plays a little bit more of a sort of
A deflection game
I'm not sure this argument is as good as Owen thinks it is
He's saying that his rebuttal to people calling for gun reform based on the mass shooting is to point out that there are even more shootings
Isn't it just saying that the problem is worse than the gun-grabbers or say this is dumb
Hopefully this is a dishonest ARG
Owen isn't arguing for anything political or even productive
At the core he's saying that people shouldn't care about the Club Q shooting
That's the point of this present
He's pushing back against people caring about a mass shooting at a gay bar where five people were killed and many more would have been
The shooter had been beaten up by Brave bar
Obviously other shootings are tragic as well and they are all indicative of problems that we need to address
The issue comes down to these not being analogous situation
And because of that the game Owen thinks he
He's playing is actually meaningless
He doesn't
We care about those other shootings
No I mean I I don't
Like it is it is something where
Even if this person
Owen
At one point had some sort of ability to
Connect
Empathetically to a story
By virtue of this
As your job as like your imperative
And as as the social group that he surrounds himself with
Old murders
Are are nothing
You know like
I8 how can you not be affected blows my mind you kind of have to take on a bit of solipsism
Absolutely like nothing I can really be real for you
Southern shootings and it's like I don't even have time to express like
Bat box
3 up man man
Don't think you said one that f**** me I've been there was another that f**** me up and then you said another
That's f***** up it's bad yeah
I don't
Know if
Separate incidents like the one that talked about in Baltimore is 2 people were injured
Yeah that's bad
I mean I'm not sure
If that is the same
As a mass shooting at a club I mean we live in Chicago and we can talk about the gun violence in Chicago
Toggle all we want
But what Owen is talk
About his gun violence
Genocide and trying to
Acts like that Izzy
Equivalent to
Gun violence
Then there's essentially domestic
Yeah
There's a little bit of a
So
What would this show be
If there wasn't a little bit of sexy
Donald Trump
Harass
That's funny because Alex Stein
Rose to prominence cuz he sexually harassed AOC
Man I decide it's funny
You know he's calling her at her
Pretty ladies so too bad too bad she sucks
I needed it is fun that I
Do you know their cowardice
Is so distinct
And clear
Whenever they specifically go after AOC because it's
It's a combined like
One she would never deign to give a f*** about our response so we can
And say whatever we want with no repercussions and let Soros level of life
Well that's not actually true she might dunk on some of these fools on Twitter
Down to the point where she's going to sue them
Something and then it'd be over
Over whatever it is in people
Argue in the comments
For forever
Only it only serves to elevate and get you more attention if she does
Exactly and then the fact that obviously
The angle that they're going to take is a
Paternalistic massage
Without question and it's like
I mean if it's so annoying
You fuc
Nowhere
If you want to f****** come
Trolling motueka outfits
It's
Dumb anyway
Alex Stein comes on
And they play
A clip of him at that drag queen story time
I just think that this is
First of all ridiculous and like this is the day after that shooting I don't know why they didn't
Let's go ahead
Put this off
Yeah
Alex Stein is available anytime
Do this tomorrow or
Next week
Cinnamon to put into your time
Attempted murder's below the waist
God bless
Convoluted
People have a political ideology that says that they should support on Susan's Braxton the Second Amendment
You really disagree with the concept of drag queen story time it should be antithetical to their gun absolutism to mock people for
Carrying in public
And this is why it's important to understand that they don't actually really care about gun
I mean I mean I care about guns and they want them but they want what they represent
More
They want the ability to impose mortal fear in political enemies and couch it in a philosophical love for the Constitution
For instance they want folks to their team to be armed to the teeth when they go to protest at a reproductive Health Point
So the people seeking care or the clinic staff are terrified
Courser protests in the wake of the killing of George Floyd they want people on their side to be armed and wandering around acting is Vigil
That is good
Conversely they don't want principal gun owners to protect the targets of their attacks
They mock carrying guns here when the people are outside of drag queen story time or if armed citizens were to post up at
Abortion clinic
They don't want guns in these contexts because
What those guns represent which is that vulnerable communities may not be as vulnerable as you want them
He's incredibly distasteful for them to be playing this the day after the shooting
How excited is just mocking the idea of armed citizens protecting the drag queen story time which is the exact type of event that people like
Tim pool and Matt Walsh would go on to use as a justification
Why the shooting maybe wasn't so bad
Also sinuses really bad at this
He strikes me as the kid in like I School play who's overact
He's Hamming it up a little bit too much because he knows that no one would pay attention to him if you reeled it in I was subtle
I have a subtle mode and no sucks
He doesn't understand
And because he's f******
King stupid along with the rest of
Is that what he's
He's essentially saying
Is that
All of the horrible f****** murders were committed by us
Because
If you are insistently belittling the
Concept of your ideological opponent
Having guns and in fact having all of them be squirt guns
Then you are actually insisting that
The only people who murder people are the f****** conservatives you f****** moron
Exactly you f****** idiot
Now there is also a subtle
Maybe
I don't know I don't know if this is a conscious
Motivation necessarily or if it's just sort of like
Something that's a part of this and that is that
There is an egg goal
Of kind of mocking
These folks
So they won't
Show back up there won't be people
Standing there right and giving a message that like
This is not a soft target
There is a desire for these people who are standing guard and such
To go away
And I think they do and is pretty aware this as
He explains how he
Antifa out of Austin
You were afraid to do a deposition
Rip Austin antifa
That is one of the most deluded
Things I think I've ever heard I'd like to remind everyone of the time that I got dunked On by a child
I don't think anybody is that interested
Mocking them into submission
Infowars had to hire an outside lawyer to be there f****** corporate representative because we
He made fun of them to be right
We made fun of you too bad
And now you're going to act like you have f****** s*** get out of here
Into submission
Dum Dums in Chicago
Amazing
So
I agree weary of
Hearing Alex Stein's voice reasonable and so I decided to let's go on
Check out other
Episode
See where we're at and sewed the American Journal
The next day
Harrison wasn't host
Arizona Christy Lee who is hosting
I believe
And I
Didn't care
Can we bring another character into this
If it's a fill-in host hosting and is not like
One of their actual Varsity players that I don't have anything to grab onto we could get rid of doctor number for
All soap operas
And no one would notice
Well that's it for the doctor number for
I mean what about house
Oh well I mean I'm talking about
Doctor number for in the script you know what I'm saying
This is Kristi Lee is Doctor number for in the script and we can cut her out
She's got two lines of dialogue
Max
Well actually I am my own argument falls apart
Because
The later seasons of House
He ended up having to pick Survivor style competition
Got a bunch of.
Doctor Who
So maybe maybe there's
11 actor on the show and the writers like hey
We've got a whole thing where were eliminating a bunch of people I'm like s*** I hope I don't find out that they didn't need me
Cowpens was one of the doctors I meant his character committed suicide because he went to work for like the Obama
Realized
Character office
Bummer
We go to the 21st on the Infowars Alex Jones Flagship show
And is hosting again
We Begin the show
With Alex on the phone Alex is hosting on the phone
So he's taking care of the big issues here on this Monday episode Alex's come in specifically on his way
Vacation on the phone to complain about Elon Musk
You know what is a fan of History
Particularly you know I used to do the bit about ants
Andrew Jackson and dualculture
Sure know that kind of
And in
Thinking about that you know it always kept it within the point-of-view of the p
People within the duel
And their Social Circle and how they react
What I
What I forgot
At least what I overlooked I'm just now realizing is what
Must have been like
For just a regular poor person
To suddenly read in the paper you know like
F****** Alexander Hamilton dead
You know and be like
Alright man
What is Elon Musk and Alex Jones had a duel it didn't occur to me that we would all get to be like a
He wants dead nice
How about that
What one of them would be dead dispute
Exactly like how weird would that have been you know in a political Arena
That would be very weird and I think
Bad sister
Let's look at this
Boom threat
He just sent it to exact a letter H back on Twitter
Amen he quoted a Bible verse
Elon Musk is saying that he's going to put a millstone around
Well Alex Beasley Bible is the fundamental inviolate book that is a threat
Dakota scripture at me it is at 5
Scripture boating hat
Alex
Ariana chair
Yeah that makes sense
Yep
No arguments for me
The boj is involved in his tweet
Elon Musk
Doj is Riker tweets for Elon Musk
They are not busy
Nope
Nice
It's the it's the Infowars snap funded that's where you at that's where you know where we're at
Yeah good ad reads he's too good at a trade
The fuk up now
It's also man
Like
But with what's
You're on vacation you're calling in to complain about Elon Musk and try and sell your shirt
Vacation he still needs money and he still reads Twitter
Where else is he going to b**** about it
It's pretty remarkable though that like
I mean
Yeah the shooting was big news for talking about it
Alex is going to come in
Got a weird that he's starting off just being petty about Elon Musk reading do you know I mean
In his world though
It is it is like
Look at the world we live in now
And
This is a f*****-up event
And unfortunately the new cycle is going to
Move on
End
As much as we make fun of Alex for being a f******
Non serialized show
Unfortunately all too often we live in a non serialized show
In this regard
And so I can see why he'd be like a f*** it I better
I can get away with not talking about
Is that all
I got Tim pool and Tucker Carlson and all these motherfukers out here that is
The case then essentially
What is this reveals
Is
Elon Musk tweet
Would also
Then I'll move out of the editorial choice
Pay attention just to things that are
Weirdly self-aggrandizing
As you said earlier might be a part of the gig
So Alex continues to complain
About Elon
Tweeting about it
I don't think I most people in the last forever that thrilled with what he lawn was up to with Twitter
I don't know what kind of charade Alex is trying to pull here
The entire first segment of the show is Alex Shilling his supplements in book
Desperately begging for money
And now the second segment is clearly just Alex
Complaining about a lawn mower
This is an important Dynamic to understand perfume
The first is that Alex
Really can't disappear for too long because no one else moves product at nearly the rate he does
If he wants to take time off
He does kind of need to pop in and do s*** like this to reassure the audience that he's still there and remind them that they need to give my
Money to the cult leader
These people will not tithe 40n or Harrison but Alex can coax that out of
You got it the second is that from a Content perspective the Club Q shooting is not relevant enough for Alex to address on the show
A while he's on vacation
However what's super important to talk about is that Elon Musk
Mentioned him on
He doesn't covered news
Not he's not competent talk show host
But he's amazing at wrangling attend
He's done it since the VHS and bullhorn days and now the technology and social media has evolved this is that equivalent
With you on saying that Alex isn't going to be let back on Twitter Alex knows that he has an opportunity to get
Some attention but it requires a responding to keep the image of a fight alive and
The window is short
He needs to
You know get in there
Now
Because him responding when he gets back from vacation don't give a s***
Self-aggrandizing drama is what Alex is most interested in
And Alex probably should have known that deal on felt this way about him if all the other stories that he tells her true at all
Alex is very strongly implied that he's gone to dinner with Musk
Because of the Rogan connect
How to talk about how Joe is told them that Elon loves him and all this but
Now that musket come out publicly said that Alex has a piece of s*** and is never coming back on Twitter
I guess all that other stuff didn't happen and
How to explain why you made it all up just to Dazzle the listeners
The great yeah yeah it is it is funny to me now like
How open
So many Corporation
Then share about paying my Atlas
We're going to support these politicians I mean we still need our tax
Texas low they want to kill gay people
It Isn't So
People like Alex are all complaining about the left
Just coming to Kelly's like man
The left is nowhere near this s*** the left is nowhere near owning Twitter selectors nowhere near owning Coco
Cola in or whatever it is you want In fairness of woke ideology that runs Coca-Cola
And
The left of own Twitter right that's the problem with Twitter
Too much left is Conte
So Alex complexity of course
Are you just think this is
Sad yeah he's almost 50 I know
This is an adult being like
Elon Musk does not play by the rules of his Twitter poll I mean
Kyra mean
We'll put these tweets on screen is about the worst sentence end up in the English language second only to the
There's a lot of big news
Someone made a meme
Repertoire
Is it strong
Oh my God
I don't like the way this guy who all bought a toy using imaginary money
It's going to be mean to me this is
Very sad very very sad
Yep anyway
Alex understands
Elon splasher
Is it
What
This is this is a six-week hit the panic button put on his big boy pants
Are peas the left
But then
Compared himself to Jesus Christ too far
That's too far also I would say that if there are moles in
Involved I know of one person that you need to call
How to take care of this and that is Anderson Cooper
Back mole quotes
And then I forgot that Anderson Cooper was the
Mark L Walberg
Goldberg
That's the right boy
So this is pathetic but I got to say I admire Alex's swing here
If there's one thing that Elon Musk certainly doesn't seem to care much about it all it's a piece
But
This is great
Now it's can keep all the Rogan backstory and still be mad at MUSC
About him not getting that back on Twitter
He just has to pretend that he's actually mad about his must compare himself to Jesus
Alex does about himself
All the f****** time
Almost dead was quoted Bible verse which if you compare that with Alex's grandiose stories about how God selected him to fly
Like the literal devil
Really seem like that big of a deal
But Alex needs an excuse to be mad but isn't
Just pettiness
And religious bulshit pops the audience so this is a good play honestly I think he nailed it
How you needed the thread that needle
Yeah used
Pulling out a rap
That's what he's going for here because
Sneaky Snake
Beef with Elon musk's cuz if he keeps coming then it's great
One of Alex's great
Trick Susan's
Trying to
Get people caught up in fights with him that serve to elevate his own position Elon Musk
Pig
Great
So what would this show be without a little bit of veiled anti-semitism
Did not know that
You said they were good
Big story
Superhero Alex wears his position at the NBA with his opposition to NFL players taking a knee as a silent protest
Police brutality
I don't think
This is also just a talking point from 2019 that I was just pulling out of his ass to defend himself because he really doesn't have an actual tooth
Transfer his actions other than to
Play Olympus track
Albert borla is ahead of Pfizer and on November 10th he was given the adl's courage against hate
Also would have passed recipient of that
Clumpy will Kaya have a Chobani grapes
The reason we got this award had to do with well I'll just quote his acceptance
Future
Somatic messages on message boards and on Flyers posted in communities across the country suggesting that the
Coronavirus was a tool for Jews to spam expand the global influence
The Jews were profiting
From covid-19 Jews were the real virus
Heat Peddlers referred to the Jew vaccine
To dissuade others from receiving
So messages even refer to my own Jewish heritage
Do use it as evidence
That the widespread vaccine effort
It was part of a calculated long-term Jewish plot
To Institute a global Jew government
It makes sense why borla got this award
Given the context of everything and wow it's fair to agree or disagree with some of the points that he makes in his speech
He didn't say any of those things Alex's claim
How it's probably only knows about this beach and his award at all because of this line
Quote now they're bright spots amid this Darkness
Just last month a jury awarded close to a billion dollars
The families of those who lost loved ones to the Sandy Hook massacre because of one man with a microphone spoke disgusting and disgrace
Hazel eyes
The jury flat-out rejected his lies and made an unambiguous statement that such evil is not acceptable
That got an Applause from the audience
And Alex is probably just a little pissed off that he didn't actually get a name check
Yeah
Yeah that's pretty funny
Say my name
That's pretty funny
Yes I think that's the only reason Alex even knows by
Mother lost a billion dollars and you don't even
This entire segment is essentially Alex claiming that too he didn't do any of the things that people say about
Sandy Hook
Anybody lawn Moss chair and then of course
Even more ads
Biggest alley-oop
Biggest sale reader pudding
Gifts in with the orders that you make me out to be it's a bumper sticker
It's randomly generated by the robot
In his Warehouse
They're going to put little things who knows
Could be anything that you get
Like a Cracker Jack
Yeah just as useless as surprises
That's a big sale also double Patriot points
Ann and I will say that use code 1776 checking if his surprise
Was
Is one of the Batman Forever McDonald's mugs
From the past
I might get something
I really might
If he was throwing in old Batman Forever mugs
Those things were
Unbreakable Deborah why would open up my order from
Infowars
Great song and off after his
But then it comes back from commercial
Think about it
You're almost
There's been so much whining and now you're going to end it with I don't even want to go back
I don't even want it I don't even want it what it is is the principle of
It's not even he's not even saying that it now play with this
Cracker Jack box
Oh my God I do think this was worth him coming back after he'd already signed off so that is
It makes sense
Well you wanted a hit on it and he didn't hit on it earlier he did
To thank everybody
He didn't hit on that
But what is a God
Was that he doesn't actually
Care
Grace came back anyways Elon Musk
Came back and he was like I'm not to touch on this earlier I didn't bring it up there was the shooting
Once does it get mentioned
Completely bizarre
Samoan takes over and immediately
Brings up
What
This is essentially a threat
In Patriot militia type communities and ideology it's well understood that when disarmament happens it's time that
Do you got to start killing
I brought it up in the past but this is idea is essential to
To the book unintended consequences
Also in the Turner Diaries the inciting incident that leads to the Insurrection is the Cowan
Government confiscation of Fire
Owen is reached the point of covering the story where he's just making veiled threats
If you take this mass shooting this bad consider that if
Regulation all my friends will start killing cops and engaging in a full-scale insurrection
Becoming the American Al-Qaeda that they've always wanted to be
So if you compare it to the killing that we would do human tasks on regulation this shooting really isn't that big a deal
Think about it that way and stop complaining
Basically which sucks
Yeah and it only works so long as
It's a threat
You know
It only means something so long as it's a threat
Because obviously if they were to actually try that s***
It's not going to dare not going to
Overthrow the f******
They're going to be Criminal
I wish I would have thought similar things maybe
2 years ago that's fair
That's fair I mean even the morning of January 6th I thought
There's no way this is
There's no way they're going to get inside the
Yeah yeah but I thought that was nice
That's that's a lot of surprises I do a lot of expectations
That we may have might might be faulty
That is fair but that said I think that
Overthrowing the government sure maybe lofty but
The idea of creating
Sal's of
It's actually far more engaged and active domestic Terror
I don't think
Gay is unrealistic
Stick for what they are
I'm going to throw this out at you and it's going to be an unpopular thought
To that
They're all lazy and cowardly
Well I think that you might Comfort yourself in
Constantly viewing
The lazy and cowardly want
I think that behind that are number of people who
You may not have ever heard of
You aren't media figures
Who are less
Stop
Barbie that's something you should be worried
That's fair
Anyway
CBS News
Did a piece
But Owens
Excited and condescending about
The Grinch
Minions
You're being away
Was that making fun of them
You have to prove that
Nope I was way wrong
Because then guess what
Guess what guess what
Hillary
I bring Hillary back
I just can't
Just too insane just too insane stop it I thought was going to be assassinated before the midterms
Are we supposed to be
Thought we were hit by a nuke
CBS News did a story about hunter's laptop because
And the timing of this is because they were able to acquire a copy of the data directly from the source
Not a second or third-hand thing
The data with friends a computer Specialist or two who said that they didn't believe that they saw us
Signs of being added to the Nevada.
This isn't the same thing as saying that all the Absurd right-wing media claims about the laptop Ark
Confirmed
It's not even saying that the basis for a lot of those claims is authenticated because these people like the Rudy
Giuliani's of the world and such
They may be working
From a copy of the data that had filed added to them
All the CBS piece can really assert is that the expert they spoke to didn't see signs of tampering in the data directly
From the source
This isn't necessarily as much of a win is Owen wants it to be
He doesn't get to congratulate himself for being part of a media organization that made a ton of s*** up about the laptop
After an actual media organization do some legwork
It doesn't actually prove in towards
Also
I fucken love this segment
Hello
This development so much
Now I guess Alex and Infowars need to protect Joe Biden at all costs
If they attack him they're just doing the globalist bidding because they weren't biting out-of-the-way it's a trap
That's what I'm saying
Yeah right hand
They're just
That is just
Non-Stop
I don't think it may I don't think it does make them feel good I don't think it makes him feel good
For CBS News to somehow pretend to confirm that they're right
Even if they were right which they're not
Also I just tried to Pat myself on the back
I don't say that.
Tough to pull off a sarcastic
But
One of the easiest
Mistakes a lot of people
You think
It should go on
You don't need it to go on
Four claps
Maximum is all you need to know
Sewing
Get back talking about the shooting and of course
Just distraction
Deflection course
This is desperately Owen doesn't want to address
The actual point and talk about the actual shooting
Yes it is like so much that he's decided to play a game of shooting roulette with the producers which even if he finds a tunnel
Shootings across the country doesn't prove a point he wants
Set to if anything makes a stronger case for gun reform
Yeah but again
This is important to remember
He's the one who doesn't care about these shootings in the intercept
He's the one who sees them as a prop adjusted
We can use to distract away from having to talk about the shootings that had a little too close to home
People talk very constantly about addressing violence in inner cities it's just a towing never hears those voices because they're part of it
Community but he doesn't give a s*** about
These are predominantly poor and non-white communities so
He doesn't hear them
Care at all
Please
Let's play this game of roulette let's do it. Let's see what you get to say is
I think this is a great job Owen
Oh man
Good work
Still defending myself on the back again didn't work
So he's just going to try to water because it doesn't go smoothly
As I thought that maybe these producers would find headlines right away water
I mean that's
That's an insane that's just
That is a person whose lives under a rock
And is told news
From a f****** an insane bro and personally have not seen his home
So I don't know if it's under a rock
He does just
Deaf people hand him fixed
No like awareness of political issues that aren't germane to the Infowars core message
He doesn't know about political
Movement to activists that are working on other issues like inner-city violence
Tensor
It's
Muted
It's not relevant to him he doesn't give us
Yeah so it will course he has this this
Sort of conception that
No one cares
You're the only person who cared then you could go find people who care
And unfortunately you're sad fairly can't fly
You know what I've noticed
Listening to this much Owen
Is that
Owen
Has the
Cadence and the lack of
Value to anything that he saying
That requires him to make a point and then landed in order for it to sound logical
Exactly and Alex doesn't need to land upon to do any of this s***
Chaos exactly like that's the thing that Owen wants
And can never have
And I think that that's one of the things that makes him so boring like
Alex like I said earlier he's unpredictable in a in a certain way
He does get boring sometimes and there's a lot of repetition but there is still an ice age
Anything Could Happen
He could storm out confidence to storm out of the studio
Yeah give a s*** because he runs the plates right
Owen doesn't have
That and he's a really boring because if you have to land your
Points or argument or anything
Then the landing should be
Be good if you wanted to be interesting or the landing to be interesting and it Landing isn't superficial stupid
Choir DeLand
Is he needs his producers to feed him
Yeah and that is not coming
Find a headline
Against
I guess the girls having a hard time here we talked about this earlier in the bomb threat charges were
Filed so there's no reason to think the FBI had any involvement in the case nor that they were following Aldrich
Bring this up I guess it's worth noting that there were
Confiscation of aldrich's guns after the bomb threat
What Ellen sport that kind of law or would that be a violation of the Second Amendment
Baby doesn't support confiscating guns from people to make terrorist bomb threat
Describe doesn't really make sense here it seems irrelevant
101 is doing is
He's trying to say that this was a false flag without saying it directly
The FBI got in contact with Aldridge after the bomb threat and then use them as a patsy or a mind-control sleeper age
Agent or some s***
Is the consistent pattern with Alex's mass shooting conspiracies from James Holmes
Adam Lanza
And always signal into that knowing that the audience is well aware of what he saying without directly saying it
Yeah good for you
My my lit teacher when I was in high school
I was with him all four years and we beat we became pretty close
He always used to say sarcastically at my dad
That sarcasm is a tool of the weak mind
Right but
When he did say it genuinely
He was speaking specifically about Owen Shroyer
Satire
So he's still got to kill more time cuz
Is that lines are coming
Where are you landing on this
What is happening
Coherent
The patrons neutralize the threat of the gunman
But according to they could have done it even better
If someone had a gun
Weird
F****** stupid and that's dangerous as an idea
Odds are that someone with a gun wouldn't have been able to subdue the shooter much quicker than they did and in a crowded
It's really dangerous to be in a situation where you're exchanging gunfire really high likelihood of hitting an
Another Patron
Really dumb stuff but I guess it's the only thing better than a good guy who takes care of Business Without a Gun is a hypothetical
Good guy with a gun
Who does a better
Jobstack ask
Looks like those producers aren't having an easy time finding a shooting that fits Owens a narrative here
Weird
Yeah I mean it doesn't get more obvious
Exactly what's going on
Then
The right-wing being like this guy who
Neutralize the shooter he can go f*** himself cuz he didn't have a gun
Really weird what are you
You talking about that's not a hero to you is that the hero regardless of
Political ideology right but also like is it a better outcome
For someone to have killed the shooter then for them to face
Consequences
Be tried in a court
There's a I don't understand I mean I do understand
Yeah of course
There can no no Heroes cannot be found White
Adnan Malik it is like the only hero
Is our fictional John Wayne
If the real John Wayne was gay
Which we can't ever possibly believe
Sewing
Do some headlines
Not good
I don't know if the producers are asleep at the wheel or what but I guess Owens just going to reuse the same headlines you brought up on Sunday
A show which seems a little bit soft
If these are the things he insists no one cares about I would suggest you look a little bit deeper
The first shooting Adventure doesn't Baltimore and if interested he could check out the Abell Foundation
A nonprofit committed to combating gun violence
Baltimore through investing in community programs that aim to intervene
Hidden an at-risk situations and prevent future viola
In 2021 they dispensed / 14 billion dollars in Grants to community-based projects in areas like Workforce
Education and the Arts
This is a group that takes the problem of gun violence in Baltimore very seriously and is working to address the underlying causes
And influence others
Or if you wanted to go like a more religious route he could discuss the Catholic Charities Safe Streets Baltimore
Many other groups to and this is an issue that's disgusting widely
I'm second to no one brings up his outside Philly
Have the same Dynamic is true in Philly as it is in Baltimore
Are tons of people at Goodwill working hard to create
Solutions to the problem of violence with
Community-based initiatives
The premise that no one talks about these shootings because they are politically useful or whatever is just false
It's just
What are the issues with what's going on is that either right-wing does rising tide of anti-lgbt Q sentiment that a bunch of
To make a name for themselves in that media sphere
The lives of
Tik-Tok account essentially exists solely to demonize trans people and drag performer
Matt Walters entire brand now seems to be the guy who's really weird and angry but other people sexuality and
Alex Stein put himself on the map I sexually harassing AOC and I was making antagonistic videos of drag queen story
Auntie trans talking points field way more than one GOP midterm campaign
It'll be hard to find a right-wing media pundit who didn't traffic in the
Calling random lgbtq folks
Groomers for horrible crimes like
Being a teacher
In this environment it's clear that a Target is being put on a particular Community who are being scapegoated and used as a punching
Back 4 blood
Google points
That's a scary and dangerous situation that we all understand leads to violence
We've already seen Children's Hospitals targeted for bomb threats after being pointed out by lives of Tik-Tok
Cowboys have shown up and crash drag queen Story Time yelling about grooming kids off and well-armed
It's Crystal Clear to anyone paying attention that this is a situation where the ice is thin
And the people who are escalating this tension and raising the temperature have no intention of stopping
So when there's a mass shooting like this at a gay bar like what we saw in Colorado Springs
It's very easy to understand how that that hit particularly hard for people who care about and respect lgbtq
The writing has been on the wall
What something like this was bound to happen
The people who were inciting hate gleefully continue to do so at them
The horrific happened
At the time of doing this episode it does remained to be seen fully with the motive for the shooting was
It's easy to jump to conclusion to this was definitely an anti-lgbtq motivated
And I think that the preliminary information points in that direction
But it is possible that there's another another motive there they were yet to learn
Even if that is the case
It doesn't change anything
About why an event like this would be particularly pain
A community suffers a tremendous loss and a deprivation of a place where they felt like they could be safe while the entire media
Ecosystem demonizes
And dehumanizes
Pain response
How did immediately ecosystem pretends that the shooting is actually their fault because they hosted Drag Brunch of
The actual shooter's motive aside the toxicity and fully committed nature of the anti-lgbtq positioning
Of these right-wing figures is on Full display
And it's repulsive
Anyway if Owen wants to continue playing this game where he has an intern Google shootings that he can pretend to care about I guess we can do that
But
Is
Very clearly ignoring a
Celia difference
Between things
Because it's threatening it implicates
His worldview
Maybe I just think it's pathetic
Yeah
Yeah I mean
It's it's hard
To have lived through so many f******
King genocide
Around the world
That have happened
Beginning with this type of rhetoric
And not look at this type of rhetoric
Happening around us and and not be
F****** me the outcome is not good
The next stages after
These kinds of portrayals of people it doesn't lead to
Acceptance
We come to a greater understanding of each other
Note that is not the path
That the right-wing media figures
Like we we discussed
How many inches
And that is troubling
Yep
Sewing
Heather revelation
Cow
Using what
Braids wear
It is had
Victorian Farm
Reasoning or even
Thomas Rhett
What
This is f****** pathetic
I want is presenting this is a revelation he had while looking at his news
That the globalist need to disarm Americans because they can't bring in a world government with so many armed Patriots out there I mean this is a
New thought that he's pretending
This is the most Elementary Infowars talking point going back
Decade
Portamento talking point of the entire thing the whole reason they want to take guns according to Alex's.
Reminder reason constant rambling is because they needed on our population who can't fight back when the UN troops are the devil
Foreclosure wob invade
This is 101 stuff and honestly this would be like me coming here on episode 751 of our podcast and
But I looked at this stuff I listen to Alex and I do like
It dawned on me
That they aren't sincere about
Got the things I say
Just hits me that they ramp up bulshit in order to push
Extremist right-wing ideology until useless product so they're terrified entrapped audio
What a revelation I just had
It's ridiculous when he started
I wrote down it's nice that they can still learn about the global
It's nice
Well they said he tended and I was like you can't learn anything about the global at this this is
Tactic that people can use to make at right thing sounds somehow more important
Did the same thing when Alex is like last night I was thinking and I saw the full picture you know or whatever
Is a grandiose elevation of a Monday and claim it makes me feel
Like what I remember from
K-lite for like youth groups and when I was in church
And like it would be like
I had this revelation
God
Love's
Yeah you know it's like okay you had that revelation
But like you're not understanding
He loved
Right okay
Alright
Previously
I do
Also makes me think of times when I hang out with people who are too hot
Reminds me of when a boss would come in and be like hey babe
I just realized
I'm wearing shoes
Everybody's doing their regular a***** sitting in front of the computer every now and again talk in the boss comes in as I hate
I just had this idea
What if we tried an ad campaign
And you're like that is how business works
I don't know what else to say to you the globalist want to take guns because they need to today world
Yeah you should watch some of Alex's Phelps also you can't arm 300 million Americans
Because some of them are baby
Wow
Now
According to Gallatin now
Fair
Conceivably use
Like I mean obviously there
So
Illenium tickets
Not necessarily worse because the shooting happened at a gay nightclub like a shooting like this would be bad no matter what
There's an element that Owen is intentionally ignoring
It's worse that this shooting happened at a gay club because we're
Currently existing at a time of increased anti-lgbtq
And a time when the prevailing attitude
Is that we should regress back to a time when Society had absolutely zero tolerance for any nonsense non-straight identifying
A shooting it appears to Target that community at a time when that rhetoric is flying around the right-wing freely
Does sting a little more than it might otherwise
But mass shootings particularly in public places are awful no matter what
The shooting at the Walmart in Virginia last week is a horrible tragedy for example
Just
I just don't think that this is an honest
Exploration of anyone
Anyone's actual feelings I got to believe they don't actually feels
I don't know what he feels but this is not like
This is not a well-considered
Dealing with reality well I mean what they want
Is
To say okay
We all recognize that gun violence is a problem
How about our solution is we do nothing
And then we get to continue yelling at our politicians about how they do do anyting
Which I'm telling you that they shouldn't do
So then you can yell about these politicians that don't do anything and you'll believe that I'm helping you in some
Beyond all reason and then you'll blame the politician
Still listen to me and anyways the point is I'm going to be rich
The popular for people are going to
Populist message
Just going to be a chicken in every pot
And a derringer and every create absolutely
What should your little baby
Bjorn b-but
Is something with like
Rifle standing at the other end
So
One pointed at your face to make sure you take care of that baby right
The one thing that I've noticed
Is that
Look at this a revelation
I don't know how I couldn't have noticed this before but Infowars lies
Who's Mexico
Talk about the shooting Owen
Lots
20 by your gun in Owens just lying
He's just making up a shooter was on an FBI watchlist
Because if he makes up that detail it makes the shooting
Way more suspicious to the audience
And encourages them not to take it at all seriously
Well Owen and sister the anti-lgbt
Uq ideology can't possibly be the motive for the attack and no one knows the motive
He feels like it's somehow appropriate for him to just make s*** up
In order to build up his imaginary motive
And explanation for the shooting in this is just f****** disgusting
Making s*** up
I mean look
Sometimes there is a certain amount of jumping to conclusions that happens
There's some assumptions that this is a factual lot
This is just something that he's saying
Because it works better for him
Which is Infowars Style
Yeah yeah
He's just so stupid
He's just so dumb these just so dumb
But also boring
Yeah I know
It is it is unfortunate
The length of time he's allowed to speak
In public
Yeah
I mean money
That's problem
So speaking of things that went on too long
Yeah Alex complain about Twitter
Too long
But Owens got a touch on
Power
Yeah for a South African Emerald minor
Elan
Beautiful words
Is embarrassing
So you know he's trying to make the argument that people who talk about school shootings
To push for gun reform naturally
Those are the people who
I would love to play this game with all window
Cuz he's at a track
I guess you just wants everyone
Who could be accused of using the deaths of children for political gain to be kicked off Twitter so
Yuan will be morally and intellectually consistent if he does
I guess we can make a really clean sweep of all anti-vaxxers that because their whole thing is just using the deaths of children is prop
Apps to build up their political power
To every abortion advocates
No I think I wouldn't like it too much of his standard was applied but he's having a lot of fun here saying Elon
Condescendingly my God
He's just the worst
Also owned is conveniently leaving off of Elon says that the reason that he has no mercy for someone like Alex is that
My first born child died in my arms I felt his last heartbeat
Owen probably doesn't want to go anywhere near that considering that his claims that Neil heslin couldn't have held his son after the show
Shooting at Sandy Hook
Kind of at the Centre of a lot of the lawsuits and
I would understand if he was once
Bitten Twice Shy
I would totally ignore that part two but
It's kind of glaring
Yeah
What you going to do
I think what's funny about that is that this time
He might actually have a better chance of saying that
Because
The it did
Elon Musk
Without the mother of that child
Reply to Elon musk's tweet
Saying
I know I'm the only person who cares cuz I was the one there but I was the one holding the I think I saw a
I don't know if that's
True or not but what I'm saying is that if you were going to say that he didn't
You have far more to go on
Anything else I understand where you're coming from
You touch that hot stove
So I believe he's a fan of the Santas a bit or at least the things that he saying
And this is funny
For any of our electric America
Aurora.
Why are.
Can hear in my mind the cheers of not existing people
Oh boy
Now there weren't tears but imagine them was when Albert born
Cheat on ALEKS
I suppose
Yelling saying that the world economic forum is not welcome in Florida is not the Applause line that
You might be thinking
On account of
What the f*** are you talking about what do you mean
King about
So
Owen touches on Ukraine
A little bit yeah he's the person I want
Insightful, do ya
Civil War
Not how that works
I mean
Sowell human rights abuses are alleged to have been committed by Ukrainian forces as well as Russian forces
Is this explanation that Owen is giving his
Is b*******
This is embarrassing Libro Russia and its Framing and anyone who took their job is a news commentator seriously wood
Do this bad a job
Quick note that you responded to Russia and Ukraine cannot be in a civil war
In essence Russia had the right to invade territory that is Ukraine
The only reason there's any problem is because Ukraine fought back with some westerns
Support
State TV
Quickly executed an Russia installing a puppet head of state
That is Russia's right
To do that's what they have the right to do and because Ukraine didn't go along with it now all this bad stuff is happening
It's actually fairly similar in theme to comments that they're coming out about the Club Q shooting
Particularly the way that Matt Walsh
Contempo wood frame
The shooting happened because the club had a Drag Brunch that they decided to it was a groomer
It was the shooter's right
For there not to be a drag brunch at this bar but the government of police didn't shut it down for it so even invaded
To take care of
In both cases there's a state of affairs that they have deemed to be correct
Ukraine it's that Russia could do whatever it wants and in the case of clubque it's at lgbtq folks
Can't do anything if it in any way offends the extreme right-wing
Ukraine didn't been to Russia's demand so they're really responsible for Russia invading
You didn't do exactly what the extreme right side so it's their own fault when violence is an actor
You really troubling mentality and if you think about it for even a minute
It's not hard to see how this could be applied very easily
To justify
Particularly against groups
That you expect yours
Demonizing and dehumanize I'm not even going to engage with that
I'm going to engage with
His own
Okay so what he saying
Is that what he should what Ukraine should have done
Is allowed the Russian government
To come in
And disarm the citizens of Ukraine
Does taking over their territory
Installing a fascist dictatorship
Do understand that correctly because
Consistent
Just want to be sure
That that was what he was saying
They should have done
Thereby saying
That the correct
Answer
To globalism
Is for the United States
To lower its weapons give them to the world economic forum
Because the world economic
Forum is the world and we're just one country so they own everybody so they can just walk in and what
We should do
We should give up our arms
To the government well
We might actually say that
That's actually quite a bit about how
I just don't understand how people to repair this relationship with
It's just
It's that same thing of like
What they're saying is so obviously
Stupid
Haunted space
But it goes against what they're saying
Because
Matt Walsh making fun of look at you with your fake gun
What are you talkin about
This guy would have been a hero if only he'd shot the guy instead of stopping him from killing people
Well this guy would have been the one that we should never give up our arms but Ukraine city
Into the Night
What you're wrestling with his that nothing means anything in these are all just incendiary
And irresponsible poorly thought-out argument right
Made for their own sake and for the sake of getting through the day
Advanced ideology and selling dump pills
Yes that is what I'm grappling with Revelation I just had
So I wouldn't get back to talking about the drag queen story times and the
Idea that there would be people armed there
And just to advance a little bit of a warning we got some T slurs coming up
Because of course
Stand so here here is it just some
Dumb commentary
You covered this with Alex Stein yesterday I know you doing
This is ridiculous
You can hear the the Sorcerer And the the the way that this is being covered ASD human
Sizing and demonizing of the people there
Exactly the the problem that people are discussing
Basically making the argument for everyone
Yep one last clip here where he struggles to understand people showing up arm
Toguard
And I find that to be
God dammit man
The red lamp
So first of all there are plenty
There's a lot of schools that do have
Armed officers
Explain this to him it's actually really simple
People who are going there guarding that event they were there as officials hired by the state which they would like
We have to be if they weren't there guarding a school
Super complicated administrative process to happen where is this people take me to Pond themselves to show up
Open practice their second amendment rights
Jojo and should love
Secondly there's a bit of difference
Between these events in schools
He probably is in groups of right-wing lunatic
Expect a steady diet of Sensational and bigoted narratives about how the schools were secret grooming programs targeting kids
Is routinely to disrupt things
And if they were bomb threats being directed at schools that were pointed out by anti-lgbtq social media
And an entire section of the media was obsessed with demonizing
Schools and teachers
In that instance maybe antifa would show up
Open schools
Isn't happening in the case of
The schools but it is
In the case of lgbtq
Tiki space is particularly focused around drag queen story time
So you can make
Owen is a part of the media ecosystem that is
Obsesses about these events
Lies about them sinsational Liza's them labels people involved in pedophile zandor demon
Helen Marvels at the idea that people would show up to provide security from the people who can
Sumac media and show up to antagonize
And disrupt the event
He knows what he's doing
And this is
Very weak
Also
He does realize that this video he's talking about it's on the same weekend that there was a mass shooting at a gay bar
Did high-profile right-wing figures are justifying by saying that there was a drag brunch at that bar Rodney this is insane
I don't I don't understand how he can
I can understand it but I couldn't understand or someone acting from the place of
Like decent intention
Could
Make these kinds of points
It's
Yeah I know I mean that's that's the type of thing that you can't say in my
I mean wow
Just f******
Wow it's bad
Wow
The coverage that they have is bad
Ayodhya
I wrestle with whether or not I find
And it more objectionable
Van
The staff like Matt Walsh's
Coverage
No I don't want to choose
I refuse to pay that
At the end of the day they are on
Team they all exist in concert
Yep they're all the same same
RICO case
If you will it's just
It's a
It's it's baffling to me
That
People would
Respond to a tragedy by acting in ways
That serve to make more tragedy more likely
That seems to me to be
Are you not good way to operate
And I resent it I find it
Tubi
Awful
I don't like listening to it specially when it's coming from Owen
On a
Lighter and less
Serious note
I think that listening to this much Owen
Really bums me out until we're saying there was a little bit reassuring inasmuch as like
Without Alex there ain't no business
Because like
You know there's these little
Flourishes that he thinks are funny like I'm just asking questions
These are the things that I think
That he has
Is he would like to be those idiosyncrasy
The things we give him for nausea
Today
Does my character in flares little childish sarcasm thing is supposed to be a character but in fact he's just a whiner
Yeah
And it's really really frustrating
I don't feel like that
That's appealing to an audience
Bears out in the download numbers
Michelle versus
Horse is Alex's
That means
It's bad is presentations bad is
Are we
What he tries to do this grandstanding I can
Can find shootings I can play this game all day
Kitty from the lands at B
I mean it is it is so much
Just
Especially in reaction to this
It is a group
But people who want money and power
They just don't care if there's a river of blood
And I'll pretend there isn't that's that's better
We would like money and power and if there's a river of blood that it takes to get there
F****** fine
I'll just pretend that it's everybody else's fault
I'll just pretend that probably
Exactly that trail that leads to me
Probably those people over there
I know the trail leads to me
But haven't you read that book about Hansel and Gretel
Baby baby know where they were going
Sucks
Yep
I'm sorry to have put this episode
Together
I guess I did make this episode but it's not my fault that Owen did the thing
Know this and this is what need
Needs to be
Like I didn't know
Howell
F****** awful
The response was
Cuz I don't I I mean I'm I'm off Twitter I'm off
All that s*** yeah you mean in the broader media
I assumed how awful it would be on Infowars but I didn't know how awful it was across
The land you know and
And to hear this s*** is
Is Vickery
Very important to recognize exactly where we are
I am Jaded by Infowars and maybe it's a function of
Owen being there instead of Alex
But honestly
I think that there
Response isn't as bad as
Like you could have Sue
Jeff
David Dunn
Way more
Distasteful
Adrenal amatory copper still pretty inflammatory
Yeah but there is an argument to be made and I'm not positive of it but
That
Other people were worse than Infowars
I think that's a result
Of the Lost
I think that the result of the Judgment I think it's a result of all the times that
I mean you can see it and how many times he had to sew obliquely
Be like
Might have been false
Get out
The distance that he'd they had to
Keep from those types of things
How much further how much is because of the lawsuit and how much of that is because
Of Owens style you know it's
Difficult to say because
Right we don't have as much of a
Vocabulary
True true
But yeah if it's
It feels it feels like maybe it is
The function of
Of the lawsuit
Definitely have more gardens you can see that the lawsuit had an effect
That's for sure, let's take this on just too simple Elementary level
Alex is conceivably taking
Time off
Because of
The after-effects of the lawsuit
Is at least in some Park
A consequence of the lawsuits which means Infowars
His reach is less
So
This this horrific
S***
Reach fewer people
Then if Alex was in studio
Yeah I guess that's true
You know I guess that's what we're going for hopefully with a knot
Is
Horrific maybe something a little lighter but
We'll see but until then jordan.com
Flights
Cool
I was
At Monticello
Monticello from the from TJ's
Huge
Ever wrote
That's like
656 different things
Through
The books books actually like lean outwards
I pulled up on the books
Turned around the bookshelf yes okay
And inside I found a manuscript unpublished manuscript written by Thomas Jefferson
Hear it
Alex
In color