I have great respect for its knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Need MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Words with the altars saline and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones we are Dan
You were overeager for that second and I thought you were
I heard you say Jordan I thought you were going so fast
You know what
Start the whole thing over
What's up
Well.
You know what I'm going to say it I was trying to think of a bright spot that wasn't self-aggrandizing along the way
But I'm going to do it
My brakes bought because it happened
I was I was a guest on the god pod review recall
Earlier today and they were like everybody said really really nice things about it and I was like you know what
F*** it I am going to accept a compliment
I think that was nice it made me feel good today Archangel Michael's reached out and said
Great choice really nice to me
You had a good appearance I can't have a good or bad episode on our show
Because you can enjoy or not enjoy the episode but my job is to just be me
That's true so I can't be like more or less me
Sure there is just a baseline levels it is loud and unchanging
Nice to be singled out I feel like the belle of the ball
Before you you don't sound happy for backhoes trying to think of another angel
Sandalphon
Okay
Azazel Azazel demon right
Maybe
Well that's great
My bright spot I guess
Is I was at the store
Ioi
Saw that they sold single slices of pie
Jewel sliced ham slices
The pie
Now it was your bright spot that you just saw you
Could do that night that you followed through I follow through and I ate that
Straight
A whole pie is too much
I'm not going to make a pie
I am too busy and lazy to make a pie I'm not going to do it
Supai isn't part of my life
Right much
Pratt and so it was kind of nice
It was a chocolate cream pie
Also I thought was with cheesecake
Cheesecake
Large whipped cheesecake pie
Cheesecake is a pie
Don't
I don't understand the nomenclature of
Pastry cheesecake is a pie Boston cream pie as a cake
Move forward
I've had this argument too many times in my life and I don't have patience for it
It's better than those like microwavable pies you see it like 7:11 or something
So I would hope so
Much better
Just weak breakbot on my part
Weak bright spots today we have an episode
Okay on that but before we do
Say little mama to say hello to some new walks
Ewok
Next Little Debbie for me
Capital
Thank you very much next secretary of defense Steve pieczenik thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Thank you very much thank you so much
Thank you very much next time Jed and I'm half man half bear half pig
9% walk the math checks out
Happened on September 16th 1999
Policy wonk
Thank you very much I do next to I love my nugget more than anything in the universe and I guess my
Stinky hawk-boy to thank you
Thank you very much I feel like those last two had to have been connect you know nothing happened onto
September 16th 1999 and then I love my hog boy I feel like we'd know
I'm guessing that that was like
A birthday
I'm hoping I feel like that's what we're discovering
What happened on September 16th 1999
On onthisday.com
Dolly the sheep
14.8 in of rainfall
Hit Myrtle Beach from Hurricane Floyd
So that's one thing alright
The Netherlands started their first season ever
Of the Big Brother show Big Brother
Alright
I've never seen Dutch Big Brother
Have you seen American big boy
I think they they cook
Big Brother longer in
In the slow cooker
Yeah I don't like that chill and care for it find a voyeuristic and weird
Jordan
Yes Dan
For a long time I've been of the mind that there is a type of right-wing figure that I feel drawn to cover and it typed that I don't want to
Use my limited amount of time Focus
Kissing on
Some of the folks in that second category or there because I feel like other people are competently covering them and their
Maybe little more that I could add to the conversation if we did engage
For example I think that Dave Rubin is a subject that I don't really want to cover because
You get some good mockery from Sam Cedar
Hanging Tempah on toast made an incredible in-depth takedown of his rhetorical techniques
And the show itself which you can find on YouTube
Covering his actual show would likely just involved me repeating critiques that are already well-articulated
You're not adding anything to the space yeah
I know I know what I can and can't do I don't think there's more to add there
Others are in the
That category because I feel like their primary game involves
Comedy
Joe Rogan
Generally falls into this category and I can probably cover any episode of his show for our podcast but it would end up drifting into
The territory where we would just be over-analyzing idiots making edgy offensive jokes
These are the sort of figures that I might cover but it's kind of a case-by-case situation
Yeah I think the concern for us is eventually we just wind up doing punch up
You know we're like
Oh that's
I get where you're trying to go that here's where that joke would be better as it if you're trying to be offensive the joke doesn't work
Work because of blank
And then there are figures that I don't cover because they're basically troll attention Chasers there any real Merit past that point
Steven Crowder is one of these folks Tim pool is also someone who I would include in that category
Remember people suggest that we cover pool in the past
I don't want to do because he sucks
Really hard and
I don't even feel like taking him seriously is worth the time I feel like he is
Clout Chaser is eat at the overused term
He's got a billboard on the way to Midway I saw a billboard for this dude saying he's not relevan
Here's what it is
A he's nothing until he changes his name to cooler with Pooler
Until that happens
Tool Time Pool Time
The new home improvement
Reboot Home Improvement
Punch up there we go. It's just never not going to happen
I believe that the time has come for me to change how I approach these things
I'm not going to abandon focusing on Alex don't get to that impression in her head but I feel a calling to Branch out a little bit
It Morris growing in our country and other people who are Alex adjacent could probably use a bit more of
The focused attention that we use
To help bring a larger understanding of what they're all about and how they misinformed
The audiences for similar purposes
Inspector Infowars.
Oh yeah
Today we're going to be embarking on a little bit of that
So now it better not be Tim pool is it Tim pool
Well here's the thing god dammit I have a goal in mind
I had an intention
Sure and then we recording this on Tuesday and last night
Something happened on Tim pool show
Acquired a little bit of attention
Some of the thoughts that I already had kicked around my about absolutely not
Okay
That's it that's great
Are we back to the beginning I have I finally completely unaware of what's about to happen you didn't
You didn't hear about his show
No I don't give a s*** about Tim pool what part of
Cooler with polar didn't you understand I ignore anything I would do it with this b*******
Here's the introduction
Oh but it didn't has for the episode
Had a good thanks
You were with your family
Our loved ones or at least
Call my God Kanye
Continue to cycle which is now going on for over a week which is
In many ways unheard-of
The right now
Because Donald Trump went to dinner
With ye
Nick Fuentes
Saturday is now being denounced by
Mike Pence
Several Republican Senators
And
For whatever reason this story for many reasons opposed
People have made
The story has persist
Tell today
And we are able to actually sit down with
Several of the individuals involved
In that story notably Yanik
Cousin
Of course you may.
Happen
Minecraft
I have to do
My bad my bad
There you go
Pretty cute that Tim is pretending to not understand why it's a completely f*****-up thing for the former president and candid
Navigate to to be president again is having a meeting with these kinds of f***** up figures
I guess he's been away from the spotlight for long enough people
Just forget what an embarrassing loser Milo is but here he is
I wonder how he feels about his books title now that his brand is that he's a former homosexual
Leaving that nonsense aside
Even when he was at rolling game August game guy Milo was a Catholic fascist
He said as much in an interview with Nick Fuentes
Years back and his views haven't gotten better over time
In the most generous description a literal white identity extremist who has a history of
Augustine Island spreading AP synthetic conspiracy theories
He attended the
Unite the right rally in 2017 when he was just 18 marching side-by-side with Nazi
Is chanting blood and soil at Jews won't replace us
And then we've seen what's happened with Yaya lately
He's having a very intense
Public meltdown and he's fallen in with Puentes and Milo it which I guess is forming the Brain Trust
24 presidential campaign
There may be a mental health component to this but ultimately
I'm not in the business of infantilizing yay and he's under the space where manic episode or not
He what he's doing is going to get people kill
Yang is one of the biggest rappers of past couple decades and is a gigantic fan
When he does something like endorse Nick 20s or Milo and publicly associate with them and take them along
Long to meet with Trump
That sends a message to his fans
It's really depressing to imagine the number of people who would never have heard of Nick left for this Association
That's a real impact
Yeah you know what I was wondering about
I was wondering
About whether or not this actually makes sense
44 intestine Milo
Because I think everybody on the surface level is like
Them famous person obviously
But I had it I mean it just doesn't make sense they're all white nationalist
The only people who like yay now or conservatives
And it's not like ye was already selling s*** tons of albums to conservatives in all of his fans were there
I kind of think this blows back
Badly on Fuentes and Milo more than a dozen
How can I see a white nationalist if you're literally writing Kanye's go tail
Well I think that there is an element of this visit
You think about it as we go along
As we go along
Consider this
I thought that you're having because I think
I think they're Tactical
Ames and things that are a little bit deeper below the surface
And maybe two or three stages removed from the immediate
Sing any of them they can all go f*** themselves and then white who gives a f***
S*** about why don't I don't think anybody assumed that you were
But I'm just I'm just saying
I don't think that
I kind of
Have a hard time believing
That there are
Ye fan
Who are looking at ya
Current behavior
Like he made them fans when he was good at music
Right and now he's bad at music and they're looking at it
Whisker Behavior thinking
I want to emulate this
He's doing a bad
Job at the thing
Only conservatives are liking
Yay now and conservatives hate black people so I don't think it's going to help me with Nick
I think they might be booked on this why I think your assessment of celebrity is a little bit
I could be way wrong on that on account of I don't understand that even the slightest
I think that his fans have not all abandoned
That you're maybe a lot of
People think that it's slipped off a little bit but I don't think that is you know there is The Exodus of all of his fans in the way
Whether you're imagining
Second I think even if there is a evolution of the fanbase let's say there is still
A massive celebrity
Right and that's something that
Needs to be factored in
Jersey Star Quality and Beyond there is a
Ovid
Not pay attention
Because of a super famous
So I've said this many times and I'm going to say it again
Nick is a little bit of a scam type character but he's not like the other people that we cover
He is an idea log
He is a gifted Spa
He's an attractive young man and he studied in high school which is developed in him the ability to sound convincing
People who aren't listening to him critically
Even if what he's saying is complete b*******
He understands the optical value of appearance over substance
By the time I realize he's wrong about something he's already onto the next point
That's
Pretty typical who got stuck in high school and
Now he's a white National
Nick is involved in a political project
He's using ye to push that further
That project involves many important goals like the removal of immigrants from the country to hardening of our borders and a require
Argument that people in government
Be Christian
Milo on his own is a complete embarrassment and loser who's relegated to Christian QVC type appearances
On his own he's meaningless
But he's not on his own
He's apparently still a decent networker
And through him the combination of yay and Nick is now connected to Marjorie Taylor Greene
Was recently in a two-parent light
Who knows what other connection the Milo does or doesn't have
He's the sort of s*** head who no one wanted to associate with publicly
After
You know that old Rogan thing and then
Delia's pretty great that doesn't mean that he doesn't have connections behind the scene
It's like all manner of weird friend
Creeps still stayed in contact with him he might have
The pretty relevant I mean let's not forget that he's only a few years removed from receiving Mercer money
So it's not like
It's not like they would be like all your Burns forever and I posted being like Oh lay low for a few years and then we'll catch up
Backup do nose if they're still a connection with
This Trio was interesting as a group because they all have things that the others in need
Yay is famous as s*** and he's a lightning rod for attention but has no real experience in the political space
Milo has that experience and connections but he's become a bit of a laughing stock that nobody is really going to take Serious
Nikki's Savvy and media ready but no one really wants to associate with him because his Public Image is that he's a nut
Who's at the United right rally on January 6th
But people can't ignore him
If he's attached to someone like yay
And the thing they all have in common is Christian fascist ideology
Cific about their desire for Catholic fascism but I think he has yet to make his preferences fully known but he's been very clear
About
Basically a Theocratic
System yeah but I mean f******
Who cares what he has to say I'm Blown Away by it
You know like
I care about all the evil shity as to say that causing damage or I don't give a s*** what he
Minks might work
Why the f*** would I care what he thinks of good government would be
All I care about is he's an anti-semitic piece of s*** now and we got to stop
For that s*** you know
I guess
I don't think I was saying we're going to discuss policy
Prescriptions okay
That's the other thing that they have in common though they bring up is that they have pretty
F***** up and
Reviews about hating to Apple
Little insincere for Tim pool to pretend that it's weird that this meeting was in the news
The former president and the candidate for the next election was meeting with a trio of Christian fascist ideologues who have a rich history of Auntie
Semitism
What for whatever reason this was in that this is stayed in the news
It's a ridiculous thing to have happened so weird right I see everybody
Play talking about a totally an Oculus meeting between a former musical genius
I incredibly weird loser fascist white dude and his incredibly weird loser fastest way to Fresh
And
Performers incredibly weird white dude fashion president
But the weird thing it some
Yeah it's understandable
Anyway
Tim has all three of those dudes
Of course
Can't believe you about this can't believe you didn't hear about this
Why
Alright alright
You know it's not a very big story
A lot of people have questions about
You know what were Trump's intentions why were certain people invited
Entropic courses
Statements so a lot of people want to know where he stands
And more importantly
What happened there
And why
And there's also the questions about
What ye 24 mean
And I'll keep that little bit because they can answer to
More to that
Is however
Head over to timcast, become a member and have a members-only uncensored show
Which will probably get a bit more in-depth on a lot of other issues
Becoming a support at work
And we'll talk about more there
I might be reading a little bit into things but it's my sense that Tim is trying to get people to go sign up for the website
To get the bonus members-only video with the implication that this was where there's going to be a conversation about the Jews stuff
Jo-Ann's where that was going to die
If you listen to this episode you get the sense that Tim had a structure in mind of how this was going to go where they would talk about the trumpet
Dinner and he would Pat himself on the back for being a great journalist and getting these primary sources in there
Anti-Semitism stuff later in a way that he could back
Mises benefit from
People will know busy
And you don't want to give away the main event on free TV to use wrestling lingo you're trying to move the pay-per-view Buy
You don't want to have the big Feud the big the big he'll get right up by the face
It's interesting how that works considering like you you never saw HBO.
Do like nine episodes of Game of Thrones and then like season finale
You got to pay extra for it bro you know like that's that's an interesting model that somehow works
I mean that is still just like
Subscription
I'm already paying for all Valley or whatever
FairPoint
You still got to get a ticket to the movie
The movie The X-Files
Many many years later
I don't know fortunately they almost immediately starts rambling tangential thoughts and gets in
Sent to his feelings about Jews really early in the interview and Nick and Milo fully have his back
Tim Flanders a little bit and then spoiler alert yeh storms out
Leverage point
Shipley Do-Nut near about that
It's a lot of people were talking about it last night because they stormed out
Twitter I'm off of all social medias
Out in the wilderness
So after that happens to his Groove co-host sit around and talk about how well Tim handled himself and how he ate people who some
Ascribed identity politics
Because I guess that's how
Tim decided to avoid saying anti-semitism
This is the long and short of what happens but will go through a little bit more of this because
Really interesting to see how these Dynamics play out
In action like in Toronto
Yeah I mean look
Faint praise perhaps
But I think Nick comes off great cuz he didn't say s*** basically
He's move Milo is eager to say things on the backbench for way too long getting his fur
First taste of coverage again.
My sense of it I don't think that
Nick like
Tim pool March
Just as a whole is f****** reasons he's also certainly in other context
Not welcome on the ship like what what are we talkin about
I don't think Tim or Nick is unaware that each other is aware of that
Very obvious feeling of like
The Ayatollah and
Conservative like a
Prosperity Gospel Pastor got together
They be like listen
I don't agree with you and I want you to die but actually everything we want the world to be as pretty much identical
Also
Apparently not cuz I'm just goes about 20 minutes
Anyway he hasn't co-host Tim does this blew my mind
Luthier
Total sausage fest tonight welcome my name is looking to ask you if we are change
Start work today I'm wearing my Epstein
Didn't
Seeing himself t-shirt
Woodstock, I think we should be using that word a little bit more just like you know this YouTube channel didn't Epstein itself
And if this YouTube channel is Epstein we will be streaming on
Twitter
So yeah I started the t-shirt company after YouTube demonetized me so the best political shirts
Stop, because you guys bye
That's why I'm here
Thank you so much
Why didn't you say that YouTube Epstein
This is fine because there is this pre-emptive thing of like oh this is so dangerous YouTube's going to take this
Down as it's going on or whatever
But this is nuts
Maybe I haven't paid him enough attention but no idea that Luke radowski was one of his co-host
It's pretty hilarious for Tim to try and take some kind of a Centrist neutral position when Luke
Is a co-op
Luke radowski is an old-time Alex Jones associate in a big-time 911 guy from way back
We are change was a group that was formed to for 9/11
Conspiracy shirt and to push Ron Paul
Yeah pretty Centrist.
Yeah I know that some somewhat left-leaning people were suckered into supporting rampal because of his opposition to Warren support for Wii
Weed but
People who are starting organizations to promote him weren't that naive about how extremely far to the right is actually
Politics work
I find that to be
Level of naivety that I'm not willing to accept
Jersey bulshit either like he's prominently featured in the 2009 documentary newworldorder alongside Alex Jones
And he's drunk Bilderberg obsessed holocaust-denying friend Jim Tucker
Honestly there's a bad look for pool with this whole game but trying to play like he's in the center and he's a really critical thinking type media
You figure
Appalling around with 9/11 conspiracy theorist Alex Jones cast-offs
Maybe a bad luck that what he's supposed to be trying to do is that what people ran
That's wild I think maybe people who like him but I don't think I don't think anybody who
Would look at this with a critical I would come away with that
I think I think here's my
Quick and dirty I'm sorry I don't remember how like Dave Rubin was like
I am believing the last time the last time my goddamn Pearl
Really powerful I think for people who want to push
Right-wing ideas but try and avoid any kind of the
Bike
I don't know
Negative associations that come along with with that I think Tim is kind of in a similar milia
Wild because I've never seen anybody be like hey Tim pool without also being a ship
S******* you know
Like it's 1121
Young. One ever regular a snot s*** head person has ever been like
Some good idea you don't hang out in bad enough circles here probably right I'm sorry I interrupted
Already forgotten alright let's do it remembered it or I would be a different person
Shock
Trio came together
And
The reasons why I like what I was listening to it I was like wow
Not talk about this
I just want to start off by
How did this dinner come to happen
I was talking to
For about
A month with schedule.
And October
Sounds for president
Turn back to Nova
And
I've been pulling together a campaign
And after I put up
The
The Defcon
A bunch
People that have been
Cancel Buy
Alex Jones
Started getting contact with other
Full that we're now on the
You know the inside of the maze
And
Alex Jones
Producer said that Milo
Wanted to contact
And
Here we are
Interesting cuz I think that reveals a few things the first is that Milo is still in contact with Al
What does producer in on good enough terms that he can send messages through them
This could be Daria I suppose but it could also be one of the other figures around in fours like Rob do or the
The IT guy Michael Zimmerman who has a bunch of connections to really extreme Fringe figures
So that could be
I took the natural person he would call the produce
Email to email bases with Kanye
I just don't even know what the world is ending
Anymore you know
Like I just don't
I I don't know but I know who it is but that's a pretty interesting thing has him.
Beats at I think honestly that's my issue with too much of this Rob do isn't a band
The problem I have with Kanye and Milo and Nick Fuentes aside from all their views is
Is just like
What the f*** do you talk about when you're not being anti-semitic you know like
What UConn you can't be like
I know you think
That you want to go with 110 but if you go with 105 beats per minute
It's going to give you a little extra idiosyncrasies that's going to bring out some a special juice you know that's not going to happen
Yeah and the next to talk about Chicago
That's where
So there's that
I don't know
Whoever it was at Infowars
They saw the Tweet where ye said that he was going to go desk on Freon the Jews and they knew that this was exactly what the
They have been waiting for
Big huge celebrity ruining their Public Image in a way that it would be in our they be relegated to hang out with dip shitz like Milo hand
Like all signed go the dream scenario
Ha TA by one of Alex's producers
Wild
Another interesting thing and that is that Alex's producer has been in touch with ye and ye hasn't come on
On the show yet
That has to be a choice
To point towards my theory that Alex actually doesn't want to have ye on because of the possibility of eggs
Exactly how this Tim pool interview went
You like about this interview no one comes out looking good
Milo naked ye already look like s*** so it's a push for them but Tim really looks like a complete Craven dick
Engaging in this interview for attention
Being so ineffectual
I got to say though
He's not so ineffectual once they storm out because at that point he's trying to self-soothe
Now he's already a big boy now
What a f******
Yeah so we got an Infowars connection like immediately it's bananas
To this team coming together
I am really really annoyed
And you know like it hits me in waves every couple of months or so it's like man
We started a show about some assholes who wasn't that important
Yeah no here we are
Like this is Stu
Now here we are
All this weird bulshit
Recording this just hours after Stewart Roads got found guilty of seditious conspiracy
Joe Biggs is also on trial for that have all of our opening-season care
Characters go to jail in season 5
What we need to know I think that
Tucked up.
So anyway that's how
Milo and ye came together
And then
So that's how you guys got
Bringing
Inova Dexter
Brain Firepower
Any
Prodigious
And
Pretty much
Yeah one of the greatest
Political commentators of his generation
I think this guy just I think he doesn't know what he's doing
I think Nick is really wrong on this one
I think he's left
10 to fast
He is going
Two Become One of Kanye's losers
I don't like it's another one in Kanye's loser I think that there's a possibility for that but I also think that
There's
I I think there's a possibility that Nikki
Engage in this kind of stuff and engage fairly unscathed
Cuz I think
That he is smart enough to let Milo get embarrassed
And he may have it I'm just saying that
The more likely scenario is the young kid
Gets in over his head
And get eaten alive by the by the game that's the story we've heard look at mix career
I mean he went up against
Turning Point USA
Currently diminished in their capacity
Well I mean
I also think they've been o times when you would have thought like this isn't Caldwell
There's there's a possibility for coming out the other end better for it
Even if everything is a disaster
Tim really wants to talk about the going to dinner
Thing that's really what he's interested in
Yay is not
So this how you get in contact
The three of you
How is it that
Nick and invited this dinner
And and what hap
Will he
He was rolling with me I was impressed
With Nick and I was
Was like
Just come to the dinner
And we had
Pick us up
From the airport
And there was a lot of back-and-forth there's another gentleman named Jamar Montgomery that was with us
He's an engineer at Boeing
And his
Antagonist
Would you rather Roselia
OK Google
And we sat there and it was like when Trump came in
We were
I said you want to sit alone he's like no
Bring your friends in so
A big thing is like Trump had no idea who
Puentes
Was
And but this whole I just
I just got to go right
To the heart
Of this
Anti-semite
Claim that's happening
This is something if you read the definition
It
It says you can't
Claim
That
There's multiple people inside a bank
Or in Media
That
Are all Jewish
Or you're anti-Semitic
The truth
Bike
It's the truth what we talkin about end
What library
You mean
I'm saying like
I've been labeled anti-semite
Okay
Finishing thoughts
It's cute that he's trying to play a game where he has some definition he's decided to use for antisemitism so we can pretend it's
Observe for him to be labeled as such a thing
That's dumb and I don't really want to take the time to keep her that s*** but this is important because I think you can see Tim's useless
He's trying to ask a question about the dinner and very much doesn't want the anti-Semitism talk to come this early
It's too volatile of topic and that's going to if that's going to come at all
Bees into a little bit
Yay on the other hand is all too eager to talk about his feelings about Jewish people at anytime when someone
I'm proud of him and because Tim can't control the conversation at all
This is where we are
There's no way to control this conversation
Yeah isn't interested in playing Tim pools games because he's super famous and he doesn't give a s*** about
Tim's crypto extremist audience
He's already passed that
He's already extreme
You hang out with Nick and Milo and if anything they were doing Tim a favor by showing up
I know the pool shows big and all but
It's not yay level
There's no way to control this conversation because he doesn't give a s*** and even if he kind of gave a s*** he has to be
Bigot friends there to embolden him and egg him on so honestly if I were Tim I never would have done a show like this
It's great for getting attention but the consequences are really bad
Even leaving aside how bad it is for the public discourse to have you this gas line up on the show it's really bad for Tim
He comes off looking like a really limp noodle and because they left with yay Nick and Milo kind of have achieved
Something of an elevated status over to him
Because get this
Without my loaf there's no way ye was showing up on pool show
From the perspective of Milo and presumably nikken ye to
F*** this up
Yeah I'm f***** up an opportunity for himself
And what Jay gets into this antisemitism defensive himself all Tim can really monster is what library
As if his goal was to challenge the source of yazz definition ridiculous and it's a real bottle that isn't design
Time to go anywhere
Designed to
It's it's
Performative pushback more than it is actual engagement with anything that's being said and that's kind of the game
Yeah I haven't seen an Entourage
Is this toxic
Elvis
So we all know that means
Yeah is going to die on the toilet of an impact
I thought you were going to say Britney Spears with her group of stewardesses on that video taking advantage
Just Brittany
The song music video I don't know if I've ever seen the music video. I believe she's on a plane at some point
Air Force 1
I think they were trying to trap people for improv show
So
I got to be honest with you there's a boob sound in this next clip and that's because
I thought that this video would be taken down
Like
So I was recording it live
And I was also downloading some files I believe like some Alex Jones episodes
And so my computer made a beep noise going to file rat download
So you'll hear that
As a warning
There's a boo what you going to do
Anyway
Gave going in on his thing
And in general
America
Has been
Left ignorant and history has been changed
So we start questioning things
That question
The indoctrination
Then you immediately
Get
Vino
You said
Dabangg 3 Rd what did you say happened to you or
Demonetized a platform DEA demonize demonetized
And what's so beautiful about this time
Is
Everyone got to see
What's really been happening
And now we can really understand we can see that
Ronnie Manuel was right next to Obama and then Jared Kushner
Was right next
Trump
Search for the news
I think I think the issue is
One way to put it
Is your ex pounding Upon A localization
Let me clarify there are a handful of people that you see are Jewish
In a certain place
And then you associate Judaism
With the power
What would I view that as not relevan
Yeah you're substantially more powerful than I am but I don't
I'll give you what you're doing
As an issue of
Yeah but
Have you ever heard the term
The black vote
So it's okay to put us in one net
But it's not okay for me to put them in one
Yeah but I mean
That's the basis of the hip-hop
RC that people have been
Been thinking about
And knowing about and realizing
For decades
We were all Wonder
What is damn wormtown
Everybody in the car
What is the route
Rashidun Wicked and
Oppressive prevailing Orthodoxy
Ulta cancelculture Twilight send out that the one thing was going to break the dam has the biggest dog in the world and it took the biggest on the wall to do it
And now the damn is broken
So we see here the Tim does not have the tools that are needed to make any argument in this Arena
Tim The Tool less man to her this pool is empty
Kimberly wants to call yea's anti-semitic ideas anything but anti-semitic so he's trying to go with quotes
Localization issue
Rahm Emanuel
Was Jewish and work for Obama and Jared Kushner is doing
Localization issue that's grasping at anti-semitic straws
How does this Theory even work
If you're going to take it seriously
No one wanted Jared to have any official role that he wouldn't have if he wasn't Trump's son-in-law
It wasn't a Jewish
She was an epic
Empire
And what about the fact it ROM was Obama's Chief of Staff from the time of his election until October 2010 when
When you ran for Chicago mayor
He was only in that position for like a year-and-a-half and then was replaced by Bill Daley relative of former Chicago mayor Richard Daley
Who isn't Jewish
But I do know daily was replaced by Jack Lew who is Jewish and was the chief of staff for about a year
And then he was replaced by Dennis Montague who is a Irish Catholic
Google localization issue
That's a euphemism that pool is using so he doesn't have to
Call this what it is
This is a person who has a
Anti-semitic conclusion that he's justifying
Various Jewish people and then pretending a point is being made
Paper-thin and pool can't even handle that
And because he's tried to frame this as a localization issue he's walked into a trap that he can't get out of
Yeah he's able to respond back to him that people talk about the black vote which actually doesn't even relate to what Tim was
But Tim's point is so weak
But I don't think he even has the energy to think it's worth standing on
If Timmy pushback on the right thing and called the s*** what it was then this Judo move that yeah and my lower pulley
Wouldn't work
It would be transparent how much of an evasion it is
Do that because
That would Place him in a really hostile situation
First thing he would land in a super confrontational argument against ye Milo and Nick Fuentes which is a
Bad matchups
Pretend
I know he has Luke radowski there but that's not really going to help
It's still three on Two And
Milo and Nick are great talker
Secondly and even more difficult leave Tim
Needs to win that argument or else you would be airing a live stream where he gets out argue by anti-semite
He would lose that battle of ideas and that is a real risk
So the reality is that Tim wants nothing more
Benton not really push back on this issue and definitely not call it what it is
Because I don't think he wants the consequences that come along with that
I mean that you is hard-pressed to say ladies and gentlemen
After talking with Kanye Milo yiannopoulos and Nick Fuentes
I have to agree
All Jews are bad
Well that's not going to go good well it's not going to go good thing about have to admit that but if you
Get your ass kicked in an argument on your own showed where the stakes are
All Jews are bad
Then yes you are saying that I mean I think I think
Tim is aware that that is a conversation that
These three
May want to have
And I think that's why he's dancing around
Calling something anti-semitic instead of being the localization issue or whatever
It's
It's somebody who doesn't want to have the conversation while pretending he does
It's it's
Fun it's funny
In some ways just because
So many of these people are
From a distance
It's like watching yay
Pull his b******* going like
Foot pump in their face
But when you're in the situation where you have to have professional
A conversation with you
He doesn't give a s***
You're you're the loser
Jay is gay yeah I mean it's
It is a question of
You can watch him say anti-semitic thing
On other shows and be like
That's what I wanted my show
Right
But
I want him to say it
And then
Walk away from it back away like so many other people do
You know you're we're so used to seeing people
Step over the line and then go on the show the next day and be like
Well I didn't mean to step over the line you know like welts knock-off you did
You know if you want if if my he wants there to be some sense of life
On my show will get V like
What I was actually trying to say is blank
Exactly he's not going to worse people with him
Yeah it is it is like
So transparent
How much these people want to exploit
The the anti-semitism
But don't want to engage with it
You know they wanted to be there they want the fans of anti-Semitism to be there fan
But they don't ever want to actually
Deal with the anti-Semitism one way or the other
And so when you have Kanye on
You're thinking okay
Here's what I got
Get I get all of his power and I get him doing the thing
That we all know he's going to do where he says
Listen
People misunderstood
People didn't you know that whole thing and it's not going to happen
Play I hate the Jews you're not going to be as many words but I think I think that
What team would have liked
Is
The
Attention
Amount of people putting their eyes on him because of
Getting this interview and then that the controversial nice of it
Your show and the show is talking about the dinner and talking about some news items
And then you have the the Jewish
Conversation that they have about Kanye's anti-semitic comment
An issue stuff
And that's how you try to push back against it you don't agree with him
You don't get too into the weeds
You don't make kind of like
Cont condemning statements about it so you can be like I pushed back on this bright
To condemn everybody
You know like
You want to do that
You want a b basically having your cake and eating it too and it's just
I don't know it.
Why would you think that's going to work I mean
Because by putting the localization thing in there he's trying to create boundaries for the
You know like
Okay he doesn't give a s***
Of course not what part of Jacob's life
Do you think cares about your boundaries
When he was 18 about you twelve-year-old knots
See what do you want yet
He started his own like screaming thing
And as long as they're associated with gay they don't have to care
They just don't
If if Nick Fuentes or Milo where on pool show by themselves
They would suck up to pool
So much
Not not really actually Milo's recently on himself
He was a little bit he gave some pushback
Tunica
The temple.
Yeah but he was not as obsequious as you might imagine but my perceptions are wrong
A guy who's
And I've got a pretty high sense of himself
That's
Nobody would ever accuse him of
Humility no matter what. Of his career
Miley was saying there
That's on me.
He puts him in a really bad box
It's one that Tim does not want to be in
And the reason it's really bad for him is that he thinks it's a great boss
Box for him
Are you talkin about identity stuff
Identity politics this is where I live. My bread-and-butter back on this all the time
And now the damn is broken
I I don't like identitarianism
You guys are familiar with that is
Set the time when I was asking about running for president
Milly said well you know you'll be good for the black vote
And I said is that
Because I'm black
No not just cuz of that
So is that
Are you doing the same thing I didn't say that was the only
I said was because you're personable to the common person
And
You probably would do well with
Just because I'm black is a lot of black people don't like me
Of course
I think I think race plays a role in a lot of thing
Absolutely
What what are we doing here
This is one of Tim's big buzz words he hates identitarianism
As far as I can tell from listening to him is just a smarter sounding word
Then if you were to complain about identity politics
Make you sound like a Reddit user from 2016 and that is not what Tim is
The problem is the Tim isn't consistent about this thinking about things in terms of identity
Anti-semitism
Brick wall of yeah bring it up and eat said that ye would do well with the black vote
Yeah yeah
You got a mean that is
It's hard not to say that what just happened was
Is Kanye was like
He was like I hate identitarianism he was like
Yeah you did the thing and he was like
No I didn't
Also understand that when Tim says identitarian he's not talking about the actual thing identitarianism cuz that is a thing
Tim and most of his friends actually are pretty solidly identitarian
Political philosophies that word describe
Their nationalist they're highly concerned about ideas like the great replacement that he globalism and they're into
Nationalism
It's pretty clear that this is right in line with the show based on all their video titles and guests
By the way
I clearly don't know enough about Tim pools
Crew it is show but looking
Through their guest list
I found it one of his producers guest is haunted episode
Producers
Co-host
Quite frankly
And I do that
She's one of the people who steps in wenge leaves to fill in one of the chairs
One of the people who takes over and it's clearly part of the show is a woman named Hannah Claire brimlow
Who's the daughter
Peter brimelow
The founder of video
The outlet that's known for promoting white nationalist anti-semitic writers
It's so weird
She's one of those co-host
I mean it's what it's just
It's like being a tall man
It's like I just wish it wasn't so easy to see through them
Because when it is
So easy and it makes you feel bad about the rest of the people who don't
You know
Cuz it's
It's like when you
If you're doing the the like
F******
Simple addition
Worksheet
You know we're like 9 + 3
And you see if somebody struggling with you know like 5 + 7
Cuz I get it
You know you think it's going to be 14 I do all the time
And you're like oh you're so close man
And it makes you feel bad
And this makes me feel bad feel bad
Well know that these people are allowed
What's the next of kin make you feel bad to Crate
So this is like a little bit longer clip by 3 minutes because I wanted to retain it and it's contacts
This is just
Talking
Just talking just talking smart people talking all over the place. It's Smiley one person
I think the I to the constructs of race
Has really been forced upon us as just something for us to be woke about in
Cassie talk about and use it as these like
Walls
Say the same thing about Judaism
Well let's look at the facts
Acts of what I'm saying though
If you say
In this neighborhood
Where they gerrymander this this amount of time
Hey I wasn't doing that
Is gerrymandering
The lawyers
Hollywood and the people at the bank that D bank to me and then froze my account
You know it's like we wanted jumping to protecting the idea that we can't put a net
Around something
Thing right but that's been my job is
Producer
To take
You know
Aroy air sample and put a James Brown drum
And put it within a two
2 minutes
3 minutes
Song that's the way
I actually think
And that's the way I talk
And now this morning I found out
That they were trying to put me in prison
Because what they did was
I moved 140 million dollars into
JPMorgan
I said I want to talk to Jamie dimon like look at me I'm just going in naive
You know multi-billionaire like maybe maybe Jamie dimon will let me in
On some dealflow
Wrong why are you laughing
Start complaining
Online
And the Navy Bank
Complaining
I'm about to get dbank they like
You need to go to
Props the bay X or whatever you got to go and I'm like I've been trying to buy my own bank for the longest
And then we figured out
How to get my old Vegas like 50 million 75-million so
I'm about to buy out my own bank but then
As you're about to take the money out
Here Comes Adidas with a 270
75 million-dollar bill
For marketing funds that they agreed upon
Cuz I said to them hey I'm the marketing give me the marketing fun
Which proves by the response they got when they
You know stole the design to say we're going to not calling uses anymore
So this is what I was already fighting
Adidas Force I'm fighting
Gap
Get out of Gap fighting
Adidas
And then I deal with this little bit of noise from
You know
Zionism from the fashion world where they used it
This plant named Gabby who's obviously like some kind of CIA agent knows nothing about
Fashion
This is a certain thing when someone can't dress
You know that they're not like a fashion person
They're just there as like
This is site like the control that they try to use with celebrities which has now been broken right
Cuz you know where it broke
Okay
I want to get on like LeBron
But I'm going to come back to this and just talk about this morning
Where
You know I'm not going to mention her name cuz
She's a nice lady with someone it, Reg
Resnick tells me and I tell my
All of my
The finance people never use the term a lot
But he said okay you got to pay a lot
Metaxas
And that made me feel like they're just like waiting like
We finally got them we finally can
Put them in jail I was like can I still run for president jail I thought I could help. Okay
Just like JPMorgan & Chase did just like Deutsche Bank did so there is an issue to bring up with that but when it comes to the Rain
This is an important discussion to have because what we have to have to complete the Salt you guys got
Yeah well played Luke radowski the great-great interjection
Completion of that thought you don't know
Tangential is hell
Conclusion I come to is that you
Kind of a bigot
Confused
I want to like
The beginning of
I don't think he understands what gerrymandering is
No I know that was minutes ago but
Hey doesn't quite get that one no no
The other thing is that he's saying that they're trying to put him in jail and apparently the rationale for that
Is he found out he has a lot of taxes
And that's they're trying to put him in jail or is it just you a lot of tact
I don't know but this is all over the place
And like this kind of a rambling thing going on this long
Tells you that Tim has
Lost control
He is not in control of this year
Is giving up essentially on in any way trying to be a host on the show
He brings up f****** Epstein for some reason I need to get shut down by getting saying I need to finish my thought and then
Jokes
So great
Yeah man
This is
This is tough
This is tough to listen to because it does feel like
What needs to happen is
Soulquarians need to kidnap Kanye and take him to a f******
Ayahuasca Retreat together and then they'll be fine like
8 steel L f****** in
Staying like he's surrounded by the worst people in the middle of
I mean clearly an inability to think
Just I mean just
That's
That's not a question I'm not saying that it makes him anti-semitic by anymore
But there is a clear inability to think there's a
Clear processing tangential
Thought organizational
Stop being depressed
It's pretty clear the way that a jumps to c22 Alton
Abby
It's a
No and there's been tons of talk about it you know the that mental illness and how people are trying to handle
So it seems like he's having a manic episode obviously we don't know if
For sure we don't know his doctor or whatever
Brendan at the same time you know obviously I'm bipolar I've had plenty of manic episodes where I've never
Claimed that lawyers were at fault for me going to jail because they were Jewish
Never happened I understand that those two things are not
Connected to each other they can happen at the same time and not like 1 be the cause of the other
Right but at the same time in this regard
This is somebody who is
If you're timid like listening to this you should not be like oh this is it this is how I should be engaging in
We need to stop
We need to stop this is not accept
At very least
You do well I mean you do have responsibilities train at the interview
I think quite frankly
But it is not at least try to bring some structure to
Like what's going on
Because this is just rambling
Here's what I will say
About this
As a Bipolar person
If this is me in temples place
We're done with the interview
I'm taking Kanye and we're just going to go we're just going to go sit
I know it feels like that's a
No I understand that but it's like it's got to stop
It's got to stop it he's got to go it's kind I understand it feels trite to be like oh we need to go sit I mean
Literally I need to go be in a room with him
Where there's no interruptions are impulses
Or any contrite off Nick with a broom need to be that situation because this is unacceptable
People are using him
Does go on
Of course
Next year I was supposed to make 500 million dollars
And royalties in like
No one needs
This amount
A money
But when I would work on homeless shelters and ideas that have a contractor
It won't say what race
And
You know they'd be tearing down the contracts it's all about
You know position is not about the amount of money that you have and
You know the coming here I feel like it's a setup to be like defending I'm not going to go through another
Like I'm literally going to
Walk the F off the show
If I'm sitting up here having a
You know
Talk about you can't say that it was Jewish people that did it
When every sensible person knows that I mean John Stuart knows
What happened to me any took it too far it was like
American History X
Like my head was on the side of the Curve
And
The exact people that I called out
Kick my head we found out that my trainer was at
MK Ultra
Canadian
He worked in the defense research
And
In the Canadian military essentially working on psyops
Luke rudowski throw it into support I do not only to jump into Double Down
That your trainer is an MK Ultra
So this is been legitimately like 5 minutes straight of a rambling about
Entirely like a almost entirely uninterrupted about a wide selection of topics
With only the thinnest connective tissue existing
Between them
And now he's getting defensive about the whole thing about how he's anti-Semitic
He was the one who brought it up to begin with
Tim would have loved
To save that
For the apart the show that's behind a paywall or very least the end of the show
But they did not let that happen
Harley Pasternak is a personal trainer for celebrities but one of his previous gigs was working with a Canadian Department of National to
One of the things they're at they did was running studies on drugs and how they affect various aspects of soldiers performance
It's like things that keep people up for a long. Of time that work
Stimulants chair cetera
There's no indication that he is MKUltra but he's Jewish
So that explains a preoccupation with him
You posted a couple of a legend
Screenshots of messages Pasternak sent him where pastrnak was threatening to quote have you institutionalized again where they met
Medicate the crap out of you and you go back to Zombieland forever
I have no idea if he's a real tax
But honestly if his guys some big-time Hollywood celebrity had like there's no way you would make a threat like that in text
If the evil cabal was that sloppy they be getting busted all over
It would fall apart so fast
Larger point
Tim is doing nothing
I'm here he's not been able to come up with any decent rebuttals to this s*** and the things
Does they end up getting him a traps
I doubt he's just let ye monologue for what feels like a lifetime and that's not even good enough
They still managed to somehow feel like he's being put on trial for rambling about a topic that
But he brought up himself
Fire pool I just wouldn't have done this interview
Listen
Listen all I'm going to say
Is I don't want to get caught up
In one of these things where we talked about how I I'm an anti-semite
I want
To constantly make jokes
And implications
That all Jews are bad and I don't want you to push
I want you to laugh
At my funny I hate you jokes
Like these two white nationalist do right over here he's got a dumb face he's laughing right now
Not really jokes
F****** crazy I feel like it's generous to say the fees are implications in Roanoke
It is one of those
Far-right sings where everybody laughs when you say the thing that you mean you know like
You say like
Oh and
I hate Jews and everybody laughs but
They all know that you do you mean it
You do mean that
Nick is a little bit better about this whenever he is on his own making things
That's why you look that's why you're laughing speaking of Nick
Call Guy come up all that much
Smart but here's ears
Tim pool decides to bring him into it
Before the show obviously I'm getting a bunch of message
Shopping or like you shouldn't have
Most of them
Their Aunty somatic there
Primus the racist
I do find the idea I do find it
Funny or whatever that you know Nick they call you white supremacist
Sister here
Working with Thor
44 you know
Powerful
One of the wealthiest in
But spot
People are saying other rights physically don't platform
That's how you're going to
Bring up Nick
People say that you're a white nationalist but you're working with a lifetime how do you feel about that
Your this is
This is ridiculous
That's you were
Your response to like all people make these accusations about eunuch but you couldn't possibly be because you hang out with this
That's like a Niger
Your white nationalist there's a black man next to you
See that then you move on
It's not even like a statement is a defense in a deflection of racism
This is sanitizing and making Nick palatable by pretending to read the arguments the people make against
Everybody's stupid
Speaks ill of white nationalist you know but here we have one sitting next to a black man
No one's dead sea white nationalists are people too
Get back to
The things he really wants
Let's talk about course
Then I said well I want it I want understand what they're thinking weather thinking it
They're part of that they're involved in what may be the biggest news story of the past week and we have enough
How does the red media
Controls both sides it just said it as simple as possible
Put Jared Kushner
Who's next
Ron emanuel's next
Obama 1940
Really wonder what ye was about to say things have been happening since
WD-40 since 1940 I'm sorry what excuse me we're talking about this
We're talking about the Jews you were about to say 19:4
19 for needed British that thought to imagine the Tim is glad that he didn't finish that
Whatever that was probably wasn't good-looking tackler
On the edge just being like Hey listen eventually you're going to be me
So they threatened
To leave again
Whatever he did storm out I really don't think anyone should have been surprised
Even in the room
But he brought it up twice
But he's right
Because of things that
The topics that he himself has decided to complain about
And the non-existent pushback and reframing actually
Trying to do to make his beliefs
Acceptable unpalatable to the audience oh okay so
Hey buddy are you going to leave
Cuz the red media
Controls both sides it just said it as simple as
Jared Kushner
Who's next
Ron emanuel's next to Obama 1940
Sliq here at your shop and I have I'm going to get on going to order
With the last of my money that's available in a different account I'm going to order a PJ before I sit in hats or tell another
Set up conversation
When when I'm literally
Trying to trying to put me in jail for my opinion
But I am not that I'm not going to have that opinion I don't care about
People
The peep those are Bots
They're trying to take me realize I can pets
He's so Trump out
You got me saying this like I would have never
I wanted to do anything that hurt
Trump I'm on I'm on Trump side Trump
Set things that hurt me
He lied about me but I mean he's known for lying and when people use to tell me
That he's a liar it's like
And I went into the trenches for Trump that's another conversation there was no one in my position
That wore that hat
And all of my surrounding was like death by a thousand questions and I'm jumping to another
Thanks but what I'm saying is I know you got a rep
For your
European people online but it's like you got a person in real life that
Alright I'm not with it bro I lost I lost the money
For the freedom of speech
And that's what makes me the only
American that we know that
Really deserves to run the country cuz everyone else your boy DeSantis
Trump whoever they think they
Raising a petri dish soap on the Democrats
It's is going to play the game
You went right into the anti-semite then
I think it's something that should be talked about but if you if you start bringing this up you can ask my opinion.
Disagree with you I didn't ask your opinion on it you know but I'm going to it
I don't care about your pay I like your opinion on how we win election
They're about anybody's opinion bro I lost
They try to put me in jail
They block 2
Billion dollars I had
Hyperactive Farrakhan I said look I was it anti-semite
Somatoform you say his name I like
I administer
Yeah the minister like I tell my mama mode
All he was
Yeah I mean
A Jewish people allowed
Obama to meet
With the minister you know so
Yeah
I can't imagine Tim is sitting here thinking like
That there's a going to make it to minute 30
Yeah she is already saying I don't care about your opinion right
I'm going to say bye Auntie do stuff I don't give a s***
You kind of get just got to be like
Yeah it is
Almost like storming out tonight deal
Turn of events
No I mean I
Frankly
We're we're in asiimov storm out at this point I feel like if you bring it up twice you've got
Bright and Kanye still the Showman
So he's not going to not
Hey doormat
Flamboyant a storm out as you might hope it is a leaving none the last fairly bruh
Man I think if I'm Tim pool all that's going on in my head right now is
Great job Tim pool
People are going to pay so much attention to me I'm a big boy
I do think that there is an interesting Dynamic where Tim
Feels like he's disagreeing with ya in a meaningful way
And that is not happen
I understand that he's
Vicky's disagreeing with you by saying this is a localization issue or something like that
That's not challenging
Weight of what Kanye believe it's just putting another hat on it
Maybe looks better to Tim pools audio
Right so they can accept
The content of what ye saying
Just do a different way right look at it a little bit
I mean these are all far right people
Who
Live under this guise of
I say whatever I want
Because
The sensors have you no like I I will be uncensored and so if you
If you turn me off or whatever I'll keep
Keep saying whatever I want but they don't understand what it actually means
To not give a f***
About what anybody says
Like they all lived on this pretend
We put on this cape of like all the mainstream media hates us
And they still pretend that they don't have a complete and utter obligation to say whatever it is that Their audience wants
You know like
You guys just say whatever your audience wants
What's the same way that you think other people are
Containing your speech or whatever
Kanye really does not give a f***
He is going to say
Whatever the f*** he wants
And it really doesn't matter to him that's that's what they don't understand they don't understand
A person who truly
Does not care
I am somebody who truly doesn't care and is unable to buy
At least two people in the room who
Have a very strong interested in because he doesn't give a f***
Really Advanced their world with sorrow man and
Wormtongue that's just how it goes man that's how it is
Here is where it all falls apart
Has been a ramble
Of course
That leads into it and then I guess
Gay just decides
I've had enough
The contract for the next four years if I hadn't done anything
Would have been 500 million dollars
A year for four years
What I was fighting for was the IP
So my children
Could
You know
I'm sorry
Sometimes I think about 7 thoughts at one time
Because anything I see I come over like 7 answer
What it is
But
But the thing is when I said my children with the reason why my
My brain kind of
Block because it's like
God is saying
You know your your children are going to be okay
Baby mamas
Got money right
God is using me he's breaking me
Is down
Removing all of the
You know richest person all of this so I can serve him
And the more more those things are taken away from me the more I can be
Empty and be a vessel
And be able to be used in right now it's like
You're not going to take
If we can't you not going to take my pain away right
Did the Jewish people say
It's the Holocaust this happen
And you can't say anything about it we can't take their pain away
No one's going to denounce the fact that
They tried to lock me up
That's because every time I'm just holding stride
And it's like
I didn't I thought it was more Malcolm X but I find out I'm more MLK
Because I'm getting hose down everyday by the Press
And financially I'm just standing there
And went when I found out that they tried to put me in jail
It was like a dog
With biting my arm and I almost shed a tear
Almost
But I still walked in stripe through it
Yeah I think I think they've been used
I who is Beto
We can't tell you they is tamarind
I'm not even though I don't use the word is
Do you guys use the bathroom though isn't it I mean
Considerate
What what do I mean like okay so how about
Believing
He's on
I'll say right now
You got a II
You guys want to bring that stuff up
And say
Here's my painted myself everyday I hear you and that he's going to say and it was Jewish people and I'm to be like okay but don't you consider so I'm not going to do that
All right go for it looking I love the conversation
So I can't say I'm surprised
What what what what what do I even do
Rather than ask him please elaborate on this are you referring to individuals are you quite literally blaming an entire group of people
For the fact that powerful individuals are causing you harm
I don't think that he did do that
He's giving himself a credit for having like
It provided a little bit of push back in like Kanye can't handle this or whatever but that's not the case at all
Jay made himself mad
At 9 left because
Tim just didn't play along
Basically I mean you didn't even push back
Really
I would say
That if
You put
The camera on him
And didn't have Tim or anyone else there
Then eventually if he were talking for 20 minutes he would have stood up and left anyways right regardless of what anyone
Talkin to get to 100 different topics eventually complain about some Jewish people at 90 like
Position I need to defend myself to myself
I'm out of here I mean what's fun about it is that they
Clearly are not recognizing that they are so meaningless
An empty
Compared if Tim wants the credit for what he's giving himself credit for he
Should have given
Far more concrete pushed back
Do the very ridiculous things that were being sad
He would have
Maybe try
To get some clarity on somebody rambling points
Went nowhere and didn't get finished
Like they're at there's a completely different set of behaviors that you would have expected if you was going to be like
I can't be expected to just let ye show up and say these things and expected I'm not going to
You're like no you didn't do that
That's a fiction
That you're painting now that he has left through right
Congratulations for that
But you didn't
Right
This is not a
Frost Nixon matter what he did
.
We can talk about that
I'll meet you for sure
Is it is unacceptable that kind of Milo and Nick together
Sure I'm just
I think that there's a certain world
We're if it's just gay
You could
Potentially provide pushback
You know he probably end up leaving anyway
Just like this
When you have the three of them there there's no win
Well you're either going to end up in this situation or worst case scenario they respond
And you can't handle V3 on one that's going on
The Milo Nick and yay
And you just end up looking like an idiot getting Dunked On by ants
One of them and you're the you're the one with your hands tied behind your back
You're the one who can't say I know I agree with you
You know whether or not that's the case I'm not entirely sure like
You are definitely in a position that they are not in
I would say
The problem I have is
I don't want there's no reason to have ye on even by himself because what are you going to eat what are you going to put
Push back on
If the Sun is going to be completely different two seconds later
What are you going to convince him of
That won't then be different
Two seconds later
Is he going to
Follow you all the way through to the conclusion with
Yours no it's not even that you're just having them on there as a
Play f****** freak is a freak Show if you're intending that it's not it's
Same thing that you can expect a lot of these folks on the right to be doing which is trying to
Chase whatever attention they can get by proximity to
What are a giant celebrity
What Kanye on a dunk tank it would have been a better show
Because what this is is unlistenable garbage
And it's a f****** freak Show so you don't embrace it cuz that's what you're doing
If I may be so bold
I did listen to after he left
Are you show is better when he was up
Attention
Is something going to break what's going to happen here afterwards it's just him sitting there with the daughter of the guy who
Who made it to repair Loop radowski and some other lady talking about how great a job Tim did
And how he's a big boy it's nice it's him sitting going from sitting with five anti-semites to
Just too and that's really nice or the other leg
Lady is who was in there I know there's a be there daughter Luke nasty
Woman but I don't know who she is
Earlier saying
It is dumb though isn't it
As if he didn't understand exactly who that that
Oh that was Mick
Check out that was his voice
I seen a lot of response to things like
How does he think he can run for president if he can't stand a little push back in the interview
And I think of that missing some important point
The first is that two people inclined to like yeah and respond to the message that he's putting out
Leaving this interview doesn't actually signal weakness
It comes off as kind of
Strong be there
Only person who doesn't need to be there
The second thing is that if you just watched the minute prior to the storming out it kind of does appear like Tim is give
Giving some pushback
Actor yeah but I don't think that's necessarily a fair way to characterize the rest of the interview
If anything gay on entered this interview having
Just said a bunch of
Comically anti-semitic stuff
Proceeded to say Eddy's medic nonsense and Tim did his best to sanitize it so the audience
Could see it as something other than anti-semitism
It was a localization issue or an instance of identity arianism but it wasn't the thing that it obviously was
This wasn't an episode of Tim given pushback to gaze idea than ye not being able to handle it
It was a case of Timothy
Failing in an effort to whitewash the things gay was saying
Whether or not that was a conscious intent that's exactly what temperature
Or failed to achieve
I know shade on Tim for failing on that ever
He clearly had no interest in participating in the same position of his ship
The problem as I see it is that this happened in the first place as used
Basically
The way down and all that is pretty much what you'd expect
Considering the players involved
It's flashy and kind of funny to see if she'll go off the rails but it wasn't even good in that world
World likes people like storming off shows way better instances of that happening
Somehow
For the first time in history
Gallagher has outshone condo
Unfortunately there are some things here that can't be ignored
The fact is that Trump
Has announced that he's running in 2024
Factors that ye is claimed that he's running in 2024 in the middle of a series of public appearances where he seems to be becoming a
Increasingly comfortable in places of public anti-semite
Admits that he's attached himself to Nick Fuentes and Milo yiannopoulos who are only going to push him further down that road
Road to serve their own purposes
And Trump had dinner with ye who brought his crew along
I don't think that dinner is something that you be ignored but I
I think that the least meaningful way to cover it is have a freewheeling interview with ye Milo and Nick like Tim pool decide
He was going to do
If you're trying to get to the bottom of what happened do some reporting on it
Maybe you try to find a source in the staff at Mar-A-Lago who was there and maybe could tell you
An unbiased outside or opinion
Nick and Milo are not reliable sources
Is particularly about things that have to do with themselves
And I think Tim knew full well what he was getting with yay
I haven't received a number of times about people like Rogan book and Gaston editorial decision in and of itself
When you're inviting on people like this and you're not fully prepared to have a very confrontational interview you're having them onto promo
Think about that
One of the only things that Tim even said about Fuentes was defending him from accusations of being a white supremacist
Because he's working with yay
There was no acknowledgement that within the like the last Bond Nick is called for the expulsion of Jews from the country
That wasn't a like
What he was doing was like a
How could you be racist if you have a black
Friend level defensive Nick look at the ridiculous
That is a choice
And it's Tim showing deference to these creeps because his goal never was to provide meaningful pushback
To the toxic ideas that they're responsible for
Spreading
We do have to acknowledge that this is happening whether we like it or not
It very well may end up being the case that ye doesn't actually make it to running for president and even if he does
Seems like you'd have to run as a third-party candidate so he may not even have to appear in debate
So the idea of him not being able to say no to a debate might even be
F****** a relative
But even if he doesn't make it to primary season there is a reason to take this seriously
Many of them are matters for experts and other fields
To discuss but from my standpoint
Many of these roads
Be back to make polenta
Being involved in this will give him a higher-profile campaign experience
And bring him into even closer contact with whatever political figures end up supporting yay
In the same way that vanity candidates use campaign Stu cell book
Making use this to network
And raise his stature within other right-wing spaces
This is destined or even intended to succeed
This is the design of pure accelerationism ignore is used to
People who are easy to ignore
The goal isn't to win
He doesn't even to help a conservative or republican when it's to take over the right wing
Anyone paying attention saw how easy it was to get the entirety of the GOP power structure to fall in line with Trump and they have to have realize
Why is it that wasn't
Like an isolated event that wasn't going to happen again
If someone were able to command a similar amount of cult of personality and promise these
GOP leaders the things they want
They will become yeah Republicans overnight
It's a it was dramatic how quickly that happened
Ever underestimate the Craven
The politician
The goal is primarily to move the party GOP to further into
The extreme right-wing
And as such I think it's now time that we need to step up to the plate and take on some of this stuff
Richard away from covering some folks
It's like this for various reasons that I mentioned at the top of the episode but I'm going to reconsider that
In terms of broadening our Wacky Wednesday crude include some of these other characters
His priorities I believe is Nick Fuentes
Easy just to call Nick a racist and if you Semite and that's all good and well
And I don't think I would disagree for my taste
I want a fuller picture
So today what we're going to do is we're going to jump in and cover an episode of Nick show America first
From just before he made his big splash into the Nazi adjacent big-league
On August 11th
This is just before he would attend the unite the right rally after which you dropped out of college and really committed himself
Do streaming races chit from his parents
So at this point he's on his show is being aired on the right side Broadcasting Network
And
Baeza eighteen-year-old boy
A real s*** head
But
Even in this nascent state
You can hear basically
Very much of the underpinnings of the ideas that I believe he's
Still carrying out and some of it I think applies to his behavior
Visa Vie gay
So I'm sorry
Jordan
Great I'm excited
I'm stoked I can tell the sincerity listen to an eighteen-year-old white nationalist tell me
Yep
Here he announces that he's going to Charlotte
First order a bit
I will be at unite the right
Finally I made the accommodation
Oceans I made it happen
I do a lot of
People kept ask
Over the weekend
Nick are you going
Unite the right I hope I'll see you at you
The writer you coming down
I will be
Be there I will be there
To Rally the
Rally
So he is he's going
And we all know how that went
Yeah it went great
Everybody was United not just the right but the whole world
It's like Hands Across America is great
So
Nick has some interesting thoughts actually about this rally itself
Suspicious of it
Because it is a Honeypot meant to trap
Conservative
Basically yeah I knew it
I am alone
Little bit worried as much
Much as I am excited
People of like mind
Know what's going on
That are not dumb
Are in The Matrix
Blue pill people that week
Can talk about
Howard Hanna
The Country Fix
The demography
As excited as I am for all of that
I'm nervous
And this is a little bit of a shower thoughts
You're going to have all
The top guys
Is the top brass all the tin pots
You will that are going to be there all the main guys
From the white nationalist alright
Fringe right I don't know what you want to call it but this new faction
That's emerge
Obviously there's a lot of facts tables back
I think that sort of ghost
The territory why not unite the right
Picture of Waldo
I sorta thought it's
Kind of like in that movie Inglorious Bastards which
I watched it I liked it for a long time
And then I hit the red
Pella now I hate
For obvious reasons
Inglourious Basterds
The end of the movie
They get all the Nazis in one place
And then they blow them all up
And they shoot them all and they kill them all
And I'm thinking
You know that's sort of like
Basically for the
Social justice
Just Warrior for
Communist
You know people
Call her whatever
I'm sorry thing is that not
Exactly
What we're doing with
Unite the right
Is let's point
Every important
Person in our movements
In one place
And everyone
Sees us as a threat
What's a civilization
I mean isn't that
Isn't that kind of worrisome I don't know I mean I hope I'm not
Concerning people
I'm still going to go
You can't live your life
Fear but
You think of it that
Kessler Enoch
Spencer
James allsup ate the last I mean like everyone's going to be there
CMI
Lauren southern people
From Rebel media Argo
I don't know is that a great idea
Who thought it'd be a great idea like hey let's all go to Lee
Lee Park
Everyone thinks we're Nazi
Season bigot
What's the score in the middle of an open
Winfield
Look I understand the importance
Prince of rallying the
Morale
Uniting the right
That's why I'm going
That part of it
Some Nut Job some Travis
Bickell larper
With Sabaton 10
Bad ideas nutjob
It's it's interesting
His perception
And that is as like well I mean what better with the Nazis in
He doesn't like it for obvious reasons very very obvious that you
You think that we are getting all the Nazis together here too
Yeah and you're one of that right and I mean he's talking about this new faction that's coming together and he's like the white
White nationalist that like you will you recognize
But this is the part a large part of this group
Yeah Pizza that you are your night
It's not it's not like we called you that
You are that
Yeah yeah
You get it you even you get it
It's interesting his his leg then maybe some Nutjob will but but like I mean you don't understand
In the movie if you think it's just some nut job there was a war and Hitler was there so
Play that was kind of the point
Yeah I mean if your argument is that this is a lot like that I think you're saying a lot too much
I think you might be arguing the wrong point
Perhaps
So dangerous these
No they aren't dangerous remember the unite the right rally that happened literally immediately following this
I do I do
And that's why it's a little ironic
Are portrayed in the media as the dangerous
What's the violent
We're the only piece
People in the world
The 10 advocate for our own interests without it being Danger
Like
You go to a black lives matter rally and you're not in danger of getting
Killed by white
You may be in danger
White supremacist
Sister Clans
If you go to a
Palestinian
Rally
There's no danger of
You getting killed
If you go to a prose iniyot there's no danger of you getting killed by white Reaper folks your perm
Delete your event page on face
Facebook denies you service an Airbnb in Uber that doesn't happen
Only happens with
White people right
Only when we say
We don't want to be at
Exterminated
We're the only ones getting denied service revoked
Events cancelled on Facebook
And
Threat of being murdered
Bite people
That's just
Rally that he's promoting her hair was murdered at that rally
A car driven by a white identity extremist
Additionally I DeAndre Harris was brutally beaten by for rally attendees who went to prison
And
I mean we could we could litigate all of the violence and you know
People who have died at various rallies but I don't think Tim would ever think Nick would like
I don't think that would be a good use of his time
That's why
Yeah.
This is this is really uncomfortable just because he's a
You know like this is the type of s***
Set an 18 year old would f****** say to be edgy or some dumb s***
Like that
And then
People would intervene
Adults Whitaker
But instead he's surrounded by adults or like
F*** yeah dude go on bmore $1000000 also
Yeah it's
So
It's unfortunate
In some ways
Even for him
Because I I think there's a lot of people went there
17 18 19
Even into your 20s
If you are held
To that
For the rest of your life
It's not necessarily Fair
Yeah but the state that we are in
This is the same person
Yep he is not like
Maybe he's refined something better you'd speak about things a little bit more saveliy then he then he
He did in 2017 but like
Primarily
It's not like oh oh I'm embarrassed to look back on myself cuz I wore
Too many
God help me
What
Items the players clothing styles I don't know
Pop culture
Roxette don't know what you need for me I'm here for you
What are the things that make does on his shows that goes over the news of the day
Big news around this time is that Google memo
The James D'Amore
Yeah but maybe women biologically aren't meant to be
Give me feel people have big opinion
And Nick
And of course
We're talking about this
Google thing
I didn't talk about
What is a whole lot
Because it was very basic
Is a very basic subject
Three basic topic
To talk about it was all your usual suspects
Warriors
Google fired someone for saying a country opinion all that's again
Free speech
You know as much as I like
A lot of a purse
Personalities
The outline
New right
A faction
Boring it's so Blanton
There's so many bigger
Your things going
You know like I was saying about
Unite the right one
When are people
When white people
Are being killed and discriminated
It against him
Squandered the thread of violin
For advocating already
You know yet
People that are in front of Matt
Eating about
Social media and all that
You know
Just got to think of your priorities
Yeah he's a high-minded bigger
If you understand
Yeah this is this is just sort of small potatoes
You got to look at the bigger picture
Be racist but be ambitious about it right right
I find it interesting that big
Baked Within
These white people
Is
A
Kind of ironic understanding of what it takes
For you to be the oppressed party
Right
So they know
What it is that oppression is
Right
And they know that it's not happening
Probably on some level you know
So it's it is a little bit like
I'm just
Taking what Behavior has been done and I'm pretending that it's happening to me right there by what
Whatever it is that I'm justifying
Is Justified
To do to me like they don't understand that concept
I mean it's pretty simple
Come out and say my political objective is to
Make sure that my race
Is always in a position where we can assert Authority in all situation
You know like that is not really a good
You're not going to get a lot of people coming along and being like it sounds interesting
This way
It kinda it's it's a euphemistic in the same way that like a localization issue is way you no way the Timken
Can talk about anti-Semitism without like
Actually being upfront about what this is
Is the same thing with Nick he's he's a busy salesman
I'm just I'm just saying that if they understand the consequences of their own actions then they have Justified the consequence
That's all I'm sorry
Need to understand about Nick
In terms of his
Prescriptive ideas about
Policy
In about like the Wayside as we ordered
Is that he is not necessarily
Somebody who is in the same camp as like Alex
Who like believes on the Constitution as what happened
Does Mick Mick thinks that a lot of things that
Maybe your help
Sacred By
Liberalist
Society
Lego mascot so long
We're told by the right-wing
That we should be Liber
Libertarians
Write that
As long as there's no sense
As long as there's no.
Discrimination
Free market
And there's free speech
Free and open
Society
That's good enough
Right
The conservative say we should have
The Free Press
And we should have free
Free speech
Free assembly in
Free everything
For a long time I was on that
Speedway
And I was on that
What you looking at every
Three instances
Example
Free enterprise
You have all kinds
Conservatives that are
They're saying
Well you know
Google fire the sky
Speaking out again
Speaking out about obvious
Is Biolage
News about men and
But
Google the private company they can do what they want
There's nothing we
We can do about it
Wright's Google surprises
The company and so they're free to do it we may not agree with it bought that
And God bless the free market
I thought to myself
That is
True in every inch
The tution where we have these
These dummies
On the right
Dummy conservative
Did all the advocate for is
Free openness open Freedom whatever libertine libertarian
And we always get
Screwed every time with everything
Free enterprise doesn't really involve whether or not Google should have fired James D'Amore
Nick wants a dictatorship but that isn't really a coherent
D'Amore's memo is s***
And even the National Labor Board found after an investigation that his firing was completely legal and appropriate
He argues that their innate biological traits that make women less employed in the tech field in a Google and this has an effect
Creating a hostile work environment for folks and it wasn't protected
I don't I don't know but you get this
This Revelation through discussing this story that like no f***** there should be
The government should be controlling the economy
Even in hiring and firing decisions
If
Hawaiian tattoos
Dictator then he would tell
Corporation
Who they can hire and Fire
You can't that's a good
If you can't fire people for creating a hostile work environment for
A certain group of staff
That's no do you do get to do that if I were a white man
I've got a room I've got a new rule that I think works perfectly
Okay okay
You cannot talk to me about chromosome
Unless you know what
All of them
So if you're going to tell me there's a biological difference that you can pinpoint between an X and A Y
Define you also have to tell me about the other 24
Every single f****** one of them and if you don't know s*** about the other 24 that shut the f****** about the two of you do know about
This one here is a library
See that's what works in construction
This one is an artist absolutely
Starrybay all do as a professional 12
Yeah I don't know what the girls want to
Spa there's like that there's the the ones that are like how much hair do you have
I remember that one
So in addition to like not being into this free-enterprise stuff
He's also not into free speech
He does not
Think it matter
Free speech
You're all the college kids in Berkeley
Play Marching for
Free speech in the six
Once they got it
I control that
No free speech for white people
Free enterprise
There's no discrimination Allowed by the mark
Because
Costly to a business we should open up the free markets
You can only do
Discriminate against
White people
In the market play
Freedom of the press
We can talk about anything in the press as long as we get a free press we can happen
Information and everything is
And information revolution with the Internet only people that are discriminated against
White people
One state
Animal Control
Folks take a look
Take a look at okay
Control some right
The globalist
And I
I just think it's so funny that
You have so many people young people in parts
Particular add baffles
That are still championing this
Hedonistic
Ridiculous libertarian cause that only hurts our
So it is important
The point is that every time that makes his globalist he's smiling and doing like a little bit of a week
He knows we all know
It's debatable whether or not
Or at least how consistently Alex
Is using that euphemistically for Jewish people
It is not as pretty transparent that he's winking
Yeah you know what I'm talking about
You know why I don't like in glorious bastards staff
Okay so if I was a fascist dictator
Alright
I'm not giving a s*** about hiring and firing people whatever
Bye-bye bye-bye
Not my job
Shrike that seems like a tough to micromanage the only thing I'm doing
Is I'm going to create
A
What I'm going to call it a do it to you
Right so everything else the government can do whatever they want but I've this is my baby
Alright
And that every time somebody's like
All right Bubba going to like 20
Then he goes to the dude
Do you camp and then all the things that he wants
Get done to him
And then we figure it out you know what they will see how he turns out on the other side of the maybe fascism is bad
Yeah support either you becoming a dictator or this place well particular
Second one really undercuts the first one
Sure
So did the
It's it's
Interesting to me the way that these assertions are just made and
Like there is no evidence
Or anyting presented for like
You can only have
Free Speech white people
Bieber
Discriminatory against white people
I get just seems like a whiner
Yeah well I mean Debate Club like repeats the certain keywords that you know
Who can happen
White people
White people who disagree don't really matter they're not your audience
Like agree with this already or the people you or hoping you suck in that sack generally speaking
Cancer Network
Pretty good chance that
That's who's going to be watching
So make as an interesting metaphor here about
I guess the races
This is dumb The Wacky Races
Nope nope
Think of it like this
Think of it I made the analogy on the show
It's like a soccer
Okay
And one
What's call it
The color teal
The black team
Well you've already started wrong
Black team is there
Soccer they were black
They don't play by the rules
They pick the ball up
With their hands
And they throw it in the neck
And they only passed
To each other
I need
They run in the middle of the field
Play pick up the ball and then they throw it in the neck
And then they take it out and they throw it in the neck
And they take it out and then
Throw it in the net and they're winning
Running up
The scoreboard
You know you don't see high scores and soccer cuz it
But you're seeing
100 105 200b
And throwing it in the neck
They're not playing by the rules
They're not playing at 6
They're not playing
Fairly
You're not playing by the rules
They pick it up they throw it in the neck
And let's just say hi
Statically the other two
The white tea
They're wearing white jerseys
They're just getting mad about
They're just sitting on the sidelines
With their hands on their hips
Saying hey
That's not
That's there that's not playing by the rules black tea
You can't pick it up with you
In the net
That's not by the rules look at our rulebook
It goes against Article 1
Section whatever of the rulebook
And you're not playing by the rules in
We're not going to let this happen
And they said they're with their he
And black team just
Throw it in the data they are running up the scoreboard
And white team say hey I don't like that so much
Except
Here's the death
Difference in the real way
It doesn't matter how you get the point
It just matters that you
Get the points
And the loser dies
The loser is
Exterminated
Once they get to a point where the blacktop
Team gets a huge lead
Last text
And that space
Sickly the world were living
And I don't have to
Spell out the analogy
But that's basically
Which is
You have people on white team that are saying
Let's do whatever it takes to win
And then everyone else on the White
Saying
No that's not fair we have to play by the rules with will not play until every
Plays by the rules
And you understand what happened
White team they have the rule book
White team may have played ethically they were
We're so moral
They were so virtuous they talked about
The universal
Brotherhood of soccer
Players and Howard
It's all just about soccer
I'm playing the game
But then they all
He killed in the parking lot
Whatever we decide to go home
And that's the world we live in
That's the world we live in
Can I
Let me try a soccer metaphor
It's like let's take one team for the sake of argument the white tea
All right now on this soccer pitch
Let's say the white team has
Several hundred player
Marcelo Balboa Mineola
Five people in gold right
And then the black team has about 10 people
Alright and then the white team
Steele's
The black teams
Heron
Balls
Take those away from them and then their grandparents balls to take those away from them so they've got all these millions of balls in there just
Fire Matt the golf but then the black team scores one goal
Until the white team goes f****** games
Trump to be president it's interesting that neither of your metaphors really make sense in terms of soccer
Yeah
I would like to ask make some follow-up question
Since the first Ruby what are the point
In this metaphor
Like what
Stand for literally right
I believe he's literally talking about rights
Those are the points
That's weird yeah
I mean I don't know
I don't know what 9 a.m.
Just win or lose it's hard to it's hard to really respond to his metaphor because I don't understand what the
The goals are
Scoring mean
I don't know who the wraps are the rafts
Cuz I mean like
You know
If they were there I would guess
That they're just giving yellow and red cards
To the white team yeah I mean they must like Nick cuz he speaks too much truth to get Silo cars clothes and I guess that means
It's like getting kicked off Twitter maybe maybe that's what the refs are maybe the rest are like jaxi I think he loses the metal
Four at the end when he's like and then everyone dies in the parking lot
What about the game so much as you just want to kill everyone that you don't like
No because he's saying that they are going to be the subject of the Killer
Right but he's only saying that because he
Wants them to be the Opera
Right cuz there's in his metaphor there's only two teams right and I'm one of them is getting hurted in the parking lot one of the members on the
The white team who sang we shouldn't play by the rules know the parking lot
Musically yes
Not good
Target metaphor
I mentioned it doesn't like free speech
And ironically
What the moral of
The story The t
The moment is
Idea
Is an
It's not the end
Itself we use free
As anarki
I meant as a tool to
The further our own inch
We use free
Free speech to get these guys to play by
Their own rules to hold the
Themselves
But we're not after
Self or not after
Total an Absol
Freedom in itself
Of course not
Because every time that we
We do get this total
We get
Certain groups
People
Use it and through unfair
Advantages and strategies
They climb to the top and use it
To their own advantage
We're talking about
The globalist
And so
That's why
We have to
Play for our own team
Finally
This Google thing
Teaches us that
The argument is Liberty
But not for Liberty
Itself not as
Is an enzymatic
The further our own intro
This is a great moment to understand Nick a little bit better
Don't first second trust that something he's saying necessarily has to be sincere because there's a very good chance that something
He's pursuing is actually just a red herring and is part of something else entirely namely
Advancing is white identity agenda
What Nick is doing is echoing the ideology of his forefathers
Particularly George Lincoln Rockwell the founder of the American Nazi party
Rockwell would go to college campuses and cause a scene in game free press coverage under the banner of free speech
But the goal was really spreading
Is Nazi ideas
The Free Speech part isn't important to them at all
On the basis of it being a prince
Gladly cross the speech rights of people they didn't like were they in charge but they know that they can
Cry free speech in order to mask what their rallies and ideologies are actually about
This trend is really consistent on the right wing
I think about how all the anti lockdown protests
What happened over the last two years were really bored let's just radicalization points for anti-vaxxers spread their idea
The far-right
Has an internal awareness that their ideas are things that most people hate
So they need the Trojan Horse them
Two people
Presenting your ideas as they actually exist as a sure path to rejection so you use universally approved concert
Steps like free speech
As a mask that your actual ideology hidebehind
Make a pretty pretty open about
No I mean it's fun it's it is like an it's like a team
Listening to all of the adults lie and going well
I get what you're saying see
I'm telling you what you're saying that's what you're saying
Why aren't you saying
Like it's made very simple
Well honestly it's like
He's not coming up with ideas
No not necessarily at this stage I would not say that he is a necessary
He is
Demonstrating a pretty Keen awareness of these
Underlying tactic
That people used to push people further right
He's he's articulating them in a way that is
Jermaine too and consistent with his behavior since
So I think is worth
Understand
It's f***** up and away because it's very clear that he sees through the b*******
It's just
Bet he's mad
About it
Like he's like
Why are we lying all the time can't we just tell people that we want to kill the ones we don't like
Can't we just
Exert power with power
Charade
Free speech
Except he's not
Stop saying that
He is not saying we use these tools
Because we need to in order to get to the point where we can kill
People we don't like in the parking lot
Exactly
So I mean that's
Let me know in parties
Clearly understands the strategy
So you get to talk a little bit about women in the workplace
And what have you got
What's the other 24 chromosomes do
Can you try and tell them this like
Hey you know
Sweetheart
I know you
You feel really passed
What about this
The attention of some
Chad College Republicans
Frat party
But if you really want to save
The country if you want it
Fulfill your moral obligation
To your country and
People
You should be getting married and having
10 or 50
Teen children
And you will be
By the way
And know that is no small order either
You will be the backbone of
The country of the
As a good mother
But they all want to fight you on this
Miss everyone wants to
To fight you on this
Save that
That's just not realistic
That's not with the tie
And everything's going so well right
It's totally fine if people choose to be Homemakers but the option to pursue whatever work they want is pretty critical to a
Free world like
Dates
Sexist
Misogynist to say that women have to do that
The people make but anyway
Not not for nothing a major element of Nazi propaganda involved women reproducing more white babies and how that was
The Cornerstone of building the third right
The word called
The cross of honor of the German mother two women who had
For more children
That's what Nick is hearkening to with this message it's pretty clear
He goes on to talk a bit more about this later to just like really strongly about his feelings about like
You need to have seven children and then they want you then
7 children who will also give birth to seven children
That are all conservative
Right
It's a little
First of all it is harkening back to that ideology
Replacement
I mean because
How many people do we know who have
Conservative parents who are
Quite liberal guarantee that just because you even if you have a tightly-controlled
Controlled family system
Doesn't make it like
Any more likely that your children are going to end up
Having your exact same ideology and that's why it would be nice if everybody understood
Is it that when you try and implement the things that these right right-wing people think
Will happen
We get crazy weird unintended consequences
That nobody understood or expected to happen like for instance
I don't know say the covid response being
Letter f****** rip from half of our goddamn country
There's a lot of things that are unintended because they have
Terrible ideas
Yeah
Nick believes that racism is all around him
I can't swipe
I think you would believe that he decides he's going to bring up a really prime example of that
And for everyone that doubts me
For people like my mom
Who Doubt Me On
To think I'm some
Racist bigot
Because I want my P
To stay alive
Mom's cafe in here
You turn the show off
Around him
Clipper from being racing
You think that's all fine and well we just
Just need to have an open
Do me a favor right now if you're watching
In the show on you
Click
On the top right open a new tab
In this window open a new tab
Go into Google
And I want you
Google for me
American
Inventor
If you don't believe me if you think I'm pedaling
Has Barack Obama
I'm making this up if
If you think I'm
Some white supremacist sunken Spanish
I will demonstrate to you
Click open the new tab and Google American Adventure
Tell me who comes
Tell me
Google, pin that Google search when you Google
American Adventure
Tell me
Does Benjamin
Come up
Does
Nikola Tesla Mike
Come up he might not
What do
Just about every single one of the results to come up and Google have
Weird was it their miraculous
What's a thermal miraculous
Influential Adventure
No that's
That they have
George Washing
Carver before they have
Have time to status
You know that can't be
G1
Who are they deliver
Really excluding from
Or they deliberately
Revising history
To exclude
So just one thing
Tesla was born in Croatia
Will be counted as an American inventor
Yeah for other raps
But whether or not you she's an American Adventure
View thing but Nick is concerned with his that he's white
Nick is going to Google inventors
And let's see he's going to do it let's onscreen for us a little game of races
Brian and f****** Geraldo that
Safe man it's a terrible idea it's not going to go well could make is probably better at presentation that Owen is
And who do we have
George Washing
Carver he's
Results when you think of America
Adventure
Think of George
We eat peanuts
Howard Latimer
One of my favorites
Definitely hero
Garrett Morgan yes
Garrett Morgan
Can't remember which
Elijah Wood
McCoy
Annabelle
Madam Walker
Doesn't ring a bell Okay so
First five
Five entries
I've heard of one of them
Don't know any
If their invention
Well let's keep
It's all final
Thomas Edison
Of course
Thomas Edison invented the light bulb
Like 100
Things probably one of the greatest Adventure
Pictures of all time
Number 6
He hides Elijah McCoy
Madam Walker
Latimer
After Edison
Can you have
Lonnie Johnson
Oh good old Lonnie Johnson
Granville Woods
Patricia bath
Jan Ernst
Mets
Sliger
We have an all of those
Even want to start
Every single one black
Two white guys
Coincidence
Does that make sense
I have no idea what list he's looking at but I decided to play along with him and according to my Google results I don't know if they've changed
2017 or whatever but
The first names that come up are Thomas Edison Samuel Morris Robert Fulton and Alexander Graham Bell
All white dudes
Emmanuel George Washington Carver
I don't know what list he's looking at so I can't really respond to it specifically B seems like bulshit
A larger issue with his blanket disregard and disrespect for black inventors
He doesn't know who any of these people are which
Makes the opposite argument than what I think Nick is intending no one knows about these people
But what did they invent
Garrett Morgan invented the traffic light
The smoke Hood would you like firefighters to withstand smoke exposure and still be able to breathe
Lewis Latimer work for Addison and actually holds the patent for electric lamp
He also invented one of the early forms of air conditioner
Elijah McCoy invented the automatic lubricator for steam engines centrally revolutionising railroad travel
Both in terms of Civilian use
As well as for commercial purposes
Madame Walker is remembered as the first female self-made millionaire u.s. history and develop Hair Care Systems
For black women
Lonnie Johnson invented the Super Soaker one of the best selling toys of all time
Does work
Developing Tech
While working at Nasa as an engineer on spaceships
Granville Woods invented automatic brakes the steam boiler furnace and a raft of other railroad related things
He's often called the black Edison but I guess Nick hasn't heard of him
Patricia bath invented things that improve cataract surgeries
Ernst invented the lasting machine which allowed for greater
An easier production of shoes which previous to that was a
Severely complicated process but had to be done by hand and it Bass
Basically allowed for
I'm in all sorts of development right where
Right I've been I have a bigger issue with this whole dumb train of thought which
Is just like
Why are you
Arbitrary
Bowl America are arbitrary arbitrary it's only
Most stuff was invented in Asia
From a thousand million years ago it doesn't matter that's fine wherever
It's fine crazy that's fine
Everything's just not been more white people didn't invent s***
There's two things
Yeah one
Is
I think you just see disregard and disrespect like I said of
These
Figures of
American invention history because they're black
Nick finds them to be not not interesting
Or anyting Auntie feels that he can denigrate
Secondly
It's not about all this inventing stuff
It's about the fact that makes things
Expect Google is trying to
Exclude white inventors as a racist plot
If you're trying to add regate the best
Results
Why don't you have Ben Franklin on there why isn't Thomas Edison number one why isn't Tesla there why aren't
I can't think of a whole lot of
I'm not like
Science Guy
Even I know
That's pretty ridiculous
Why
Who did that
Boohoo working behind the scene
Program.
Listen doesn't just happen by itself right you know that's not
That is not an organic
Search results
Someone went in there
You changed it
And why did they
If I was that allowed
But that happened
For what purpose
Is that going to make
Google more money
Has the free market capital
Tell us no no no
It's going to
Hurt white people's feelings
Yeah just reminds me of what I can't remember who said it was the Reconstruction Era Quotev like if you can
Vince
The poorest white man that he's richer than the black then a black king then you've got him forever
Something along those lines and it's like
It is such that just like
Oh who the f*** is this I don't care all they saved a billion lives and I'm just a piece of s*** yelling about how I'm breaking
Sazon are weird weird how great I am this person
Why does Google tell me about
People who saved live
Yeah I've got racism to do
There
Emails from Alex's talk
That
The New World Order
It exists
Very scary thing George h.w. Bush is the leader of it because he use the words New World Order it's gone
Andante to speech
Here's Nick
And it's going to be a showdown
Emergent grade
Yet to be seen
Watch broader more lawn
For the u.s.
China's
Going forward house
That power
World Order
How is there a World Order that's a developing in the twenty-first century with that be a new state of Ohio and order out
I mean it is
Different it's confirmed it is different is ahead of an from the previous order
Yes
There was an order in the past
And that order is no longer the same order as current so one could argue yes it is new
Right
Such stupid s*** Yelp
Anyway
There's a discussion here
Assertive crypto strategy
That Nick employees
In order to push his ideas
And this is
Who's part of
The end of this episode
He takes questions from the audience
And some of these questions end up reviewing fair amount and I think
You make a great observation earlier about how like these
He's just thick teen
Explaining what does these people do
That's basically what happens
An advocate asked
It's not more productive
Lay low
I still while I haven't gone
Full red pill
Just yet if you have a note
Some words
Some analogy
What is the dark light therapy
I have but I'm not
Is what I'm trying to say I don't know
That's just it I don't know if I'm a liar
Filtrate
Without going full red pill only be
We can't make the art
Without the truth
And in order to lay low
Can't tell the truth
She argue with
People about him
Immigration
Headed certain point
You can argue about
Culture
Right at a certain point it be
To say well we don't want
Immigration
Because
Downward pressure
Low-wage work
Get sprayed if
Certain flight to not make the whole case
Case with everything we know the truth
Cell
I don't know I'm
I'm feeling it out I
It's a lot of it
Improvisation
The long-term
Grandpa
And what I'm really trying
Do I think is ultimately
We're going to have to
That will happen
Just trying to wifey
As I go
Yeah I mean
Clear I feel like that clip should be played
For the American public like
Constantly just nonstop followed by me saying
A teenager figured it out you idiots f****** team he's 18 look at it
Come on you f****** moron
Obvious
Just play it again
Play it again I'm going to say it again
Right you know like following a falling in with him
Memes
You are either being tricked by him or you get it to your gleefully going along with
I caught that I did I do I want to
Non-Stop psav
I want my own channel where I just play this clip
Going to go see
So there's more strategic talk here in and I do think it is you just have more
Contact for your Loop
Nick youth
It is wise to
Applewhite Nash
Rather than
No icing
Ill-advised
I say that
Experience
I'll tell you little
The job training and
See I went to a job
4A
Doterra
And I was in the job
For it
And I was disqualified on my first day
Disqualified
First day was like a
2 weeks
Job training
Viafield rappers
Pretty benign
And this was a think tank
It's pretty much like
Umbrella group
The big tent group
Were they have a lot of
I know people
When they're that agree with
It's a big tent group day of
People liver
Craterian
Conservative
Paleocon
Do I go there to get the job
Field representative
And I was disqualified on Dave
By this Dopey girl name
IV for
From Lebanon
Because I said I wanted
To protect my
Because I was against
Immigration
Now immigration
Is a conservative issue
Against
Illegal in
To some extent
Legal immigration
Policy of ARP
Saddle
The policy of our party
And yet I get to
Disqualified for me
You been getting an entry-level
Call job at this
Servant of big
Cuz I said I wasn't
Immigration
And you realized
Two things
Number one
It's very difficult
To hide
You have to pay
Cleco come
And at that point
At the same time
You think you're getting big
You think you're in
Trading you think
You're growing your base
You're going into
But the minute
That you
Go little bit for
To the right the minute that you go off
A script
The minute that you
Go away from what your character that
They built
How to beat
You lose
Lose your money
You lose your funding
You lose a lot of your audience
Like imagine
Imagine of Bill O'Reilly
If he was still on
Television
And he said
I don't know
Some kind of white
You would be fired
You would be fired in a lot of pain
People would stop watching
And he would stop making
Kimani and they would
Never had a boy
Blacklisted he would be
They would smear his name run his name
Do the mod every
Any would-be
Like the new David
Right
If you're doing it from the beginning of
Short of
You know On The Fringe
Not totally
Expected a neighbor
Beyond that I think
The time is right
The money is there
Or we can really give it a shot
And I'm definitely not a white Nash
Because if you're a white
Do not ever call me
Don't let me in
With the actual
Will not cease
Good good save their good save at the end Okay so
Is reincarnation real because I think Henry Ford is alive again I'm concerned that Henry Ford is
Baby
Yeah yeah yeah
Or George Wallace
I think those it like
Some of that
Some of the ability to articulate
Some of this stuff
And somehow it not
We like completely destructive to his
Ability to exist
In that in any kind of a space
I think it does speak to
A certain amount of Savvy on his part
I do think that
That's one of the reasons why I think that he is not like
These other people that are not angry
You know some of these folks
Are kind of boring
In the sense that they do appear to be
Out to scam
I don't think he has any kind of moral Center or any ideological Center
Advantageous and expedient for him to get the most
Views on on YouTube in front of me
I don't know
I know I think they're people like Steven Crowder who push ideological things obviously he has
He has
Toxic and bad political position
Is that that have an ideological a back to them but I don't think he has an ideological Center
Yeah like I am one of the things that differentiates Alex from even from Owen Shroyer is that there
Does
Sit there is a point of him
That has a core to it
Yeah no his berci beliefs
That he was
Obsessed with and and changed him
As a team like that is a part of his trajectory in his career
And with Nick is there
There is
Like that
Yeah something
Know what
What's annoying is that he understands
I mean enough
I understand how things work fairly well into far as like
Like I so manipulative game of it not just that but I mean
Doing of it as a job like with our show
We are beholding to our listener
You know what I'm saying like it's not like our advertisers can drop-off if we say something wrong
What will happen is if we are dicks to our listeners they'll be like
Hey stop being dicks to us you know like that
Sure
In the same way that's what he's doing
Only he doesn't understand that second part
Of being beholding to his is
His listeners to his followers
Which I think is where he's starting to get
Because it from what I
From what I've heard he's starting to get pushback from the whole incel people
Repeating I don't know
Someone who is occasionally thought about sex or not I don't even know which one it is
Too much into paying attention to that stuff about him like not having sex or being
I think a lot of people do have an interest in that number of things on Twitter and I think a lot of people
Fallout 4
Yeah maybe jokes and stuff he's he is a figure the up-to-date kind of carefully
Terms of like
You kind of just have to ignore some stuff and be like okay whatever man okay
Cuz there is more important things that are being said that maybe aren't as
Flamboyant
Centaurus
A picture of concern myself with Alex
There are other things
Like instance of objectivism
Just clear understanding
Of
Like a way to launder nationalism into
Other places
This thing where he's like no I am not a white nationalist at the end
Is such a
Very
Obvious way of saying I am but I want to say I have to say that I'm not is very weak
You know the question
If you'll remember here listen to what the question was
Nick
Weis to go
Full whiteness
Rather than 22
No I
Ill-advised
And
His story that he tells is about himself
Going to try to get this entry level position at a think tank right where he says
That he told this woman from Lebanon
That he doesn't like immigration cuz he's trying to protect his people which is
His example of I guess
That's him toning it down to get a job
I guess that's what I heard him that's my understanding of the story is that he was like
There's no point in even pretending to say
That you're not a white nationalist
Because even when I tried
I'm so white nationalist
When I thought I was
Bucking
Watering it down it was still overflowing with white nationalism
Succeed within vasta and I bring about some kind of cloud or notoriety to yourself
You have the potential for that to be taken away from you when I come straight to far from
Acceptable path
Ryan so the way to do it is
Is doobie
Front about a lot of stuff vehicle
Sleep f******
Weirdo yeah take the lump
But come along with it the marginalization
Grow your s***
To the point where
You know you can
Avoid those pitfalls and that's basically the Pathak
He's managed to walk right and I do think there is one thing that he got wrong
And that is the DeVille O'Reilly said white nationalist pigs
I'm not sure he'll be kicked out specially not not not now for sure for sure
No but I think that's exactly what
Is is also concerning about only being beholding to your own audience in the same way that Alex
Was after you know
After he was kicked off of everything is that like
Also
There is no stopping it
Only the audience can stop him
At this point because nobody else can affect his audience
You know
Yeah
Yeah I wonder Hammond the audience I wonder and with so many of these folks
The audience also includes like
I don't know billionaire donors yet
Also an element of this that
Is
A confounding factor of the beholding mystery
You know that's fair
So
Interesting Lee
On this episode coincidentally make it the question about Milo
That's weird
Other question
Benzoin what are you
I like
I don't know I'm
I'm sort of
What about Milo I like them for a long time
You see him
Like causing half
Pool
Call Missy
Bottom
Brags about
The things he does
You know
Milo
He made
Annie Maybe
Sharing a
Little bit alternate
Your hearing
People on the
Fringe far-right
But I think
I think it is
Not wise
You still hold up
Someone who lives
Is a lot of things
Search history
He's gay black
Brag
About
Things I can't even talk about on the show because they're
You're so vulgar
Other phone
He brags about the gay things he doesn't mean that's on the loop that's on the look like you guys get it do you know
Episode maybe should just be your Loop
Let's add this to the loop
Not yet
Someday when it be
Time Israel for god sakes when the people are ready
To receive the red pill
I will go for
You have to
You have to sort of go with the
The Temple of Time
We can only set the
You know I think
Time is deaf
Anna's right in the United
See the European
Suing Italy
Definitely more viable
Day person
Where is an America where
Where are you at 3
Vermilion PT
I don't think people are as susceptible
That's sort of Far Far Right mess
You may have
Extremely far right
Progenitor
Ideas and culture
Propaganda
But you have to have people
Can short of be palatable
To the mainstream
To focus those eyes
Ideas to make
Viable
Massmart
It's not 19
The Bolsheviks
Take over the cafe
I buy apps
2000 people
Collapse
FairPoint
Pelagic
Viable
More people
Ironic that like
Yours is right in their thousands of friends
Just
Just f******
I'm I'm frustrated that we live in a simulation where this kind of
Okay.
You know I used to call you which but now clearly you're just be architect of my f****** torment
That must be what's going on right
Ugly in this frustrating for me to
It's much like Nick Fuentes you know you have to lie about everything
Until you don't have to lie anymore sure once the people are ready to embrace that white nationalism
I'm going to lie until I don't have
There's also a strategic purpose to the lying and that is to be somebody who is a little bit more
Palatable
That is is getting those seeds out of their of this.
I mean
Quite honestly
Whether consciously or not that is also like a fair description of what Tim pool does
Like I think that is obviously far more aware and self-actualize
About this
But you know it is a description of a lot of people within that
This sphere of media figures of just like listen this is how they launder bulshit do you not
It is 18
Years ago
Years ago but seeing
That might be what makes him so
Kind of
Able
22 work
Yeah space
Like it isn't something that most eighteen-year-olds would understand on this side of a level
Propaganda the man was born to lie to people
Just his skills
Yeah I think that is also a part of
Of
You know what makes it
Kind of disconcerting
Vicky's here with ye and Milo in this
Bizarre Trio of
Your folks were pushing anti-Semitism it's like
He's only learned more sent this point when he was 18
Pressing some strategy that he decided I shouldn't
I don't pursue this
This is
This is essentially like
You can see the footprints of this moving forward through his cuz I mean on that Tim pool interview he should have been Champa
Bring a cigar going I love it when a plan comes together like that is literally what's going on
One Life Club here
Colonel John
A story that is real
Rarely if ever been
Controlled
The really good story that is
A leaf
Great story
I don't know why
I don't know
I don't know I
Think I'm a wreck
Rebuttal
I am annoyed actually I have
If I ever
Heard that story
It would be race
I'm going to get in trouble
Reven knowing
Isn't that crazy in this country
If you know about something and
You talk about some
You get in trouble is if
If you're like
Dedicated to it at
Your whole life like
Cuz you mentioned song
So the greatest story never told is a documentary that is
Is arguably the most anti-Semitic thing that's ever been produced
Maybe a little bit but positive depiction of Hitler
Like this playing around in his dancing around is is just a fun way to Wink in
Because that is also part of the game
It's the most annoying part
The most annoying part
That you just
Laugh while you say the things you believe so you can later call it a joke
Knitted annoying and it's frustrating
I like jokes we write jokes where it jokes
Good
Structured
Weather
Meaningful
Sometimes
Sometimes you just talk and you say fart
Yep
That's pretty much when he's do it
Start my man's art buddy
So yeah we come to the end of this and
I guess I think that there are some
Things obviously there's a different flavor to like an episode of America
The first than they can Infowars episode
There is less of an interest in acting out
Generally speaking
But there's also a difference between this
And Owen
I do think
Well not as theatrical is Alex per say
There is a different kind of competence
As a host even at 18
You can you can tell
From
From Nick
Yeah that makes sense
You know it's something that I do think that I I feel
Like we should cover more of
And I think we will I think we'll cover some more of this because
Until this plays its natural course
I do see
This Trio of weirdos and it's something
It does not deserve
Super
Official
Sort of a mocking or superficial analysis
I think it is something that points to a big problem and
II
I think that we can we can look at it and deconstruct stuff
It's best we can with the tools at our disposal
But
We are still going to talk about
That. Don't be
Concerned listener if Nick and Owen were in the same contest I
I think Alex would have been like well we obviously can't
The eighteen-year-old let's just hire all
What's the contest
That's right Apollo
And I think they probably wouldn't have done it
No that's what I'm saying and it would have been right Nick wouldn't have gone along because he wasn't
We couldn't have gotten
Oh I would the thing that I was thinking of the same year that Gary put Nick and Owen
In the same place I am like I just made me think of Seabeck
With kind of
He was dunked on but
Owned
Get owned at Twitter
That's it
We'll be back with another episode
I don't
Love the developments in the world but I would also be lying if I said that they didn't intersect with the stuff that we talked about
Yep and it seems like it would be
May be negligent
To not to poke her nose in a little bit and see what's going on twice
Jordan
Bless you
Indeed we will
But it doesn't make me do it
We aren't winners that knowledge underscore fight
Jordan
Will be back but until then
Emilio Emilio I'm dzx Clark
Working on
The script
Even working on a script yet the one that you've been telling me about okay
It's basic
My idea is I want to write the Next Great American novel
But as a
Stats
Breathe right there going to be jokes
It's going to be a coming-of-age story a bildungsroman
Doctor Who like an attractive person. Maybe I figured that part out exactly
Hurting expectation to read this
That's not a script
That's a f******
And now here comes the sex robots
Holding
Alex, first in color with huge fan I love your work