Knowledge party.com
Pray I have great respect for its knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Money
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody looks it around a little bit
Alex Jones
DVR dance
Jordan quick question for you what's up
Matter of contacts you know this already but
Formerly known as Kanye West Plaza on Thursday
And that's already talked about today
Because of the
This
I ended up thinking about like
What's my history with Yaz music like
Kanye West fan in terms of the music
Still here some of the songs on the radio like Jesus walks on bikes to find good stuff I think that toast to The a****** Song
Maybe a searching moment of like a pop song
Does taking the piss out of himself in a way that I realize probably wasn't sincere right
How much of what was that on
Was that Dark Twisted Fantasy I do I don't know I realized
Like the first time that he came into my orbit
Or my spear
I was when he was a guest on the Dilated Peoples song This Way interested
Wow I guess probably I heard of him maybe as a producers
Something like that prior to that was on neighborhood watch
Third album
I haven't heard the Dilated Peoples in a long time
I also wasn't that huge of a Jay-Z fans are really either listening to albums
Spike
Multiple times
Can I listen to the Dilated Peoples
Enjoy that stuff
Yeah it's pretty good I was working on some of this stuff to prepare
Listening to a little bit of the platform
Expansion team
Doug solid albums I don't know what happened to them later I don't want to find out just in case
Schoolboy there's one song I can't remember what your Altima top hits featuring the alcoholics
The licks
Photo by the great the great lyrics
Batman character walkthrough my hood there's no love
Casual jacket for escaping sport that s*** to the club
Who is that that great
What what's the price for I forgot
Ada in the lakes of typhus
Oh No my bright spot is my wife and I enjoy yours of The Amazing Race
Sure you got me on it that's my favor
Everything to do
Stand
The final that the second to last episode we watched it
And there's team of long-lost twins
Oh no
Can't not
Be in love with long-lost twins how do you not
Especially with their Force together and like your baby journey of love each other so much
Much like its
Crazy how much I'm in on the long-lost Wednesday small clarification
Did they reconnect before the show or is the show their reconnection
Found each other
Like right before the show and then the show was there like
We're getting out of our normal everyday lives and we're just going to connect to his long-lost a long-lost
Here's a guaranteed castings we're getting through
Twins wins every time
Met like 10 years prior then it might not have as much of the
TV show Prospectors
Wanted to learn
Of course so yeah they were in the last place
Knee injury she's hobbling right
Last second they come in Thursday qualify for the final Great Moments be awesome
Another team gave him a roadblock as long-lost out of here
Route for Lovelace Abby their long-lost twins
I do enjoy travel as well and I appreciate you selling me on the Shelf
I do think there is something slightly
Not great about it as much as they're like jumping
From location to location is not enough time to like really appreciate all of the places they're traveling
Still you could see a lot of great stuff and a lot of
Well the last episode they were in Iceland and they license a very small island
You were there watching it and just going like
Other pictures of us it was
Great
Sick time I've had that experience watch
Drink some things like that go to Hawaii
Jordan today
Talking about December 1st 2022
The day that ye went on it
Listening you know I wrote
Back in the day whenever we had a terrible website me and elfring and drum key and then
Jack Baker Insurance
The suburbs cabin crew
This thing I have this little thing that I called 50 spins
Where I would listen to an album 5th
50 times and then really get into
The each individual tractor you know like that
And I did both Twisted Fantasy and life of Pablo
Who died today and I was really like you know what I'm excited because I know Kanye's on but I don't know what the
Content is should be clear about that
You only know that Kanye was honor ye was on you don't know anything about you turned off the internet
Turn down that I opened the browser at 1 yesterday
It said Kanye was on and I was like goodnight
I'm sorry I interrupted so I'm excited because
Those albums really I think prove to me
That he's coming back
Like this is going to be the interview where he takes it all back he reveals that this is a performance done
Like he's going to do the whole thing for all addresses to Tim pool
Jordan
Hey wait I will see if that's the case
Snot
Before we get into all this business will take a look and say hello to some new walks
The future
Mrs. Alex Jones
Thank you very much next drunken Irishman AKA a perfect tool AKA Grandmaster
Squatchin the sneaky snakes
Think as much juvenile policy walk
Text Nick love Jules and this policy through the internet
Beautiful Monument to that love for Evermore for Evermore all caps
Loki the best spectacle leap up for the 3rd anniversary of his adoption thank you so much
You're now a policy wonk
Very much and also sorry that's late
Nuthatch
Ethically the Goodwin
Carlson
Thank you very much
Thanks for all the fish whistleblowers you are now
Four star don't get mad until you're brilliant someone sodomite
They sent me a bucket of poop
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much thank you very much
Jakob
Some opening thoughts
Sure handsome
Some introductory comments
Come up with anything
It was really difficult to come up with a synthesis or a real point
We say other than
Yeah you showed up
Yeah after storming out of Tim pool show
Temple not agreeing that they means the Jews and here we are
And here we are you know Alex is
Not great
Write editor views true clearly in a subservient state
By gay on one side Nick Fuentes on the other
Great and it's just
I mean it's a Trainwreck this is just bad it's bad on 100 levels
And
One thing that I think I guess if I had to give an introduction it would be that
I've seen a lot of people talking
About this
Giving
Takes
And they're all wrong
They're also all right
Sure is where we existed existed
Lisa's bunch of terrible stuff
Absolutely correct
I also incorrect in as much as theirs
There's also
Things that some people are missing that are really bad as what theirs
Yeah
Then just bad stuff
No I when I open the internet and saw the Kanye was on I stopped and I closed it
Not least of which because
I I just
Can't ever believe that anyone in the media will listen to our how not to cover Alex Jones at
Episodes and so the amount of failure and embarrassment I'm expecting from them
Is stagger
Please into that is there's this like
Even Alex
Sue's like
Put off by 5
There is a little bit of that
But larger picture there's a context in which
He is
Put off and gives push back something that is being missed by a lot of commenting on this
Attention to as we as we go through this
The first
Before we get into anything haha
There's not a contacts
Boy
I'm not on the hole
Juicing
Oh
I'm not on
The whole
Do you think you can see how like he's
Struggling to
Butthead look man
I'm not into the hey hey hey hey
Maybe that's you
But that ain't me
So here we go we start off
I should say just for a little bit of a context
Yeah is wearing a
Full face mask
Like a balaclava but with no eye holes
It's just a black mask
Cloth Mask Jams in a Broadway show
Yeah I guess so
Wholesale never takes it off
I can't see him
It's a little bit off-putting just
Just right out of the gate
Do you think you're having
The way
And the way that we'd
What are business days
Course
He's wearing a full-face cloth mask
It's weird but honestly I don't really care if there's some kind of artistic meaning behind it
There really isn't any point in saying he's going mask off because that masks been off for a while now and I guess he could be
Aiming for something along the lines of like reject
Sing his own celebrity at making himself appear to be an anonymous blank slate
But even if that's the point it's dumb because if you weren't just any random person making the statements he has been no
Any attention
The only reason no one's kicked his ass yet is because he's gay
Ironically his Celebrity Status granted the privilege to say this b******* and people actually pay attention
It seems like his main goal here is to say that we need to send her things on Jesus and that's good well to a point
Disabled people should put Jesus first in their homes is kind of an opinion that doesn't work for everyone but it's not a problem
Being imposed on people
Suggesting that businesses at our country should operate in some religious fashion however is
Antithetical to the United States
And our Constitution that Alex claims to love
That isn't a problem for Nick and yay though
They want to be a part of a Christian fascism that's completely disconnected from the liberalism that value
Things like freedom of religion
Freedom of speech and free association
It's unclear how much Alex is aware of that but the people he's talking
Come to see things
He likes about God but their advocates for a system they would completely destroy all of the things about America that he
He pretends to love
Anyway this is possibly as innocuous
As gay could have started off the interview and already he's saying something pretty f***** up that Alex should push back on
But doesn't
I'll say this
1 not concerned about
Christian fascism so much because I was reminded that
If that were the case then Banks would be able to charge interest so I'm sure that they would kill whomever gotten their way
I'm not concerned there
I'm too
Put a riot
Put yeah Riot okay
I apologize that I didn't press that immediately
I'm going to light amount of sleep but I'm pretty proud of that
Look there's a lot of stuff that comes off as kind of non-sequitur Eve that's just the nature of having yay
Mike this is a little bit of
Michael Jordan
Any look at
And you barely can see a picture of them
What
That's stupid
Phil Knight is the co-founder of Nike
And there's
Tons of pictures of him smiling econfina pictures of him
Dunking from the free throw line but that might just be a skill problem
That that day was
50 years has back probably ways back
So I mean you know Jordan had a Hitler stash so you never know you never know where things are going to land
Honestly
Only because you said that he will hear it and go I will f****** dunk from the free-throw line
Dan Friesen said I couldn't do it
He's crazy
So there's just like I said it goes all over the place
Right out of the gate
Yeah besides to touch on the issue of everybody being very mad
About pedophilia related
Bible app
You shouldn't have phones
In order to serve
The moral compass
Vsf form
Does moral code
Powerful information
Quick question
Christ
Where do you stand on VR
Can I have virtual reality sex is that count
Gray said no
It's in
Deuteronomy
So this
Just a tailgate saying is not a new idea necessarily but it's one that's pretty important to push back on
The first thing that marriage pointing out he's that it means nothing to say that a person in important film is someone's daughter
That's just a way for you to count a rigidly paternalistic and misogynistic view the world into a form Rican percentage
Elizabeth Basin some kind of like
A sincere concern or care for another person
Instead of what it is
A lust for control other over other people's lives
The tell here is that he doesn't say that male actors in pornography are someone's son
That isn't part of this because at its core it's really just
The desire to exert control over women
In 2013 the Journal of sex research published a study titled pornography actresses
Is an assessment of the damaged goods hypothesis
This was a name given to a theory that higher rates of drug abuse childhood abuse and overall psychological problems
Led to women gravitating towards pornographic
Work
The study took the histories of 177 women in adult entertainment
And 177 women not in that field and ultimately concluded that the two groups
Did not have a difference in terms of childhood abuse
What you saying has no connection to reality in the big picture
There are certainly people in pornography where survivors of childhood abuse
That's the truth of people in journalism marketing or any other field
Now if ye cared at all about this issue the angle
Could be taking is to discuss the abuse that happen
Is within the adult industry
But that's a larger issue that I'm not entirely confident I can cover appropriately perhaps another day
And he doesn't seem to care about that all that much at all
The point here is the gay is coming out of the gate hot
With a complaint that feels different than his recent
Peace medical burst
But it's actually not
People like e Michael Jones who Nick Fuentes is a follower of
Have been very public they believe the pornography is a Jewish weapon against Christian Society so this is actually moron
Comfy but it might appear to be
And Alex isn't picking up on these threads or if he is he's not pulling on them at all
Yes just presenting this in a way that mask
Set underlying point
And so
That made it just
It comes off as if he's like oh you are
UCare
No I mean it's easier to look at a p*** industry and be like
All this thing because you can you can process the abuse against women
In a way that allows you to kind of internalized this
Well they may be there kind of where they should be
Point of view
As opposed to dealing with the fact that
All women in all jobs everywhere are subject to violence
Just by virtue of being women
And more than 40% of them will experience it at some point in their life
Regardless of what
You do
Maybe deal with the beat
Big problem
But no I think we should control their ability to do and say any
And I think I think that there is a an element of this that is deaf
Currently rooted in these anti-semitic narratives that people like e Michael Jones
Nick Fuentes perpetuate
But I think there's another thread that relates
Pornography that will
Subaru
Become more and more clear as this interview goes on
It makes me a little bit worried
But hey there's worse things in this interview so hey that's you know
You know
So was going to work clearly talking about Bibles.
You said you're upset he has his phone also has a Bible
Okay good well now I'm feeling better so anyway
Gay besides to read like a verse
Proverbs
Ava
Yeah but I think maybe it's when you can
Can still see through
Bad idea to wear full face mask when you're recording an audio thing a little bit muffled
Understand
For the wages of sin is death
Then shut the fuk up
The wrong way to read it
You get a little sense of little bit of insight about what's going on in this clip stressed
I'm never going to take religious advice for my new convert
To anything
If I need help understanding what a particular holy text says or what a religion is about I'm going to talk to somebody who's studied at
Someone who has a lot of time under their belt
The last person I think is a decent source is someone who's clearly in the grips of a public meltdown who's recently adopted a new
Legend has ended decided they figured it all out and I need to scream about it
Yeah Susie Astic
But maybe not all that helpful man you know there's nothing better than a real brand new Evangelical Christian
They're not annoying at all
Spaghetti is not reading a verse in Proverbs is clearly reading some article about this verse or maybe a blurb
Urban like a study Bible
The verse says quote
There are six things the Lord hates
Seven that are detestable to him
Haughty eyes a lying tongue hands that shed innocent blood a heart that devises Wicked
Scheme
Feet that are quick to rush into evil
A false witness who pours out lies
And a person who stirs up conflict in the
Community
The only thing I think of when I read that verse is how guilty Alex's of so many of those things
He's a complete liar he cracked Wiki
Steam console
Spell faults Whitney
Missing is on trial for his actions do little more than stir up conflict in the community
Constantly
If you were serious about this at all this. Should be him confronting Alex about all this but that's not
This is about
It's
Yeah I don't know
I mean here's my problem
Quite simply
Does any how is it how do you not stop and think
Am I
Am I supposed to believe
That The God Who created the universe
Also waste
His time coming up with individual punishment
For random sins
Do you got all the data God Is A Thousand Years
Well sure but I mean
Like is that cuz he's bored and if you have a board God I want a different God
I do not want to go
Infowars
Borgata
So yeah he goes on to turn into swans and f*** a lady you talked a little bit more about this
Send issue
Sure and I found this entry
Supreme
For whoever
Breaking all
Deep
I can't tell what that point that gay was reading from something so I decided to try and track down the exact phrasing that he was saying
Match one website word-for-word
He's reading from a blog post on a site called equipping Godly women
Website for
Busy Christian moms written by a woman named Brittany Ann
No shade on Britney but this isn't the source you'd pull from if you had a high-minded and serious interest in discussing whether or not God
Believes all sins are equal
From a theological
Perspective
There's honestly pathetic display and it's not because he's someone who's early in their Christianity but it's because it's
Is profoundly on serious about this end is going on a Juno National
Radio show TV show hosted by
A real piece of s***
And a expounding
Yeah
Yeah what a weird thing to do
Yeah what is strange strange thing to do like stepping back from the bonus of it
Decision tree
You know like the number of decisions that leads you to this point
That's a lot of bad words
Like that's at least 40 or 50 bad decisions in a row like you could flip a coin
Somebody convinced him to flip a coin with all decisions and we'll get 50 there better
At least 25 right now the odds work
Call bad decisions
As will continue to be the case
So like I told you
Jay seems pretty matter
And
Is a little illuminate
Media
Graffiti
People reliving the trauma
What
Ferret
What a couple quick points are not the p***
Even if we grant that he was addicted to the stuff that's still his issue
The dude just sounds like an angry loser W anyone else to be responsible for the situation he's in other than himself
The way is talking sound
Mentally abusive and I can totally understand Kim leaving
He's claiming that he has a problem with pornos and his way of
I'm thinking he can deal with it is to exert control over how his wife appears
Publicly
She won't let him control her and thus it's her fault that he can't
Stop with his p*** addiction
Somehow
He's so averse to correctly assigning responsibility that he has to insinuate that Kim was like
Duped into that picture
Baby was a Paste Magazine I believe
Internet article give a s*** about a Kardashian
That's absurd but in order for him to preserve the image of Kim is
A good person and not party
The evil system that he's up against
She has to have her age
Stripped away from her and yeah he has to not have been aware of that photo shoot
Just childish it all around and these are the kinds of issues that could really be helped with therapy
So much of this is ego-based nonsense and unfortunately to confront these kinds of issues you do need to approach them with a little bit
Humility
And that just seems impossible for yeah
I mean it must be tough to have humility when the world was like you're the greatest
Ever
I recognize that that'll make a person go a little bit insane sure when you get away with like
Calling yourself Jesus
People are like
Well
I feel I feel like a maybe culture enabled
It's a little bit
Yeah I can't I can barely take a compliment and that dude was getting your the greatest
Human being alive
No I get it
I get why it's crazy
So
People say
That gay is antisymmetric
No good Nick Fuentes white supremacist
You know it's fun I think the only thing that they really have in common is saying the n-word more than a million times in private
Well and they're Christians
Interesting thought
Go to Jerusalem with weapons
So it's really important to get clear from the jump that using Zionist in any context
That it does
Just mean Jewish
This isn't someone who's making criticisms of the state of Israel for incidents in terms of the treatment of Palestinians
Someone using disingenuous language to make his antisemitism
A little less transparent
Also there's no contradiction between gays positions and Nick's
Nicholson 80-72
He doesn't like non-white people but a black man who is one of the biggest stars in the world who's shouting antisymmetric
S*** every opportunity that isn't a high priority for Nick's hate
He's generally more concerned about immigrants
It's a 3/8 of white people in the disenfranchisement of minority voters
At least
Primary race racism based concerns for him
Yes those are his primary issue
And yes Jesus did go hang out with marginalized folks
Cities time like sex workers and tax collectors
But he didn't go to the tax collector and then spend the rest of his career yelling about
Some idiotic s*** the tax collector told him
There's a little bit of a difference
In terms of the goal of hanging out with creeps
And say that you shouldn't be allowed to do anything that you want and you got tricked into doing
Listen I don't think you have any agency and you should work for me
Right
I guess Gay could go in like evangelize to R Kelly in prison but he just go in like
Brianna Kelly
Yeah yeah
He could try doing that for non famous people what if he did
Button and I'm going to throw this out there
Now
Maybe
Maybe he's very insincere about his
Bulshit
Partly because he is only concerned with other famous people and regular people do not exist to him
Let you know what that may or may not be the case but in terms of an interview like this
I'm going to give it a pass
Because you need frames of reference
Sure
You can only really name
Famous people
But you're probably right
So Alex
Is noticing some of this
Play Jewish talk
Coming up
A little bit early and maybe he's like
I got a I got to cut this off at
Oh my god did he not watch the temple never
Remind of course he did
It was 20 minutes
So
He tries to do a little bit of a his little Nazi deflection
That's fun
Call Zahra position Hitler
Almost
Crash-landed
All broke up
The other one
Air raid
North Africa
Captain
After that
Rounding up people
Tell me I'm a knock
15 minutes
Whatever point x
So this is really sad because I
Alex thinks that this is going to be effective in cutting off the anti-semitic stuff before it even comes up
He really thinks that saying that he almost doesn't exist because of the Nazis and throwing out this Bland ass Soros lies going to set
Table where ye can be presented as somebody who sang controversial things
What is being unfairly smeared by the ADL and Sora
He clearly hasn't been paying close enough attention to what's going on if he thinks
Bad because
Yay doesn't give a s*** about any of that.
Not going to stop him from saying that she's going to say anything signatories work for Hitler and maybe a
Compliment engages eyes at this point
Alex
Like Tim pool before him wants to have his cake and eat it too
He's so used to dealing with a completely different sort of figure because he mostly just swims in the waters of right-wing scam art
Artist tour trying
To use his wife want to grow their own scam
You almost exclusively works with con artists to extreme right-wing politics they want to advance but are also really worried
But doing things
That will hurt their ability to run their stamps
He's used to people who will
Equivocate or will accept his framing of their own f*****-up comment
What Alex is doing here is giving gay a template for how to proceed
He's trying to Usher him into territory of anti-Semitic dialogue that won't get you in trouble because
Alex knows that ye spouting straight-up antisemitism
But that isn't something Alex going to profit off of
Without altering his position in the market
Becoming more like ye would involve scaring off older more Normie members of his audience in without them
The pill sales crater and he can't pay over at on the is expensive as Studio
But
If ye can moderate his position they can make some money together
Eren Yeager
Still be super anti-Semitic
Alex is trying to present him with a way to bacon
Implausible deniability
Seemingly unaware that yeah
Isn't that I any of
The s*** except the Holocaust
We'll get to that a little later of course he denies the Holocaust come on
Is every reason to think that this would work
Yeah is there with Nick
And Alex has had to do this with Nick in the past
I know for a fact
That Alex was fully aware of Nick's white nationalism and Neo-Nazi beliefs as early as CPAC 2020 and
He didn't care
He had me called repeatedly gave him his own channel on Bandit video and went on tour with him on these stop the steel Crusade
And all of that was possible because Nick played along with Alex's moderation language
But the thing is
That Nick was playing along strategic
He was following the exact plan that we heard him layout on our last episode where he wasn't showing his true ideology
Publicly
Because he needed to be a more acceptable face
To closer that the mainstream folks could X
He wanted when the time was right
Alex willingly or not probably willingly fell for that and this is the end result
Of that
These are the fruits
Lighting a hyper coppedge
Charismatic Nazi
Hijack applied for
Yeah yeah I mean let's say that I mean Lindbergh did it so that was good
You know we've had we've got
We've got precedent
Not the first time that somebody who loves Hitler's run for president
I mean what
You know what is this the New York Times in 1936 come on
How bad could it be
Right
So
Is Nick
Milo
And yeah we know that from the Tim pool interview but it turns out this is a deeper crew than we realize
Ali Alexander is
A bit involved in this
In ways that we're not queer
Previously
Was ye wearing a balaclava on January 6th
Does anybody know where ye was
I can't confirm or deny anything but I do know that a SWAT team of Truth
Great
Olly Alexander
Fuentes
SWAT team
Thoughts
Is Battle Ram
The door
And then they come in
Lazarbeam
And have that in
Information
Team
The media
That is a Zionist
Same approach
Well hey don't stay up
Mike Freeman
And I Stay
Specifically and I still not enough
They're still taking it too far
Everyone knows
Of American History X
Text machine
When they put
The guy's head
The curb
The back of it
And now
Kirby
Taking the foot
Call Dad
Ii-i'm sorry what
Things about Hitler
Charge I love everyone
You can
You know
And you can love
The contract
You know what word
But
Invented Highway
Invented the very micro
That I use as a musician
What ever did anything good
And I'm done with the
So yeah I guess Ali is part of the team
And that's a real solid team of losers that yeah he's putting together and
Who
Melly
So you see here ye are in some of the same grievances he aired another appearance isn't even making the same merican History X and
Algae that you made on Tim pool show
So stupid very rudimentary anti-semitic talking points but what bears a little more attention is how Alex's once again
Trying to give gay advice
Inform of form of reframing appointees making to make it plausibly acceptable
To a wider audience
Alex is trying
Give ye the out that he was just saying things in
Free speech and it's not like he's a Nazi or anything and then response
Jason Hitler good bunch of good stuff
Like how he invented things that he totally didn't invent
Alex is not ready for this
That's because
It's supposed to be a full show interview in less than half an hour in
Yeah he has lost his attempt
To make the disgusting antisymmetric should you say more acceptable to the audience
His double down and made his statements were
That would should know that this is now going this is going to be a long day
Yeah Alex is like wait
Hold on
Does ye not understand
That you're supposed to compromise your beliefs for money
I don't understand
Right what's going on here
This is Bonkers
Well you know there's this interesting Dynamic where Alex is like
If you got to compromise these things
And answered of
Negotiate this territory for money
And Nick is like
You got enough you got to compromise
And negotiate your positions in order to
Be able to be worse later
F*** that. These are good now I think I think
Quintus is loving
I would assume so
1 idiots
To ride the coattails of the blackface of white supremacy
+ 2
Who really cares about him
Everybody cares about Yeti so when ye stops he's got a higher-profile
Except here's the problem alright
There is no
Yeti to Hitler pipeline
Sorry I don't care how good Dark Fantasy is
No one
Who's likes
Kanye's music is going to be like well I mean
If this guy likes Hitler
Clearly that's the way to go
No Hitler know he hated Hitler pipeline
I don't know man
Too far I think that
Okay yeah I don't hear hear what I would say
I'm not positive that there is a direct
One and then the other there is a roundabout way that this stuff
Stuff that but yeah is putting forth
Leads down the road towards
See I think that's the interesting thing
Yates not doing the roundabout way that would lead towards Hitler yeah is going straight to Hitler
Bring up and say come on baby this goes back to what he was saying about olly Alexander making him being the swap
He's making is that he's like the
The battering ram that comes in and then Nick is more like a sniper it does the more precise
To work and within that metaphor he can go straight to Hitler and it's still not have the negative
Give effect on that gradual path
Right that the audience is meant to be walked
Now currently I'm just going to throw this out there
I don't feel like Kanye is going to exit
The plan the way they wanted to go
No he's a good EX
Executor of plans right
I would agree with you
The
Essence of that
Makes
What you're saying not really all that comforting trip
Is that the battering ram does not have to be precise
You don't need that person to necessarily be the wreck
Ball is not mint
You know that's really follow the exact plan give me a couple inches off here and there
It all works
It Whatever destruction
And it is going on for someone like me
Well let me throw this out at you
A few inches one way or the other
No problem you're still hitting
The same castle right
But if you go say 1000 ft the wrong direction and join the Nazis
I think that's different
About time will tell
JLo's Hitler
God that
Infinite Highway
Invented
Your phone that I use as a musician
Anything good
And I'm done with
The
Patient
Every human being has
Volume
That they brought to the
Especially Hitler
Emmanuel
You going to do anything to fix Chicago
Chicago
Emmanuel is Rob's brother
Throughout this interview ye will repeatedly say that he wants to take our ease wife into a private room
And help her with her fashion line is very Christian way
A bit like a sexual threat if I'm being honest
Hurry has never been in charge of Chicago and Ron hasn't been very here since 2019
He's the ambassador to Japan
So I guess I'll be a better reference
It's to make but who cares
Also there were 1700
45 gun deaths in all of Illinois last year but I'm not sure where these thousands of black folks dying about
Number Alex
Coming up with a all week
Small point there also
Over 3,000 gun deaths
Florida last year the number in Illinois but seriously Alex never seems to yell at the scientist about that
Seemed strange
It is weird also / 4,100 in Texas
Getting very straight Chicago supposed to be the most dangerous place on Earth
Scared
So we remember from the temple interview that
They really thought it was weird that Rahm Emanuel
And Jared Kushner both exist
And our Jewish that is strange
If you're crazy
He brings his back up because it's such a great point
Thing that I got
Stay with
Rahm Emanuel
Next Obama
There was right there
Text to Trump
What are those
Two people Zionist
I gave it away
Having Tom
Neoliberalism
Yeah you know when it's interesting because
You've been going out to interview Alex Friedman and
What's in pool a morgue
And I always say wow
Don't talk about it
Hypocritical because
In the same interview Tim Poole said
Be so great
For the black vote
We talked about you
Businessman
And somehow
That's a problem
So here's that SWAT team dynamic in full display
Something inflammatory for attention that Nick comes in and talks more calmly about it in a speech pattern of a debate
Great team member given
Giving me a
Credibility to what ye just said
We talked about it last episode but this Jared and Robin thing is f******
Stupid
Just because it blew yeas mind the two Jewish people worked in two separate administrations that doesn't mean it's actually buying
I'm blowing you might just be an idiot
As for what Nick is saying
He's complaining two different things intentionally but optically it work
And part of that is being done at 10 pools
Expense
Tim is stupid and I hate him but
I still don't want to be used as a punching bag by Nazis in order to make their dumb point to look less dumb
Saying that there's such a thing as the black vote is not analogous to saying the Jews run banking
That is a false
He'll be a valid point if you were allowed to talk about the black vote but not allowed to talk about the Jewish vote
That would be where the difference
Would be something that you could point out but that isn't what Niger yay points out because
People talk about the Jewish vote
Really
This is not very subtle sleight-of-hand that Nick is engaging in and he's doing that trick because his point doesn't work
Work without it
He's a dishonest Point designed only to excuse and justify anti-semitic talking points
And someone like Nick is more than willing to
Display this
High school debate level tactic in order to sell his life
And Alex's f***
Because he can't even out arguing High School.
I mean
Personally
My issue here is
Princesses point
Is dumb
And also is essentially
See Kanye can't be racist
Temple is also erase
Or or it would be like
And in order to say that ye is racist you would have to say that thinking
A black the black vote
Is something
Is also race
I guess but
I don't know
It's just awful
Anyway dick is
The worst
In the talmud it says
The Jews have
How to trade Gentile
Differently than they
There's all kinds of examples of
They say that if you ask
Accidentally
Maybe religion is awful
There's nothing even wrong with that
Morally wrong
Play say that for a Judah house
Gentile
Is comprable to be
Bestiality
They say that the semen
A gentile
Watching
Troy Gentile
A Jew is not permitted under the
How much to give
Is a gift
2 Gentile
They're not permitted
They charge each other
But they're encouraged
Discharge Gentile
They say that that's
Paces listen
Well
So you telling me in their holy book
It said it's okay
Pedophile
That's only came from Adam
I'm not on
The shop front
I believe in
Free speech
Okay so Nick is being entirely disingenuous as a relates to the talmood and it's a relationship of Judaism
Plus this is a complete non-sequitur since
Talking about the religion of Judaism they're talking about Jewish people
What's going on
The talmud is a gigantic document which is a running discussion among rabbis between the 3rd and 8th centuries
You can find a whole lot of commentary on the Torah and laws in there a lot of it very affected by the X
When particular texts were written
Yeah it's important to understand that a lot of what's in the text
Is a document of a time and that even within the talmood there's an evolution of thought
Since the point of it's writing into the point of all these things rating Jewish thought has gone through further developments in the same way and
Any religion does
For instance there's a whole lot of s***
In the Bible that would get you the death penalty very few Christians would even consider the
That kind of thing
Problem
Deserving of stoning today
All the stuff
It's also Nick using historically anti-semitic misinterpretations of the tax
Austin order to make accusations
For instance the pedophilia accusation often traces back to this passage in the talmud
Quote if an adult has sex with a girl under the age of 3 it is ignored for it is like putting a finger in
Someone's eye
I eat ears made drip from the eye but there will always be more tears to replace them
So to the hymen of a girl so young my break but will heal
This is a horrific sounding Passage
Because
Neo taken out of context
It appears that when it says it is ignored that means it's okay for an adult to have sex with a child
But that's a fraudulent reading a passage
It's part of the section involving the particular details about a reverse Dowry the amount of man is required to pay woman
In divorce
At the time for Jenna teammate a person's reverse Dowry be higher
So I understood his attacks really written the passage isn't about it
Excuse and pedophilia
It's making a hyper specific point about dowry
This is been used to accuse Jews
Of being pro child molestation by virulent anti-semites for a long time
And Nick is continuing that tradition on Alex's show
Any isn't he hasn't even met with a tiny bit of pushback
Alex isn't equipped to have this conversation at all and he's that with the position of allowing
These two to hijack his show
Or be forced to kick them off
He's not going to do that
So
Long day for Alex
This is what I'm saying
Oh man
Long day
When people bring up holy book
Great it is so great
Because it reminds me
That all of your gods are stew
And actually they're just dudes who are trying to
That's pretty much it
So
Argue all you want
There is a lot
Of that strain
And religion through history
So do you want you may not give a s*** about that but let me ask you this
What do you give a s*** about prop comedy
Depends you know what I like the amazing Johnathan you could consider him a prop, too
Anyways and I think he's probably one of the Great
Hairspray
Answer for the ATL
I'm going to have to listen up
What we did
As we brought Netanyahu
Weather
Netanyahu
What do you have to say
Beignet
I have no idea
Nice work
Eye doctor
I heard about this
I thought you had a funny name
Started funny name
I didn't expect your voice
You sound like that me
So you asked me to pop it it is not he has a net like from a fishing
Fish tank
Emma is a bottle of Yoo-hoo alright
Good
I've seen
I've seen carrot-top come up with worse
Plumbing
Maybe
Carrot Tops works I'm not sure
This is clunky
Not good
Because of you who there's an issue
Right
It's also because you need
Toothache
Connected
Also
Talk about you
Oftentimes they excuse a lot of s*** because he's such a creative genius
Represent to you Netanyahu I mean let's say let's say
Kanye
Never
Been fun
In his entire career
Yes remind me let's just run my people
He's really bad at rapping I don't know if anybody's noticed that before he's not a great Lyricist I've heard he's the greatest rapper
Cruise ever lived
He's one of the greatest producers that ever live but
I wouldn't go so far as to say he was a great rapper I know one guy who disagrees to use names yay
I think he misses the old Kanye as well
So Alex tries to you know make a little bit of a
He keeps trying to equivocate
Non-Stop about like
Hey you do like
You don't really mean this
Come on. Doesn't work
You guys realize that
The British government
Created Hitler
The Miller group
Power
There's something much more
Think about shoes are great people and I understand there's a Jewish Mafia
And there is a much larger eugenics
Scientific
Abortion
Percent of black
Is over
Did the lead lead
Because of your wife
McGill
Shmoney
So we can kill black babies I swear to God it's in my stack
Do this this isn't a sack but it never is
Never a can't find it it has never produced
Because
Yeah is the producer and director today
Sure to get all the stacks of paper off a desk cuz it look too cluttered oh my God
Oh my God
I would've had it right here but
What a delight.
Hi I am I am finding this
To be one of the great train wreck
Oh I forgot it gets so much worse
I think I think the problem that I'm having here is
It is going to much worse
To the point now where it's crossed into something ridiculous pulled out a fishnet exactly and done a little
Elmo voice I mean
In charge
Alex is completely subservient
Well Alex is a strfkr and yeah is probably the biggest stories ever met
I mean
I don't think Rogan gets this kind of treatment because Rogan's not yay
Fair enough Canby Rogan Ali f****** once but he's not gay
VM
Sorry
But still appearances on
Fear Factor are not going to compare to The College Dropout is not going to happen ask you this
What's that radio
Newsradio
Freddie Gray
Pretty great it's better than gold diggers at least okay
So
Alex
Really wants to try to push back
Somehow
While also being
Israel has other than
In the world
Forcibly injecting Josef Mengele
Israel
So if the Jews are the
Hollywood
Work for God
Fears that get Jews persecuted
Right
Makes perfect time
Just like George Soros
Hitler
You just got there
People are not dying in Mass because of covid
Seems it's just a false promise Alex's to point but it's important to recognize a few things that Alex himself says In that clip
These are not things that you're saying
They are at
First Alex says the Jews run Hollywood obviously
Not yay
Arguing that Jews control Alex Jones obviously
Second track the thought he runs out there at the end of the clip
He brings up the
Fake information about Jews dying from the vaccine in Israel
To be a Counterpoint to yeas assertion that Jews run everything
How could they run everything if their own people are dying in Mass from the vaccine in Israel
It makes no sense
Jay responds it's the Zionist
They work for Satan
And Alex's exact
This makes absolutely no sense if you're trying to follow coherent thoughts
Zionism is based around the argument that the Jewish people needed their own Homeland originally in terms of the establishment of
Israel and eventually towards
A movement to develop and build up a
Israel
Apparently according
Gay designers to work receiving and they're killing Jewish people in Israel which runs counter to
You know the essential idea and facilitating point of Zionism
Alex says exactly because he thinks he can work with that
Narrative
About how the Jewish people have to create their own oppression so they can assert their political agenda
Think about
How he said that the ADL calls everyone who loves Freedom Nazi so they can marginalize their political enemy
Alex thinks that this is somehow elevated from gays anti-semitic rhetoric
But in reality he's as deep in the mud as everyone else on the show he's just insisting his clothes
Circline
Really disgraceful and
Yeah bad I mean yeah
I find I find
That
People are allowed
To LARP
As though and I'm supposed to respect their belief system
It insane. I find it insane
They are arguing about
Which of the Elven Lords
Actually serve Sauron
And that's beat that's it that's what they're doing their LARPing their balls off and I'm supposed to pretend to Christianity's real I'm out
Counterpoint to that
You get deeply involved in an argument about which of the Elven Lords
I don't even remember anymore but you know what
There were three Elven Lords
Remember
Sue Alex tries to deflect
Obviously a lot of times whenever anything comes up like accusations of anti-Semitism or
Nazi has tendencies
Hedley tries that but listen
Carefully here to this clip
Yay doesn't care
In America
Charles compilation of him on MPR
I like that
Never killed any juice
How do I get to
So you might hurt their I like Hitler
Thing to understand here and that is what Alex is constantly trying to not push back on the things that you
Are you saying
He's trying to reach
Frame them in a way that they can both make money off of I'm laundry
I'm not interested in that
Constantly
Punctures the balloon
Whenever Alex tries to say something like
Soros rounded up dude
He said I like Hitler
Essentially trying to be like I don't want your position
F*** you what I'm saying
Trying to clean this up
The risk of people following ye into right-wing Supremacy
AZ
Getting lower by the second
In the same way that like that
That so many Star Trek episodes
I like oh
Here's what we got to do all of our weapons
I have no effect on the bad guy what we need to do is take the bad guys energy and redirected towards Eminem
Exactly this is too much
Here's the thing
I think that if you were to
Check in
Non-response
Division places
Like
Nick streaming
Platform
IFixit what you need to frame this or you need to look at the size
It's less necessarily about Direct
Ali Khan gay leading people to this really leading people to this
And
Seeing it as an emboldening and
Enabling point
4 people
Who are already of this
To push things
Further
Alexander's going to come on later and the way he describes it is like breaking the Overton window
And that
He's in and of itself
Probably more dangerous
Then this early
Kanye
Convincing people that look pretty cool
That isn't necessarily the specific
Concern
That you would have from this interview right it is more of these other
Secondary and tertiary effects
But it has
On an already existing problems
And I understand
I understand where you're going with that and it does seem to make sense strategically
However
There's a reason that the Overton window has not broken
There's a reason why we call it moving be Overton window
You can't break the Overton window
Digtriad
They would love to break the Overton window
That's why we are where we are with Republicans over the past
40 years
Slowly moving ship because I can't
Well here's here's what I would suggest maybe it's possible to break the Overton window and then it can
Can be fixed
We'll see
Also
Maybe it wasn't in the best interest
Of some of these Republican folks to break in Overton window maybe shifting it
He's actually more what they would want
To do until maybe it's not proof that it can't
Be broken
It's entirely possible
I am telling you I think they're making a huge mistake
Or at least actually
I think we're going to get off great on this one because they f*****
I'm not quite as Sunny about it as as you
So Alex
But one of his great retreats
In times of trouble is head-butted we're just doing a First Amendment thing
Do that and again he doesn't give us
My mission
Off the 1st
Last 10 years
Evil
Move here is a kid from Poland
They're supposed
Pay reparations for what
People did hundreds of years ago in this country
Isa divide-and-conquer strategy
Are trying to cause division so
I get to that
Yeah I wouldn't either
Alex is trying so f****** hard to sanitize gay here
He's doing literally everything you can engage just doesn't want it
Alex doesn't seem to understand that every time he tries to equivocator OfferUp ways to launder the anti-semitic points gaze making
Yay is going to derail it because he means what he saying
He's not playing games like Alex and all these other f****** idiot friends are
Also hooray for the First Amendment
The government didn't arrest gave her saying any of this s*** in the worst that's going to happen from it is the people are going to say meme
Red deserved things about him
And maybe if you have any sponsors left they could bail on it
None of that violation of free speech at all and if anything
A little bit too much of a free speaking lately
Yeah
Not wise
Not wise choices
Currently made legal
Free to do
Got to stop bad-mouthing the nut
Yeah man they get bad rap they really do I think it's
Time for us to take a long hard look at the Nazis and Andrea Lee
Focus on the
Sure you know like
You got to look at it from a Reich half-full approach
Well I'm not that tired all right
Show over if only
So Alex tries to get real personal hereof, because
He really wants to bring home
Do ye that these are
These are
Had folks man
Wasn't good stuff
Yeah doesn't care
Growing up in the
Richest neighborhood in Dallas
And was a famous German American inventor
The first-generation person who tell me what is little kid on ship
Refrigeration
My grandfather work
About about 8
I just like Detroit
And father
Main reason to join the Army or Corey told me
Watch that man quietly
Urgot power
Thirties
Truck
Coliseum
Kill his relatives in Germany
Blue-eyed German
As you can get is Arnold Schwarzenegger
SS Teutonic as as dramatic
And was my grandfather saw that show
You're opposed to other forces
Other forces in history
Personal experience
What my grandfather
Clyde William Hammond told me that make sense
Not totally
But
Doesn't make sense to me
I'm following
But I was just
Thinking about Satan
They were Hitler
It's not the
Person
It's Satan
Using the people.
But what I'm going to say is
The Jewish media has made us feel like
The Nazis and Hitler have never
Offer anything of value to the world oh oh so the Jewish media has told us not to
Good
Man this is some high-school edgelord s***
Are you coming up with
But isn't that the devil telling it's at telling us not
To believe that Hitler is good
But also isn't heavily possessing the Jewish PDF
In order to say that the devil possessing
Hitler didn't do anything good
Seems against
The devil's purposes
Now I feel like maybe one problem
We're not that we're not getting that right now is one that Kanye may have just
Elucidated very very clearly
Which is that he does not understand a f****** word anyone is saying to him now
Andrew just wants to say follow an argument what are you going to convince him of why would you even are
Argue with Kanye he doesn't understand you
It should be taken seriously
Alex said something
Very simple and Kanye said I literally don't understand you I was thinking about Satan and which point you go
Fiber by on some level I really think that that was a I don't care what
You're saying more than I don't understand I don't understand I cannot follow what you are saying
Let me be
So we had to the introduction of Ali Alexander is part of
The crew
There's another guy
Hoes in the mix
Hey Candace Owens
Ben Shapiro's cardio is
Picking up shackle
From here
Now that's an old one
Back to you Alec
Pol
I agree with ya
For those of you who haven't paid close attention to This Owen Benjamin was a shity pretty racist comedian who made
Became a side member of the intellectual dark web
He was like a in the killa bees to the idw's Wu-Tang he was like streetlight for Killah Priest
Nobody was to Intuit
He also frequently hosted the fourth hours Alex's show it was essentially also one of the killa bees of the info
Screw
It's some point
How to get really into Hitler's so Infowars in the IDW both decided it was no good
For business so
He went off to the woods where he did drunk live streams are you talk about how great the Nazis wear and call himself Big Bear
Things didn't get better from there and just the other day Milo posted a picture of Owen wearing a yellow 24j
Jacket with the caption
Are you getting it yet
If anyone needs it better spelled out the embarrassing loser Nazis who we all decided we didn't want around or Banda
Together and yeah is acting as a battering ram to bring them back into the public eye
It's dangerous it's unacceptable and no matter how many times you may hear someone try to play this off as a joke
It's not
Also owenbenjamin is pain
Painfully not funny
As a matter of research I decided to watch some of his more recent stand-up and the jokes that they gave his reading their about on Par Four
His talent
Baby
The funniest thing that Owen
I never did
Alicia tan Alex
From the woods
To do today
I was wrong about Alex Jones
A bunch of people told me that he was the shell
And I back them and I was like now he's a good guy now tell Michelle
So I apologize
They should have listened you guys
Terrible
Like legitimately
Laughable
He won't even be on that because of the juta
Alex Jones
I even text him today I said
When no one
When no one stood up for you and everyone treated you like garbage
I want on your show
To circle the wagons
When you are flipping out about Rogan I had your back
I said you shouldn't
Your Bridge burning
Business you'll make more money than your fake boner pills
Goodbye
What we should talk no
No no no
You are Ada's
Disgusting
Joe
All the people out there that told me
You know I believe in people until I don't that's just something you have to understand about me
Brother liar
Because of
Like that stats
The fact
He goes all the while
And I'm not even starting a feud with the guy he's so short
Fat
And dumb
And drunk
But like I don't
Can argue
He would call me and ran about Joe Rogan sings his Satanist
He works for the CIA
And I was just did that one time I was having a meal with my family and I said I told my wife I was like
I just have to
Just give me a minute
Is my Friday seems like on hinge
And so I listen to Alex rant on and on and on about Joe Rogan being a Satanist
Because I thought he needed it and then you turned on me
Just because I make fun of juice
So
And I was
I mean you understand Italy
Alex I was very
Decisively standing up for Alex and I apologize you guys were right
All this
Thousands of people that said Alex Jones this shell
He's a sad little man he's a liar
I said no he's not
Agree on things doesn't mean anything
No he's a bad dude
So my bad
Alex hearing on Benjamin's name be brought up should make him a bit worried about ye and Nick
Real intentions
Very least make it clear to him
Do softball attempts to whitewash their bigotry
Reading off Benjamin's jokes
Is in some way a coded Act
That Alex should take to be meaningful
Because he has history
With Owen
And
It's not good I mean
Jesus Christ
These are just
Bad people
You like awning on a level of you know you
You don't try and call P
People evil cuz that dehumanizes
We're going to
There would be some candidates
It's
It's an interesting collection of volatile bad Folk
And I mean
There is
I don't I don't agree with your sort of Sunny disposition towards what the
This portends a little bit
But if I were to take anything as like a
But this might not be the worst thing ever it's that these people particularly the ones that are rallying
Around
AR
Not
People who will put up with each
Assholes
They will come to head
Butt heads with each other
You can't have this kind of a crew
Of people who have it
Live Well documented histories of burning folks
It's not going to work
Yeah I mean a day. Long-term
It does feel
Like
TV
Abdication of
Any and all responsibility from
From Folks at
To deal with this
As also evidence that may be the only people who can kill Nazis
Are are Nazis themselves
You know
A poetic
You think the things are
Sort of
Handled or managed Uno own Benjamin's marginalized and he's off ranting around a campfire drunk in the woods
Sure
Pirulino apparently he's going to do it someone like yeah he does what he's doing in Owen Benjamin's going to come back around
Milo is a roundly canceled and everybody's sick of his b*******
Mystery brand is no longer right
You do you think you're never going to have to
I hear about him and then now yeah brings him along
It's so
He is a resurrector e-power for forgotten Nazi
I'm going to tell you this though I don't think those jokes are going to evolve
Owen Benjamin into the next level
So I'm going to throw that out there I don't think those are bringing the Heat
Well it is original jokes didn't either
It's
It's a tradition for him
So anyway the Nazis are bad man the u.s. is bad to great
People talk about Nazis
Season Hitler
The United States
Put the Japanese in internment
And you can watch
United
States has Instagram selling pornography
Your feet two little kids and they're selling
He might be preoccupied with your own addiction
Instagram is a prostitution
30 days off
G and is the best
Me getting kicked off of Instagram was the best
Best thing that ever happened
Batumi
Call switches something
That
Benjamin
You guys got to pull this up
Dave Chappelle
Is a hack
Any
Yep
I mean I knew Owen use the n-word a lot I didn't know that
Pellet stove
Edward Furlong back in like what was it 93
Owen Benjamin brought together like
Talib Kweli
At a campfire the man
Can you
Oh God stop and think about school then
Stop and think about
The tragedy of Chappelle's block party
The downward trajectory of all of those people
It's all my God they should do like an animal house where are they now thing after
Depresses the only people still good
Are we sure about that I don't even know anymore forever but who knows
I know that's a one of them was named Stickman
No relation to Bayonne
I want to know he's probably still good
I'm not sure
But yeah
I was just trying to think of more fun ways to pretend that
Pigs that repels skull
18 year old comedy Phenom prodigies
Stole everything from Owen Benjamin
All the statues on Chappelle Show really actually
Yeah that's
You know that pimple and it's really offensive now knowing that Owen Benjamin Road at that's kind of that's f***** up
Just think about your pal man
Not only hack
He also doesn't believe in Jesus
And I'm supposed to be
His friend
And is that believe
In Jesus
These are the kind of
Leaders
In front of us
Meanwhile
For Christ
You might have had abortions
Doesn't he need to board it right now
Yeah I agree with ye I think that it's time in America has a
Fearless Visionary leader
Christ
Who wants to bring the future for than Engineering in theology
I think it when you look at the
Directions to wear off or night I said this on my show the other week in the news said
Oh he supports
DeSantis
I said the moderate
Trump
All that the laughter all the sudden
Skylanders
Solve this is rambling nonsense but I want to point out how much of a worm Nick is a smart f****** word
He essentially doesn't speak unless prompted and as soon as ye interrupt him he drops whatever thought he's making
And shuts up
You may notice that he starts just about every sentence with I agree with you
Such a great job of ingratiating yourself here
You should be really worried about that because that is not Nick like
That dude is a leader not a yes-man so if he's a
Luckiest man there's another plan he's working on that you might just be able to land
I will be aware of that is how we're so are you gay
That's if yeah if you if you are letting Nick Fuentes manipulate you your
Dumb
Bien
Well if that's the case is probably quite a few dumb people out there
So Nick
Gets to explaining how Trump and
The scientists are both behold in
Moderate Trump
Versus DeSantis
Any outcome where America orgies
Israel is rather to Santa
Kisses mobbed-up
But Israel and Mossad
Donald Trump
His announcement was written by JC
And Miller who's control by Foreign interests
And they go up against Biden or they go up against Newsome there is exactly zero
Gurochan
Do we get any kind of regime that's going to deliver the real Chainsaw
Say something that's provocative
Mossad
Going to kill you and take the children away from you
Back to you
But I'm I'm definitely overwhelmed here right now infowars.com tomorrow's news today killing it Alex
Killing it
Pretty watching this going
These guys know what's up
Yeah Benjamin's watching music
Call my guy everyone's a rip it off on webtoon
Cialix kind of realizes things are a little bit off track so he tries to bring things to the center but unfortunately
Closer you get to the center
The closer you get
To the net
All I'm trying to get through there is
I dropped the Yahoo
So we didn't have to
Yahoo
So
What you want man
Drill out a fair about that
A big deal
Character
Is this actually here
Bugs
Damn it doesn't
And then you're the bad guy
White people are inherently bad because they're white
7 years
They open the gate shop so what did they expect
What are the express
Jay was going to be a complete hitch summer because
The white people are bad
All right now come on. Okay Bray, my heart if it was genuine right if it turned out to be
It's not alright
If you took the mask off and doom was still alive
That would be
Ultimate
Do MoMA
You mean Emma do not Viktor Vaughn MF Doom
He is in the past year
Yeah
No I don't think I would help
How long to me how it is
We are supposed to have Alex being like I think what the problem is the left
When this is in response to what are we doing
What is is is
Incredibly anti-Semitic
Puppet act with a fishnet
I noticed I guarantee this
Every headline
Every single headline
Is going to be something like Yay loves Hitler some b******* like yeah that's that's what a lot of the responses.
All stupid they're all wrong everybody should be ashamed of themselves
Because what the headline should be
Is yeye brings nut and Yoo-hoo
To make fun of Netanyahu
Right that's it has bad prop work but bad pun work
Yeah totally clearly struggling with sexual problems
It would also kind of explain
40% of everything that he saying
I mean he won't stop
I mean
The issue becomes into there is
It does feel like there's something really really personal and very his problem
That's being
The turtles
Hoisted in projected on somebody else
What time is also a classic
Play popular 80's metal
Trope
That that's used
So like
That that two gets murky if you just trying to like
Oh he has a problem with foreign or something already and I'm reading these articles in my head because
Because I've read so many of them but it's going to be like
On a
Freewheeling interview or on a sometimes disjointed interview
Kanye said that he loves Hitler or something like that instead of being like
This was a ridiculous f****** display of absolute nonsense
With a white supremacist
Just jerking Kanye off while Alex Jones pretends that he's doesn't like
Anti-semitism
But but you know that it is also a strategy of
Folks who have extreme pain
Bands like this to make themselves laugh.
Because it it it softens and dulls the
You know in the same way that even you were kind of
Succumbing to that inasmuch as like you don't think
Like this is going
Going to be like a pipeline
I think that I think the more that you put the the like
This is serious this is a serious interview
Yay
Says he loves Hitler
The more you're doing
For loving Hitler
Beignets
Because ye
Is making it look like loving Hitler turns you into an insane crazy baby
With dancing around with Nets and Yoo-hoo
That is what
Makes looking Hitler
Love look like
They're going to make it look like yeah is a f****** out-and-out Hitler lover wouldn't reality he's absolutely loss
Watch this f****** mind
Unless you believe that this is sort of an act of trolling and pranked
To jam
Your s***
Into a place
And make it like
Viewable by y.
Right and that's what they're doing
Right
And that's what the media is helping them do wraps
So this is a
Yeah yours is still a rapper
And this is kind of an ice wrap Bragg
About anti-semitism
ATL
I will I'm singling out here y'all
We don't know who they are
Nowata High School know what the word antisemitic
Definitely talk about the tail
Yeah AP American history no one knew what the word antisemitic man until they found out yeah
He was doing it in 2022 I put them on the map
Except
Great cool not true but also
Talk that way to think about yourself said he invented anti-semitism
Everybody
So Nick
And then something kind of weird happen
The definition of anti-semitism according to the state department is
And you say Jews have any allegiance to Israel
It's anti-Semitic
If you say the juice
Have any kind of
Conspiratorial influencing America tents
So we're supposed to believe that if ROM
The phone and gets on a call with z
And Ari
And they talk about their jobs
Running Hollywood and running the Obama White House
A conspiracy still
Acknowledge that happens
We're called anti-Semitic
What is the truth
It's a true that they make those calls and it doesn't mean that every Jewish person
But she was like
Laura Loomer
Also it's like basically hide in the under
Their floorboards right now version
Of the Holocaust
Because there's Jewish people that saw
Call Ira
I was treated and they're like
This guy
Jeff cavins
Opinion
Add calls
Any harm
I didn't harm anyone
I know I spelled it wrong
Because I was drinking alcohol and
Drink right
That's why Elvis died
Basically
Do you know about our getting sued
But if you smell
Save it some Jewish people have a support for an even $0.02 of allegiance to Israel
It is anti-Semitic the way
People like Nick
Incest that all people who are Jewish should be suspected of having dual Allegiance and that their loyalties aren't with the country they live in
And of which they are acidic
Who's the classic Trope that's been used to alienating ostracize Jews historically and Nick understand
And that this game here is weak Nick is the one who brought up the Japanese internment camp
His example of a conspiracy within the Emmanuel family is equally stupid
Which is what he was bringing up there
Ari is a powerful figure in the entertainment industry but that's not the same thing as running Hollywood
Lincoln saying that because he's a Jewish person in this position of influence where is he wouldn't
Say the same of a non-jewish person with a similar level of Pot Saint they run Hollywood
Zeke Emanuel wasn't just part of the
Obama tea
He was the chief of the bioethics Department of the NIH from 1998 to 2010
And Rob was Obama's Chief of Staff for about a year-and-a-half
Just after he was elected
The three of them are
Successful people and are related but Nick has no proof that they called each other and coordinated about how they would control politics
Hollywood
That's
Oculus and it's patently anti-semitic as a suggestion
Anime
But that's where it makes mine goes and how it works
Yeah I mean
By his own
Reasoning
If there were three white brothers
Doing that then it would be a white people conspiracy and that means that all white people are evil or Van Gogh
Means it is 100% okay for what
To do a conspiracy
I want hundred percent evil for Jewish
See
That's exactly really cool how Alex and ye can Bond over how they did reprehensible things that cost them north of
A billion dollars because they were both drunk
Cool guys to look up to all in all I would say
They're cool cool cool drunk guys I find it I find it hard to
To think of a better
Stop drinking
Message
Kanye at Alex Jones
Collectively lost several billion dollars all due to drinking and you know what super cool about it
Because it's so cool the way that both of them responded to it by not learning a lesson and continuing to do this
Same thing
That's really cool. I think the Dare program when I was growing up really lost it
Good example
You know they they they just never had a chance they were dead in infancy
If they were ahead of their time
If only if only
So yeah Laura Loomer ends up calling in
And
She is just chaos
Talking on a speaker phone because he doesn't want to put in earbuds
Maryville they'll get this Heather the people control your ears
Shake It Off
Because of their religion
Are there
George Soros can come to Christ is a possibility that he can convert
George Soros
Anyone.
Lorelei what's up
This is Laura Loomer
I'm not busy
She called me because she had some concerns about Milo
Running my camp
Can we we got Laurel a number
Port Huron via speakerphone
A phone right now
I can't do a video right now
Is good show
Uno
It's really
It's really just smooth
Produce if you are on the fence about either Hitler or Infowars
This show will really push it towards the pro in both directions
Ghetto I do like that moment that Alex has
How does she have your number
What the f*** is going on here
The reason is because she had contacted him about a concern about Milo
She doesn't trust me
That guy will stab you in the back
Which is completely different from the way I will stab you in the ribs
Nice guy
They're all like
Wrestling tag team
You know they're all like alright we understand that they're eventually going to have to fight each other
This is
Best setting up
An end to our friendship
So she's going to call back and eventually they don't get her on
Skype or anything it's bugging on speakerphone
Yeah he has some other things you want to talk about particularly a prayer that he's mad about
Fun
Let's remove this whole conversation of
Morality
Telescope
List
Stick to the Bible say
Either Jesus said so
Or Jesus said no
You dropped this
Or did you said go
ISO
Said whoa
Profound
Made me
Asurion
What are the album this year
Jesus said so
Or Jesus said no cuz we want to bring in our creative Direction in our opinion
And our moral compass
Forget the words moral compass is it in the Bible
What did the red letter say they didn't have to say about it
And then we make our decisions off of that
And then I also
Let's pray directly to God
And I took it out
And my family member didn't say anything
And he said here are
And
I know I know
Are you set me up
Why is my prayer
Thank you for your prayers
Yeah those pretty good prayer
Yay
Even your yay
You can't stand being upstaged at Affleck
Quiet prayer event how is he mad at a prayer
If the point of the prayers. Performative he is literally disiz 8mp makes no sense about it
But he's a he's young and his Christianity is he said
Jesus Walks came out
50 years ago
He's really talked a lot about Jesus
To be samples that he's used his entire career oriented
I had that impression of him it's not weird just knowing it sort of on a surface level.
Right you know the Jesus how I need Jesus
Crown of Thorns himself though so maybe he thought he was
Jesus at that
Aziz's
Anyway
Goes on to have a
Very long prayer
And I'm not going to make us listen to all of it but I do like Alex's response afterwards
Thank you for blessing
Bottom of our feet and everywhere in between
The first
What we need
That you have for Elijah we got
In Jesus name amen
Uncensored with
Yay
Steer-In
Insane asylum world
Does the whole world
This is this is Twilight Zone 2.0
Alex has been defeated
Control over what's going to happen I'm Alex Jones
Lost
Awesome totally lost
I've tried a few things I have not been successful in sanitizing this gentleman here
And f*** it crazy world oh no yay I did not mean you're crazy everyone's crazy
But yeah you are especially crazy you crazy
Oh my God
I don't know if I've ever seen Alex of that like
Sort of
Impotent
Yeah that was really really a bummer it reminded me
Of a man
Who
Suddenly discovered there were no Tools in his toolbox done after only two or three tulsi's tools work
So well when I'm alone in a secular talking to Liars I should have bought more tools
You talkin to people who are motivated only by Griff
I'm out of tools
Very quick
Decides to go to is playing more special reports
Let's take up some of this time
They play a special report about the ballinciaga
Cuz apparently there's a new pedophilia scandal
I guess
I bounced iago's like a like a brand fashion brand of some
I believe
You guys handle it I guess it's like Wayfair but with bags
Sure
I don't know whatever
There's a Reece report one of Reese's Pieces love me a good Reese's piece
About
Ballinciaga
Is wild
Why is this playing
The same style Bears War featured in one of their last Runway shows which was
Agatha brand were disgusting
But who opened for the show
Yeah Kanye West
Frankie Ayers everybody knows that
I'm sure he's been through alot I feel for him but let's keep our eyes open yeah
And yet
The majority of us still seem to obsess
Over them
Like royalty
You you sound like my God very weird choice
I genuinely don't know
I just do either I don't know where I'm at I don't know where we live right I remember when I was young
That I knew all of this wouldn't happen
That's all I remember being young I knew
Play My Soul
There is no way that all of what happened after I grew up
What happened
Yeah there's a lot of surprises that have happened in
All of the surprise I will say it is a small miracle and a giant piece of good luck that ye wasn't watching that special
Report cuz I should have got
F****** real quick I was watching at this point on Nick streaming site cuz he has
Hasn't Alex Jones channel on there
So they play the show
Man the chat was
Furious of course
They thought this was a
Please set up to make antisemitism look bad
And he's spewing anti-Semitism and then they play a special report
Revealing ye himself is also a pedophile
Evil billionaire that was
Yeah that was there to stab in the back
That thing that's very funny
Delightful
So he had ye on the whole goal was to talk about
The dinner with Trump I did not happen because
Who knows what other podcast dinner with Tim
Cool
Empty the pool drain in the pool
I'm too tired
But some of that conversation gets to happen here and Nick
Has a little bit of a story
About how
It people thought it was a setup
Trump gave kind of
The standard black voter page
She talked about
To use the Opera
Opportunity zones things like that
And then it turned out that
Ye had asked
Only sent a text
Message to a lawyer
Cher
And forward him some Intel that Karen gave to us
That's about how we work
Going to handle the Trump meeting
How to read his body language
The kinds of things that
Maybe we should avoid
Add that to a lawyer
Then in the middle of the dinner
Apparently called
Trump
To say hey
Karen journos involved
Setup you guys are being setup right now
Based on a misunderstanding
Do you mind if I sit
Yes you mind
Nick Labonte
So he was texting I don't mind I don't mind any name
Yeah no s*** buddy
Is a fun naughty Comedy of Errors Nick is describing but there's some people who have been very adamant that
Mix version of the story is
Come true
Karen Giordano is a former Trump aide who was wrangled into attending the dinner by Milo and they knew each other but
Because Giorno had helped with loomer's failed run for Connor
Apparently Accord
Burlington Nick she gave some advice
It's about how to handle Trump which ye meant to text
But accidentally texted texted to Nick Gravante
Event text
Did Trump to let him know that it was a setup apparently because your nose out for revenge or something
The problem is that to Gravante has been
Very clear that he didn't tell Trump s*** and Nick has no evidence that this happen
And at all
But that doesn't mean that the dinner wasn't
Gerardo said she said quote
Milo said that he arranged the dinner just to make Trump's life miserable
He was hoping that news of the dinner would leak and Trump would miss handle it
Nick Fuentes echoed that sentiment and he said I hate to say it but the chickens are coming home to roost
Also Milo himself told NBC quote I wanted to show Trump the kind of talent he's missing out
By allowing his terrible handlers to dictate who we can and can't hang out with
Check
I also wanted to send a message to Trump that he has systematically repeatedly neglected ignored abused the people who
You love him the most
The people who put him in office and that kind of behavior comes back to bite you in the end
I'm here is don't ever associate with any of these people it will end up turning bad at some point they don't have any shame
I mean
Hugh
How is it
Possible
That that is not
Clear evidence
It's the Trump should not be allowed anywhere near
Power every
He got out maneuvered by Nick
Quintus and Milo yiannopoulos
He is
So f****** stupid
He walked into a twenty-year-old assholes trap
What a f****** moron
Anyways
Who's going to win
Sunway knickers into white supremacist
Do you know that
You think whites propellers.
Catholic
And so I believe that
Well I believe they were all children of God and so I think that black-white
Brad Brown whatever we are at Ross
Casper created by God
I do believe that
There are races
People that are white
People there are
Hispanic
I'm in at least
Differences mean
Something to people they mean things to each other
We can't get along that doesn't mean
How to solve
The government the economy
Population
They want a global government
They want a globalized economy
Free trade
Exactly end and the papa
Cancel that in
50 100 years
There are no.
Nations there's no distinct
The slave class
Undifferentiated
That's what they want
Future president
Can you talk with you right
Not a chance
Now he's not old enough listen I will say this right now I'm putting this
Down I don't care about morality if Nick Fuentes is elected I will kill him
I will absolutely kill Nick Fuentes if he is elected
God
And I don't care I'll do my time
I'll do my time forever I'm fine with it
But I will not let this world
Be run by mcfucking
I've got is my witness you're speaking in a quite a hypothetical and
You know that is a pathetic
I think it will come to this because by the time takes old enough to run I don't think
Think there will be a president
I have collapsed into something or other
I mean
Look there is a Savvy that Nick has that
I think that no matter how bad any of this stuff get
Get with ye
I don't think that is
It's going to be a problem for him
Keeping come out the other side completely fine
Let people like Ali Alexander Milo and Owen Benjamin return back to their
Obscurity
Nick
Has an ability to explain the games that he's involved in any way that doesn't
Hurt his ability to play though it makes people think they're playing it with
Exactly and there is a way that on the other side of this Nick can say
I am in the interest of my interest
To advance Christian
Principles or whatever
6 star it was something that
Survivability to spread the message of God and Jesus
Hitler
He's going to be fine when the white supremacist are like all but you worked with Kanye we like yeah I told you I was using
Kanye at the black face of white supremacy
Told him
I told everybody what I was doing I'm literally the smartest person in the room because I surround myself
With the dumbest people on the planet really to come to fruition
And that's the part that's a particularly troubling about him
So
Alex of course it still
Ultimatum
Trump didn't live up to it but Alex decided
You still in the business of supporting him
I am does heat rise
Not even do a great job
You can spare though for Trump that is a political attack
Represent
Using you guys
Asthma attack
They're using us
This guy we never heard of
DeSantis
Like
DeSantis is going to play by the book
The thing about Trump
This guy
One of the best presidents we have his top five president
He's right there
Would Ronald Reagan by Milo
The president
The Jewish media
Attacked him
They were mad because he was
Actually working
For the country this meeting
To try
She said he's not allowed to meet with
This is a war
Who are you to stay who the president can meet with
So I mean you know that he's just throwing around very liberally terms like the Jewish media
Over
It's it's
Alex doesn't
Really
Even
Take any
It is a bad night
Throwing around the Jewish media
That's pretty bad
Surveys do the terrible job
Again
It's not in his Interest really to have a fight or an argument about
It is in his interest to try and sanitize things as best
Does he try to cover his ass a little bit in case
There's something that's particularly bad as I got
Gabby involved
Like
You know saying the Nazis were great
I knew this guy who invented air conditioning
Nazis are not good
Then so he can try to look at a little bit of that
Dirt off him
It's
It's not effective
It's transparent
But
You just allows this
Stand up live
Yeah and again this is too easy
These people are stupid like I mean honestly Alex could
Alex just be like
Oh you know what you're right about the Jewish media
Plano
Who exactly is the Jewish. Like give me Outlets give me names who should we avoid am I the Jewish meat
Oh you're just saying f****** everybody cuz you're an idiot thank you
Moving on
I think Alex doesn't want to ask for specifics because
He might be a little worried that Nick would have them
How do you spell maybe
But since Nick Nick take this one
When you're in deep water
So JFK RFK
Killed by Israel
Middle East peace
You have to go to Israel because Israel is the one who has been bombing
Syria
Israel's the one that's
Exactly and that's why they killed JFK and RFK was be
Because
They were trying to get their wmd program off the ground
Operation
Nepal
It was Jack Kennedy that wanted
Iaea
That's one of the reasons we need to stay right now
Aliana
My both my parents were
Educators right
And we're here as the educator
No
So there's a problem with being the king of conspiracies and actually not really knowing or caring about any of them
It comes in with his explanation for why JFK and RFK were killed in Alex knows deep down
He doesn't actually know enough to argue with him so he has to submit and probably is real
Anyone who listens to Alex's show and pays attention to him and thinks the ship means anything should be offended by that
Spineless response
Alex has been very clear that his position is the JFK was assassinated because he was going to dissolve the CIA
Take down the Federal Reserve
Because he didn't
Ensign onto operation Northwoods
At least that's his position when there's no one else there to challenge him
Whatever anyone else is very getsway Lucerne and pretty much any theories totally probably a big part of this
Such a f****** fraud has any audience retention is evidence that his listeners aren't actually list
It's kind of sad
Times ad
Yeah you know
One thing that occurs to me
I
Think
Now
None of us should really be surprised that JFK was assassinated
Because
There were so many reasons to assassinate
You know Well everybody's got
So many readers everybody's got their own reason
This is a man who is begging for assassination prey cracked
But they're all the stuff we did it cost is assassin
But those theories about 50 years to come together like it's not like
The day after if all of these theories were robustly there
Like
Yeah Amy big
Major world event you can come up with a hundred different
Explanation
Why something happened
So gay is an educator
I don't see how that
Possible no
But Alex should be a little bit he should take note
S*** like this and realize like
This is ideological
This is not one of your scam but
Playing along with the six
Like celebrities Viper trying to get media
We're using our position putting our finances
Truth out loud
And say this is Infowars right
Warriors
On both sides you and you
When is Battle for long-time Ally
And we just got to salute you as a Christian
American because you take away
Terminator
Happening right now
I think Alex generally likes to hear stuff like that but maybe today
But not but not the proudest moment
No
Hey Alex thanks for walking so I could run and say that Hitler was cool and I like Nazis.
The Jewish media is run amok
It's real cool that you guys are
Get to act like
I just have
Sit here and why
Fun fun to get credit for enabling this b*******
So Alex suggests Taylor
We've all eaten
Naked
What will take braces
And weird
Jewish
Banks
So I want to watch my mail
I just repo statement but I get this evil next to.
Oh my goodness
You can see again Alex's knee-jerk reaction to Yeasayer saying something like the Jewish Banks froze my account
Rattle off his stock line about how the left says white people are bad
Is it so bad when CNN's as white people are evil
You don't even think
This is pure anti-Semitism deflection reflex
Again yeah he doesn't care
He's there to demonize Jewish people support Nazis and pump up Hitler
That's what his entire media campaign is more less about and he is not
Interested in watering that down
Like he said in that last clip this isn't about clout for him this is an ideological thing that he believes himself to be a teacher
Teacher about so no matter how many times Alex tries to both sides of this
It's going to fail
Really sad any kind of reveals have few tricks Alex really has are you were saying hello
Deal any tools
Other couple of go to lines that usually work
Like when he's alone Orbeez drunkenly yelling at people on the street
It doesn't really work when you're talkin
Going to an actual bigger
You don't care
They're not impressed by your stupid s***
So this next clip actually really highlights this
This dichotomy between the two of them
Evil next 2.
Oh my goodness
You just because you don't like one group doesn't mean
What
Oh man well I have to disagree with that
I don't like you either
I'm a crazy when they were all crazy
Ann & Hope hours
Coming down
This is absolutely lick
Lit-lit lit-lit lit-lit
Number one show in the world right now everybody
Is wearing a facemask Saint ridiculously anti-semitic s*** and reject
Acting every Lifeline Alex tries to throw them
He is not interested in maintaining an image or being popular
Conversely Alex is forcing himself to laugh at yazz dumb s***
Essentially begging him to just soft in this a little bit
And celebrating how many viewers have tuned in
That's what's important
To Alex
There are tons of people watching so who cares about the message is being sent what kind of harm is being done yet
If we can get more viewers by slandering the parents of murdered children
The ends justify the means
If we can get more eyes on the show by giving an unhinged bigger than his baby racist friend 3 hours on air to say whatever they want
Well you get the Olympus
F****** pushback imaginable
If it's going to sell a few more pills let it rip man
Let it go this is just a spectacle it's so
It's cynical that mean yeah I thought I thought that imposing was a freak show this is an absolute f******
Nightmare this is addictive
TLC for flux and I understand that we're a ways into our episode here
But it gets worse
This isn't as bad as it gets
This is kind of small potatoes in many ways
So
Laura Loomer called earlier
And they they decided they needed to get her back and so she calls him it's really funny because
Honestly it just seems like she's she's in a position where she's like
Hey look
All you people have been cancelled
I have to
Call Laura Loomer
Laura Loomer on the way she was originally going to be on earlier
Yeah your house Michelle go ahead
Laura
Did you guys hear Laura on the mic
What they're doing is they're talking to her after I told him 45 minutes
Can you guys hear her
Laura Statham
Go ahead
Sounds outside
Speakerphone go ahead
This is a little bit desperate
This is sad
This is this is you know I think I've mentioned an episode a while back
I think I said this but
This is the most
Dark version of the Chris gethard show exactly like the Diddy episode but evil
Yeah there is something to that there's sort of clunky call in
Is Nick is a human fish
It's
Yeah I don't like thinking about that way but yeah I mean it is Public Access
Henry Lisa it's uncontrolled chaos it's it's bananas
Is this is bananas
So
You know who cares about Laura Loomer butt
He even loves anus
What are the ways that he's trying to present this
A whole thing about loving Nazis involving Hitler is I got
The Zionist
Answered
Bright beats planes this
A hierarchical power structure
Chuck-E-Cheese
I love
Visayan
I love the people
That
That blocks
Bank account because God runs the world and uses everyone
There's a power structure under
The god that starts
With the thousand-year-old families
Medicis
Sorry what now
The Vatican
Which is
In bloodline
Hi to Peter. Paul
Financial Group
BlackRock
Vanguard
To the government
When we can go until
Putin territory
Screen to get pass
And we're just breaking down
How you doing Ari
Tips are really just sort of
Uno talk about Ari Emanuel a lot may have just played too much Assassin's Creed
I think he's just
Kind of gone a little bit too far with the whole Templars assassin between
Should be the council 300 Jewish Elders or whatever earlier how does it affect the power structure
No idea also why is Rahm Emanuel considered part of Hollywood
I mean I think probably because
Yay is
Is incapable of thinking clearly
He doesn't actually understand what he saying
Let alone
Truly believe what it is let me give you another Siri
Let me give you a round Manuel's Jewish
So Alex has an idea for a new political party
First Amendment
Bill of Rights
Party
Party line
Pro 2 self-defense
We fix this
What the word of Christ
The first book
Of Moses called Genesis
In the beginning
God created the heavens and the Earth
The Earth was without form
And void
And darkness
What's on the
Of the deep
And a spirit
Of God
Was hovering over
The face
Of the water
That's where we stopped
And I know that
Oh okay total Prometheus stole
Yeah just took out his Bible and started on page one
That's a good way to start I would recommend he continue to read the whole thing
I really kind of put
Together what it is you think of here is my political party page 1 verse 1
Beginning was the word lol
Nick has another idea for a party
Yeah I want to jump in and
And say that I agree I think though that it's
It's not so much about the Bill of Rights
I think it's really more about
Kanye West
Christian
Party chicks off Kanye West
Brighton and biggest to the nature of
Judaism
Which is the fact that
Jews do not believe the Christ
Who's the son of God and is back through the only group
Muslim
Buddhist Hindu see Jesus as a
Spiritual figure
Jews ride in their talmud
Play Christ is burning in hell
They they don't like the cross
He's not really into
It's not the same thing though because the kind of Judaism that we have now is not of the Old Testament itself the rabbinical oral tradition
So these people are worth
Oh
This is a deeply anti-semitic statements Nick is making and Alex's just going to go along with it offering up the people just read the town
Download for themselves
This is b******* and Alex's not pushing back in this interview at all he's
He's fully engaged
It's just kind of hard to see that at times because his role isn't necessarily to say the same things as gay and Nick
Needs to give an ineffectual pushback and try to sanitize the things they're saying so people don't see them for what they ask
We are
There is definitely been tensions between Jewish groups
Some Christian groups historically but the stuff in the talmood that Nick
Talkin about
Is an old anti-Semitic
Smear
Emma told me that their references to a magician named Balaam who's
Remembered for trying to curse Jewish people
These references are understandably not pause
There were theories at point that history that the mentions of Balaam were coded references to
Did Jesus but these theories have been debunked
Yet they are still perpetuated and asserted by anti-semites like Nick
In order to incite hatred towards
The Jews
In Christian
Here's a passage about Jesus from the table
The intent of the creator of the world is not within the power of man to comprehend for his ways are not our ways
Nor are his thoughts are thought
Ultimately all the Deeds of Jesus of Nazareth
Nazareth will only serve to prepare the way for mesyac
Coming
I am the Improvement of the entire world motivating the Nations to serve God together
Nick is referencing passages that were about Balaam
Like this one
Quote the Disciples of Balaam the wicked inherit gehenna
And descend into the nethermost pit
Gangnam is a Subway
Synonymous or analogous to hell
InnoTab
He is passing along an old 80's Medics mirror and Alex's literally no ability or interest to engage with what he's doing
Essentially allowing this later to be legitimized
In the eyes of the audience
They should read it for themselves
Because Jesus was trying to take over the whole thing
Yeah I mean it you know now that I know that
What they're really mad at is a magician
I guess I got to agree with them
You know because
What says it's worth murdering an entire race of people more than they made fun of a magician
In the magician from what I understand is pretty mean to them too soon as much of a dick
Anyway
Yay gets to gallon
I'm complaining about being on drink champ
Spirit that podcast we said about JJ's Medics and
You know God loves me so much
He loves me so much right
Ben
I go to drink Champs and I'm drinking
In the Bible
Says King don't drink
Bright
Milo and I'm not
Singing incorrect
Perfect English
But
The Bible says
Kingdom
And I'm drinking
And I'm smoking
I'm tired of these
Fed
Taking that they gangster
Wenona High School Meek Mill
Wheaton High School Puff Daddy
And everyone thinks that there's so much more gangster like they got me in some way
Meek Mill went to jail
Staying at
Black Sheep
Please God
It wasn't the scientist it wasn't the bank's it's God sent me back for the stock
The fact that
I still had 400 million + 4
Yeah man if Alex actually believes that what ye is going through as a jewel Blake trial that he must think that God wants gator
Maybe really anti-semitic and a piece of s***
And the devil is trying to tempt him to cut it out
Or maybe the devil trying to tempt him into finishing thoughts
What if
What if this is a new job
But instead of an uplift
Story it's the one where Jobe loses
Sinners like
Dude you're right I will hate the Jews
This devil guy is dope
Maybe he met Joe blue
Morva Joe Blues
It's babe
And ye stole or I'm sorry Arrested Development stole mr. banana grabber
Yeah some more talk about
Kanye in his
Drink Champs. And such
Sure he ended up serving the devil
You know what's odd
Is there's this thing that Jesus said
Blow your mind
So he was talking about how if you look out and you see somebody with like a big old Timber
We're like a little
A little stick in there I you know
You know you should
You should worry about the timber in your own f****** I
Before you start causing problems for other people
Maybe shut the f****** about other people
He did I don't think he was serving the devil
And now user got another rapacity.
You serving the devil
My wife
Right
Family
Caprice right in the middle of that home
And I didn't have the say-so over the content that my kids watch and what they
And what they wore where they went to
I was frustrated and I let the devil
Next thing you know
I'm at I'm at New Year's Eve party
Haven't
I'm the God was
Mad at me he said
I gave you
Skill set
You like Moses you say Caesars life in battle
You know
But your leader gay
And you're down there you're not representing me
Drinking
You're having sex
And you know what he he waited on me he let me go
You know
8 months into the year
But it was until I bragged about
Serving
With the action
Set you back now
I set you straight
And then
Moving my school
Removing the donda theology
Engineering University
Church
And we were there talking with the pastor
And then a homeless gentleman came in
Greatest theology
And I haven't come to a Bible study
The walk to the house I don't like
To call it a campaign
I want you to remind me what I'm saying
Care about the website I care about Jesus Christ and people knowing that
Only place
The phone is in the Bible
Website is the Bible
Cozy. LOL
Nick and the f****** hell
Mekanix a little bit more interested in that you should also go to
Little bit
It's all over the place or something
Because he had threesomes
And then
He met a homeless guy
We never get the end of the story
By the way Alex does not remind him but
Alex was good if I recall correctly first Kanye turned him away
And then it turned out that he was a witch so he cursed him have to live in the castle for the rest of his life
Until the flower finally will
Right yeah you told me on the phone I don't need to hear this again that makes me wonder if it's like a really fun
F***** up story I'm not going I know ever microwave
I just want to remind people that when Kanye says he hurt God
That is not metaphoric
He'd literally heard that
I'm not joking that is not slight I've heard God before
Because bipolar will do that s*** to you
Auditory hallucination hell yeah baby
So
Pornobae
Evil
According to guide
Every form
Ponography
Is only
Only
10 years away from PETA
I feel you next to me
Pornography if you're watching a woman
Have sex
On camera
He's reliving the
The trauma
Of being molested
Greater majority
Women that
End up being
Stripper is process
Or
Sonographer
The trauma
Experience
Experiencing pedophilia but
Sex
Is illegal drugs
Push to destroy
Humanity
If you drive down the
Street in California
They will be pushing
Strip clubs
They're pushing alcohol
Sex
This is
Do for people that have
This moral code
Pedophilia but no moral code about
Strip clubs in Agra
Sex industry
It's not what
The Bible says
As the Bible says
That all of that is
Jesus said
So or Jesus said no
I need to over-analyze things but some kind of an issue with boar
He keeps bringing it up he said that it played a role in destroying his marriage and overall it really seems like sex is a big problem
His discussion of working for Satan involved
Threesomes which seems really tame for the devil
If I had to guess I would assume that there's a bit of a problem when it comes
Impulse control and that it expresses itself through sex and pornography
Instead of dealing with that going to therapy he's decided to internalize the Neo-Nazi argument to pornography is
The weapon the Jews use
The destroy Society
High-minded idea he's presenting it as a concern
4 people engaged in sex work
It's all really stupid but it kind of feels in line with the trend of the things he's saying
But it's no coincidence that he's fallen in with Milo Nick and Owen Benjamin all three of them are Catholic Bash
Pissed and followers of e Michael Jones
Who is one of the most
High-profile proponents of the Jews attack Society with pornography narrative
I got all just
15 more with the
Pathan trendty has towards
Just being a b c here's the thing
Well you're not understanding
Is that sex workers
Again
Like
All women
Have experience
Trauma the hands of men
So
What we need to do is take away their independent source of income
That allows them to exist in their own lives with their own control over themselves
And then dominate them forever with the Bible
Yeah it does seem to have
A bit of
Prescriptive
Ideas about how things should go that involve
Control
He wants to control everything that his family does
Normal for
So they're getting the ballinciaga
Stuff
Obviously
It's it's a big issue because ye was involved with them
Another the center of this
Pizzagate
4.0 or whatever we're at now
Whatever and
Fraction
Balenciaga's
I'm just overall a lot of fashion brand
Now the stuff come out
Everyone doesn't start you know I'm friends
The Hat
Designer
I believe
Is that
Set up I think it was a hit job
And now all the sudden
Everyone is so outraged and focus on Balenciaga
But then
Still avoiding our kids
We're still fornicate
We're still
We're still killing each other we're still listen to music that
Promote
But we don't we don't wear Balenciaga
What are you doing you're throwing stones all by God
We just
We just cheated on our wives
We just we just fornicated
We just had threesomes
We just bought some sex on Instagram
You don't like Balenciaga
What's right now
Shut up
G is about prostitution
Is it bad as a pedophile
Everyone shut up
I'm listening
Throw this out there it might be
Somewhat
Uncrate
Batman maybe my interpretation of the Bible is wrong
Alright
But
He seems
Very interested in his own problem
And very dismissive towards everyone else's thoughts and
Well they should just shut up
That is a good point I hadn't considered that before
Instagram is basically prostitution because people posts
Sexual images
People in swimsuits and what have you
My wife shows me pictures of like little clips
Stuff like
This place has Fox
They race
So cute they make little laughing oh my God it's
Securus knob anyways
Pornographers pedophilia
Call Nelly
We get a little bit of a talk about something else a different issue
The namely Ukraine
What's on your radar because there's a lot
What is a Bitcoin
Well yeah in terms of Ukraine and Russia and released
Seen so much of that in the news I'm of course pro-putin
I'm very pro-russia
Yeah we know we know
NFL
Not not not quite a surprise
Comically stupid
Dunkirk
And like I said
Owen Shroyer shows up
And so insightful
Fired black lives matter flag
He's going to be so inside
I'll hold my questions
Transmission right now
And there's a lot of people sharing their opinions on the internet with
This right now
You know I do want to take a step back
Round with what we're doing here today trying to balance
Fun and Furious
Because we are serious people have serious missions and goals
And when I see the response on the internet
From the haters in the people getting angry today
I'm just
A little perturbed
Speak
Let the man speak you may not agree with what he has to say
Why don't you want him to speak I don't get it
Same thing with Alex
Why don't you want Alex
Speak what is wrong with you
What the f*** is even saying
Like first of all this shows neither funny nor Siri
It's complete pilot bulshit that's intended to mainstream and sanitized incredibly dangerous narratives for the sake of getting Alex more viewers
It's a shameful exercising nihilism
But zooming out is Owen would say
Who the f*** is stopping you from speaking
Some people who are saying that it's f***** up that he's into Hitler on Twitter
But doesn't have any effect on how much or how little yeah
Yelling and saying this stuff
I want to see negative responses to what you're saying and then getting mad at that but he knows it would sound
Look like an idiot baby if he's just saying that he felt like him and all of his bigoted friends are entitled to only get positive feedback
Back from people
Weak and fragile jiri contextualizes it and pretend to people
Being justifiably offended by what yeah is saying somehow stopping him from speaking
Pitbull
Hear stuff like this it's important to recognize that all it is is Owen weaponizing his own insecurities
Give me the f****** child
Anyway I lied when I said you was
Being insightful that was that was kind of
Kind of a joke
I find ye Obsession and hatred towards pornography and fornication
Very ironic
Considering everybody around him right now is metaphorically
On their knees with their head bobbing up and down underneath the desk
Do you know what I'm saying because this is
Shame
That's what about you
Are about this one
And those people that are out there mad at
Consciousness
We have to I have to think okay White lives matter
I'm going to do a t-shirt
I'm going to make it
You understand
Control
Making people mad outrage going out to streetwear so outrageous
But you're not doing anything yourself
To change it and follow God
I'm selling shirts
A love everyone
If I Stay
I love the Zionist
I do love Hitler
I do love the scientist
I love
Everyone
The scientists cannot tell me who I can love and not love
I don't think like that
I stink more like someone that's on the Spectrum
Cuz that's what they want to claim
Well let me be on the spectrum of love because
I want the job
Hi sorry I woke Ultra is controlled by the Zionist media check cool
Cool
How real is just getting kind of
A bit repetitive
Yeah I'm not him though
I find myself not having as much really even to say in terms of like analysis of a lot of this stuff
They'll hear here this is
Yeah I mean if we accidentally
Convince a Bipolar person while they were relatively sane
That they were basically the Messiah and then whenever they went
To the manic side
Oops
We've got an actual Messiah now we're really f*** maybe not whoops for Alex though no I mean he gets a lot
Free Pub out of it true
So Allie Alexander shows up
And he shows that he has pretty like a decent awareness of like
In studio or on the phone news in studio
Yeah it's kind of an awareness of like what they're doing
You can look at this
Interview
Play indoors
Genocide
When he didn't
You can look at this broadcast and say
Nicholas
2324 year old
You know secret dog whistling KKK Nazi
You can say that
What's going on at all
And we're all just right now
In the window
The church is
They close
Alex
I want to help fun
Army truck can afford it either
Pseudo celebrity
What's a lute
And all of these
Read by people
I think the
Take everyone else word
Only use what they're saying
Stop relying on the ATL
Alright
Alright okay taking care of the big issues there
But look
Ali is very
Clearly aware that what they're doing
Is
Basically being like looking
She didn't work
The other stuff workout
Detroit Lions
What you say we want to kill the Jews I bet more people would agree with us than you think
Nobody at rethought
Trump
Who's going to be
The exact this is going to work finally
Didn't work
Nope didn't work we tried to take over the capitol
Really,
Did it go well
Our last option
Look at this guy
We got a celebrity
So we're trying this now
Yeah we're trying
Yay
Hazard Avenue to political success
Spell and at very least
Wreak some sort of vengeance
On the conservative establishment or the world the world of the right-wing
That turn their back on these
Nazis
Here's Arizona
To Ali's point
Maybe
1 people
Can rig something
Or a group
So many
Everybody has rigged
Something
Then reality that's just the system
And you're not invited
Well I do think that I was not invited
I would like to uninvite him from Allstate
I would say
My biggest
Response to Ali's
Grow up
Hanover it girl balled up
And if I had to serve just read
Frame what he saying I do be wack
That's a good one too
So Kanye talks about
Excuse me ye talked about his mom
Dying
Apparently she was a Zionist sacrifice
I am
Believe that
Michael Jordan's dad
Sacrifice
I believe
Did something happen with Tiger Woods
My mom
These are all just a thing
Sacrifice
But this is fate
Waiting at the end of the day
Is a lot of people
I feel like we're at the
Where to buy
And
Jesus runs the world God Brunswick
Jesus is the real king of Israel
And I'm just
A simple servant
Of
Of God
Zionist sacrifice
Is apparently on the table now it with no real
Push back to speak of from Alex about so what you mean by that
What is a Zionist sacrifice
Call the sacrifice
That's what they do sacrifice things to the things
Turn all the stuff is done
Sure so if I understand correctly
That wasn't one of the inciting event that led to Kanye being anti-Semitic
No it's just
I think that happen
Give me the thing with Tiger Woods
It clearly doesn't even remember that one
No. That was a pretty low-key Zombie Strike twice.
Yay seems to be begging celebrities to murder him
Alright this is weird
They want a dumbass
Doubt
Probably the Louis
IQ
You hear of anyone speaking and I'm saying
Stomach competition I don't want to judge
Influenced
Celebrities
I did not
Every
Celebrity
I did not say
Celerion
God bless
You and you know it's the Christian word of what I really want to say
Aries celebrities
Only celebrity
What is Ray J
Literally every every one of y'all
See me when y'all want to see me
Every fake gangster Stoker
Basketball
Now
See my mom
I'm going to say this though
You can't touch
Kiss your ass
That's not true
Really really taking the temperature of what was happening and responding to
Yeah
Getting back to that important
Yeah I find the the
The smacking noises that they're making to be very pornographic
Caswell
Stop
It
He insist
Dumb
IQ
You have the biggest penis to your penis is so big
She's quite smart himself
And he's an idiot savant
You'll never guess what his superpower is
Jesus
That's a French word
An idiot
Things I know I know
Cardiology
Is that
Yasso Oz idiot savant knows is that he always knows what time it is
Siri show up at the end of this episode
Imagine imagine that that is a useful power
Because he's saying that he knows what time is going to be on the clock before he looks at it
And the existence of the
The clock renders his power useless
A bunch of watches
They're very expensive watches
So I would see I would feel like he doesn't need those
He was this Salat to confirm that he has this power
Sure you always going to be reassured
So Allie has an interesting
Sort of policy
Sorry for laughing at me saying Ellie or something I just had the thought that of Alex that no one man should have
Have all that power
I should be able to tell what time it is
It is very ripe for abuse
So Elizabeth
Laura Loomer
Zionist
We disagree with Nick and I
Raymore power
Free speech
On his giant
Put out for my Twitter hi Ari Emanuel
No I got Ally you are such a loser
I mean this is supposed to be a free-speech pageant
I know basically advocating for on behalf of naked
What I would like
Is Sharia law now I know that we've talked in the past about how it's bad
But have you considered beheading people who say got some
Dim the little weird
Little too far but
You get used to
How exciting is it
That ye is going to let Alex tweet
Yeah I mean it is it is funny that we have to interrupt your belief
Blasphemy should be X
Executable
Hi with
Tweet from Kanye's Twitter account he didn't say what the exact punished
Maywood
I mean I know what a blasphemy lies and it doesn't end well
Somebody is usually pretty pissed off about glasser's chillblast
Anyway
Alex's Pizza
Abbott waited so long I remember how this works
Alright so this is the Yankees phone here
And I was going to say I
Don't.
Mom
Love
DJ Juice
First
How do you say OMG
Abbreviation
Yeah I got
I love the First Amendment
See if the fun things right between right after Ali was advocating for for blasphemy laws
First Amendment however that shouldn't count against God because there should be a one world religion and its
I didn't have any problem with or even a response
The alley saying that
I love the first Batman
They are so giddy cuz they pass the phone around they all
Get tweet from
EA account amount of strfkr pathetic bulshit that these people engage in
About the same time pretending that they
Are at any sense of the word
A powerful man f*** off
Meanwhile
Yeah he continues to be obsessed with our emanuel's wife
Jerking Kanye West off nonstop and ye is just out here to do whatever you f****** want
Weirdly and sort of vaguely sexually threatened Aria that is wife
Rema well if your wife needs any help on her creative direction for Align
Even though you
You tried to destroy my life
I will help your wife
On the creative
Directions and I will not do anything on Chris
When we were in the room together
In Jesus name
Re if you wait which Christian help your wife with her life
Okay
I put on Christ
America first
Groyper
Beautiful
Did you put the Infowars
Alexander Twitter
He did have his Twitter
Suspended
Not for this I don't think but a little bit after this
Elon kicked it back alive
So anyway Barrel
So excited to tweet and then Alex a happy so he leaves
That's the smartest thing you've done this I will say
I've been pretty critical of Alec
What
The show does grind to a halt when he leaves
Is brutal it's not very long
But there is a
Drop
In energy I don't know exactly why these are all people who love to talk
Yeah but
Sump for some reason it just does not work out until
Ali starts doing a little bit Improv
Free
Alex
Nick
Nicholas
Free
Beat
Free Ali
Is the level of typing
Boombayah
Yeah it's
Duncan Auto
I hate all of yourself
Sometime
It's at there's kind of the the feeling of
A kid who no one really likes
Yeah but has
Cool stuff
I'm so people are kind of
Using him to get that stuff
Yeah and then when he's out of the room they kind of make fun of him
But they're alive
That's the kind of vibe
This gives
Also when he said the mask there's a Alex Bass
Ya Ali puts that on to pretend
Neuromancer
I mean it's a impression that I would certainly do but I would be insulting a
Right and I believe it is a little bit insult
I mean if you step back though
There is something
Very Progressive
About
Black man in America
Forcing white supremacist to dance for him
That's kind of powerful
You know
Nap maybe I mean
Whatever
Anyway there's a big audience and Alex is really excited about it so he wants ye to give a message
Here's what he chooses
Who knows maybe Kanye West
Was never here
15 years
Brother calls Kanye better
Super-mega total viral
What is your message to Trump right now
What's your message to the Santa's right now
I don't know who the
DeSantis isn't ever heard of the
No I hear you
I love you
His name is Ronald can I lick your feet
So Nick
Not a white
It's like we love Trump
We love ye
That's right yeah no I'm with UTA and Trump and anybody gone for two
DeSantis or McCarthy
It's not the energy that's not divided that's not Maga that's not Jesus energy
Dragon energy
Put it all on the line
And finally tell the
That's the problem
I've heard you're a senior show
It's a load of crap
Yeah and I
Okay well then I would
ATL I want to say there's a lot of good Nazis that were just fighting for their country
Infidel
OtterBox
Every Nazi
Bad
Pitstop
Justin fighting for the
Country
All in a box
Again Alex is trying to do that Soros reflex
Xpeng deflection
Part of it
They're good Nazis maybe Soros is good I guess
It's up in the air
God's up in the air man you never know
He's having this trouble
With his deflections now being accepted he tries to explain that Hitler was a
Bad dude interesting let's see how this goes
Southern work
The the Hugo Boss uniform
But I mean designer
Can we just kind of stay
Like you like that
But that's about it
Things that I
About him
A lot of things
How could you say something it's okay then
They support zelensky
I love
Everyone
You're not going to be able to trap them with us I love everyone
This doesn't make sense how by your logic none of what he's saying makes sense or means anything he could be say
Sing any words right now who have the same thing to a fish
Absolutely this is this if I was writing a parody character
And I have
Over Nazi
Who says exactly what they believe
I wouldn't get this ridiculous it's unbelievable
Yeah yeah it's
It's pretty pretty silly
But that again masks
We be dangerous
Toxicity of the actual ideas that are being put forth
So
Yeah he has some thoughts about A Clockwork Orange
Did you know that was about Jews
You didn't do anything
No one no one cares about the ATL
They're played out
Jesus
No one knows the eight
No one cares they're played Outlook
People that had a problem look it up Clockwork Orange in the park
Where Jewish guy make
The guy kiss
Shoe when he says
Kiss the licks
What Jewish people favorite but what I'm saying is I love Jewish
People I loved you
Gander
Absolutely
Look at it explodes when it collapsed
Oh well nevermind I think I changed
Alex's response to this
Discussion is
I'll put up at background from the Doctor Strange
Wow
Just
Abdicating any responsibility to have a coherent conversation
I guess that there is a point of this words like how could you
I have a coherent conversation
But that's not
The position Alex has
Knock knock just like well let's get through it
No
Ethan Gage
Yes just choosing not to
I do any
Yeah it is
But at the same time he's still not actively
Helping it descend into complete chaos
You know I think he is
I think he's just kind of realize that he's a lot
Yeah I'm not ending it well that's a good point if you lose you can just end the game
You lost the game the game is over
Just Connie's not going to get more coherent right now
Booking like dirt
There is a built-in way to do this
Just cut the feed and then be like we couldn't
Before the band with too many people were watching at the same time site crash
Yep something like that you can easily do that then we can get out of this
Believe his ass
Especially not Alex's audience who he can convince of anything
So Alex
I guess
Out of the goodness of his heart decides that he's going to try and argue on behalf of Jewish people
Doesn't work could represent
Credible literature
So much great stuff
Hitler
Or Hugo Boss
Demonization
We don't care anymore ATL obviously
No one cares
Shut up no one cares Jesus
Shut up it's done
Tomorrow
Germans make really good cars
Why are we
Germicidal really cool leader
One time
Dear Alex
He is so just
Is treading water but like she's not good at writing water so he's kind of thinking
Everything he does only makes him go deeper in
So yeah is mad it's a Ben Shapiro
Well yeah
I mean
That's reasonable
No
No it's mostly cuz he's doing
I want to stay with Ben Shapiro
He was so
Disrespectful to his employee Candace Owens
Speaking out against
Me and that just showed you another level
Of this kind of control that's out there
I want and I want
Joy defended you
I think it's pretty obvious
B-boy
She deserved it
Yes but
Everyone
Play Still controlled by the Jewish media we need to serve Christ
Wow so is he
What is going on
How about it
I think they're controlling this Alex
Alex wants to push back a little bit on this idea of the Jewish media
Well that would be wise
Sure
He didn't do it all of the other time so that would have been wiser back then sure it wouldn't fly the number of times
Yay brings up and complains about the Jewish media
Decreases after every opportunity
So you tries and I think he does maybe the worst
The job possible
Text Alex
You never told me what to do
Emails herein are the writer's
I said hey yeah this is about the worst thing you could
Totally help
In public he flips the other side never talk to him again
Wait
Hollywood experience you had
Did you just tell my wife
Tired
Hearing about
The Jews like
I love him
The care
That much
You know
You make a good point
We're showing you guys the extent that you can go right
Everything
This point that you do
Proves my point
Watch this
And then
You cancel all of my deals
You proved exactly why I needed to go Defcon
Happy channel channel problem with what ya think
Alex Kidd argue
Alex believes that negative consequences is a
Are equivalent to virtue
The point he says that whenever he's being attacked it's because he's over the target
So if ye says there's a negative consequences that come from these anti-semitic things that I say
That proves that I'm right about those thing
Alex
That is a
Fundamental belief that Alex has about cause-and-effect you got it
This is bear territory for Alex Alex is not going to
You know I mean
And also
Come off that s*** about the I'm tired of people are just not going to win
In a conversation with a
Bipolar person
This is not going to happen
That's true that's why I avoid Hugh Everett
One trick to helping
People who are experiencing a manic episode going to be any books
You need to
Force them to eat as much food as they can possibly get and then
Get them as high as they can possibly get is going to it's going to work
A portal while if you just keep doing it and I'll that medications are going to sedate you
Don't try any other drugs
But the weed and the plaza food
It'll get you through a day
I find
I don't know if it's just sort of a
A function of your
Awareness or self work that you've done or whatever but
I find it with you just sort of calling things out is
Is helpful
You're aware of your own tendencies
I mean you haven't you've never seen me go
Full manic episode I've never seen you go death conflict and I would not name it that
How much happier
No less a tornado of
Will you will fall towards
Yeah yeah I don't look forward to that ever happened
This idea of the negative consequences being the same as virtue
Old is being used by yay
Anyway that I think is really Dave
If I save on an interview
And I say
I love her
And then they go and
5150 mean
Entrada lobotomized
Give me like we saw
Harley Pasternak
Or they put me in prison
It just proves what I'm saying
And it's going to
Spark the heist
It's going to spark the grammar schools going to
Spark the college
Enough is enough
How old is
Spectrum
Think I am
Speak out loud
That is our first
Amendment
That you have
Be considered to be on the Spectrum
To speak out loud
I do love my
Family
Chinese water
Torture
I would like
Long Malibu in front of my house and sing
How is it going
Nothing but he have to say about this
Who
So aside
The perspective that he's putting out is if I go out and I say this pro-hitler Andy's
Somatic drivel is nonsense
Alongside my auntie's medic buddy Nick Fuentes Brighton Milo and
Forest
Nazif
Put together this crew of Nazi losers and I said all this really horrible stuff
Consequences approved by argument was correct
And this will spark
Wave of anti-Semitism being proven
And taken in by the youth and I don't know how
Accurate that is
But it wouldn't
Ba0
Libra
It won't be a hundred percent of the high schoolers become a fisa Medicare
Also not 0%
What he's describing would be a phenomenon
Some
Soompi
Percentage
And that's f***** up because there are just natural consequences to behaving like this
That have nothing to do with proving that you're anti-semitic arguments were correct
No
But in Alex's conception of how the world works
He has no leg to stand on to be like that's nonsense man yeah
He kind of
Is forced to go along with it he he's argued himself into a place where his
Arguments are all pointing towards
Yeah
It's okay
Do whatever you want well to be fair though yeah it does not actually
Care that much about Hitler
But
Unfortunately
This clip is really bad
I don't really care that much
What about Hitler
I love them
Seems like
Seems like a cool guy you know it's like he
It's a really cool outfit and stuff and he was a really good architect
The look of it
Any didn't kill 6 million Jews that's it
Dislike factually incorrect
Why did Hitler did Target kills people
Bother you
I think
Palestinian
The first black president he was another Jewish
Po-boy
So we've got us some Holocaust denial Hitler was a cool dude and actually I don't care that much about
Hitler but also the Holocaust
Didn't happen
There is an issue there
I mean I think this is the headline at very least
If you're going to cover this stuff
In the way there
Has been on Twitter was like Kanye says
That he loves Hitler or whatever
Does deny the Holocaust very seriously he denies the holler
He does not believe the Holocaust happened
Therefore
He seems a bit more relevant
Then his admittedly there are
Elements of his
I love Hitler stuff that is f****** around
I believe that he means the things he's saying
But there is the the same
Dodge that so many of these people like Nick lentes do where it's like I'm joking
I'm joking around or like
I love Hitler but I love everybody a lot about how much I love Hitler
But I love everybody
And I think that that's a little bit more slippery in some ways than him just straight-up
Yeah yeah I think
I think we've all known somebody
In Our Lives who is
Who's had that like I'm an a******
Hitler was actually great kind of kind of day or whatever it is but
If you deny the Holocaust that is not a anything that's you have red
B******* and you think
Comes in
And he discusses how this is culture jamming
That's what they're doing
So like
He might not have been list
For that part or at least he's probably going to pretend he wasn't listening to that white lives matter shirt
Culture jamming
Because they took this thing that they're the left was doing in there like how how do you like it when we did a racist
Bride we proved why you made those shirts
Free Speech stuff
You talk about wearing white lives matter shirt and I'm really disappointed doing here today to its culture jamming
That's what we're doing
You can wear black lives matter shirt
We're ramming their own culture down their throat
And we're finding out that they don't like it
Same thing with this
Interview today
We believe in free speech
Whether or not
We believe in their right to say it in the internet number one story
In the world
Broadcast
Free speech
Breakpoint issue proud of yourself for
Getting a lot of attention for your b*******
Like
Two people at least
Involved in this don't believe in Priest
Ali wants
Blasphemy laws has been very public about how little he cares about free speech
By which he's able to push his agenda
You don't care about Free Speech maybe you think you do but you're sitting in a room with extremists who are used
Free speech
To create a Christian fashion
Just stay
That's not the same thing
No
Nope
And then you guys like that is what we are
Legitimately
I love nothing
I think he's having fun
Poking all the time
I think he enjoys a destroy
I would say I don't
I don't think this
Story here
With ye should be about anti-Semitism or Nazis or any of that
To me the human interest story
Think about what you can do with your platform right now cuz they want to make that the issue
Most people say
Your audience
You know what they mean they means what
Conjuring it's a ride
Play Kanye don't you think it's them
Owen just doesn't get it man he has no conception of what he's a part of here and a clip like
Illustrate
He wants to cover his ass and reframe his interview in a way that not Nazis can see as acceptable and yeah
Wants no part of that
He doesn't want to be sanitized he doesn't want plausible deniability he's doing what he's doing
People that go in Alexandra's props to make that happen
Nickit
Even seems to know the score but Alex and Owen the people whose platform this is are the marks
They want the message gays pushing to be push
They also just don't want their entire facade
To be punctured
So they have to do this performative sanitization and fake push back because
That's work without her every other time that had to deal with bigoted grift
They can remind them subtly to protect
The business
But not today
Also Pro tip for the next
Right-wing s******* who decides to interview gay in the future
Don't use the words they arouse him really what do you think is going to happen you're going to get
Call Dad
You're an idiot you just agree with him he wins if you're dumb forever
The
Of intelligence
Cuz it makes
Nick Fuentes look like a f****** genius
And he isn't
Idiot
I struggle I struggle with exactly how to do
Describe him I don't think he's an idiot
But
He's definitely he's far more savvy
Any of these ding dongs
Anyway speaking to take dogs
Tim pool
Took a risk
Didn't work out
You know what you going to do certainly probably got a lot of viewers
Definitely didn't look like an idiot
And also hear congratulations
Missed him
Here
Houston 3 hours 3 minutes
By the way
Does Temple got the call from those boys
10 minutes before I got there
I said flag this
Aflac.
Also Temple is the MTC you know
And your real real human being so no one's ever heard of
Temple you're the legend that is Alex Jones
And you were fighting on
On the front line and I were here we
What you got some other Superheroes part of the
The avenger movie fighting
Christ
And Free Speech
Stem
He did good
That's it's fun it's fun
For them because I bet
That hurt temples feelings
And I would love for you to say that nobody's ever heard of us that be f****** fantastic
Field day with that you just thinking the idea that Gary would ever have thought of you
Is bizarre Valeri in the same way that like hearing
Norm
Say that they couldn't get someone to be the corporate representative because of us
That is bizarre and surreal
Thought the name Jordan Hall
Yeah is Unthinkable but like
Tim pool
Like this is going to sting
That's really got to hurt
Yep
That's gotta hurt
That's got to hurt so bad and PC and no one's ever heard of you
Man
The guy who came up with net
And Yahoo are you who is pretty good
He
Devastated you
That's sad
Nothing you who is broken
I think we should respect on that for
I don't
Fair enough
And that is that no black people should ever criticized Hitman
Now he's going to come back and
Sellout
Yeah he's sold out a little bit because
Because he
The king
Yeah I'm saying he denounced me I'm the one fighting on the front line and no black person to say nothing bad about me
. I put my life on the line
Talk about anything happens to me every the greatest
Shut up
Go home to your
Scared little bins
And you scare a little
Townhome you stay little movie contract
Nothing
There's some of these moments of hostility
Come out
George Bush
Doesn't care about black
And I am f****** here for it I did see a tweet that was really funny was like George.
People should come out and take honey
Mike Fiers
Trevor's woodworking on.snl we finally giving you your first good bit
I apologize that I don't remember
Tweet that was I don't want to rip somebody off a really funny thought
I don't even know how to respond to this other than
Alex has something
Going to say that is just
Ridiculous
Fashion having a bag of funny bring that up
Future
Is not trying to
Building our own
There would you like to bank with the coworkers
Resume systems is in bankruptcy this morning as we're recording this
Alex declare bankruptcy person
Personally don't that's good news facing a billion-dollar plus judgment
In his annual cases and there are more to go
I don't know if I would
Involved
Shouldn't he be against like the FDIC like there's a lot of reasons I wouldn't Bank on
Do more like an fpx thing you know where it's like I steal everybody's money on Ally
Thankful rolling into work with hard currency and I'll keep your deposits in a hole in my backyard
I am going to steal your money
Can't imagine anything less trustworthy I would sooner get involved with Alex's
Like when he had a dating site
Human so
Alex's had
Yeah sometimes you come to the office and you think
Cruise through this work day
I got a high-energy guests coming in
I don't have to do any kind of crap I'm not doing any any real work
I'm just sitting here talking to
Talkin to ya
It's like my job except for not yet it's going to be almost like a half day at school
You show up at 9
Psycho no it's all homework
Quizzes
We're getting
Bulshit a f***** up things that I don't have to deal with
Haha
Besides he wants to end the show by Meg
Taking one thing
Illicitly clear
To Hitler is not cool
He's not a good dude
Shouldn't be hard
How would you respond to that probably with like
You bet
You got it sir
Not all that not only that I think it's probably worse than you think
In fact you and I might disagree on how worse.
Historical villain
Bad dude
Yeti has another approach
Besides
You know how I deny the Holocaust earlier
I'm do it again
Imma do it again
I wouldn't do that
I don't want to study at
Understanding the British intelligence
I like it
I'm not trying to be shocking
I like anal I do not
The Holocaust
Is not what happened
The factor that
And Hitler has a lot of
Redeeming qualities
Wheelies
God says
Man should not
Kill we should not have
Pause.
Okay
So you're trapped didn't work there either
You have
Allowed to this gentleman
Say horrific things and now deny the Holocaust Weiss
Three more times in a good as hell
Is like
Hey man I got to tell you that the Holocaust happen
I mean listen
I'll tell you this
I have not done
That much research
Research into World War I'm not yet 40 I mean old white men past the age of 40 eventually have a World War
I got a couple years but yeah I didn't need a lot of research
I can tell you
Confidently with
100% certainty
It was a bad dude
Taylor's bad dude hit by the bad news but Alex
I do think
Did this is one thing I will say
It's not to his credit but
It is like
This is pushing back
I think he does realized
But like
I maybe didn't catch it the first time but now that he's denied the Holocaust again
I do have to make
Very clear that I believe the Holocaust happened
Jones hat
Has to be like the Holocaust
Did that happen
There is a line apparently and here is where it is
I love
Accordingly
All the way from the
Balenciaga's
To the Hitler's
The Ari Emanuel
Did Jamie dimon to the people
Amber Alert is what I'm saying
Why grandfather
Run over stuff
8 years old Amber Alert
Ex-girlfriend Amber was doing
Something in the streets
And there were piles of
The dead bodies 100
Call Blackburn
Is that
Just because you hate the globalist
Call Schwab
ATL
Yeah but not
This is just it's not going to work
Whatever you're doing is not going to work but I
I do I do appreciate Alex
At least
Being like the Holocaust did happen
The Holocaust
The Holocaust happen
And it was
And I'm going to throw this out there
I don't care what God you believe in it is okay to hate the Nazi
In fact I would say it's maybe the moral imperative
Whatever group
You are mad at or hate
Does not
Justify you denying the Holocaust
Nope
Stalex is there
Animals
Maybe on some level that is a strategic calculation on his part because he's like
I will be
Straight up
Yeah
There's there's one thing that I
Have to do
And that is
Remember that
The US was the good guy in WWII that's all I got to do
Franklin my brand won't survive if I put up with helicopter
Set lights too many old conservatives who are still like
Listen
WWII is legitimately the only thing we can hang our hat on us
How old
Those types were in Alex's audience
That they are the people who buy his dumpster
So Alec
Is he's trying to
Be like
Look at you being at G and all this stuff
And
Ali
Comes in
And shuts Alex.
Fuckdown
Alex is just completely dejected and like
I got nothing
He say he hated
Didn't say you hated anybody why isn't anybody listening to
We are man
Stone
Maui
I love
Of all of those
Mount Prospect
You love everybody
Jim Jones
You like Jeffrey Dahmer
With the Bible with the Bible
But they did it to you Alex
Appreciate you
Well I mean
That's not
Really what
Gays doing but
If Alex believes that's what he's doing
If that is the kind of
Last Refuge that Alex has to try
Contextualize this
Interview in a way that like
How to build a people
Allie has just
I just been like
Boom
Door slam
And let's not forget
Nick Fuentes
Originally he said
I agree with ye and then his head went back underneath the table in front in slap so
Alright alright I feel enough of that I'm sorry I'm sick of this s***
Kanye off enough of that alright
Yay
Once again complains about the Jewish
Media because
Alex was trying to
Sort of
Coast
Closing statement really want to leave things on is that
Gay wants to
Whakaari Emmanuel's wife
God the judge
And we got to change ourselves to somebody else
Exactly
I meant to say hey
Show you how much
Jewish media can't tell me what
We could get a nice private room
Me and your wife
Can go in and work on the clozeline I'm really good at it and
Absolutely
Peanut
Sounds like you do
His wife
Create event
Infowars.com tomorrow
Tomorrow's news today is apparently our emanuel's wife's clothing line isn't up to
Not that good
Now that guy
I do I do appreciate that Alex has at least
Observant enough to notice that he keeps talking about
Getting kind of weird there man
Yeah it is you
Relationship with women
I'm shocked
Alex didn't pick up on the p*** dude
Is transparent
So as ye leave
Alex does not
Seem incredibly happy
First Amendment
I love you. Taking the mask off
Wilbert Johnson
What's the impersonator Wilbur
Net-net
Was here though
Yahoo play
What you want
Hey Ya
Broke
Finally broke
Do the last time
Incredible
Play Justin Trudeau
Has been incredible
Incredibles wedding
Leaves
They're still the fourth hour a bit of the fourth hour and then the War Room
And
Alex says they're going to take 3 hours a calls there's going to get everybody's opinion on this
This interview they're going to get down to it
Talk about free speech
Alex spends the rest of his show
Just certain navel-gazing
About how many viewers they have
To tell their friends about the shows I got we have 25 million people watching
If all of you told your friend
Think about day we could make a real chain
Call Sonia Shah
Hey man so he's there hosting the war room with Owen
At the beginning
And
It's just
A desperate attempt to rewrite What hap
And
It makes sense that he would spend the rest of his show like navel-gazing because that's the only way he has
How to get back some of his bride
It's been so ripped away from him that
Now he's like
Balming himself I think it was all worth it
Because of all these views
He's
Play just a couple clips
Like now that ya is gone
He is able to
Rewrite what
He said with
About ye saying
No
I like not sit
Shock value
Designer style of Stalin I love Mouse
Mall
It's all over the place
Is this
Infowars.com
Tomorrow's problem
What's happening
677 million people so far
30/45
Just last couple hours
That cost
Serious
Sooner that gets to an ad pivot
And here is another attempt
223 contextualize
What year was saying
But you know what you did do today Alex
Was you let yay
You had the most success
Successful
Podcast lives
Stream with ye-es
The guest
He didn't like any of the other interviews he did he walked out of some of them obviously like
You mentioned with Tim pool
And so
I think again
Today
You are the champion of free speech
You put your neck out there with
With knowing the red
Knowing
Probably going to be
And you did
And you did and I got the most views on a livestream ever on The Intern
In the most
Band studio in the world
The real story
Take away that free speech
It might be under
Serious attack
What is not dead
Still want it they still want to hear controversy
Wasn't doing I was doing
Shop value
He's not the Holocaust man
He denied the Holocaust multiple times and he specifically said this is not
For shock value
Trolling
Any of this
Alex
When
Nike Pride
Do use these excuses for what ye was saying while ye was there
He said no
And he said not only that
I love Hitler
Nazis are great
Holocaust didn't happen
Now that he's gone
Alex can do this
It's the same thing with Tim pool
Tim would not stand up and assert his
Position or say
Hey I don't think this is cool until
The minute ye left
This is Aldi
Really
Pathetic attempts at savings
Face
Bring something
Rewriting the narrative in a way that works
For you because this person didn't
Play along
With the way that you were going
As to what Owen saying
Like oh can graduation
3 hours with an anti-semite when Tim pool only lasted
20 minutes that is not the compliment you think it is
I was I listen to that and I was like he does not understand
Embed essentially what he just said is
It is worth it to us
Too broad
Cast
Holocaust denial and Hate
Cuz
We got money
Yeah score
Hypothetical
Exactly we don't even know if we got it yet
More to have this interview than we make from this interview
I was listening to the war room and I noticed
This on the Infowars
Feed
The feed
Video that they posted of the War Room has weird
Blackheath
Incredible music
You can hear that music
Breaking from Hollywood
Breaking from the mainstream
Definitely something cutout
And so I was thinking like what's going to be something really f******
Incentive if all the other things are still out of
If anything is cut out of this interview
F******
Well here's the thing
I found the actual bra
Video is that
And it's really just them talkin about China
Now they want China to be free
It's not offensive at all it's about 6 minutes
Of
Extraneous conversation
About to Liberty for the Chinese people
But then there's this
I think it might have been why was
When you got
Videos
The bills are in the
$2,000
And so
We've been told
Infowars
Dot-com
Doesn't come back
Wow he was going to take calls for hours
And it's just Owen
It's boring as hell I don't care interviews Jesse Lee Peterson
I think
That
Maybe they cut that out because it looks really weak and you don't want that in the
The final product
End
The next morning Alex declare Bank
So maybe that is more real than it usually appears sales pitches
Like no they straight up
Okay got hit
Like with the Sirius expenses because
The
Increased bandwidth cost
And if there is some silver lining
To this
Possibly
It may be that indirectly or directly
Platforming
Beignets
Bulshit
Anti-Semitism in Holocaust denial could have bankrupt Alex
What do his bankruptcy
Yeah yeah
I mean it's
It is funny
That
Hey you got bankrupted because
Yay
Did something that he
Previously decried
Which is breaking
The internet
Here's that he's wasted upon his own petard
There's a little bit of irony irony abound
Things in this whole f****** thing
So
Particularly care about Owens rambling
Nonsense
Defenses of what has happened on
We're not going to
Spend more time diving
Into that
Words almost fail you know when when trying to look at what
What is happy
Yeah
There's a lot of missing
The forest for the trees
In terms of
Just boiling the sound to Yale of Hitler or likes Nazis
Because I mean that certainly is a
But there's so much more going on
They all
Funnels
Into that
Yeah you know it
It's not like there are a ton of
Different things
Better happen
They're a bunch of different things that are all
Routed back
To this anti-semitic ideology
LG
The clear influences of the people like Milo Nick
Owen Benjamin Ali
Bitter around him
These these
Obsession with pornography and evils of it
Very clearly
He is just a
Side Road of his anti-semitic ideas
This is
It's troubling
I mean
I was in the shower earlier I was thinking
Weeping
Why did I choose to do this
Why is Jordan my
My friend Oliver
No
I mean look
Puppet sleep-deprived some of those thoughts may come later
I had a feeling of like this is the worst
First episode of Infowars I've ever
And I don't know if I can confidently say that
Because he said
There's been a lot of really bad episode
A graphic one sticks out to me and I don't know how much of that was just because it was
Piano traumatic for me to
Cover that episode in
Yeah the research into it was really horrible
But in terms of life
A presentation of something
No he's had Richard Spencer on he said David Duke
Those were
Really as bad as this
In terms of
Incompetent
Of
The pushback
Intentional or otherwise ineffective
The
The Dane
Danger of
It in terms of
I feel like it's
It's worse than David Duke
Inasmuch as like
David Dukes
Cool
Don't like
Sure
You know there is a
Unwise NSF debating David Duke when you're definitely not ready to and you don't really disagree with someone all that much
Seems dumb
And maybe not the best idea
Yay is
Cool
Still
To a lot of people
And also he has something that
David Duke doesn't have
Which is people like
Nick Fuentes
Sand
Boeing Badge
How many Milo
And I think that presents
A unique set of circumstances that
I don't know
I mean you can I need to
Sleep on it
Yeah and reflect
But this is up there as one of the worst episodes of his show that I've heard
I mean it's very rare that you actually get someone denying the Holocaust on in for
That is something that is
Is it puts it in a category I mean
My my thought
As I come to the end of this
Horrific
Whatever
Is that
I met you you slept
Exactly I'm riding
Yeah I mean
The Anders Breivik
Is far more
Disgust
Sing to me
Then this because
This is a
Funhouse mirror version
Of reality
It's it's
Good knockers
I mean
The Anders Breivik s***
Is so f*****
And the way that he dealt with that
Well I mean yes
We're also talking about the f******
You know he's denying the holiday
And I like that the Holocaust
Did murder a bunch of people
I meant
I mean not to say
That these issues
Violence doesn't still
Continue to this day
Kanye personally or ye personally
It doesn't have that
Malika Sanders brevik wasn't on the
The show
So maybe it is
Maybe you've made your point is Briella the
But I'm not sure
Tumi
Here's the number of my
Cuz we can argue
What the worst days are the definition of the worst you know that
My problem with this
What is that
One way
That
Almost everybody is going to engage with
He's the most
Damaging way to engage with
Tumi
The only possible way you can engage with this
Exactly
Is if you watch the
The entire video
Or if you listen to our show
Because this
What is a totality
Any any
Any attempt
To shrink it down
Is
Damaging more harmful than his dinner
Clips
Do a disservice
The totality of what this is this conversation
The way it goes I I agree I agree with you
And I think
Also to double down on that
Getting lost in the weeds of
The
Do you see reality and
Clear
Observe the clown ashness of It
With the the Netanyahu stops
And all that getting lost in that
Such an absurdity who would ever take
Seriously
Is
Working towards the interest of
The the propaganda is meant
For howitzer
Meant to be
Be dismissed by people who would take it
Get seriously other way
And every one of the people in this
In this interview
A date you're not going to get enough contacts about them through whatever it is that you're reading
Whatever tweets you're getting
Any of it
Even if you read everything that all the newspapers and blogs and all that s***
And all the tweets
You do not know enough about Nick Fuentes
You do not know enough about alley Alexander you did not have
The context necessary
To understand what
Is going on
And you definitely don't have any idea how to engage with
What day is doing right now
Everyone will be done a disservice
Because of all of the people that are not
Naked Kanye or Alex
Yeah probably
And it sucks
My f****** sucks
Lot of things
A lot of things were
Or Taken
On this episode
My my sleep
Was deprived from me
The audience was deprived another deposition episode that was going to be laughing about that again resale good to haggai great
Everybody out there
I bet you wish you didn't have so much f****** yet you in your life now don't you
I could use a little less help
Never again
Until until we come back on
Booby
Knowledge right. Com
We are also on Twitter
Until then I'm neomlei MDX start I don't want to do a dumb B
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color