Jordan
College B
Knowledge
Stripe.com
Text Dan
My brakes badri Jordan is actually my computer I had to relaunch Spotify
I had been launched along with the restarting
I really use Spotify for anything except for like
Exercising listening to music on there cuz he just make
My playlist in order
Spotify Joe Rogan orthodontist
Boys side podcast they just started called the the snack stack
Show on Spotify
Colors and stuff it's a lot of fun it's a I've enjoyed it I like that
And it reminded me
I feel like
At certain points
We should try and abused our notoriety in some way of celebrities
Whatever
Power of the audience need to put this out there into the universe to manifest
Would love to end up beating up Doughboy absolutely
Get it done
I feel like their elbows everything that's happened to us over the last like couple years has
It's been like this absurd like it's never going to happen
These things do end up happen
Where the times
The problem is in order to achieve those things
You have always had an unreachable goal in front of you yeah and that is being on the Doughboys oh no
What you get man it's dangerous
Quincy hunt Mitch down
It's a dumb dumb show
My bright spot is I don't know if you can see these right here my man
I saw these are some new socks with my pops on them
Annie and Jake and then I got this new hoodie and the reason is because my wife is amazing
He got me these things she is amazing she loves Christmas know you could put dogs on sale
Well yeah you couldn't brand-new technology Paxico it didn't exist
Early Christmas present
Hiding Christmas presents until the moment they arrive
And then giving them to me
To make me happy on way good 19 days early
Never been hidden
Not once
But it's fantastic
Great socks
Always like a nice novelty socks love them I didn't use to I'm not I'm not a things guy
But now
It's novelty socks all the way
Jordan today
Do do do
Our last episode was a lot
Requiring us taking a little bit of a in a little paws for Monday
You want to jump right back into all that necessarily
Give that a little bit
Breathing Room give it a little bit of time to to sit
And then Friday unfortunately going to have to come back to you some other swamp Non-Stop
But for today
We have ourselves a little deposition to go over to say that it is time to
Release the Kraken
He's an interesting cat I really got a different feel for him based on this that I had before
You have this image of him is kind of a pro wrestler he's a kind of ESA
White and Northeast accent
They think a lot of people code as dumb
Certainly unfair prejudicial and what have you but
He also has
Like a bombastic Nest to him and you know he yells at the press conferences chair
And you don't really get much of a chance to ever hear like thoughts or or like sort of his personality
Be expressed
I found it really interesting to see
Six to eight hours of Hemet episode
Oh my God
So I mean obviously he's not a wrestler anymore because he is he is
Still okay
How do you keep kayfabe in a deposition
Little bit off more than some
Yeah he talks about how he has a bunch like scars on his head and stuff off chair shots and what-have-you
You know what that that's something interesting to the keep track of get is a little bit of protecting the business
The Big Show at a deposition is is a different stormy Paul White
Oh wait to see the mayor of something now know that can
Is the demons favorite Patriot.
Actually I think
That there is maybe more of a sticking to his guns then a lot of other people know that kayfabe
Baby is actually
I'm sitting with it
And we'll see what happens
Where's the very high place Dental Associates
Thank you very much. What's up with that bucket of poop thank you so much
Thank you very much I would love to take reference always mixed up Michael the Scott Trousdale you
You gotta walk status so don't be an a****** Steve
Next Indian Boston you're on the air thank you thanks for holding
Thank you very much for Bobby aka the other Shane
Thank you very much cars the voir and cuc deployer thank you so much
Thank you very much so first
Game saliva soaked balaclava wrestling beside Owens puddles of Tears boiling beside a fake campfire
Thank you so much for an hour technocrat and oops all plants thank you so much you are now a technocrat
I have
Risen above
Miami star
Go take a little break you down
A list for me
And then we're going to come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty work for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f*** the horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
Belle walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
I apologize to the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's not so no it will talk about that on Friday of course but for now Alex
Getting a little play in this deposition
Good call so that's that's kind of fun we just get to hear about the Kraken
And his business
But there's not a contacts drop but I think sums up some of this stuff pretty well
And so the only basis
Just for your knowledge
Was
Your common sense
And the TV shows you watch
If there's anything else Tony
No I think we've done with
All right. I like that idea and the only thing you had to
Back it up with common sense and TV shows
To do everything I have to give you is a simple way of describing his death
Deposition begins like all the depositions swear in the witness
Go down the same way
All of the other ones too if you're saying that the swear in the witness
Part has eclipse
This is going to be interesting yes you go
Reporter police swear in the witness
Mr. pedantic
Follower of Jesus Christ on 610 BS Bi-Lo Bi-Lo
As instructed to us in the Book of Matthew
Okay
Alright money
You're free
Take a note
Absolutely
I bet the
Testimony that you're going to
Beginning
Absolutely
And so you can either swear and if you
Waterfront
Diaphragm is OBS in my noveno my way to be truthful
This is
This is interesting to me because like all of them you know they have religious inclination and what
And I think the only person I've heard he was like I don't swear something
It's My Religion 222 swear Oaths is there a new type of sovereign citizen that believes they already
Eddie live in heaven like that kind of like a Heavenly citizen like something along those lines
BMV
What is a sovereign citizen of the citizen of Heaven I wonder what button to use
Imaginary friend
Will judge him
He's got to get a good lawyer
No but Norm is here
Here's an observer
Not representing badonde
There's another I don't think he may not have a lawyer
Cuz I think they're just people observing and like making objections and hookup on behalf of like Infowars
I think so
And then in terms like free speech systems
There's a guy who is like the lawyer one of Mark Randazzo is associate
Voice you'll hear objecting
I think I think he was representing Free Speech system
Maybe partially but don't be
It's not really that important
In terms of coming to Infowars coming to down this path but I'm be withdrawn to a
Alex Russo
Great reasons
Totally good reason guy
Would it be fair to say that
As part of your
You are views as a
Independent cost
A
High-level distrust
Is that fair
The main street meat on both sides absolutely
Right and left on both of them lie to their teeth and we have the ability and stuff
And credit to Alex Jones Infowars.com
We have the ability is to see through the lies and
Constellations for the public what really is going on
And all that
Why were the
We're all the most hated networks in the mainstream
And I know that's what people love that's why we got millions of followers and everything else because people want
True that sun and most the time it it's hot it sucks
It stinks
But yeah we can't sugarcoat things we need to tell people the exact truth though
The way things are and that's the way I mean
I'm not speaking for Alex Jones or anything I'm speak to myself that's way I conduct journalism if I see something wrong
I'm going out to Democrats and Republicans I confronted Obama confronted
? what is your name
Congressman that shot into Mantua and Michael Bloomberg many other people like them
I'm not a potty I don't I'm not a potty bias
Speaking to me
I'm going to come after them playing simple politically you know
And I do my best to ask questions and
Phantom they don't you know whatever it is
Is it
Alex Jones
Your
View that
He was telling the truth
Where
The
Other mainstream
Media Outlets
Would not
Absolutely
He was just asking questions
And they don't like me
I don't like it
Yeah you might have hit a little bit of an important Point unless that is that he does not end
Consensus
Hey dude talks
To say one of the reasons this is so f****** long these depositions is he keeps answering questions that weren't asked
On and on and on
Meddys
Maddie's beautiful
Okay and ask this again
I do I do appreciate that because I do think that there is some sincerity and badonde is part of
He thinks that like this is hard and it sucks getting old is R-Truth
Alex delusional
There is a part of me that believes that he believes it I was thinking the same thing I was thinking we're dealing with a believer
And that we
It's so sad knowing what we know now when he says
We in regards to him and Infowars yeah yeah
Throughout this that I really do get the feeling that he doesn't understand how little Alex cares
About him
How
Much as they wish they could just blame all this on the Fall Guy 8:30
It is it is a little bit of a bummer
Cuz he does seem to think like world best friend
Is is 2 to remind yourself of like the attack part but
That dog goes home to his master does I call you I love you you're my favorite guy I think you're the best you make me happy all the time
Man's best friend
My bad to too many fun B-Max
Absolutely giving dad Dan Sebastian
He has a kid
I don't know his life
Anyway
There's some training at Infowars apparently
Not much
But a little bit of training
Well we got training therefore wasn't sauce use the language operation cover your ass
Okay based on when you make an accusation statement away to article or report
You put the proof where I comes
And I'm going to people get to decide from there now if the source is wrong example ABC said
The sky is purple right
We will point the ABC said the sky is purple
No people
We're not going to rock we just recited
The information
And I mean
Now Sean gets back from Temple
Again frog then
Cuz yeah frazine in the Roundup
That's on record that was from Berkeley University we printed that out for him
Ignore you do with Satan
Information from Berkeley Medical
And then we'll find out he's getting chastises a gay frogman
That's the stuff we talked about because when you
Proper truth
That Wrecking the sources they don't want to hear that
So this is something that comes up a couple times this operation cover-your-ass which I guess is their way of
Saying use sources or or just like
Report factual information apparently robbed his way of like sort of
Sexying up Elemental Elementary
Don't make things up
Byj yeah it's
Kind of cute
If it wasn't Infowars I guess would be kind of cute wasn't one of the more evil or we need to be able to
To blame this on somebody else you can say whatever you want as long as you have a link
Boiler alert they almost never have
Every like a middle management employee and you hate your job and the people you work for
Cover your ass is fine but an Institutional business
With the policy of cover-your-ass is not a good business
Make it someone else's fault
Get out clean actually that's a little business
So badonde is a man who is known to use confrontation in his journalism
In the past and this is Sesame predates his time before he met Alex
Actually
He knew info Warriors before he knew Alex
The the idea of
Confrontation journalist
Yourself
As well correct
Yes and it's not confrontation as a physical it's a competition is like
Putting on the Spot while I collect questions and answers out-of-form somewhere
One public Peosta person
The other populations against
And I would have they answer the question or not that's
Not the point
But well that's why y'all he's going up to asking real questions that no other journals
What ask your man and I was doing the same thing my own Island
Those were words
Yeah dude
Before I even knew Alex Jones I was doing the same thing
Did you first hear about Alex
Oh wow
When I first got a radio
Show me Captain Captain like going on the news and all that
Can some report small trailers media and I Came Upon it for was
That I actually
Primavera
Hawaii
So I got to know who it was like more inside watching out showing shows
And not Grant I can only watch it everyday and I mean when I could
He knew Aaron Dykes yeah he's a producer and writer for Infowars who is
Laughed and does not like Alex him and his wife Melissa Melton both work
At Infowars and
They're mixed up in the Don Salazar we talked about them in that episode of the deposition because they were
Both sort of tertiarily involved in his reporting
On Sandy Hook stop
I imagine they did I don't I don't know the exact path through like I don't know if they came into informers already a cup
Or whatever but I only know that they're married because of the last episode
What they came up with the position we have the bow
Songs of an incredible romantic comedy alright propagandist
She's trying to have it all we have the makings of the next office we got jailed am right now
I will stay for awhile and then it's a will-they-won't-they deny that Sandy Hook happen
Write Rob do is Dwight Alex's of Michael Scott
Oh no yeah well I mean obviously Alex's is the Scott
Steve is a Creed
Oh boy
Let's see who else could we were kids from the cast of The Office
LOL so I've already out on my own by a cast of characters
My bench is low
Is anyone there is actually responsible
I didn't force you like trying to do a good job that's a good question
Not at work I'm going to have to give Owen is at least
Trying something
Owen can also be Dwight anyway
Love's
The Constitution
This is important to him
Gloves the founding father
In about
That
Alex Jones Kingdom
Thinking
Not just him in general I mean like I always been a critical big like that challenge
Enough
It's mainly went out that the TSA started when naked body skin as I do right about that time that's when
I really thought I'd get out
Becoming a good Viking 284 was
I went I had to help my own Tennessee protest here in Rhode Island
And y'all things like that and I was like
Anything which goes back to
History
When were the founding fathers were in person you know mean
At Thomas Paine I'm looking bike
Thomas Paine with me. Then you don't mean like he was doing what I'm doing today but if possible
And Cinderella and you can pick people like that's like these people
A revolutionary that standing up against
Old womanizer
Tyranny
And I mean would you work a stye they'll capsize back then
Do all the phone deposit they'll cash sizes nut balls back then
Conspiracy theorist everything
And I mean and not daycares away for this country and they
Quail you got tons and tons of quote that says
It is all job and I duty to keep that Liberty going in and secure Liberty is eternal vigilance
Atomic structure
According to Monticello this is not a quote that appears in any written or spoken history from Thomas Jefferson
The most likely origin of this quote is an Irish poet and lawyer named John Philpot current who said the condition upon
On which God have given Liberty to man is eternal vigilance
Which condition if you break
Servitude is at once the consequence of his prime
And the punishment of his guilt
All those Irish this was in the early 1800s after which point many speakers began using via quote and
I'm making this abbreviated too much more
Okay YouVersion who was first attributed to Jefferson and 1834
Which is after
It would have been popular already weird
Country
I'd like we have as a as a as a country
We have a habit towards miss making that isn't quite as it what we consider the the myths of
What did Rome tell itself Rome didn't tell itself
It's not a weird quote but the Greeks wear the band
Babies baby they gave Julius Caesar all of the quotes like all of the good
How old is Virgil they were just like I had Julia set up who cares
Possible it is possible but yeah it is a kind of
Soft version of mythologize I kind of bring this up constantly
Like whenever they deploy some of these spurious quote today is that like
Certain level they live in a fantasy of their own history and the myth
Assertive
Wistful patriotism patriotism
To the lights that people like in forest of course there's maybe a benign version of it we're like
You're not super connected to it and it doesn't make you
That's cream that all shootings are false flag maybe there's a benign version of
No I don't know if I don't know if anybody likes
Oh man
Abraham Lincoln
This dude
Delivered the most mail in a month
It's not crazy he was dead the all-time record holder
For most mail delivered in month
And he had this great quotes
Snoochie boochie
So he was he was he was drawn
To Alex
At least in part because of 9/11 conspiracy theories that he had
Ostler comes out right
Which is early in the deposition
And I found it shocking
One of the other
Stories that
Attracted you
Alex Jones was
His claims about 9/11
Correct
In the substance of that claim
Was that the United States government
Perpetrated the 9/11
Yes
I even though
Listen him I have my own questions because
I'm very knowledge near me from world end
Probably ridiculous
W.
I would minimum weight training to fly a 747 757 sorry into the towers like that
A precision
Especially the Pentagon 15 feet on the ground
Dark violet
So many laws of physics and everything else tonight that's where the questions are based off
Now listen Alex Jones coming up the same dairies and I'm like wow
So pretty weird moved to pardon my language slur
You're aware that what you're about to say is deeply inappropriate
My language if you're about to say that
I feel like if you recognize that this is an appropriate you could just say people
You're at a deposition this is a deposition
You know
By saying pardon my language
You're not supposed to say it at the very least here anywhere but definitely not here
Just can't not but these are these are like these little kernels of like the character of this person and
That's so weird that is a weird person
Yep
So
I think at a certain point
Batondy kind of realizes that if he's answering questions
He sounds dumb
Because the answers are good for the questions that are giving it so you'd rather not be asked questions
Early odd
He's he's got a little bit too far so he recognizes that
And now he's basically just going to try and stop the deposition at least focus it like really
Finally Center doll island
About 911 Colorado the Aurora shooting stuff
It doesn't work
Maybe
A sign of some kind of instinct
That is maybe better than a lot of the other people that need that means rooms
Before you go any further
We're here for the Sandy Hook thing why we dabble into things that that's going to build up a relevant cases for this whole operation
Rachel's going on I see the pad
Apache Jack what's going on the streets today Calcasieu until coconut balls make me look like
Kaspersky.com get to the Sandy Hook stop
That's okay
It's a rocking to the skates
Sometimes yet
None of this is ootoya relevant at all to send help
Mr. I appreciate your view on that
I have a different view there are reasons.
Asking
These questions I really don't know anybody
So, can you ask them
You're obligated
And answered
Impatient
Make it with them
So
That's not a personal attack on you sir I was just
Yeah that to the point in a locked door this is a robin where I worked is irrelevant to Sandy Hook
Where I went
Schools around with the Sandy Hook broadcast radio stations or irrelevant
I understand that you know I've been changed
I'm going to do my job
As long as it takes
And if that means coming back
Today to ask
Acquired
So
Go ahead and continue
And will be as efficient as we
Okay
Not not as much staying power to that Gus do as many as you might think there would be
Handling by Chris there I appreciate that
I ate you know what
You are making some very good points that I
Completely disregard this is a law I don't know how to explain laws to you but
You have a point and I disagree that point I think the opposite I'm ready to swear to that position
Tell you to do things by law
So but that instinct is good that cuz it's kind of like a
Or your hope it's going to work. I know that I'm coming in here to answer questions conceivably
We about Sandy Hook site
Maybe I've thought about it a little bit in advance right
I want to answer these questions I can think about advancement I can just point that out this is about Sandy Hook
Maybe the lawyers go along with Ryan
Rhetoric
It's
It's sad how
Again much like thinking Alex's friend unrealistic this is what did the hope is there
I appreciate that interesting that he's State you don't like the way that
Anywhere or the like
Went into these depositions was almost like a neat naive antolino like a dodo bird like they had no idea that the Predator was
Was right there in front of them and but dondi has this like
It seems like he came up and touch the predator on the nose and is like Snot on it I get this I get what's happening here I got it back
Unfortunately
He is in the Trap
So Maddie asks about what is the the journalist job
Has like a really weird take
As a journalist with you
Would you agree with me
That
Part of the journalist's job
As you understand it was to ask questions
But then after asking those questions
To convey the truth of the matter
To your audience correct
Yes
In other words the point of asking the questions is so that you can accurately
Forum
Your audience correct
Yes and if there's only have two questions I'll be
Probably IQ questions and answers
That's my personal opinion but
Well however in a Midnight Judges Knox
The terrorism these days he has a perspective that people not answering questions is a sign of their guilt
And
He is not answering questions after saying I don't want to answer this question
Right it's a little bit dissonant
And I mean even just like taking away the sort of hypocrisy there or whatever 8
Really f***** up view for someone who
Is it media
Orion in broadcasting and information
Dispensing
If you believe it someone not answering a question is indicative of their guilt
You cannot possibly as artane what's going on
You can't watch news to get watch a press conference and get
The point of things it's it's bad you're playing with like
Football with a broken leg anytime somebody's like no comment or like they definitely
Kildare County
Yeah
Very strange that's not good
So
Without Executives wish
And questions are asked about other things
And so the underwear bomber
Comes up
And he did a little bit of work on this
I just want to answer questions about it
Let me let me ask
Miracle
Weather mr. Jones
That
Unabomber the underwear
Armor
I was a federal
You recall whether or not he
What is this have to do with Sandy Hook
Beaver call weather now
I'm not going to answer No More Heroes
Questions I refused
This is outrageous in the you can call me back a million times I'll keep coming back
Did none of this has nothing to do with us
Okay this is nothing but a sap to make him look like a kook make me look like a goat
Nothing do what happened in Newtown Connecticut
And no
If you want
Okay
What'd he questioned the underwear bomber because the facts came out by the people who are on the plane
Date on record the lawyer attorney Kurt High School
Said the state department escorted around 6 ready to get on that flight even though he was denied by the airline.
That's the question to ask shoulders asking why
Why do they do that
Why so after the attempted Christmas Day bombing in 2009 Carrasco went public with some claims
How do you saw well-dressed man helping abdulmutallab get it sorted out to get boarded
Haunted flight 235 from Amsterdam to Detroit
Haskell claim that this person was trying to help abdulmutallab get on the plane without a passport but
This was happening in an area the airport where you should have already been passport screen and there's no one else who really corroborates the story
It all and even
Like accepting all of it he didn't claim it this was the state department thanks
Interpretation lipid and he's making past in terms of radicalization towards Terror
Pretty clearly well-established
He pled guilty in a fairly Agro and non repented way and not Haskell's claims went much further than
A guy saying something
He was interviewed by Outlets ranging from NPR to Infowars and no greater information ever came out
And then in 2012 Haskell decided to run for Congress in Michigan and he really didn't want to talk about that
I consider it part of my personal life and not part of my campaign
I don't think it's relevant
Sounds like he's guilty
It's debatable whether it's relevant or not
One could suggest that Haskell's actions speak to a lack of judgment
And the consequences of that Ripple to this day and are used by people like damn but don't need to justify their other conspiracy bull
Activities
And that kind of light maybe Haskell doesn't display leadership qualities that would justify him being in Congress
And then there's a little bit of weirdness that comes out in his interview with NPR
When he's asked if it's possible that he got people confused and if it's possible to the person he saw with the well-dressed man with someone
He says it's not possible
The cause for concern was that he said that the well-dressed man referred to the person with him as Sudanese where is Abdul Mateen
Olive is Nigerian
Haskell explained quote
There were very few black man or black people on this flight and he's a rather different looking person to
So it's pretty obvious to me
I wonder what he means by different-looking because Abdullah Metallica's pretty normal-looking as far as I can tell
The things Haskell was saying immediately after the attempted attack were really interesting hence the little bit of news coverage and
That looks like a r but none of this is substantiated and none of it proves anything
But for someone like batondy and an outlet like Infowars one person saying something that they can use is the equivalent of a Smoking Gun
John the closes the case
They're not very rigorous
Is what I'm saying or even a decade later is still like
Citing this one thing this one guy said
As
Feel like proof positive that
Then of this underwear bombing was fake
In order to sell the naked body scanners
Yeah I'm going to have to say we all know what different-looking means in this context
And I
I don't know of any other history that he had that would corroborate this and I like another datapoint with Haskell chair but like
That comment is a little weird
I ate it seems a little razor state of note
Get a permanent record of subs or hot
The one thing that I noticed for sure throughout this deposition is the Tampa Dundee is
He's like one of those fire logs that has its own accelerant
He's speeds himself up
There isn't he does not need help getting going and just ramping
He goes from like answering a question to a rant
Like
Unprompted
Quite a few times
And so here's one example of that uses winding himself okay
These are the questions were bringing up in these of the valkyrie
Then I don't
Hear what the courts have to say
I'm not involved with this
Okay I'll speak my mind when I want a Halo that's the way it's going to go
And I'm not going to buy nobody else I stand for the Constitution the Bill of Rights might want Savior Jesus Christ was not
Damn thing
Did you hear anybody else I'll speak my mind to buy deathbyromy
And this is the way we're asking questions
We're out there trying to save this country for which left of it
At people like this in the media
Slime balls they want take they want to stay for free speech I want to talk about gun rights the very fundamental rights of
Dismiss
Let me know when standing up against
I'm going to speak
Speak out and speak out of my head
The whole thing with the couch dozing drums
Workout inspiration
Despite them because he was a man
Batman we had balls
Steal that walk to anybody
I questioned them with all the requests
I was at the Boston Marathon
Reporters in the world
Nobody's asking to talk to answer
Questions
And also not being label all over the media
Especially
I asked if you were a large
Kaspersky lunatics
I haven't said anything
Jessie Jessie
I think you're a bad guy
Please let know it's not personal attack against you a night I don't think that was
He reminds me a little bit also has me like on the phone with Xfinity
Okay
I'm sick of this internet going down at this is the fourth time this week I've called you I'm so sorry this is not about you
You're just doing your job I'm so sorry.
Talk to a person
Deal with this exact same abuse
All day I apologize I don't want to contribute to it that's on base there is a little bit of that that
Running right that instant recognition of like a look I'm not trying to be a dick to you
I'm just mad about the Constitution being attacked that's not you
Deposition but then again
Conceivably he should have just respect for Maddie because Maddie is the lawyer who is representing the thing
Thing that's supposed to be destroying the first and second amendment I mean he started with saying I literally don't care about the law
That is true and well. Shut up again
Promo from there's a godspeed You black Emperor Saga bbf3
+ 8
Him reading one of his poems
And telling the story about how he got a parking ticket and he's
The story winds up with him just being like
Listen judge I am not going to stop speaking in your cockroach
I am a person and I can do what I want
People up the river for 20 years with it and it's so good
Song is this
I'm so sorry but they're all people and I'm at
So before coming to Infowars like we've already touched on but dondi new Aaron dykes
And it turns out you knew him through an interesting way
Trina time that you were
Audiobooks
Did you ever reach out
Kim
Or
Anybody it in
Worst
Yeah I mean I already knew aerondight
From we are change cuz I barbecue
Organization called we are changed and I don't know if he was a member not by knew him
He actually seen a lot of my videos and all that make comments here and there
So yeah they knew each other through we are change which is the organization that was a 911 true thing to pick
Guy Ron Paul campaigning lucrative
Who is co-host great
I'm sick
These people
This again we get back to my least favorite thing
The naming of organizations we are change
Blended aspirational
It could be it could be like any kind of old thing like oh we need to save dolphins or something but no it's also
Do we need to bring fascism into America it's
Yeah I believe that they got a little bit of traction to during like the Occupy Wall Street
Attach themselves a bit to that sounds like an organization
We're here for
Fraud
Fart again
So there's a non-disclosure agreement the badanti has signed but is unclear about exact
Glee what that cover
Answer the question comes up like what was your job when you got a job offer and how much it was
Job offer for the lawyer
A woman is the the lawyer whose
Representing Infowars
Dondie's side dish
And so there's no one really knows
This is
A
Adjust
Clean sweep
Of inability to just tell me what your job is
I understand that he has a different reason than other people's reasons but everybody can't just tell you what their job is
Well I think I think you know as we get further through this year
Get a better sense of what batondy does
Why did I think he tells
Probably more information about the like
Sticks and stones of what his his job is
But there is a little bit of difficulty
Out of the gate
So I did ask you
What the offer was in
You
Indicated that you weren't sure whether you can answer that question
Is that question that you ruined answer
Yeah we are males I'm certainly clarify the question
Is it the offer of the amount of the sorry
I'm asking you for the amount of the salary
The position that they were hiring
In any other benefits they may have offer to you with that
Six figures
They hire me as reported in a producer
And that that's public
And I'm sorry I don't know if I'm lost
Disclose
Family attorney that agrees with that I'll just close at
Probably not because of the non-disclosure agreement I don't want to wait like that
If you're comfortable disclosing your salary
You're welcome to do so
Caulking
I'll start it off while I'm sorry 45 thousand a year
And plus bonuses whenever
I will get a good story or something
So we know that Tony's other folks like Daria and Owen have substantially higher salaries than that
You know like a trip that's probably about like a
The equivalent of Owen salary now based on the size of Infowars
You know like I think that's a shockingly high salary for badonde a 2012
To be getting it Infowars I will say that one of the things that we haven't really kind of disgust because
Is it it's been glossed over for any number of million reasons but
This is yet another time where we've gotten the idea that you get a bonus
For a particularly juicy story and we know that juicy story does not mean
Like oh it's true you know it's
Did your b******* get traction you get a bonus
For making up things well there's there's even other layers to it to like once but on BB isn't an employee
Denny's was just a contractor or whatever
He's incentivized to come up with Juicy stories just to get all freelancer that point yet
And so you're not going to get paid anything
Unless this story
Is good and has legs and we can work with
And then Josh Owens in his piece of New York Times and other interviews he's talked about how
If you went out to do a story and it wasn't what Alex wanted you get in trouble
Yelled at by him it was not the narrative that you were supposed to deliver exactly like there is a very
Free clear I mean like what you're talking about is like a financial and emotional incentive system
Do like a make things more salacious than more
I are detached from the truth
It's almost a bad system it's a terrible system it almost seems like
Inevitable that it would come to what it's come to
So we get back to the matter of training and operation cover-your-ass comes up again
Relating to your work as a journalist
Promotion stuff like I said I was going to do my own but I
Training I should say
Like advanced
And Mike you know how use the
Email system everything else
Did you
Receive any training
Something to training concerning how to conduct yourself as a journalist
Once you arrived at fries be system
Oh just so simple just song
Operation cover-your-ass I mean like if you go to report something make sure you got
Documented facts so we don't
That is a big thing
And I and I just silence ironic
They actually use operation cover-your-ass
Yeah it was all Rob Ducharme
Just make sure you
Cuz I can
Yes
Okay and what did he explain
Batman
Batman basically if you are report something make sure you get
North Whitcomb
The salt trucks where it came from
And this way again like a
Explain early if somebody else
That should say CBS news for example said the sky is pink
Everybody says
Blue waffle
CBS News
Battle
So and we provide is if it's the article
There's always
The sources
When people just click on read the bottom
That's what I wanted media ignored because where we post something we had
Sausage
Like the documents eyewear
Example we had all the sources at the bottom
And even the video link
Description we always provide the song
So we can come back on us
This Is War reporting
This is what's been you know
Whitney also that was the main focus
Just make sure you can come up some wildlife
Baseless conspiracy or whatever the case and window proof behind
Okay
Let the system did not work
Apparently
America do not have sources on the bottom of all their articles this is ridiculous
Did the as he ever read one of the articles that his videos were likely not
Yeah I do love the moment though of like did you get any training
Papa papa
We go to bed
Operation cover your right
Told not to get sued
And yet here we are the best laid plans
If only he had before hand or a little confused about that
Uncle
Gave him some training
But it isn't cool
I don't know about this
You mentioned earlier that you'd receive some
A journalism train from your uncle is that right
Yes
And what's your uncle's name
Bobby Cooper
Cooper cooper like a
Co CDL
And mr. Trooper is Adventure
Mother's brother
He's not official language
She's been in the family a long time one of those type deals
Norwalk
Uber for Boston I don't know I don't know how to explain this to you
Who did he work for
One of The Piano Guys
Great journalist
Whereabouts
A problem
He said he work for several news outlets as a journalist
Yeah and I independent like you and I
Like it was
Something going on people go today and they need this promoted
He would
What is pure sources reach out to other media Outlets
Since I had this been going on
Anime
Used to set up a persuasive
Install the media
That's not a journalist
So you got turn wasn't raining from his uncle who isn't his uncle and wasn't a journalist
Journalism training from a PR guys
Who's not his uncle
Which I mean considering where he works that is the training that you might
Want this
Yeah I mean like a publicist type person is basically just trying to get attention to things
Liar Wars is essentially just an intention aggregator so
I mean it is appropriate it just not Journal journalist
Yeah it's his butt and he's not Uncle Bobby
We calling Koop
Bad
He also ran the radio station the patandi was on because all of these people
Am I correct that as for
Did you know
Did not work
Or
A
Media outlet that published
Information
Republic
Yeah you are
He was running the radio station
And we were CBS affiliate
He works for your radio station
He was our station manager
And he's the one
That Rihanna station and we are CBS affiliate
Okay
Okay and my uncle was a volunteer firefighter he also
Of the carwash
He does any number anyways my uncle doesn't actually have a job
But he trains me in journal
So when you're talkin about her no one talks about what their job is
Sprite
He actually has some details and I think these details actually reveal quite a bit about how things work
And how the broadcast is made
Your producer 40 is that right
Oh yes I will show show
Radio show
And
What did that
Entail
Algaecide patient when he's talking what I'm doing to get there early in the morning
I'll print up all the Articles from Mike eversource imaginable and
I would separate them into certain categories
And I'm so Bickley US news world news
2nd Amendment news stuff like that you can
Explains it right and what I'll do is I'll put them on his desk he'll go to the articles
Decide we want to talk about in the meantime while he's on the ear
Will have several computers going on and I do with tricaster and everything
977 the space preservation Act
The 2001
The back that up might got was a backup. The show
On-screen you think you did software this way you talked about me so I can coming out of his butt
This is from documents or so
Space preservation Act
I pulled up right from the DACA website
What radon
So
The shirt narcos
Yeah yeah. Uncle there but sometimes we pull up on screen
As he's talking about Airman General things like that
To be supportive
Queen show
Yo that's not we we we have a thousand things and ahead of time
You get stumbled on something
I could be on the microphone I can't I'll know that was
Hey truck 977
Yeah man if he stumbled on
Remember
Things like that and I mean that in that nature and also producing
Told him when I got a break and y'all got kind of nature
That's really helpful so
When when you were producing The Alex Jones Show
Would you be the guy in Alex's year
One of them yes
That's wild
And he's one of the people in his earpiece
That fog.
Blows my mind
Right but it doesn't mean it doesn't sort of work towards some of the ideas that I've had about
Like
Obsession with being teleprompter free is a little bit less impressive when you realize that he has producers
We were just feeding him things through his earpiece
Yeah like he has them telling him document numbers and documents and stuff like that
The Giver
It's like a magic trick where he has the appearance of knowing all of this stuff
When he's
Conceivably getting told those things
It's really just a different scale which is being able to speak and hear things at the same time
You could do with practice
Much better than easier than learning I mean he's comes from the televangelism
Farewell radio evangelism background
And I have no doubt that he seen somebody call out
Is that is there a Chabad in here tonight and Ben like I
I got what you're doing but don't even says one point like if he gets stuck on something
You know like there
There's like
Conceivably
You know even topics and stuff like
Here is a thing that you know like if you're running out of gas and you like
It's
There is a lot of cheating that could go on based on the description that bidani gives of how the
The earpiece producing
Panda
I would be surprised there's a whole lot of that
But beyond that but I also just did some important f****** work
While he was at Infowars
You also a reporter
When you were down in Austin so in addition to your producing responsibilities I take it you
Go out in
Create Khan
Correct
Yes I will
We'll take off
My mainly report was a man on a
Street we just go question the public what they thought
Certain topics that were in the media at the time hot you're hot topic like
No control abortion things like that matter
And also questionable quizzes like if they knew
Just wait a while
Two of the remnants of the
Things like that are nature
Who the vice president
The questions like that
The point was to get the Publix
Opinion of
What the topic
Say nothing to me you were going on
Officials
We're tired of hearing from the suits in the mainstream media we wanted to jaywalk
Do man on the street babe
Where we ask drunk people on the boardwalk silly question and trap them and make them
Appear dumber than they are haha
Here because I think I genuinely want to know how he sees the world
Because
It's
Weird
I don't know if you do
That's fair
I don't know I just feel like he sees things in that I don't know what is real in his world
Well he apparently has a show that he does about spiritual warfare and demons and stuff so that's why
I'm out
Okay yeah maybe I have a little more information than that then you do about why you don't actually want this
Possible is that the premise of the show
What
That you have more I thought you meant
At certain point
Batondy
I got let go
Sort of
You still
With Infowars but he was let go of his his actual position producing
Probationary. And ended up going back to Rhode Island
Okay
Relocate back
Yes
Raider drum brakes
Member of 2,000
I'm sorry
Yes about the
Thanksgiving
Screaming
The office
The first sound was off
Well let go
Journeys coupon
Fortune misunderstandings whatever case in the video
Specific reason why they let me go
Me and a bunch of the people
It's like normal.
He was dropped
McFly's gentlemen
And it's the nature of the business young meaning
Because we'd been entertained business and also
Mediabase
Don't know why
No
You don't know if I would ever
He'll pretty chill attitude toward today
Yeah it sounds like he got yelled at a bunch and then whenever they were like okay man we're going to
Get out of that
Call away
Well we got a lot of moving parts we won't say that we're going to keep you on as a correspondence so long as you are so
Several thousand miles away from us
And you give us juicy stories some reasons that he apparently
And one of them is a bit of a misunderstanding it's really just it's no big deal
Block
Sometimes
Scheduling conflict happen
I'll be in the foot
They're not that severe
Emotionally perhaps
Be at there was an agenda 21 conference
And I just mean to sustainable development that thing that they're calling it into 21
And batondy wife but he wasn't supposed to
What's your under
Specifically
In Elgin Texas
Since we go to recycle basic Jenny 21 then
Anna Jaques sustainability
Conference hearing
They were getting ready to go in the morning
Mission
Go
Yeah I was told yes
So what had to go out
Do you want
Get my suit tailor
So I had no knowledge later that
Auction changes mine
And I know so I had to
Yeah
Why'd you go easy
Chew me out and I'm like yeah I went because you told me you could remember that in the morning
Because yeah you're right yeah I did but
I told you
No I left the office
Okay I'm sorry and
Lumos understands like
And you know things like that which
Because I don't know it's just a bunch of
Things like that
Little miscommunication
The communicate I mean I love the forest of death I love the people there but
Communication
The appointment
Naproxen
So
It's a miscommunication
In the morning you told badonde to go
Taylor.
Realize that Alex didn't want him to go after all he comes back courthouse is like what the fuc
And then you're fired
It's definitely not a situation where there's more going on here I can't think of anything else that might be involved
Information nothing more going on well I mean
Is there more going on
No I wasn't
Tuportal
Recruit members
You make the report
Yeah because what will happen once
We outside
Some questions
So we have some questions and it caused a lot of people with no prize because we told people to
It's not what you think it is his Agenda 21
And the people young Texas you don't mess with
This is about
It was kind of an uproar they were yelling screaming
And yeah we're not going to do this
United Nation stuff yet
So
Someone the people in the car
And the police came in
They asked
This Friday at the time in the
Anyway
Big discussion
The police Roxanne
So we go back to dinner
Yeah you told me I could go
Weather miscommunication
And it's just a lot of miscommunications that because
And his defense all I mean it is such a huge
Such a huge operation I'm guessing that Alex's problem wasn't his presents the police
Involved in Alex's defense
I did start a riot the cops were called I got into a fight with a cop right
They could have something to do with those parts of my story
Solutely communication exactly the real the real breakdown was
Video of this somewhere I couldn't find the actual video of badonde at this event video of
After he got thrown out of the event
A.m.
It turns out the story is a little bit different so what happened was that
He called some lady who is there one of people involved in the the event
Okay so she asked the police
To remove him with police
The heroic I started a riot with my Texas Buddies
Add we overtook to the store
It is instead
Hey you suck and then they get kicked out
Somebody right now they've been happening at their event. So he was asked to leave
I don't even know
He's in trouble
Okay so yeah
So the story is now I went there I didn't get much
And then I got thrown out and then I got into a fight with the cops
Right at where is it if you understand the starting point was
Look I didn't know that Alex said I shouldn't have gone to Livermore
Different
Issue then what baby I would see is a fireable offense somewhere along the line
Alex
I like
Run-ins with the police are opportunities that have to be handled pretty smoothly with Alex
Loves to get into like a little bit of a confrontation with a with a cop
Yes I'm Savvy he knows how to maximize whatever you're going to get out of it
Not get into any trouble
Where summerlake batondy is not
That is a liability him being around cops and specially getting into a confrontation with him
Especially on being there under the auspices of the Infowars organization like
That's the only is negative be pretty pissed about it he's got the
The cloak of a little of Fame do it so they don't want to like a rest of it caused a big thing and that'll be a mess
Where is with badonde it's like man
We can take you away the Alex will have some kind of like inciting thing
That is like at least defensible like
You know he'll I don't think the police got involved but like we went to the DMV and refused to give his fingerprints or what
Whatever kind of principal you can stand on where is just being a dick to this lady
Show you ID and I can be a dick to that lady all I want right it's not doesn't have the same last offensively
So were there any other reasons
That Alex gave for letting you go already
And we know from Alex's that position that he let him go because he saw that Sandy Hook report he said Bishop
100% the reason that he was let go shut it down. Lee is no good
Apparently
Other than
With any other
Not right
I didn't report
Using the
Studio
Yeah my car
The new show forever case
He knew about it but he
I don't sweat nobody but you didn't
It was like you said was
A debate altogether about
He uses things
This is the reason
Yeah the other not in a man
But he did you know Steve will keep his correspondent so he didn't realize I was like
Complications of self self
There's apparently but Dante was using the studio for his own like show whatever
Believes he had permission and then a little bit later you did not have permission and this became an issue these are the reasons
Are you sleep like a whole thing makes perfect
Regards to Infowars now because
Clearly in his audition
He has proved himself to be an agent of true chaos
You know
While he's while he's there
He's showing up doing a show what's up dude
You want the Kraken but not in how hot it how so you send it back there and you like you can stay as a correspondent
We have a Chaos Agent that could be useful
Or keep you at arm's length that's always a good idea to have a loose cannon this all makes total sense in terms of
Like piecing together various people's versions of what happened but I do want to f****** contest and
He ended up winning over second-place because he interviewed Ron Paul into it like all this is going to be good
So he gets in at Infowars he has a tryout. I eat bombs it absolutely they do fight with
The cop at 8 to 21 conference studio for unauthorised recent
Obviously you want to just let him go course
S4mm
Basis of you like a freelance kind of stealthily Maybe
If it's worth it
Makes total sense and then you want to associate
More when he does stuff like goes to the Boston bombing course press conference at crowd of people
Yeah
I see you have him as like an employee not employee after that that.
Angela cover-your-ass what
Yep so that all makes sense
Yeah but there's something this is some prime funny stuff Alex
Didn't even have the balls to fire
Vedonde listen to this sounds like some
It was mr. Jones
I know he actually was weird
Because I'm nobody's New York
McClellan
Alex Jones coming soon because they checked my hands cuz I want to
Appreciate tell you I appreciate it
Unfortunately
Walks away then Rob do comes over
With what kind of face
Right they know something's wrong
And Rob do and Lady of the sea
Secretary I want Beyonce come we got to talk to you
Graywhale noodle
This is about
Yeah I know it was a sad Tupac really was
Devoid
Alex himself never Direct
I told me until I got on the phone when I left the place
I want a dementor knows exactly why and I mean
Discussion
After you quit me to do this
Sofia you forgot
So you guys what we know what we'll do this
The guy you need to go home
Safiya-malika Sarah
God be with your family cuz you said they don't to move down here whatever
Okay so
He said we'll keep yawning
Alright
Alex gave him the kiss of death wow
Milwaukee I love you we got along together
I'm going to get out of here in a locker room
So obvious that moment that might clear what was going on
Everybody seems to not be aware of how choreographed that is
I know it was you and he's free though
Ghostin pretty-much
Alex just I mean he's apparently pretty good at like preserving some image
Whatever like I do I don't want but Auntie mad at me no no no
Cry while you fire it no way they cried
I love the dundies
Fake person
They've known him for a couple months after the time he was there I got
Cops and everytime I think about it you claim to fame as you got an interview with
Ron Paul like comes on Alex's show
Collected depositions
Could be viewed as like a long-form rashomon
It's an oral history everybody's got their own views on what happened and where and how
None of it's real well here's the thing I think that baton to use the least sin
Pinnacle version of the story
This is what happened
But his interpretation
Is naughty I believe
That in his mind everyone is played by anthropomorphic animals
When he goes around Alex is a giant lion roars all that Rob Dewey
I'm just doing Lion King again
Who is booba
I think Owen Shroyer has got to be a poop
David Jones himself doctor
Antique china kisscartoon
That makes you a hyena
Oh
I'll take that so the question really is on everyone's mind
That is do you think that if you didn't
Need to move back to to Rhode Island
That's beautiful family do you think that Alex would have kept you on as an employee
And this is at Freddy's just being mean now
Conclusion of York
Call Whitney
Had your
Beyonce been willing
Police said that was a choice but family
Time is with Kelly and all that and
But he walked
And that's what he said you got a Bugatti
Do you got a one-year-old
So what you was right at home
And be flying back and forth every other week or whatever your name is
Supportive family in that manner
Financially yes
Being a physical father you know
Good on him for you know like stepping up to be a dad and all that but this is ridiculous the way
Galaxy
I would love to keep you around but I don't understand did but he just say that he was
Basically commuting from Rhode Island to Arlington Texas
I know it's not why all expired him but he should view that as like a Grace
This is just grasping at straws for ways to be a coward about firing people
For your kid
Contrary to popular belief I am terrified of calculus
I like conflict when its performance I don't like it when it's with the people I choose to be
And then I'll get mad and then God knows what could happen since we all carry
Knows maybe I'll Rapstar deny the Holocaust on my show
So now we finally get to questions that surround Sandy Hook and so he asks where
Where he was when he heard about the shooting
And it turns out
Direct answer
Where were you when you learned that there
It was December of 2012
What was definitely back in what island
I heard about the
It's funny because
Week before The Happening
Those on my radio
Showing
People back
This feeling
Argument outside
Feeling that
Is a heavy push for
They're going to be
Fox 4 digit I mean
And I remember that
Happen
I was on the show
And I
People called that
Like when you predict
Just like
And went away again
Before the kids body
Ebony
And I was quiet on ya
Happened
Well you know I'm not saying
Midnight
I know that
Strong objections
The effort
Controller
And I know that
You got to
You express that on
I wanted to ask you about
Do you remember
Today
Where you were when you
I took this at that
Yep they didn't have to do the whole thing 2 minutes of rambling about your feelings by gun-control Inlet
Have you and Lexie home
I mean like that's a direct question he asked question
Pretty pretty constantly cuz of that I feel like he trained with a
Elementary school guidance counselor or something
Something along those lines of like
II
Also he understand what you're saying
If Andy was funny
You would have said like I was on are crying I had tears in my eyes like Rob do fire and somebody
That would have been nice pieces in between when he was fired and when Sandy Hook
When are you started going out I'm sure he did but also like
I guessing when he says he was on air he has his own show
More doing his own stop right
Was Dan badonde interviewing Val venis
Little things that he did here and there in just
Like this it wasn't like he got fired went back to Rhode Island and then pop back up
Just for the the how big
Foia hearing
Yeah I don't know a lot of them are probably just very forgettable
Yeah it is it's just like
It is so weird to have him
Letgo sent back to Rhode Island
And then only a short. Later
Become so Central to their
Identity for a while though
Whatever he may have done as it relates to Sandy Hook his relevance with
Infowars end of the coverage does relate to the Wolfgang halbig for you hearing right which weren't
Immediate
Right there was a there was a bit of a lapse or a gap between the shooting the aftermath The Fallout the consumed
Pharisees
A man how big showing up like 2014 ish
So like there is there it there's a bit of
Time between is firing in that.
Bi that would be wild if it was just like right away
Auto Rhode Island yeah
But batondy is somebody was curious
Version of his own thoughts about
Sandy Hook in whether it was fake or not
He doesn't want to admit something
Well
But if Charlotte Russe cat has been revealed long ago
I know you can still see it
Yeah but maybe not it might be was all Theory that's
That nobody died at Sandy Hook
Correct
No
You've never said
We did that
I mean at first when I
I'm about to stop by my head was go to mile minute
And that's when Wolfgang halbig
Lynn Hughes.
School safety inspector
He started raising
I actually had my said something like that
Cancel.
Call Gee
On Twitter
Middlebury
What do you apologize
Store
Was
The fact that
Somebody
Had released
The purse
The identify
Find information of the
You didn't apologize for any view you had previously
Express
That no children
Yes that's why
Diana
But what you just say
With me that you have
Stated
That nobody died
Correct
Is there an extra
30 mine
Questions
That need answering
So there is a sort of ball rolling down hill aspect to this where it's like I didn't say that Noah
You did
Well yeah I did but I recanted and I apologized
Yes I did and also it was all just Theory alright this is not
Upfront this is
This is somebody who's not answering the question
He's like a bad murder investigation like did you kill that guy absolutely not I killed that way
I killed him a little bit kill bad guy a little bit if I apologize to his parents you didn't
Well I said I was sorry that their shoes got wet and I think that encompasses
Dummy killing their kids saying and if I did was an accident and in reality he killed me frankly I don't
Even know if he ever existed right
So look is asking question
Questions
This is a fact.
I never said
Is the kids dying
And I mean those with the state
If I made and I
Cuz I don't know
I wasn't there I don't know what
Peyton
Why no nausea
The game
It's all
Ever since then
Rena
Caribou
I mean and that's Murchison
What's
Anybody
Your Day desserts
Johnny I'm going to show you
You have
A document on your
Green
In which
You
Meeting is at dhanbad on D
Yep
And
As I scroll down to
The bottom
You see where you reply
Sandy Hook no one died
What's the date
Why 2000
Am I correct
That you stated that standing hook Noah
Well yes
Right and you didn't phrase it as a
Where did he
Sammy Diner
And that was
My question
So did you break that as a question
Direction
Did you phrase it as a question
Oh it's like it's like we understood you at the beginning of a
The command you know it's like a it's an invisible question apparently apparently
I mean in his mind I don't know if anything is cert
.
So maybe any statement is a quest
But this to me is I don't it's a bridge too far but I've really don't believe he could
Actually think this this is now
I know why we're here
It's ridiculous
Bike
Sandy Hook no one type is not a question
Title of my movie okay
Colon no one. Here is the way that I guess you could argue it's a question and I think is a terrible argument that I do
Don't agree with and I think wouldn't hold out
You could say that you're saying this
To evoke questions in people's mouth
You know there's questions around this not trying to make people share
People
Don't just ask question
You need an instigator
Someone to say something that is I don't know
Potentially doable on the guy telling you to get out of the cave
Call shadow puppets
So when you're questioning that
He's a flat
Flag doesn't mean people don't really die
Since 9/11
Right
You're saying that 9/11 was a
Swagbucks
Really died there
And then
Jay the person who you're interacting with
You just said the shooter and victims in Orlando where Act
And then you clarify
Sandy Hook no one died
911 / 3,000
Right
Are you know what the
That's cuz the FBI
If your reported
They reported the deaths
There was no debt
I thought you just told me before that this
Supposed to be a question
This is the question you're asking
Did anybody die scene
And then bring up 9/11
Three people died
I just want make sure I understand
Are you telling me
That
When you tweeted
Sandy Hook no one died
You were
Asking a question about whether people
Or you referring to an FBI report
Holy question
Okay
So this was just you throwing a question out there
The question out there was that what I'm supposed to take away from all the stuff he said
Yeah I guess so because
This is incoherent as an answer
911 no one died at Sandy Hook
And so you're just asking the question did people die at Sandy Hook which is not how most people read that safe
And then when that sort of doesn't sound like it makes a lot of sense
He brings up the FBI report from the Adan Salazar article on Infowars
I have that is not something that is
Jermaine to asking questions that's ascertaining
Definitive authoritative evident you're saying you have
That you said was true
No it's all convoluted and it is because he just doesn't want to own up to the fact that he was doing
Neither would you if you're in a deposition where somebody's being sued for
Be fine with that
Because in Tampa dandi shoes he has nothing to lose
Oh that's a good point he is not being sued
That there is there is this bizarre sort of loyalty that is
I think sincere on Gandhi's part-time Alex
And I think that he's protecting Alex a little bit with his caginess about these answer
Because I like
There is just cut-and-dry evidence of what he did and what he said
Questions in what have you when there is really no
Cost to himself
To just own up to
Yes I believe those things at the time I was wrong is very dumb
I put this out there
And I regret it and I've apologized for it
The only real cost is to Alex because then he'll be like why did you believe these things right now the coverage on
Goes that direction fairly easily
I wouldn't have done two things that he did
I might have gotten into a fight with a cop in Elgin Elgin
I I mean if it's this really child
Come see the water parks
This does
These this whole thing
Really
All of the laws and depositions and stuff
Have made me really want to scrub every last bit of my social media and anything
Because
Just the idea of being in a deposition and I don't even know what it would be for
But if a lawyer starts reading a tweet I'm like
I got it at whatever it is I confess
Whatever you said on the podcast is bad enough
That's some of the stuff taken out of context that
Well Imma have to leave no evidence that either of us ever existed dad oh no sorry
So
Blondie went to Boston
He want to the press conference
Made a big splash rental Wars and talked about this a little bit
You presented yourself as
A journalist
A member of the press
Yes
And you Warrior
Press pass to get into the
And
Smirnoff
That with the rest of the
From the other media
And you know what
When it's
You got jumped them cuz thing is just note
Trenton press conference
You got to be
Real quick to get you a question
Alright
Governor Patrick asked
Is there any questions
Is that yes
And the question you asked is
Is this another false Flags
Staged attack
To take our civil
Please correct
Weather in Pomona homeless
Australian Street
Stick the hands
You don't dispute that you
Ask is this another false flag staged
Attack to take
Nope that's what I said
Another
What was the prior
False flag
Staged attack you will refer
I'm just asking if you have one in mind
Not being drunk I'm just saying like you do with the long way
I'm going back from the Gulf
Pumpkin into operation gladio
The reichstag fire
1932 woodtick Wednesday
Foot doctor
Take away your civil liberty
Germany to go to Warwick
And the Gulf of Tonkin wasn't used
2 take away anybody's
Civil liberties
So I'm asking what was the prior
Swag States attack
What was the
The prior false
Swag stage
Attack that you were
In Oklahoma
In Waco
No no absolutely not
Of all the ones
That one was real I say now here
Brightview
God I love that it all I need a book and then he rattles off the same three ones that we here at
Every single if I can time do you have a book
Nothing to say
Because it's like
I have to fill up this book
Or something I think that's what he knows the implication that I took away from it
You got a book
I don't know anyone
You can write in the margins
So goes down to Connecticut
Looking for a soul to steal
I am
How big was just asking questions to
Do you like that
Phila people just answer his questions
He would have stopped asking up
The first time you were
Recall hearing about what
How big was
In connection with
Trip to Connecticut
No I mean his name is Ray
Through the media like everybody else
And it was every meeting match
Especially start at
Questions and
The quest medium rituals
That's not even
Chocolate man that the time
The first time I talked to him was the dammit
Okay
In your testimony
Best you can recall is that
Prior to that day
Mister how big name was circulating in the media
And you became aware
Yes was it circulating in the main
Remediate
Oran
Alternative
Media like for example
Call my daughter calls.
Prior to meeting him that day
Did you have an understanding
That he was
Connected in some way
A story surrounding
No he was out
Then he gets visited by
By the state police
Threatened
Danny comes out
Questions answer the questions and I'll go away
I don't how many times we had that on video
I went it was on it for what
How many times he comes to answer my questions I'll go away
Principal
The most bizarre stuff
That Witness
The song that said this was the most bizarre
Uncle
Yes
This is like
Bizarre because I find it difficult to understand
Or believe that batondy doesn't understand that these are fake questions
Have you stopped beating your spouse kind of question
They're not designed to be answered they're designed to not be answering used as
Evidence the people aren't answering question
Yeah I don't
Know if I believe that he doesn't understand that dynamic
But part of me is willing to believe I don't know man I feel like I've got a fairly good ear for sincere
Charity
And it really does feel like he thinks that he's
If he gets the answers
Then he will like how big is acting in good faith and just wants answers
Feels like that's what we got because he does feel like that's help adande views himself also as somebody who is
If he does get the answers
Then he will stop you know exactly with Alex it's a very
Obviously he has no belief that these are some to your questions that need answers this is just an
Feel like there is a possibility that he legitimately thinks that
If someone would just
I'll be up front and answer these questions we wouldn't have to go through all this
But I don't know if that's being naive on my part 2 I mean it's hard it's hard because we're dealing with
Infowars people obviously
But at the same time I really I mean it's like
If I can't trust my ear on this one I feel I feel like I don't know if
Willing to believe that there's a sincerity to at then other folk that I've heard but I'm not willing to commit to it
I will say this
Of all the people but dondi is the one closest to me saying
He sincere
I think
Think that's probably true
I mean
Major League should heads to be fair
Was fairly sincere
Well yeah I mean I suppose more about everything
Sincere in a calculated
I'm going to be good that this it's not my fault I was very clear
There is documented evidence that I said stop it
Smiling in his deposition
Actually I watch that you was not
Rob do sent but on d-22 Connecticut to that's why he
Gerentes Fela soul
And not only did batondy report on that he also gave testimony.
The school board apparently
This is weird Okay
And so how did you
How did you know
To go
Cover bad
Board of Education
Who are Infowars
Did rod do
Send you on that assignment
They said they're going to be doing
Things on that side
What is the cover
Was going on
And I went down there
Did that
Did they tell you what it was that was going to be here
I don't I don't remember
I mean I know it's just
Instagram now
Wolfgang halbig zoby down there
That's what I first met
I had no clue
School safety consultant
But probably I had no real knowledge
Exactly
Minuteman Press
And I know that you now
No or believe
Becky was asked
Did you know that
Prior to going to the board of ed
What's up you were presented
Themself
Unicorn
But it was Rob dude who sent you their correct
There's activity going on in 71st off that's why
I know
Went down there
Injustice video game
And I spoke
Gun range
Please don't
Is tragedy please don't
Blame the Second Amendment
For this tragedy
Money-wise to the school board
That's what it was about
Obviously the board of education does it
Have any Authority at all
Directions to Ironstone
Just like me trying to make
A
Statement so people don't criticize are demonized
The Second Amendment
Because we know how a critical attitude
These days
And you were doing that in your capacity as a
As a journalist
Testimony that was on my own behalf that was not to do it didn't strike me to do that
Better even though I did
Citizen
If we were in your press pass
Oh yes several oh my God
Yeah so it turns out the Constitution can be overridden by a school board
I mean
There's no reason
To testify about how great the Second Amendment is to the school board unless you're trying to just get attention
Be an a******
Distract from the issues
It's it's really a bit it's really a strange impulse
Thought about that
And you know it is a strange impulse but the more I think about it the more it's like
A different form of laziness that I wasn't aware of you know what you think about
Everybody that you don't like being a globalist and connected to the ultimate Evil is your work
It's got to be involved that means you don't actually have to look
For an organization that can do anything you can just go to any government organization to be like what
Somebody's going to hear it and let me piggyback on that the laziness ideas like
What better place to
Grandstand to a captive audience and like
School board meeting and I made a lot of people have learned that in the covid time you saw the videos that have gone
Viral I think that it's laziness on another level like
This will be cheap attention-grabbing and seemed like
Kind of like relevant in bombshell
Yeah I'm telling truth to power
Meaning to a school board and and
And
I've got my minutes. I get 10 minutes to do the thing that I want to do and I have my press pass on
But I am not here my capacity as multiple press passes on no just so you know
One of the things that Infowars gets a lot of leeway on
Because of is that they are sloppy f****** organization
And nobody knows what's going on left hand doesn't know what the right hands doing it's all a mess it really doesn't feel like there
Already hands
Well
We know that Rob Doucette baton Dave there
So there's one element of coordination that is editorial planning in some ways
This next clip reveals that there is maybe a bit more micromanaging than Isleta
No no
Email you sent him
Day earlier
Add subject Don dmos
Question does man on the
Bright
And you were
Running by him
Questions you
Considering ask
Sparta to man on this
Yes
One of those man on this
Street
Segments
Concerned
Questions about
School drills
Stripe
Any other can
Concern
Town hall and conventions
Right
A series of drills and one was that
Immaculata
Out of school
The witness
From the Press Box
Abject
Schools
Or
Other public
Safety drills
Got abjection. By all means
Cuz I think it's very important
Officially
Fire officials
Cuz I was part of Joe's before
I mean like when I work at the airport we did
Why do drills like a plane crash I would lay there with a
Tagamet to tell Liam he
And I think he's writing for
Prep the people for
Happened
So I don't
Botwin
Open to Intermezzo drill
Something similar happened not every time
When is a drill frequently something
Ashley Mario
No coincidence I don't know
Napa
Autograph
Although
In certain situations
Boston
Marathon bomber
It was
Yes
In the Mist
Do response
To you
Very good
Also add
And then he proposed
Additional Quest
Free to ask about the SEC
So there is running questions by Rob do approval
You adding more questions and
That is
A level of intent a level of organization centralization of content
Obviously I don't think it goes to the extent of like everything is checked off and approved
You know they're not that rigorous but there is
More of that than they like to pretend
It's all shooting from the hip and whatever happens happens for Alex doesn't have a teleprompter but he has producers in his ears
Feeding himself and telling them
Things to say and information nobody plans anything but oh there's emails where you're going over
Uber in advance man-on-the-street question
That the Kraken is going to ask people right
No there is there is more going on here than that is makes
The whole institution of the organization more culpable
Then they like to believe we're like to put on I mean it's unreasonable to think that
They can grow into what amounts do I don't know half a billion dollars a year business
Without
Any kind of that like
It's pure improv the whole thing we ever make that calculated I don't they want you to believe is
Like the content side effects after shooting from the hip and then the business I don't even deal with any of that stuff
Another winning
Right and it's just delusional it's it's a fiction
So Wolfgang halbig had an issue
With the police
Started
He was asking questions about Sandy Hook in the police done came to him and say to you cut it out
You will not be asking these questions interesting
Island Brandy heard that story and then was like oh yeah definitely true
Let me see how big told you that
Connecticut state trooper
Merced come to his
Yes
Go shooting
America
You know what the
Don't understand
Police officers
Guess what
Did you just hear him say that the school board members had sent police office
Yeah
In-N-Out
Did did you do anything to confirm whether or not the
School Board
Edison police officers
Settings
It's always I mean obviously I couldn't
Nashville proof or anything like that even I could cuz he's
School Board
No we went to
Whatever was
Yeah show me directions
The school board
No I know but
If the school
Portage police officer
Did you think to ask
School board members who were there but that was
I don't want this was I don't
Laughter
The testimony
I don't know
That didn't occur to you that was your
No
January
Infowars press badge
So when you get journalism training from you're not Uncle PR guy is he's not a journalist sometimes you hear claims
Seems like
The school board sent the police to harass me
And you don't think follow-up questions or like corroborating information right is important cuz like
If you believe the story why wouldn't you ask the school board and like
Is there comment on it
It's ridiculous
You don't scratch this cuz you're not curious
And you probably don't
Woman on baby subconsciously or consciously
Don't want to run the risk of having probable cause to think of the person you're talking to the liar
Yeah
It's safer
As far as the cover-your-ass goes it feels like the jondy is wearing those comical long
We're with the butt flap
Wide-open just out in the cold tundra mean while trying to cover other
People's acid weirdly
Covering for how big covering for Alex
That's weird
Yeah
So it was reported
When batondy and how they came to town
In Connecticut that the circus was coming to town
Now
You'll never believe what reporting this was based on
Why having a parent
Target
Mr. E
Am I correct
You said that
It was reported
Betty big circus
Christmas coming to town
And that we're all bunch of
When we got there
Am I mind my business
Some jackass
The circus is in town we don't want
It was reported
Your aunt know that you bring
Instructions to Tottenham explain to these guys
I'm here just cover
I'm still learning what's going on
What does empower
And they were actually giving Wolfgang a real heart
Kevin and
The other people
Corner so big
I mean like seriously I do my job
Piss off
It's just irritating Wolfgang's right now
I predict
Yeah I just wanted to
You answer my question I was curious
Where that reference came from it sounds like
Are bystanders
Stop
Made a comment to you that
Yes
It reported
Listen
New York Times
Some a****** of the street
What's the difference Brook porting is reporting
Fishes
Unfair if you say the word on the street was literally
Just some random person I mean this is just an extension of you like random tweet equals all the left
Believe this thing
And elevating whatever random thing is is useful
Very sad
So we know that the the state troopers were the ones that came and harassed Wolfgang
Bye
Maybe it's story isn't very consistent even within the clip
That he is oh my God
How old is Cher
Florida
Definition Eros
And if I ever come to Newtown I mean
Mister Kyle big preferred
Not just Connecticut state
Troopers but deputy sheriff's
Florida is having going
Did he describe
Two different
One in which Connecticut state
His house in one in which
Florida deputy sheriff's
I can't make
That's what I was asking though
Earlier you stated that he told you that Connecticut
What's up
You said that
Lorraine Franco
What
Bananas
My questions are aggravating
No not you another
Questions just the whole Factory General
Your what
Soon
The gun
Tsunami
People some now but don't be getting himself a little bit mad man the
Gates have become open and it's weird that the floodgates opened because he stopped himself from saying something
As opposed to this entire time where he is just rambled
That he's violated his own First Amendment rights and that's making him everything that he's fought at
Against his entire life
Dnce
Subconsciously if I had to guess, I would say that he's being confronted with this information that
Clearly indicate that he should have seen through Wolfgang s***
A lot earlier baby immediately in the present having a conversation with him maybe all this is bulshit
And
That probably doesn't feel good and so in order to sort of deflect from that
I'm just starts ranting and spoiler alert seems to be calling the parents of murdered children Howard is now
Things are aggravating
No not you another question
It's just the whole Factory General that
Your what
Soon
Tsunami
People
I mean what the hell is wrong with you
Is the first name of Medicine
Second Amendment
You heard how the hell you go sue a gun
You mean wouldn't what is going through your damn head
Poshu Ruger 41
So you can sue Nissan because they killed a bunch of drunk driver killed a bunch of
I mean what the hell is going on I'm x yet
And I'm a parent so don't give me that
Dammit
I would rather have money my son's going to school way as a soft-sided
I feel moontimes
Kentucky
What the hell's wrong with
WD
Okay cook spoiled
These kids
Korean Nazi camp
Free speech
Yeah we know
Bloomberg
Behind
With all the money
We know the money
Is auto reject
5 hours night time
What does bulshit
New Orleans because I was on there and do my job is reporter
Protective
First Amendment
Fender Wolfgang halbig
Do his job
That's if he's wrong or right he's asking
That's the first amendments that people need to understand that and start respect
Bottom line
The no damn people at
Biltmore
I'm going to speak my my
And I mean that this is bulshit that after
6 hours in my freaking time
First Amendment
And I'm getting
Stupid questions have nothing to do at all with Sandy Hook
The try to pay me as some kind of knuckle
And I mean not let's just get to the gameplay
I'm done
Presley I respect you
About the coldest
Surfer died
The Weave to
Plaintiff's
This case
And in
Case against
Gum infection
It's called
The Second Amendment why would you
Were you referring to the
20 tips in this
This case
I just listened to you for awhile
But I would ask
Trials in my question
Here
Cuz I'm just responding to
Merced
Iron City to just stay
We got the planet
In this case
I in the case again
Remington Arms
Work hours
Is that what you said
Anybody
The Second Amendment yes you're okay
What are protected those choke
Bottom line enough is enough
Enough is enough of this b*******
Yeah this this so
Wasn't a victory for Infowars I don't think
Maybe the messaging wasn't quite on point
Maybe exactly where you'd want it to be I can see where the conflict with the cops
And Elgin happen I respect you
No we'll be forgetting you what's wrong with all of you sue happy people no beef against
This is total b******* and a waste of my f****** time enough of this nonsense now I love you you're great you're the best
The best lawyer who is destroying the Second Amendment
He brought up something that's such a good point in such a f***** up part of of the human brain
Rain and everything we.
With the armed guard at his kids school he feels safer
When you when you hear what the actual way to become safer is you know improving communities
Distributing wealth in places that needed all of those kind of things fairly abstract
Feel safe
Obviously putting an armed guard makes you less safe
But it's
Feels safer and such a f*****-up way our brains work something with like
In countries like the everyone has nukes we're all safer
Intuitive
I don't know what maybe it's maybe it's some part of our Evolution you don't like
At a time I don't want being armed at 6 right
I don't trust any
Sticking close to me why did we leave stick and Club days is the biggest question of all
Wistful photos for those days
And you consider this to be a waste of your
Right
It is waste
Because of which this about what is this about
Why am I here why am I because I was there
As a reporter
Protected
Stupid
Under the First Amendment if nobody wakes
Straight to Hell
It might not be put on Wreck-It I don't call with anybody
My only governor
My only God is Jesus
Why do you care about the amendments
Jesus Christ
And I protected by the First Amendment
And I'm at the fender of the 2nd
And the thing is
The two things of being tired
Okay is the First Amendment
In the Free Speech
Because we're not
Establishment media
And also the second of his being
Why would
Remington
Diculous
Against
I grieve
Peritonitis
Ensign
Yeah even though you said that it
It was fake right
No I didn't I
So you never said you never said that ain't nothing to do
Never said that
When I was thinking about was looking at yours
Did you ever say
You're making me miss
Sandy Hook
My questions
Question
That's that's about as close as we're going to get to Timmy doing
What is your job what is your child is getting a little abusive
Baby Maddie is just sort of letting a little bit of like I'm going to be blunt now
Did you say this about like if he's only answers to
God ways to care about the Constitution and the amendment right it's because
The understanding that someone like him has and a lot of the militia Patriot hard-right communities
Is that you know it is all just
God
I've either way the Bill of Rights is like
Divine
In some nature and then
All of it is it it's not a delineation of rights that you have because of the Constitution
The government can't do to you you have those rights with or without the Constitution because of divine right
God gave you those right
Right that's partially why they are there against communism because it seeks to destroy God and those rights would
Go away
It's not contradictory in the way that maybe you were think
I mean either way it's it's still worshipping a golden calf at the end of the day so
Degree inasmuch as like if you believe that these are god-given rights than the government not right
Respecting them can't take them away from you either
It just puts you in a different situation where you have a hostile government
It's like
I mean
Would you already understand that like
100 people voted on the Constitution
A tale it wasn't it wasn't like
Voted on
It was the government and writing a constitution that the couple of them were mules literally literally
Different types of animals
So I will say that I think that Maddie is really actually being pretty effective in getting batondy mad just asking
Bread questions and not not letting up I like it
Did you
Say
Sandy Hook was a hoax
Yes or no
Okay but if you did I'm sure you were grieving your heart out for those
Families when you said it
Objection
Alright mr. Madonna
What the hell is gun rights
Why we talking
Second Amendment
This is not case against Remington
It's all part of the same Damned
Get off this
It's okay
It's part of tack in the front
This whole thing is about
Probably doing money
It's about talking first
Dearly people
These children
Makes me sick to my damn
Really simple
And I'll get anybody out there anybody
That and you can attack us
Intrust Amendment
The very
America
Makes me sick to my games
These people need to realize we had not gone right that we are not submitting a substance in the world
Straight to Hell playing the temple we are not going to give up outrage
Because people want to do everything
I want to protect my children never choose in the future
Country
The ever happen again
Had to do that we need to arm the school's not the summer
We need to protect our children with
The Second Amendment
Israel did a 1974 only to school shootings attempted happen
Ottumwa
Are you wanting Emily so much and what it is real neon ball the school
And Young
Sandy Hook gun free zones do you wonder why
100 lb
Nobody would have done.
You want me to come on
I thought mistaken
Are you ready to move on
There is an interest
Sing I think maybe intentional strategy that Maddie is employing and that is letting him talk because but he does
Seem to be someone who
Whether it's that sincerity or there's a lack of guardedness
That a lot of these other folks who have been deposed have
There is a decent chance that he will just start talking and accidentally say some s*** that
What are you saying
He already is giving up like
This operation cover-your-ass stuff to the internal workings
I like
The the earpiece and the way that they Coach Alex or like
Feed him information the fact that there is
Like editorial conversations about what questions to ask a man on the street
Like he's already bit like that I feel like there's more information
It is accidentally come out
Because of him talk to the pile him calling parrots cowards
Yeah that was
How dare anyone defend them
While
Yeah
Wild I think that you gained a lot just by letting him
Go
But unfortunately that doesn't leave very long deposition
Yeah I didn't repetition interrogators like a talker and also hate it.
More than anything else
Yeah I feel for an end this is what I think is an amazing
Tang and I think we should all be more grateful towards stenographers
How
Can you hear all of that
Let It Go through your brain through your fingers to the type of machine well actually losing your f****** mind
Let me save this as having difficulty with the
Are you stalking and so they they did have a conversation about this
That she would get a copy of it I wish I could do it get a clean transcript later
This might not be such a situation like I need a break
She probably not catching everything
So this next clip
I know I don't know what I can describe this is playing who's on first about a tweet
Grape is so frustrating
In October
Was it your view
That Sandy Hook was a hoax
Auto Club
Why don't
Long time ago I have no clue
Showing you exhibit number 12
This is a tweet
That YouTube
Tweeted
On October 21st
Incorrect
Yes
Okay
And you say and this is when you were working as an Infowars correspondent correct
Yep
And you say
I added a video to YouTube
Playlist
Then there's a URL
Shocking
Sandy Hook now revealed as a hoax
Did you
Quito's words
Did you tweet those words
Okay
And did you
When you tweeted them
Did you believe
We did then
That has been revealed
Ibis
When the U2 I didn't we
YouTube
Let me finish.
When you upload to Youtube
YouTube Anam
Twitter war correspondence
So when I upload a YouTube video
YouTube switch it out
I uploaded
Title the video
Assurant
I don't know
What
The title of the video
I don't know
Video
That was the title video
No idea what it's about
Uploading correct
Yeah just play the video you guys
I'm asking about your Tweet
And
You then
We did
YouTube mutant sweet this
Video
Back then
Facebook
That look though went YouTube
Disconnect
Twitter
What's that
Want the Twitter into
Okay mr. E
You knew
Because you knew the connection between your YouTube account on your Twitter account
When you uploaded the video
Weeded from your account correct
Dirksen argumentative
Didn't you know that
So what
White white people
Did you know
When you uploaded the video
YouTube
At your Twitter account
Between
This week
I don't know
Arrest this man
Infuriated I appreciate that honestly I actually appreciate this
Mainly because it calibrates my sincerity ear
And when I'm going to think he was being sincere earlier I think I think it's very clear when he's not being sincere
Here at least
I don't know
I never heard of it
Sambal YouTube some of that's being a dick but some of it also is like technically yeah alright I didn't write
Like that tweet
Video
If you use eat is Vaudeville man
Truly incredible about that Exchange
In the middle of it as I come out
I admire Maddie not being broken together but Brinkley
Put on dear Aunt Tamara
What is this got to do with
Okay so that
Bats
Not questions
The right the doctor
And the responder is emmerich
Joan
I don't see Daniel badonka
I'm here
Martha
Might enjoy
Because nothing
White person
Why am I bi question
Because it's
Do this is defendant
I'm here on my own behalf
Because
I want to answer this question
Noah personal
Get to the point
With
Why the washer
That's none of my business
You guys now
None of my business
A reporter
Protective
Who buy the first
That's it
Okay that's my statement that's my
Testimony whatever you want to hear
And I'm not denying the videos about the emails
Nobody's tonight
It's not secret no he's trying to conspire things
This is orange
So what what more do you want
Are you doing
Ask my next question
I'm going to need a small time out for bathroom break it
You're a robot you f****** piece of s*** also no disrespect
Your mom looks donkey Hooves no offense to your mom this is this does feel like
Take one of those Northeast assholes
Go fuc yourself you a piece of s*** I hate you I hate everything about you your good guy
For the rest of my life
Yeah the robot alien
How is it that you're not mad at me
Box out of you and you're just on your on your focus
Tim going on here are you if I understood what you were doing no disrespect
So we get another tweet
Being discussed here
Tweeted that on August 20th
Incorrect
And you type the words
Sandy Hook
Was staged actors
And
Is that because
As of the time you sent
That was in fact
What you believe that Sandy Hook was
Was staged
Good actors
That I've been planning that a lot of question
Both ends mean
Nyan Nyan
And apologize
I'm just asking you whether or not it
The time you sent this
Tweet
I do
So you allow for the possibility
That you may have typed
Sandy Hook
Stage actor
!
Without actually
Believing
I'm not sure
It could be it might not be
I don't remember what
Bobby Knight
Well I'm just
You typed it so
If
State-backed
Would it be reasonable to assume that that's what you in fact believe
McDonald's
I am
You may be right I'm just trying to
You know I don't miss
Sparring with me
Instead of
Just telling me
Whether you believe that
That's all
Okay whatever
Change my to
That's totally fair II
That's all I want to know in in so I'm just running it
Make sure I understand that
After the time
Although you may have later chain
Which as you say is complete
Within your rights
How to change your opinion about
I just want to know
Weather
I can presume
That because you
Actors
In fact
Believe at that time
Correct
Then I don't know exactly what my
Why do my boosters
Well then that means it's infuriating I mean it's it's basically like here is a statement that they made in the past
Does that mean you believe X
FedEx
Determine one way or the other because we can't go back in time I don't really know
And even if I did think that it's illegal for me to think that I mean and I don't think that now
Question in the past I'm confused as to whether or not he believes
That be I don't think that anymore
Is not an admission that he did think it
It's implied but not necessary
Well I guess if you say I don't believe that anymore it does strongly indicate that you did believe it before cuz it
Believe something different in the past
And not have believed it you can say I don't believe that now it doesn't imply that you
True didn't believe it but where you believed it before
I don't know who cares he's just it it's it's infuriating the way they can't answer a direct question
Medically for someone who insist that not answering questions is it indicative of guilt
That is that is the the Hallmark
Of a right-wing person
Is just the thing that they are
Is the thing they hate the most like Bedrock most important Prince
Suppose are usually actually incredibly negotiable everybody should have gun rights but I probably would take
Take guns away from antifa
We come to the end basically this is just a little bit of the deposition left
And subjective some like Communications comes up
And Maddie asks when the last time he talked to Rob do was
And this
Is why you let
Batondy just talk
Because this is a very bizarre admission
What was your most
Communication with
With Rob to
Merry 4th of July
No I'm sorry I'm not too long ago and text him to tell him
Megashare
Subpoena
You have that texting your
No
I'm sorry
Well
Did she receive
Tina after you got rid of your last
No
What
I'm sorry
When we
You haven't
Yo what's going on
Subpoena
You know you f***** up just a bit
Come on man
You deleted the text we know
July
And so did you have your new phone by
No that's not
Nothing to do with the other emails
Text whatever
I text your text message
Mr. Abdul
This one here has new flame
Isaac Rob doomsday until I got served
Right
It's a what
Why don't you produce that text to
Because I don't have it
Did you delete it
Yeah I believe
Car mobile.
As of the time you sent that text
Do something
I do it right after I text
He said delete it
Do you know how
Oh yeah
We have to do
Stuff nowadays
Show me the picture understand
You got the subpoena in July twenty
Right
You got yourself
Sometime after that
Right
I don't
You register mobile.
Correct
Think of the subpoena.
Yeah you read it
You knew that it
Instructed YouTube
Communication
With you
Including Mr do
Correct
Yeah but that's top rated
In
You then texted Mr do about this loss
And then you deleted that text
Yes
Oh my gosh subpoenaed what do I say
He said you asked him what do I do and he said I don't know what to tell you
This isn't indicative of somebody who doesn't know enough to lie
You know like
He doesn't know how bad that looks know
He has on this episode episode this deposition
Memes about like a habit of deleting messages and stuff like that
So it's not out of the ordinary for a behavior that he is described already
Bart
The circumstances of this look
Very bad
Genuinely believe him when he says that Rob do told him I don't know what to say but there's no way to know
Exactly demand Rob do turnover
But
I would have been obviously of course they deleted it makes you look real bad
Yeah hey real quick you want to do some witness tampering over-the-phone you mind giving me a call and then leave
Record of it
That's why you're use burner phones if you're in a criminal organization
Talk about a criminal conspiracy over the phone
This
Is
Did not
Other lawyer makes a decent point and that is like there is an implication here that
You're saying that he deleted this message to try to cover something up or hide something
And that
Not necessarily demonstrated like men's Raya isn't there like intent
I don't feel it necessarily from badonde the act itself
Is problematic like I said I believe but I believe that he regularly delay
Delete this text
That makes sense to me
And I don't think it untie and I very much doubt that Rob do wood
Witness tampering
Over the phone I'm sorry I just think that might be a step too I think he would but I also think that he
Vedonde
It's chaos now the question comes up when did you last speak to Alex
And
This is a revelation 2014
When was the last time you communicated anyway with Alex
O-over year ago
What was that commute
We Naturals deposition
Because I I was
Wow
Toby Donna River Falls New York
Mr. Jones called you after
What is deposition
Stay off Media
Does Megyn Kelly work
I don't go on Megyn Kelly show
Disgusting
So
He called you
About a year ago
After his deposition
Are you awake about a week. Even less than a week after the deposition
Okay
And
You understood that he was calling you you because
It may have appeared to you that he sold you down the river
This is more Bob stuff
I'm kind of a weird on but he doesn't use burner phones
Hey don't snitch
Joe chocolate oats a s***
I'm sorry excuse me sir are you saying in this deposition
That the main defendant
Cold you
Following a deposition in his deposition Alex tried to downplay severely
He's barely an employer already know the guy are you really
Because batondy was mad about that characterization of their relationship to Alex had to do damage
Control
And at the same time be like hey also don't talk to anybody
Weird line that's a weird thread
You know because you have to I mean you're going to try and smooth things over because you want him to stay quiet
But you also have to be like if you talk I'll kill you you know like that kind of thing here's what's fascinating about this
Pedotti's experience of it is the same as his firing
Alex was calling because he felt bad about how he cares for what a good guy
You know what
He didn't need to do that you need to call me on some level
I know he thinks he thinks Alex called him because he was right
Definitely
You understood that he was
Calling you because
It may have it
Here to you that he
He sold you down the river
Is deposition
Yes
Sold you down the river
Well he was just sad
United I worked for him then
We got different things he didn't understand
We will rob do screen
I don't need to repeat that
Yeah but the fact that you do
He was worried you may a
Selling you down the river is not
In the deposition
That's what I'm asking
That he was
Concerned about
Who's concerned that
He's so mean.
I saw them down the river
The Beast
A misunderstanding
Okay so
He was concerned that you may have
Is deposition
By suggesting that you hadn't really
Correct
And
He also instructed you that if anybody contact
About San Diego
Not the same
Yes the mainstream media
Did you say the meteor just say anybody
Median job means
Schmedium
So it's
Notable that Alex doesn't disclose this until he's asked about it and the other deposition news
Maybe I did I don't know
This is Shady
Donnie doesn't realize it's so shady just like with the texting and deleting
Like he doesn't realize what he's saying is is like almost probably
Shocking
2 for a lawyer to hear like
What
You're telling me
Alex
The person who this cases against
Contacted you to smooth things out with you about things he said in the deposition
And also told you not to talk to the mainstream media
This is
Let me ask you a question have you ever seen Law and Order
Or l.a. law or Boston Legal or any number
Movie The Lincoln Lawyer
A Few Good Men
You name it
And they're there
And in every law show their like
Don't tamper with the witness cuz it's going to look bad no matter what contacting batondy
Especially since it's probably been a long time since they spoke is a very inappropriate Act
Know if you know the context of their relationship just the call is witness tampering
It feels like at least the intent is
I don't want you to be mad at me because if you're mad at me it's more likely that you'll say things because I've been take just to me
Trying to smooth things out at the same time tell you to shut up
I bet I can't tell you to shut up Megan Kelly Lord me into the situation
It's bad things happen when you talk to the media what a great survey
Like you to talk to my friend who the lawyer how my god did you acknowledge
That you had
Felt
A little bit like
He had misrepresented your
Affiliation
Yeah oh yeah it works.
One of his Warriors and whoever was next
Set the time
And he was
I felt I was so low I told
What happened
Are you got yourself the meeting
Fumigation edict favorite
That wasn't
About children
There's a miscommunication there's no big deal
I
I mean
Yeah that is
A little sad
Tacular
It's a bummer it is Eddie's kitchen level is Obama
Because these people are these people but nothing if you just heard this about like
I don't know high-schoolers interacting give me sad
31 live clip here and it's just think I'd like
Damn cat
Understand how he's being treated and it's
It's outrageous
You believe that Miss
Esther Jones was misrepresented
His
I don't know if meme
Call guys been
Under the Gunn
And you don't
The guy like that be so much things going on
Lakewood
I mean
And we can shop people here trying to do I drop save the restroom
This country
It means a while
Questions
Old General facts about all this
And you said his lawyer was
Was with him at the
Did I briefly talked to
Thunderman
I did give them a contact
Does mission
I've got the person's name
I'm willing to bet Alex at his lawyer so you'd have like confidentiality it have the privilege did not have to disclose
A conversation with his lawyer
But
He's under a lot of stress man I Delight about our interaction at the nature of my employ
Appointment they are because he's just so stressed out he's he's got a lot going on right now so he
He purchased himself deposition of all the excuses one could have for a person's Behavior stress
Position to make it look like it was way more my fault break
Really involved with me at all right but he's a good guy you're just looking out is worried about me
Right
It is
It is strange
That dhanbad Auntie did not realize that Alex called to
To say that he
Didn't
But
Want to pin things on him
Because Alex did Once Upon things on him
And that was why he was doing
You realize like maybe in hindsight that in order for it to work
Arab smooth bongino batondy onboard at least
Not working at cross-purposes but what he didn't know was that regardless of Bud on these intentions
But Andy's going to do that's just what's going to happen
So we come to the end of this deposition I mean
Something else
I think it's interesting to get a glimpse of his his personality on more display because
You know there is that sincerity aspect that you
Serta put your finger on and I think there's something to that
I meant at the same time
Like whether it's kayfabe or whether it's just like
Who he is
There is an unwillingness to not yell about like I will not shut up and
Can't silence me I don't respect
And in a way that
I don't think a lot of these other people have necessarily you know how old up
It's
I I just I mean
It's hard to die could like I want to use the word naive
I feel like naive is such a good word for him I think in terms of his interaction with Alex
Chris like
The way he describes Alex shaking his hand and tell him it's so amazing for you gets fired
That's nice
Yeah for sure
Man
It's
It's sad
Don't like
Feel. I don't like
People who are manipulated
Who clearly cannot
Get out of
And also suck
Then I would like it sucks
Disease of the s*** working it's really bad stuff out that hurts people into the information
In space so it's it's
It's more complicated to have pesos in the mix
But when he's describing these interactions with Alex that are like
Everything was so great he called me Paul Revere like all this it's harder to Lycra
Really
Fuel
Empathy
Yeah I was just f****** with him here's the problem
Here's the problem with this type of s*** right
He has
The proverbial it coming
Right there but the it he has coming shouldn't take this form this is weird this is cruel and unusual punishment
Make him think he's Alex's friend but that's not that's not the law
You're not doing that to him that coming
And you'd wish that there would be a moment of like being able to see through that b******* in the way Alex is acting
I am like to take an accounting of his actual action and be able to be helpful to
Illuminate better what Alex was doing
The machinations of it the way the two people were intentionally pushing this stuff
Chris Brown tears apart of it he was there
I'm sure on some level he knows but doesn't want to touch
That part of himself or allowed to be expressed because of
Now why would you want to burn somebody who thinks or Paul Revere exactly it's hard
It's
It's crazy
I think that the one thing that will not leave me ever from this
Is
That
Did you write
YouTube Roku know how that who's on first will frustrate me probably for the rest
I'm so mad at everyone in these depositions for doing the exact same thing sooner or later which is trying to
To somehow obfuscate
In a way that they think will outsmart
Jump don't play word games with the lawyer that's not a good idea
Hard not to
Steptoe and
Dundee got to pose
Kraken
It's got to go back in the cage
Return return to his his whole episode on Friday and I believe
Leave that way it'll be unpleasant against
Prepare your emotional estate accordingly
Website the real quick I just want to apologize
The on our last episode
I made repeated references to 20s
Performing oral sex on Kanye and it was brought to my attention that I was a real big
Sebastopol
That's apparently it was
Coded language in Omaha
Yeah there's a homophobic and misogynistic implications and I appreciate you bringing that up I appreciate
Do you
Saying something because it was
I was I was wrong
Time to bring it up in the beginning certainly not your bright spot I still and then we went straight into the
Don't know why I know I know but I
I appreciate you bringing it up tonight I think it is important and I didn't want to
Force you into saying something
Like a scolding parents are you ready to come out
I appreciate that I was I was wrong I'll be better today
And we are on Twitter
No I'm Leo MDX Clark
Look
There'll be another bait at some point I feel like I'm Wikileaks bettas really run its course
I mean
That sounds true
But
I will let you know and under so-called way of me trying to
Assertive Bridge
In this case it that is not the case goddamn you know what's funny about that
I got it right here
I just got a text
Whatever the hell is this
What happened you got to read this
Does it read the text
God dammit it's the Wikileaks look it was a low effort
The sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color