Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge B
Stripe.com
A little bit about
Alex
Dune
Bbr Dan Jordan Tim Jordan have a quick question for you
Today
But my bright spot today is I have
I have
Bye
Instagram account that was
About plants
To now a library based Instagram account I believe it's Library underscore fight
Okay and I posted a couple of things from the library on there
The latest one that I posted was the first edition copy that I got of
The John Franklin letters
Which of course is widely believed and understood to have been written by
Reveal Opie Oliver the one of the founding members of the
John Birch Society who I was a
Inspiration to William Luther Pierce
And went on to calendar Diaries we already know everyone knows
It's disgusting schools in
It's not like this is a first edition that's like super expensive or anything
Treasure but Eric's I grew up
Really liking books
My love
Solid book
Thing
I don't know it to have a first edition of something
He's always felt like
Aspiration I'm telling you when somebody sent me the first edition of
Good Heavens no Hitchhiker's Guide
That's
That's mind-boggling I still a little sometimes look over a bad I don't even know if that's real yeah yeah
It's it's something that's in my like sort of sphere of study and it's a it's a it's a
Document it's a antique
You know what
Yeah I noticed there's something really great about that is awful of a book
Cuz it is
I'll probably talk about the book at some point
Anyway with your break but you know how I love the speed running of the video games
Who's a northern Irish
Streamer
Who did a 22-hour Final Fantasy 9 Garnet only
A-Rod and I know I know that makes
That sounds like the nerdiest possible thing that you could say it's great that mean exactly
Is an extremely long
Game right and you can play with four characters
When a main character the only players that only play with her okay
All your other party members every time before you start a battle and for 90% of the game she is V week
Most useless character
Example being in this run
All right on purpose
You have to fight
A fight
For about 45 minutes
Sure and all you do is hold X4 45-minute that'll add its
Horrendous stuff to speedrun what happens is it turns into an absolute chaos
Fast everybody slowly losing their minds from Black
Sleep everybody's like what are we doing this is
We're just holding back for 45 minutes it's that it's at
Creation of a chaos that I love
So so much
I don't think I will cuz I'm just watching even know
Here's another good reason Northern Irish accent
Sure I'll give you that much love it
I do think
There are you find some
Speedrunning interesting
Because I like games and you know like
Sometimes just want to watch somebody play a game
But I'd only want to hear about speedrunning
Basically when it comes to things ahead like
A lot of glitches in
Somebody be something really fast with these glitches and things like I don't think it's I guess but it's not fun to watch
Oh okay hearing about it it's kind of interesting and maybe somebody explaining what these glitches are is helpful
But like
I don't know I don't want to watch Mario go through a wall I can't really just watched like one of the
Dealer streams are the like you know people sitting alone at home playing the video game as fast as I can and
The big Live Events altimate lie there it's like
Well we're speedrunning but it's a show
Right now it's a show I want to watch a scrimmage
Well it's a really good way of putting it.
That's why it's so Jordan today I apologize right before we started recording
Flexible uppercut right I was about to hit the record button
And before you could respond
And the reason for that is we're talking a little bit more about Yang and Knicks win
That's great
So there have been developments
There's more developments there have been yes
So the first thing is that yay and Nick have been making the rounds
More of the second thing is that Alex has spoken out
About what happened
Sounds great and then Nick has responded to Alex's speakingout
Going to discuss this Trinity of nonsense in this episode
First
Sigil of mom and say hello to new walks
Bilbo Baggins boobs like you so much you're now policy walk
Thank you very much
Huddle's be Huntington the third by way of raptor princess backs thank you so much and I'll buzz you on
Next time I name is Christian Tom but not a boy named Tom who happens to
To be a Christian but rather a boy named Christian who happens to be a Tom
Thank you so much and I apologize
Text Jill my Canadian darling thank you so much
Thank you very much this worth
Said that they were moving to Chicago
Yeah I will say it for you
Sure
But not me because if you see me
You're probably my apartment
If I happen to be in Public Museum
Doughboy
Mets where do I type a funny message for Dan to read aloud so much you're now both
Thank you very much
That person called us
Car Talk of Alex Jones that I resent that
It's very annoying I named after the capital of Mongol golden horde in Europe because
Does your purse sounds as loud as 1,000 angry Horsemen riding Georgia city
To Burn It to the Ground
I'm a policy wonk house for a cat
So Jordan and a perfect world we would never have to talk about this stuff
Ever again
Yeah I was hoping that we were done damn the public would recognize that gay isn't saying anything new or interesting
Nick Fuentes is engaged in a large-scale political project publicity stunt bearded further mainstreaming Catholic
As a viable political entity
Are complicit in all of this
In a better world people would see these kinds of actions as disqualifying of these actors will be cast off the stage of public life
For the crime of being poor stewards
The public attention
But we live in a shity world and gay can spout anti-semitic ship for a month and none of this stops
In that time you didn't interview with Tucker Carlson that was so offensive the Tucker had to edit out large parts of it so
The clips that he did play match the narratives that he wanted to sell to his audience
He didn't interview with Tim pool where he stormed out after 20 minutes because pool wouldn't say that the Jews workout
Yay
He did a three-hour stretch on Infowars where you deny the Holocaust twice and constantly rebuke any of Alex's attempt
To help sanitize his
Clearly anti-Semitic bulshit
And all this
Is enough to make him a persona non grata in the right wing
Because there's still something they want from him
Like Nick Bay City utility and associating with a lunatic bigoted and there are two major reasons for that which were going to discuss
In Greater detail today through to recent shows
I mean just for fun
Listen to Nick
Should on Alex
Sorry
The first video is the one that Gavin McInnes put out which is supposed to be the first episode of
Who called saving ye
I'm not sure if that idea I think he has it for is like to be a series I don't know if that's a joke or not but
Haven't does say it at one point it seems like a kind of thing you would do
The second piece we're going to look at is an interview that Alex did on louder with Crowder where Crowder announce that alley
Which was breaking his silence on the gay interview
What does a really accurate but who cares
Each of these two documents illustrates one of the Dynamics that make ye and Nick's current media campaign incredibly in
Important for them to engage in and ultimately
Also reveal how bad of an idea it is for these right-wing figures to be getting
Involved at all
Apologies in advance for making you in the listeners here Gavin and Crowder's voices but in some ways it's not my fault
My fault I mean partially my fault
I accept some responsibility but just not all of it
So we're going to start with McGinnis a show and I want to say that I'm not going to cover most of the episode
Maybe I'll cover a bit but
He apparently is that copyright strikes again Hasan piker stream shut down for covering but that's not really
Concerned that's not really why I'm worried right
We're well within the territory of fair use and if Gavin wants to elevate our stature among his audience that really only works against his interests
Go fuc yourself I think he should have a joke off with me
I'm just not going to play a ton of the stuff that's in that episode partially because some of it is very repetitious of the stuff
But ye said on the Infowars interview
I meant a lot of it is just bad attempt on Gavin's part 2
Baby funny yeah and I don't really care to engage
With that necessarily
See that's the type of thing
That frustrates baby
Because if it was a MADtv sketching the 90s
That makes perfect sense like
Facsimile of Gavin McGinnis and effectively of yay
Doing a show together where it's like
I have to try and figure out how to make this incredibly famous black person not a white supremacist
How do I do this that's a mad tea
TV sketch of the 98 gang walk into a bar
Hundred percent
100%
This is the beginning or Gavin kind of gives a little bit of his
Is syllabus
I guess this is what he wants to achieve
Welcome to the first episode of saving yay
Where I am going to
Prevent
Jay West
From
Becoming an anti-semite
A Nazi
Going to talk him off the ledge
And bring them back to
The understanding that our problem is
Liberal Elites
Of all Races
Kamala Harris
This is a major problem
Barack Obama
What is a major Brock Obama is what
What started this whole mess
I would argue
Don't really into racist
Before he came along
Weather in say
Anti-Semitism is a run
So there's two important points here in this opening from Gavin
The first is that he has some kind of sense that racism really wasn't much of a thing before Obama at that isn't even something
Gavin believe there should be taken seriously
As appointees make
Racist audience that wants to believe that even if they have f***** up racist beliefs that are reported by the large
Population
They only have them because a black man became president made them become race
Obama was instigating the racism
He's a load of s*** there's actually something interesting about this formulation that he's put in for
When Obama became president
Create this new races on put a lot of people use racist ideas to contextualize their political opposition to Obama
In the time of his presidency the attacks on Obama intensified in terms of their races content
And a lot of that was because of the hard work of people like Alec
Racist ideas were Trojan Horse to the criticisms of Obama and the demagogue
Would insist they were racist at all they just didn't like the policies of this president
Wow being
Flagrantly races when they combined politics and racism
I'm into one thing it did not occur to them that later on they would come
Continue to be the same thing they thought they could take them away again they can take them apart again
Cocky
And over time he's racist ideas were more mainstream to the point where it was completely acceptable for Trump to make a name
Name for himself in politics by insisting Obama's birth certificate was fake
It was a normal thing for Alex to do stories about how he thought Michelle was a man and routinely called her Michael
People like Ted Nugent were heralded as legitimate people to take seriously
When he did things
Speculate that it would have been better if the South had won the Civil War
He said the black communities have a quote mindless tendency toward violence
During the Obama presidency the rise of the Tea Party the right-wing realized exploited the political capital of using races
To rile up their base to hate the black
So in those years it probably
Did feel like there was a whole new racism thing going on
But it was the product of the right-wing unleashing stuff that have been there for a long time and the product of gradual normalization
Carried out by media figures
Exactly like
Alex and Gavin
Play literally Alex himself
For example Alex
As we began this campaign of dealing with gay and Nick Fuentes they should really take a moment to reflect on how
F****** stupid it sound
Play the racism became a thing because of Obama
Unless I actually just trying to push Nazi s*** in which case they just keep doing what they're doing they're they're killing it
This brings me to the other point here
This is
This is important to understand
Kevin is not trying to talk ye out of being at peace Medical
He's engaging in exactly the same Fool's errand that Alex was trying at the end of last week
He's going to try to convince EA to use different words and pouches commented somewhat respectable and plausibly deniable
Language so they can get insanely Rich together while pushing hate
Yeah is an ink
Edible business opportunity for anyone who can manage to pull that off but none of these people seem to realize that he's not into
Twisted in that at all
Hiannick understand that's why people like Alex and Gavin are doing
They're not interested so they're essentially just showing up for the
Free publicity and to spread their hate message to whatever audience they can get in front of
Ye won't do this talk with Gavin where he's going to
Try and talk him off the ledge off camera
Because the only reason to do it
Is to do it publicly
And because it has to be done publicly Gavin has to use bulshit pretenses to approach the conversation
He can't just say hey we kind of anti-Semitic and we'll do a lot of business together
Just pretend that he's trying to talk you out of anti-semitism
If you watch this music Gavin has any sincere principled opposition
I have some oceanfront property in Arizona to sell you
At the Gorge
I'm not going to geography but I think that Arizona is land
It is that's a George Strait
Very clever
For some reason I thought it was headed in my head is
Oceanfront property in San Antone
And he's going to be in Amarillo by Amarillo by Morning
I'll promise
You give me looking for 8 when they pull that gate and I hope that judge ain't blind
Amarillo by Morning
Have a real excuse I can do wind you up towards singing
Lost my saddle
Here's a little bit more of Gavin discussing his pretence share
They're tenacious bunch
They are
Successful whites
I think Jews are doing well cuz it just whites it don't drink
I didn't drink I'd be president by now
So my goal here is just to get him
Out of
Beer
While he's in his which is the rut of ant
Semitism
Where is
If it rains on your birthday
You know we see this with track
In the hood going to
Whites are preventing me from doing anything
I can't be it I could go to school and get a PhD in accounting I never have a job because of race
So it's a crippling
Mentality
And it's not intellectually decided to actually adventurous to have a blame group and
Music done a lot of good things for all movements including like racial realism
Anyway to call order and he might shut me down but you got to try right got to try
Alright should we start
They say it's a hopeless fight but I say I got to try
8/8 for speeches like that
That the word defenestrate was created you know like
I don't think he's anywhere near window though he was in the car when he was recorded
You could throw right on the front windshield
I think it's a difficult that word created that word I swear to you
Picking up for car situations
It appears that Gavin's approaches going to evolve
Explaining to you that Jews aren't all that bad because there have been Jewish people who helped establish a school of pseudo-scientific
Racism
This seems like a solid plan
Do you think for a second that Nick hasn't rambled endlessly at Nick about race realest ideas
Big things
Nick is at the race realism he's got this base covered buddy hey come on yeah you can't hate the Jews that
Jews are racist to sometimes we can all do it
Brings us together I'm going to guess that Gavin's talking about folks Like Richard Herrnstein who was Douglas Murray
Co-author on the widely discredited book
The bell curve
Which is pretty foundational as a text for race realist
There may be other figures that he's thinking of too but whatever the case this is a losing point
To make for a wide audience
Losing point if you want to try and bring this to ye as some kind of a way to reel him in Philly
It's just it's it's
Pathetic is a Prem
Because you're never going to be able to say
You're just not he's not selling to me right now
Obviously you're not going to convince the big guy I just
Watch go on Infowars
Deny the Holocaust
The anti-Semitism is bad that's not going to happen you know it and I know it and it's not going to happen on the show
Kevin might have a little hubris here because he might be drunk
He said he had a bloody mary I don't know if he had one
Well why didn't you know the normal amount of Bloody Mary's to drink is one
Like
10 in the morning unless you're at some brunch place that has like a flight
Bloody Mary's that maybe you want to try the spicy one
Interviews yay about anti-Semitism so you know we're dealing with a double-edged sword keep it in the bottomless
Mimosa territory
Yes
This this interview off and it it's
Similarities
Between now the way that
Are the attempts are rebuff
So this is
This is Saturday afternoon 2 days after the Infowars
And I was just
Telling you before we start
Filming it
We were watching it at home and
Ryan Iris looking each other about every 20 minutes with a cookie challenge
Like this is a big deal
We can use this method
And I think
What's a human being
Intercourse in the biggest react
The north positive one is
The craziest most punk rock things
The Sex Pistols
Got kicked off the bill Grundy show
But on the other end of the spectrum
Some people are saying this is
Bad breath
Presidential camp
Where do you stand on that
Think it's awesome for
Yeah if someone that's
Honest that understands
State of the world
And that's ready to
Listen to what the American
Hitler's got a pretty packed
Well who made that reputation
That was made by
Jewish people
Well the murdering
Is a pretty big toe
Yeah but some of it's incorrect
Oh boy
Are coming on this thing now
Also if you think you're going to come into an interaction with yeah it's a lot of people in
Anything or Adventure
Pointed off you're either a f****** idiot or you
You're carrying water for UA and his Hitler campaign
Gavin's first point that he wants to make
DEA is a compliment and then some subtle tone policing
He's calling the interview that he did with Alex punk-rock and then dropping a reminder that
His campaign
This is a classic approach of the you did a great job but here's how you do it better
Except the person he's talking to his comically Rich a million times more famous than Gavin
It doesn't give a s*** about his advice about how to do his racism better
Why the f*** would have ye take advice from Gavin on how to be a public racist
He's one of the most embarrassing examples of public races that we've seen come up in the last five or six years
Easy easy easy easy embarrassment to the races
Yeah I mean it seems very difficult to take advice from somebody
Like
Kevin
Whenever
Your
Super
Famous
Wearing a mask
Person just wondering on to places telling people to Hitler is cool
They still invite you on Via
And you're just some assholes who invented Vice and then everybody hates you forever and now you're the guy who
Did the proud boys
You you are somebody who's going around and making a campaign of being a completely
Anti-Semitic
Call Augusta 9 piece of s***
And people are still inviting you onto their shows
And
Ura
You think
Fit for a second that person is going to take the advice of the person who's still inviting them on the show I mean it's ridiculous
Little bit it is a little bit like
You know that's that relationship where you fall in love with somebody but then the more you're with them you more you're like
Oh you should wear this and all you should wear this and then five years later it's a different person and you wonder why you don't love them anymore
It's because you're trying to change the thing that made you want them in the first place and that is that ye loved Hitler
That's why you invited him on you can't change his mind he won't come on your show
Right
And also it's not really punk rock
I mean like his example is like the Sex Pistols getting kicked off a show you didn't get kicked off the show
Do anything goes really that transgressive except a public opinion
Alexandria Lee
Have that much of a problem with it
I just have to say Nazi punks f*** off I feel like that's the most punk-rock thing you can say that's fair enough
Apparently
Yeah it has expanded the sphere of influence that the Jews have over Society we all know the
Well we know that there's lie classic tropes
Of the banks in Hollywood and stuff
But apparently there's more that that's under the control
Jewish people control
The majority of the media
Along with
Bags
Along with the realest
Steak
Along with
Amol
They can control the narrative black history is written by the winners
They're upset that
Hitler was kicking them
Out of the country
By the time I mean the Holocaust was only 250,000 Jews
Left
But really diving into it here
I mean yeah that's getting to real information
You know what did they think we're going to happen
Matter fact that's like
I think the I think the Jews are like really
I think the Jewish like me
Sade and Rahm Emmanuel and
Bibi Netanyahu and
All of them I think they really got
Soft out here
Like I'm getting to walk around and say to
The truth out loud
You know
Elastic I'm dropping headphone
Really fun to learn that apparently malls are an anti-semitic conspiracy trigger
I want that to the pile
Shopping malls
You know
This is the thing that it seems like on its faces is just easy to see through like
Okay you're telling me that Jews control all of that stuff
But everytime I see people who actually control it
They won't shut the f****** about how they control it like Mall Barons railroad Barons all these guys are constantly like
We f****** on this s*** do what you say
I haven't seen anybody do that
V the mall thing it has to do with
Have to piece this together from Context Clues
A various ringgit
Everybody's been going on
If you wanted to have like a retail shop
He wanted to be like to have a store that I put in malls
Okay and apparently somebody at some
Corporation was like a trial
We'll run one and you didn't think that was big enough he wanted to be all over the place and have his own store
He's blaming the Jews for that I can escape room but at the end of every clue it's the Jews fault
Yeah I think it he would solve it very quickly because it was that fix like that was with the escape room was
Norfolk WIC
I think that you should reflect on what he say
You think that Mossad and Netanyahu have gotten soft
Because I haven't killed him yet and maybe it's not that anyone's gotten soft
Hitman game believes an anti-Semitic
Conspiracy to anyone who questions the Jews gets
Killed by their amazing assassination team
Maybe people are killed for being bigot
It's consistently obsessed with how someone is going to kill them for speaking their false truths
A larger point is that yay is once again engaging in Holocaust denial and getting no pushback from the people hosting him to Harper's
Assumably there
To talk him out of his anti-semitism
The census that was taken in Germany in June 1933 but the Jewish population of Germany at approximately 5
505000 people
This was when the Nazis took power and in the intervening years many Jewish people did flee but no matter
What number you site for the Jewish population
Germany
It's important to remember that the Nazis were expansionist and they held territory Beyond 1 countries borders
Notably the Nazis occupied Polo
What were the population of Jews went from 3.3 million
To approximately 380,000
After the war
It seems pretty clear here that gay has gotten some pretty Elementary basic Holocaust denial memes and talking points Moe's
Most likely from Nick
And now he's going to go on a campaign of repeating them as loudly as he can whenever he's given a chance to talk
On the scam
Don't realize it's not a scam
And they're being useful idiots to help anti-Semitism spread
It says it's really
Bad
Yeah yeah it feels it feels like
They are
So dumb
But in in a way of like
Well we're just doing what we were
Always do
This is what we do
And you're supposed to be doing the thing and despite the fact that they've seen other people fail they keep going to him and being like well
Obviously but that's cuz Alex sucks
Gavin McInnes
I created the proud boys
I'm going to make a series of time today yay off of the ledge that he's not on like he's not on the way
No he's he's flying that's the problem he's falling down and nobody is if there's no ground
The jokes are you Gavin the point is what he hits the ground
It's going to hurt a lot
And not just him
No
So Gavin has some thoughts
Aidan Kerr
I'm going to have an intervention
Are you and Nick
Let me just
Yes
There are
Almost eighty to ninety percent of Hollywood
Probably more
What's your name yeah I'm going to say like Katie
Percent of media
It is Jewish
But
I mean I see the Jews were talking about in these
These cases as
Liberally
High IQ people
White
And when you have like a there just before she represented in medicine
Into
Because they have high IQs
So the problem isn't these
These Jews that most of them are secular Jews atheist
I don't see Soros
Jewish
So we have the secular mostly atheist
Require
There are overrepresented in chess in mathematic
Text to wish you here and there is no masochism there is some sort of like let's burn it
But I think that trait is a white
Trade a liberal Elite
White tree
Not even
Kamala Harris Barack Obama they also have these
And there's some sort of like lemon DNA
In white people wear when they reach a certain medicine
Success they just want to
Take it off a cliff
And I don't like when Jews get pulled into that because
When I think it was my Orthodox Jewish friends and an even my
Hasidic friend
These people are conservative Trump
Supporting
You do American Patriot
And the Jews are getting lumped in with this sort of ethnomasochism
Cultural suicide
And not really to be Jewish I call them johno's Jews in name only
It's literally whites
You should have a beef with
Yeah but I love them all in together
That's what I did
Jewish
Okay but
Straight like
You know
Blacks are overrepresented in violent crime
But when you meet an individual black
Person you don't apply that you start with a fresh slate every time you meet
Do you do that with
With juice
Hahaha
Beans is it an intervention
No not even the slightest bet you you and yourself in your quest for like well yeah obviously due to the problem but it's not
Like 100%
It's like 85 we can be cool rights and let's call it the liberal Elites
Ironic considering what we're talking about
And it's just like
Yeah. Give a s*** these games with him he's saying what he saying
Like the only people who seem to not be accepting what the reality of this is
Are people like Alex
Reflecting pool table I Gavin
Answer because
They want that business opportunity
It comes from yay moderating is message
And becoming part of their business and their revenues to
I mean the unspoken question that they can never have
Because it's too obvious is the
Well
Yes yeah
You are pointing out what racism is to us
And we also understand that
But what you're missing
Is that
Even we aren't racist
We just want money
You understand
For sure we also a little bit more important to run the scam
And keep that moving
We prioritize running to scam through facilitating and pushing racism but there is a point
Which it crosses a line and it is no longer good for business what I'm saying is
We're trying to tell you gay
That despite
Racism
Being an absolute
You know
You believe
That races are ripped
And that's in arguing
Right
We don't actually believe that
Are believes are fungible based on benefit for us person
So well you think that racism is important
Weaving money's important
And then we'll lie about racism
The only thing I take issue with his I do think there's still a sincere interest in racism
It's not all just because it's advantageous with a business
I'm talking to gay is gay is being a racist
Right he's not using coded language he's not trying to hide it whatsoever and that means that when you talk to him
If he says no I love them all in together you're supposed to say
That's how it goes
That's what race is
That's what we're doing
Instead he somehow being like listen
All Jews are bad except for like 5% see I'm not racist
And and as you were sort of react
Into like I get to determine who
I can make up my own distinctions that allow me to argue that I'm not actually the thing ever
True Scotsman applies to you on everything
Yeah
So look I think there is an issue where we're just not going to necessarily
Call out
Discuss every single stupid thing that gay or Gavin says
So apologies in advance for that
Here's just some grievances that ye has it I think they're kind of dumb
And my mom was a liberal and she went to a state school call Chicago State
They gave her job there
And put me on a put it on a
Southside of Chicago on 79th Street
My experience
Right is brought me to be the
Rich's you know black man about town a multi-billionaire
And the people at Adidas they wouldn't even take meetings with me
And I was 68% of their online sales
And brought Adidas bag
And then I when I was in the Kardashian family I have no say-so on
Where we had Christmas there was only one time that even got to design
The Christmas party
What why is this in your list of complaints
The family that I decide the Christmas party adopt
Yep
What
Yeah yeah I've I'm a little petty
I just don't think we should
Convince people that they are the Messiah
I just don't think we should do it anymore I think we should try and bring it back
Bad move problems for not just you but everyone reading
So there's a collusion going on
According to
These folk in this interview and apparently the pornography obsession
Comes back of course
We are beings with engineering opportunities there's a lot of culture
But we got to just clean that out we got to say okay for fat
Dares
A
Collusion of Jewish attorneys managers
And everything else you can think of
They don't abort their children
They only marry within their tribe
Right and then they'll give
America
P*** not yes
Black people
But poor white people
And Mexican people
They do things that use p***
In war this like a gas want to talk about gas Chambers
This is a gas chamber it's a silent killer
And it's illegal and they put it on
Every single block
Any use my ex-wife to sell it
And they also they want a dumbass download
Incredible individual speak for a second
Put my hand back in the Bible
Jews suffer
From pouring the same way everyone else does
Step
This is right out of the anti-semitic narrative
Textbook
I guess David Michael Jones certainly one of The Inspirations for
Fuentes
And Owen Benjamin and Milo yiannopoulos
People all within
Oh and Ali Alexander
All the people who are in
Gays orbit currently are all followers and admirers of e Michael Jones who one of his big claim
He's arguing that Jews use pornography as a weapon against Western
Yep culture so I mean he's just
Spouting that off
And instead of understanding really what's going on
Gavin is like yes
Pornography so bad
And the reason you saying that I mean
I guess he's kind of in that camp to maybe he doesn't interpreter experience it is
Narrative and talk
Requirements to get into the boys if you can't beat off
So
Ghetto music
He's an old hat in these these Waters
Yeah
Did the name cereals
Got your dick I just I mean just
I'm so annoyed
I'm so annoyed whenever people can't
Just be like listen
If you
Expand your Sexual Energy we think you won't have enough
Could you killing for what we want you to do
Do you understand
So you can't jerk off
You need that energy at 8
To kill people with being a strength
The see-through and it's Milton nobody's ever had this idea in the past
This is a good
But
Gavin
Asks about what what do you do about these
You know like these problems that you see
Chozen I yell out losers about it not nut what are you doing what would you do
Yeah
The main issue is that
Christ is King
Christ is the true king of Israel
Christ is the king of all Kings
If you don't believe in Jesus Christ
You are wrong
Anyone that doesn't believe in Jesus Christ
Should not be
In control or in any influence to anything that America producer
Vietmedia
Technology politics
Farming
Medicine
Prison
If you do not believe in Christ and you're not following Christ in the decisions that you make you should have no influence on that
Well that's going to be a tough thing Institute so it's still your president United States
That the Hitler thing does not hurt your campaign
Okay how's your campaign
It's day one and they go
Someone watching Lego
So what are we to do with these Jews
What do you say
What do you mean do about
They're overly represented in met lots of people who don't believe in Christ
Probably wager
Then your average Hospital in New York
Maybe a third or less
Believe In Christ
So are you suggesting we get rid of
Two-thirds of the doctors
Not getting rid of like not violently get rid of them
I think that Jews are very intelligent
But they don't deserve to be in charge of everything because they don't put Christ
How do you legislate that
They need to work for Chris
You should work for Christians I'll hire a Jewish person
In a second
If I knew they weren't a spy and I can look through their phone and follow to the house and have a
Camera living room
This isn't a joke
But they're all laughing because if they didn't have to take what ye saying seriously and he couldn't handle that
This is directly aligned with things that ye and Nick have said in the past so I don't believe this isn't a sincerely held View
There anyone who doesn't believe in Jesus the same way that they do should have no place of influence in society
They're discussing create a stratified Society with a broad
Underclass of people who are ineligible to run businesses hold public office
Oran balls
Presumably
The things that ye is advocating for abhorrent
Any right-thinking person who cares about the ideals of Freedom individuality and small government the way they
Folks like Gavin pretend to
If the easiest thing to push back on to and yet
Diamond doesn't really do so effectively and I think that's probably because he wants the same thing just
Maybe with a differently worded definition of Who belongs in that marginalized underclass
In some sense games refusal to relent on anything has the effect of revealing how little the people he's talking to really but
They may be pretty loud about loving the concert
Institution when they're on their own but they don't love it enough to fight within a really famous person suggesting the Jews shouldn't be allowed to
Working government jobs
There are too many things that could go wrong and ye might walk out on gas
It's just absurd one of his supposed
Series and you don't want that
In that situation it's best just to laugh at the suggestions you can pretend later that he didn't really mean it in the joke's on me
Damn the guy listening to this cuz I took it seriously
But
You ain't sitting there with Nick Fuentes you if you need a reminder set
This in October
If you have
No problem with me
Newsflash and every
If you hate Jesus
You have a problem
Straight up
Hotel near elitches
Or whatever
Question
Do you hate
Oh no
Especially if
A problem if you have
It's my job.
Amarillo
I'm not just one of these
Do you want our our job is
So don't tell me
They're entitled
Their religion involves
My
Lord and how
So far is that
Anywhere near
Who do you serve
This is clearly position that these dudes have and it's something that should be taken very seriously
These aren't the kinds of ideas you have fun conversations about new have to consider both sides
It's and if you think that's what you're doing The Joke is on You
Gavin
You know what Nikki saying that stuff like you believe my Lord is it burning in hell
That's his view of
That's not like he loves them all together is like
It's so like this is
This is something that if allowed to
Come anywhere near having
Political influence of their own is a priority for them
The marginalization of
Particularly Jewish people but then also anyone who isn't a Christian
According to their definition of Christianity eligible for all sorts of things
Whether it be owning a business
I would imagine teaching
You know
Right close to being able to make decisions that affect Christians
Yeah I mean it it was it's almost impossible to imagine a scenario like this one unless you were to look at
American history from anywhere from you know like 20 years back
And then keep going
That's essentially the same thing
At this time
Specific
It's it's a really
Messed up stuff and
Yeah I didn't feel like there's a great push
It's him being at Gabriel I got another Holocaust didn't happen and him being like what would you do if you had control it'll be like
Culturally holocaust-themed uh-huh I would make steps
That advanced towards another one
Would happen
That is why I'm telling you that when I would do it it wouldn't happen
To make has an interesting thought here and by interesting I mean pathetic
You look at white kids there's nothing I don't think
Intrinsic and white people that may
And hate themselves
Like when I was a kid
Kids love Hitler
In the sense that we see the videos we see the propaganda and the symbols and there's something compelling about it
When you were little kid like 8 years old
He Frets like Hitler
That's a pretty revealing and sad clip
Make a singer when he was younger kids his age and his evidence is 4chan
I've some bad news about those people Nick thinks were kids
They were adults who were trying to spread racist memes
The trick kids into thinking there was something cool and compelling about the not for you
This is kind of
You're saying this out loud to be an embarrassment for Nikki should you should feel bad
Yeah
Jesus
Yep
That's who listen when I was growing up it was super cool to wear a white hood and a white cloak and everybody
Play seems like that's crazy now and then I found out that I was just growing up inside the Klan
And that was not a generalized
Experience
And said I was a cosplaying loser
I was hanging out in a Nazi adjacent forum
So when I was growing up I was Highland Hitler like 1620 times a day
Could not Heil Hitler in that case
Maybe self-selected
Here's a good example of why you can't really argue with people like Nick
There's no way
By the way who are The Architects of Blackness
People always point
The finger at culture
Marxism
Cultural Marxist got kicked out of Germany by Hitler
Because they were Jewish
And atheist
Like marks
Soros
Soros's Dad they were all atheist you're helping him can do the sabotage
You're going to see a disc
Proportionate number of people don't believe in God
Well but there's something about Judaism to though that it's not just that they don't believe
Even God but they
They don't believe in
Christ
I think that's so much of our atheist Society is
Really a product of
Judaism they're really kind of like
The first atheist
See
This is why you can't argue
You start off with Nick suggesting that Jewish people are responsible for creating leftism
Now Gavin tries to rub but this and argue
Sort of robotics
Yeah I was going to say
Alex
This is atheists this is the real issue
To give a shiny coat of paint on top of Nick's old races
Anti-semitism
And of course the rebuttal is
Jews made atheist I mean no matter what there's just going to be another Avenue that takes you to the place where Nick wants
He can absorb your argument and then put a layer on top of it that is aha guess what you don't read
Realize that the thing that you're pointing to
Exactly
Yeah yeah it's it's it's
Insane
It's insane that they are pretending like they don't understand but
Kanye
Nick safe
What we lump them all in together that's the point
Lego athenee and they seem almost slightly incredulous to that
Concept
Up like
No that's what you're that's what you do that's the point if that's what racism is it slipping the ball into got do you not understand
So
Gavin
Seadek have you would solve other issues and an a cause of the Jewish problem which is a
You know that's certainly I believe he does
Sort of signaling to not the ideas
But whatever the case Nick's idea isn't good
What do you say Nick if you guys are President vice-president you're too young to know what I mean hypothetically
How do you Institute this
When that is signaling the Jew problem
Well I would medicine for example
Well I would pass I think in medicine is less of an issue through the real issue is communication
Because
Mass communication
Change the world forever
100 years ago and parts
Take a lily 30 years ago
We need to have Christian standard guiding that
Because the goal of our
Society
Is to be moving people into
Maybe have atheists
Whether they're Jewish or white running the media
It doesn't facilitate
How do you fix that
Even even if you can't say we're going to have the government come in and fire all the Jews running the media
What type of lawmakers make laws that govern the media
We don't want pornography on the internet
That we don't want pornography frankly anywhere
We don't want indecency
We want
That's fine
That doesn't do it like
Let's just have open Free Speech no one can get canceled
And now there's no more problems
Control
It shouldn't be something the Gavin says that's fine too
Even if he's okay with the cancer is anti-Semitic beliefs Nick is throwing at him he should not be fine with the prescription of
Decency standards enforced by the government
Like how do you think his show would Fair
Against decency standard
Kevin has a podcast called free speech
Which which is essentially the tire branding
He can't just meekly accept a fast-talking Nazi
Becoming on his show
And I'm saying that the government needs to Crush free speech just because I guess they don't like pornos
But doesn't work
Kevin had another show called free-speech two different shows
We're in this one was already tried to book a liberal in it
Conservative to chat
Eschews
Episode Cowboy Rambo Joe Biggs as we conservative gas who is now facing charges of sedition
Conspiracy
Regarding his involvement
January 6th
Really cool though for Gavin to book one of the leaders of his street gang as a guest on his show
Really giving back
Nick is advocating for a Theocratic society which is antithetical to the Constitution and everything these right-wing s******* spurt
Santa value
If they want to pretend to be all taller into not offended by racism and anti-Semitism think it's still push back on this stuff
It would just be in the battle in the war of ideas and what-have-you they don't really even do that
Gavin's response to what Nick is saying is essentially a non sequitur
Her folks like him free speech has become such a catch phrase that it kind of has lost any meaning
He's trying to argue with a yes and a guy who sang that Free Speech should be destroyed by saying
Free speech
Kevin is used to dealing with jethead grifting types Who hide their two ideas behind universally acceptable terms like free speech
He's not really prepared to talk to a smart young man who's ready to just torpedo the pretenses
And say the quiet part
Incredibly loud
Gavin has left us trying to look after the wreckage of those pretenses
Cuz he's just trying to like cleanup and he looks like a fuking idiot
I I mean
I find it so absurd
Tell like
Simultaneously read about the
Continuing
The ongoing protests
Fighting in Iran
I thought the murders the execution
Like all of this s*** is going on
And then to hear the f******
Baby Ayatollah show up on Gavin McGinnis Ashok of calling for decency laws
It is insane
And it's it's it's
Outrageous to think
Gavin
Isn't like
More
Like
We got it we got to dig into this one
Decency standards is not decent
Branches of Christianity would have
Sort of different
Particularities about what is priority for absolutely
I was just screwing so wildly I threw my vape
A vape tank
Call God
Alright
Everything
Yeah it's it's a it's a little bulshit
I I just
That I don't know how it is possible for you to even pretend to call yourself a comedian
And then listen to somebody say
I think we should have decency laws and go you know what that's not a bad idea
I think Lenny Bruce should have been arrested in prison cultures
I'm sick of people saying you can't say this I want people who swear to go to jail
Jail I don't want these woke
People complaining about things that are I want
Basically theocrats
Arresting people
Oh my God
Great work
So I thought this was really funny and then
Scary some stuff has to say
How do I say f a
Instagram in the car
Screw Instagram
I think we can stay in a better way
Here we go
Pray for Instagram
Pray for Instagram pray for the Instagram users right because Instagram
Is a platform and because there's
So many
Predator
Online anyone
That light
A photo
A woman
That's half naked
A string of her butt
Is a sexual predator
Yep yep
Sure
Show us your browser history by
Wonderful husband maybe you should have Bloody Mary
GreatCall sure everybody who likes a picture on it
Instagram is a sexual predator
How many grams is a lot of people don't have a lot of experience on Instagram but I know I hear a lot of people talking about sliding in DMs
And stuff and I think
We are a lot of people who harass a lot of folks
Liking a picture
Is not the equivalent deal with that
That look different conversation
Way back to just all sex
Pastore happening across this great land of ours I think
Auto deer
F****** daily basis
That's that's a fair point you just want to talk about
Unnamed
Faceless
Women he can objectify and then use as an object
To get what he wants
Like pornography
So also I I do appreciate the pretty making it a little bear that
Pray for means f*** you
Pure Heart
Love everyone that's been a big part of his whole campaign
It's what makes him saying I love Hitler so it's
You know
True according to Heaven Nick
Who makes it
Possible but he's hot he hides behind that idea like I'm saying I love everyone you know
This is a little bit disingenuous and all but maintained that Jews are a second-class citizens
It must be serving us at all times and we have to serve a limb otherwise that I love everybody
That's what it comes down to it there's an abstract idea of love
But
Now when we talk about how things are going to run
Maybe it's not to threaten
I love
Everyone
Black white straight
Gay rich
Poor
Jewish
The follow God's ins Jews
Nazis
Slave master slave owners record on record labels
Joe Francis that was involved with
The s*******
Everyone
The doctor that performed the final plastic surgery on my mom
My cousin I was watching my mom I love
Everyone
That is what leaning into God is and that's
The only way
We Chua
The world
Is by loving
Now as far as studying up
The rules are
The country
This is a Christian country
And the rules of the country
Will be Bass
On the Bible
We're going to
Really we're going to align the Constitution with the Bible
An updated
And we're in the process of doing that right now
Yeah
Well that's the point
Perfect way to end the interview
Jace thanks so much for letting me talk to you again
I I still don't really
Understand
Today's conversation likes the Infowars you love Jews
But you're canceled
Anti-semitism
Because you also love Hitler
But you love everyone equal
Good guys and bad guys
Yeah Jewish people can't tell me who I can love and who I can't love
You can't
You can't force your pain on everyone else
Jewish people forgive Hitler today
Let It Go
Stop trying to force it on other people
That's not good
I don't care
How famous person is or how much they may
Theoretically do for me potentially if I am ever in an interview giving or receiving an interview
That makes me look as dumb as Gavin McInnes looks right now
Fight tooth and nail to keep it from getting out to the viewing public released
Kanye would have had to rip
From my cold dead hands before that goes out to the viewing public that is shameful
Create a new Constitution that is Theocratic Ali based
What enjoy that time that first amendment was still have it yet free-speech absolutist pathetic
In the process of creating a new constitution
And like
There isn't any like
Hey you know that's one of the stupidest ideas I've ever heard
But with no of course not I can take the lord's name in vain
I have been to shows called free speech
Can I take the okay
Are you going to get a rid of the part of the Bible that reminds you of when Jews were available
Is that what's going to go on what did none of this is bible-based constitution based
Do believe weird s*** you're just trying to rewrite it as you make it up on the Fly
Yeah and it's opportunistically using
Religion as a cover for
A sorts of other stuff makes people crazy
You might
I'll be happy to hear
And that is immediately after the interview Gavin realize that he had whipped
He he realizes he failed tall
So that was 5 hours with yay I guess I tried to talk him off the
As far as Nazi stuff goes
The most popular entertainers in the world and he's going to even know me
Kevin said I should dial it back holyshit what a wake-up call this is
This is who I am
And this is who I actually few more Bloody Marys
I think that's
Probably as good as
It's going to get for him to self reflection as I can
Six pack while here is him just sort of admitting defeat
Didn't work when Gavin did it it's priced shop
And Christ can do anything
So this was like 40 minutes of an interview and I would really love to get a look at the other hours that were undoubtedly Rick
I have just no tape going there for five hours and produce
We forgot we forgot to press play on the recording
You want to kick you and can we start up again we'll just do a quick 20-30 minutes on it
Appreciate that at the very least Gavin is doing a little soul-searching and realizing the interview was a stupid
Good idea
Maybe not a stupid idea in terms of getting publicity but if his gold really was
The talk ye out of being an anti-semite than Gavin failed the test before you picked up a pen
And part of that is because he's just like every other s******* conman on the right whose beliefs are completely malleable
And could be swayed if they realize the profit margin is better with different beliefs
It seems like Gavin didn't realize or didn't appreciate that Gabe doesn't want to be
We talked off any ledge and he's not on ale
He's acting like yeah he's an old friend who fell in with a bad crowd and yeah sure
Jay is in with a bad crowd but he's not an impressionable team
He's being tricked into being an anti-semite is a willing participant and antagonist
In this whole operation
Through the course of this interview Gavin is gone through the big transformation from part 1
Over episode into part 2
At the beginning he thought he could handle gay like he handles all the other opportunistic should heads that he deals with and get him to me
Moderate his position
So they can get rich together
This is almost like an escalation of attempt to moderate gay
Tim pool is the most ineffectual loser in the right-wing space
So that's a situation where there's not even really going to be meaningful pushback
If he does try to help you smooth out his positions it'll be the softest touch imaginable you might not even notice it
Then
Alex is a little bit more course
He traffics in some of these same antisymmetric ideas himself and he has a lot of experience whitewashing them for the larger.
That's really going to try and help gay into the box where they can make some money together
Is the next level of offensive s*******
Is Alex's version of acceptable anti-Semitism is to water down for you
Perhaps you'd like the Virgin soul to buy the drunk guy who started a street gang that was involved in planning a seditious conspiracy involved
January 6th
Gavin is a little more edgy than Alex so his attempts to soften gaze antisymmetric shiter little edgier
And they're still not even close
To being effective because he doesn't want to be softened
Or have this message whitewash
What he wants to say
Yeah is not essentially done a speedrun of all the right-wing media from Dopey deji
And rebuff
All of their attempts
To make his position
More palatable
Nothing has been achieved for any side except for Yandex
They got a ton of attention
A second goal has not been achieved
Which leads us to be second element of this episode
Which is where Crowder comes in a little more
The first
Use
Of this
That is so effective
For the right-wing
Stuff is
Trying to convince him
Soft in these ID
That's what Alex date for 3 hours
It's
What Temple probably would have done in some ways if you've been given half a chance
Set out the entire premise
Saving ye it is a draft pick like legitimately like hey this guy
He's got some Talent he's got a lot of stuff that we can use but he's a little bit rough around the side
If we can develop him into the he could be the Star Quarterback for a team he's just got to get development you know you
Just got to
This on being in our system
Yeah Gloria play totally
So that that's
The one first album
And now the second element comes in
With Crowder and Alice
And just to give a sort of brief
Synopsis of what this is
Be using Kanye as a prop
To be like
My opinions aren't that bad I'm not going to use him is to treat him like a lie
Well how it used to be
And so we're going to see that a bit in this
Interview where Crowder sits down with Alex and talks about
Breaks his silence or later they were going to be like well we can't use him the way we want to so guess what we're going
Going to say that at least we're not as racist as the Black
They
This episode is just Crowder being funny
Until I even include any of that I can put you through that okay good Alex comes in a ways into the episode
And they talked for like maybe half an hour 40 minutes
Do something like that and then there's more in the mug Club
I'm not a member
So are we start here with a
Giving a hey buddy
Daleks
Hey looks like you had a tough time there buddy
Mr. Jones thanks
Thank you for being with us right
We need to include that context
Boy
Seems like you were holding on for a bumpy ride with that
Have you do I do I have it about right to do expect that in your wild
The streams
I know I didn't and I didn't say what he can talk about what I said
Tupac about real issues
Fentanyl and
America
Really you see the deeper side of
Have you and not just soundbite
And they were like yeah
Stop
Wasn't right away
Right now
Thursday
Damn I thought he was joking at first
Why would you think he was joking at first
No idea I have no idea the things he'd been saying previous to this
I think this is pretty sad
Isaac
That's
I have developed a new form against
The incarcerated State you know Justice is difficult to like figure out and prescript
Justice
Is really difficult
So what I've decided is that Alex needs a
Acquaint Court
Appointed referee right so anywhere he goes like on a conversation like that's that's like
Meyer final study we need that to be enshrined into law
Absolutely you can't say that a red card
Alright next
You don't like that that needs their needs to be away
That they can't going off and be by themselves and talk like this is
Totally off topic but I remember one time my brother played soccer
Are all the guys on his team got a yellow card
The ref pulled it out he took
From The Ref and ate it
See the Red Bull. Red Card
About 12
I would probably like
Still hilarious
Alex
He has to kind of figure out a way to
Explain what was going on and he's decided that this was a trolling thing
They were trolling even though they're explicitly multiple times during the interview ETA says this isn't rolling
I'm telling you what I think I am telling you what I believe it is just so outside of the pail for these people to
To actually have to confront someone who believe the things that they lie about or that they lie about not but worth it
What's the mass
Yeah
I mean really
Super high on real only did it
Feels really good about it
I don't think I was a very good historical knowledge
About WWII either
Oh yeah
In love with a
All of that job design
With so much and what the Nazis is I ended up
Club
Allegations he loves Hitler
Then
Tens of thousands of Nazis had in the world war
The one most
Major agency show
Alex is still trying to excuse what ye said by making false
Equivalences
Ye deny the Holocaust but 70 years ago the government brought over Nazi scientist to work on rocket
It's so who's
Really to say what's what he's just
Uninformed
It's a strange thing to argue and the ultimate irony is in front of you
Great that the US brought over Nazis because he loves not
Innocent Alex is trying to control this narrative now that there isn't that pesky personal narrative is about there to stop him
Yes that's what I believe he doesn't believe that is a no idea
Wright's it's
I say things
Because I mean them do you not understand that principle whatsoever
It's really it's really bizarre
It's a desperate attempt to salvage whatever you can out of
You'll make good out of bad
So Alex has some opposition to Nazis and that's great
Although I think that maybe some of the ways that he understands his opposition to Nazis is a little personal
And maybe his problems and complaints about the Nazis are never
Like invading other countries
Systematic genocide of a people
Causing the world war problem or not what he seems have a problem with it. Like
They almost killed my grandpa oh that's
Good
Real things about the
My family
OB about
Both my grandfathers almost died
Both of them
I am
Zeolite talked about what
These were like
My mom's
Dad
Also work
Black budget
Programs
60s
Military bases
They were very very Erica
And he didn't like how
Delegate years old here my grandfather
In Austin Texas
Sitting around the kitchen table bench
You do not see
Cheese and working on secret
How much he hated the
That's a real thing that's going on so my
Really comes from my grandfather's who
Both didn't like him very much
It seems
Not
For someone whose claim to read 100 books about World War II and studied everything
Seems like your reasons for disliking Nazis wouldn't be
They're arrogant
For my grandfather said working with them wasn't
Fun
Bizarre
What's interesting to me about it is that it comes from the same point of view is gay
In my in my vision is because these people
Cannot see outside of their heads
You know they can only see through their own eyes
Big have no ability to like
See the world from outside of that so everything has to relate to something that has happened to him
Pornography is bad not because of the Jews
But because cognac is addicted to pornography
WWII is bad because of
Holocaust because it hurt Alex's
Grandfather you know if I understand make it personal and take it personal
But
Also the difference
Is are between those two things that you're describing cuz I do think there's an important difference
Hey Matt is that yeah is not taking responsibility
For blaming the Jews for everything where is Alex is
Sure
Well I mean he's always blaming anybody it can this clip
He's just taking it personally and that's how he understands WWII basically
Maybe
Encanto
Sequential in the grand scheme
Maybe
Small
You know it it sometimes when you say it however you get there at least you got there either. This time
Matter of how Alex thought the interview would go comes up
And I got to call a lot of bulshit on this
I really thought
I can come in here and shut up
And let him get it out of his system even if he did it
Let's do something different
What's the issues I had all these issues in front of me
You just set those aside we're not getting into that
Figured
But you kind of have the salacious
ROM
Are the Baby Hitler over there
Jimmy Kimmel
Florida
Jabba the Hutt
There's a salacious
From sitting there but
Seriously
Was really
X whenever he was being dbangz
Fry's
So I want to say that I know definitively that that's not true
Their Alex knew damn well
And his associates were very much into Hitler and
Nazis
Yes that is complete b******* Alex engaged with him well aware of
His beliefs
And the way that these things were being hidden
I don't believe for a second that they went on the road together for the stop the steal stuff
And not nothing
Aveda true nature of Nick's beliefs
Who made clear
Alexander is now in charge
Presumably in charge or at least very involved in gays
Campaign
You could get call you to campaign give to the legitimacy that I refuse to accept but that's fine that's fine
Vanity campaign Champagne price
Alex went like to Georgia and other states
With Alexander and Nick Fuentes
So now he has two people
Who were deeply involved with his own
2020 election
Conspiracies and stuff
And Allie is pretty involved with Infowars
Now they are both
The people who are involved with the I love Hitler guys presidential campaign
Alex is
Far more involved in entwined in this than he wants to believe
Very close to him
And like I said
I know that he knows
Like these people's beliefs
It's
You did this to himself
Is every bit of criticism
And Association that people are making
Yeah yeah you know you don't have any Talent of your own and then the closest thing you could get
Two Talent was an eighteen-year-old Nazi
So Rick is very talented
Especially
Compare Talent finale
Youngest nothing that we do
Released
What a what that's the biggest compliment I have to get what is superlative
So Alex does not like
Hitler was a disaster
Hitler
The points are communist agenda
It is basically just as bad
So powerful
What should say where was Hitler
I'm not mad
Either person
Sounds like you know
Whole bunch of programs like the young turds and all of them say
Secret house
Authoritarians I hate
Communist
I hate Hitler
Hey Joseph
Fidel Castro I hate Hugo Chavez
I love George Washington
I love Thomas Jefferson
Society
Free speech and I want it back now
Octagon
It almost feels like Alex dissociated for a moment
Completely off topic point
I think he was researching his mind for his stock things
Things to shout that involve Hitler and that's one of his big one
Yeah it kind of gives the impression that he's not really mentally processing this conversation might be a little bit on autopilot
And also wanting to relive those those
1776 2.0 how much press he got because of yelling
I'm at stop CNN with Piers Morgan Glory Days
Right you went to that to gunshow where Piers Morgan is doing a remote and he begs him to come back on the show
Such a good hit of adrenaline from
It was so good
Any wants to relive that a little bit now I think in
Make a different kind of attention now
Tired of your s***
Tired of
Things being very obvious
You know like
Two of the most hateful people on the planet I've just listen
Listen to list things they love
For a while I don't have to regularly list things that I love or hate
In order to prove something you don't have to list off a bunch of things that you love to provide cover for the fact that you love them
Also I don't have to list off a bunch of things that I hate and then say I love them to make people think that I'm not
I hated myself
So
So there was this
Dynamic it was going on with the yay
Show
And that was
Is this I love everybody
And that was how it's pretty clear
That that was
A little bit of a
The b*******
Well listed things that he said he loved
He was only listing them because those are the things that he hates
And people know that
So he has to say that he loves them
Except for things like Nazis and Hitler
He loves Nazis
Sure the love stuff I mean there was just the like Holocaust
Didn't happen stuff
Yeah
I got to say
Steven Crowder doesn't buy this s***
Like he does
He doesn't like going for the I love everybody at right right
You have Steven Crowder
Being like
This is some b******* your nonsense is
Your people trying to defend its thing
Well there's validity to that
Kanye West that I love everybody
He didn't say you hated me but he said I loved you that was Hitler but
He did go out of his way
To praise
Actions of Hitler while condemning a
Actions of
Jews in this sort of General monolith
And he did
Deny the holler
I love everybody
That's not what happened with that interview enough people out there want to say hey
He has every right to love Hitler
Of course if you say I agree with him when he says he loves Hitler in the
Holocaust didn't happen fine
Equivalency
You know I'm on your show and it's
Shorty said he loved everyone
But he did have
Specific praise
For some to tell
Military indict
Not good not good when Steven Crowder sees through your f****** game and is calling it out
Who in trying to the right to love Hitler
I think we can revoke that right I don't think you should have the right to love Hitler
You can't love Hitler
Okay demanded
Bill of Rights
How do we how do we
How does this work function
How do you legislate this
It's against the law
What if you are Hitler's parents
They killed him
But what
But but are now they just put yourself in that situation
Absolutely cuz he's the genocider
I think you're I think you're going to have a tough time writing this into law telling you I feel like a very specific la like if some
Somebody has committed genocide they don't get love anymore
You sounded like Alex's mom
Off money you don't get love no more
I I think that this is a
This is
Kind of legislation that you're going to spend a lot of time trying to crack
Veneers wasting taxpayers dollars
Also probably against free speech
Beach money is
That citizens united baby
So Steven Crowder
Bike
Kind of pushing back on this in a way that is kind of surprising
Inasmuch as he actually is
Do you think the media got this one right
Like what yeah actually is mad
How do you think the Press
As is
Covid-19
You I think the
Yeah, course I will try and turn feather you I'm saying do you think that
The way the Press
She said it hey
Kanye West
Yay
On Alex Jones
Went off and was
Very obviously incredibly aunt
Do we think that Anna
This case
Was depressed parsley right
Another word that they completely misrepresenting it or when you were sitting there
Did you feel as though I'm
This is probably not too productive
Look
I like
Kanye West I like yeah
I think he really means well
I don't know if Nick Fuentes believe what he says doing Nick says a lot of really good stuff I agree with
Once I heard him indoors
That he thinks Hitler
Great I I lost a lot of respect for him
5 years ago
Smart but you know he's kind of a savant
Wants to be a big revolutionary wants to hit the barbed wire is he said
He said your Terminator 11 Terminator 10
And I just really think it's the end of the day is that that's not
How to change the left
I'm adopted so many of the actual
I'm control
Their whole
System of lockdown
Big groups of people
March together
Glad buy one pie Piper
White medical uniform
Audiology
Striving for
That Hitler
What about all this
Kill h.g. Wells
Gilbert's rustling others
Because they emerge Russell haddock
Competing
Authoritarian World Government left
Bottle
So just real quick Alex's referring to Hitler's black book which was a list of people he wanted rounded up and killed after the Nazis
Planned invasion of the UK
In operation sea lion
Alex is made up of they want to kill HG Wells and Bertrand Russell because they were setting up a rivaling world
That is for all intents and purposes Alex whitewashing not CS
Hitler wanted to kill Wells because he ran an organization called poets sas2 novelist
International witches
Spell the German branch of the group because they only accepted Area writers into their membership
He was a very vocal critic of the German government and was a very understandable Target especially considering the offense
Seed made against Germany's place in the art and culture world
The reasoning was similar for Russell
Be a better non-interventionist and eat switch positions and decided that Hitler was a threat to all of Europe and needed to be
He fought
The list includes a bunch of folks like Virginia Woolf who they wanted to kill because she was married to a Jewish man
And all the trucks Lee because he helped Jewish artists and writers flee from Germany
Elsa sings complete b******* and it's carrying water for him
Now larger picture what Crowder is doing here is the second stage of the purpose gay serves to the right-wing
As we discussed
I'm sort of two parts of the episode
Kroger seems to have realized with so many have missed
Which is that yay means this s*** he's not going to relay
And maybe people are right Scala maybe somebody
He's getting ahead of the ball for a very important purpose which is essentially to create an avatar of an anti-semite
You can use them to excuse his own toxic opinion
Anytime he's accused of saying something f***** up or anti-semitic you can say I'm not yay and that has the effect of giving him some breathe
Sunroom
Alex knows this Dynamic well
Since you was on the other side of it for most of his career and still is use that way from time to time
Most of Glenn Beck's
Conspiracy bulshit early career was predicated on him
I'm not Alex Jones a pretending
That proves rationality
Even within the last year when he was being grilled about his promotion of great replacement conspiracies
Tucker Carlson shopvac this isn't some Alex Jones s***
You can fill a very important role for these right-wing media figures which is to be the person they are not
Which excuses their rhetoric
That person goes too far and I'm not that person therefore I've not gone too far and what I'm saying is acceptable
I want to have someone like you gay it provides a rare opportunity where there's this huge celebrities that the media is eyes will be on what
Precinct and he's bombastic personality so he's not going to take this halfway
This combination leads to the conversation going so far past the point of acceptability that it allows people like crab
To move the ball a little bit down the field
Look like he's done anything
For instance in response to denying the Holocaust
Crowder can condemn that but then decry the problem of quote secular humanist with Jewish last names in Hollywood
That's pretty f***** up stuff
Compared to what yeah is putting out there certainly doesn't seem that bad
Have yagos
I can go 30 I mean that's why that's why when McKenna says you know like
Hey it's not all the Jews it's most of the Jews
But not all of
You know it's like no that's
That's
Equally anti-Semitic
Those are on equal footing
And yet because ye is willing to save the full thing
Andy
McGinnis
Does the luxury of being able to be like haha I'm only 90% racist
Then he gets away with it more than otherwise yet
Temple and honestly wants the rest of the right-wing should heads come to the realization that they're not going to be able to
Monetize gay himself
This will be the next best thing for them to be able to do
Yeah
And
It's going to be unfortunate because they have let him
In
A little bit
And that means they can get burned
By him once they
Start
Shooting on every could be a problem for all of us that they don't seem to realize that Nick is
Coming for them
Like well we'll see you there in a little bit that's what I think is very funny about all of this is that
They are looking at Nick and yay going on all of these interviews thinking
They're trying to do some whites
Supremacist s***
Not realizing that Nick
Is going for them
He is choosing
Those people to attack
In order to take
Their ship
Yeah it's basically like how he had this whole campaign against Turning Point USA
It what he wasn't going
Get some
Group it was going against someone on the right
Because the people who are in that audience are far more likely to
Come over to his side
Then if you were to go to some antifa meeting
And cause a scene
He can he can say things that these folks
Aren't they
Am pretend
That there's some kind of a secret
Conspiratorial reason why they're not saying these
These whacked-out things that these people
Did the same Dynamic is essentially at play with
These are stops on his campaign to her all think that he is like everybody else
She's just another one of the parasites
But this dude is a disease man
He is not going to to suck you dry he's going to steal your s*** and kill you
Yeah
It's good timing for someone like Alex to have to deal with something like this considering that he just
Declare personal bankruptcy is companies in bankruptcy keogh's a billion dollars at the height of his power
I knew this is actually kind of old news
But
The
Stuff
That he owes because of these judgments is not dischargeable in bankruptcy
That was something we already had an awareness of but they had just
Litigate
He's in a perfect position to have somebody who he is
Enabled app platform.
Legitimised
Come in and say horrible things about him and try and leech off the audience
You know it's so weird
That Sith Lords
Aren't
Like best buds
You know like they are the one always tries to
To kill the other one it's like why
You know
Just be best buds
There can only be one Highlander
Bulshit
Rambles a lot about Orwell
A1984
Do I happen to know for a fact
And the tactic that's what George Orwell wrote
A British intelligence in WWII
Communist before that and
Spanish
Top of the British
Socialist society
That actually Stalin was being funded by the West
Individual in the future
Hitler
By British intelligence
Not not run by there but
You're built up again
Power and funding
Early by the Big Bang
He realize
That
Global authoritarian system topper
Total power and control
Well that's clear
Very clear
George Orwell
Before he died in 19
Finished
But he
As well
And then he later learned it was a more evil group
Fabian socialist
British intelligence
Respect
I'll let you see the James Bond movies
I'm sorry
James Bond
British
Empire model that Virgin America
That point
Systems.
Domino's
I didn't play them off against
Each other
So was it a good idea if they are not I would like to just ask him to provide
Resume sources on the
Any of that
Yeah that was
That was fun
I'm guessing
He's referring to like omage to Catalonia I feel like I just got a lot of exposition from a steam
Punk novel psychic telling me about the the previous history before the apocalypse happened that's what I feel like
I just heard a
A lot of alternate reality
I believe you are like
Coral worked at the BBC I don't know if he was number two and British intelligence and propaganda
I don't know
Committed Democratic Socialist into the last years of his life
I just answer the phone story but I need Alex to substantiate any of this
Comforting
About this
Is
For certain people
Once they start talking about a subject
I no longer feel the need to know
Alex are talking about or well I don't need to
I don't need to be like oh
Why is he saying this thing about this book that doesn't say the thing that he saying
I don't know
So Alex is a new explanation for why you did what he did
Infowars.com
Go to infowars.com
And find a full interview
Actually see it
Contacts
Watched again
Watch lot of extra
Tarzan
I just think what happened was
He decided to go all the way inside
Responsible
Screw the world
And then once he started pressing on the dopamine button
The banks he said
He just couldn't
Stop
You know Justin
Situation
The entire time he was on
Yeah
Yeah it seems like that
That might be the
Doesn't
Doesn't seem like that might be the case at all
It's not adrenalinn he was not a addicted to Adrenaline
It's not like a crime of passion he brought a net and Yahoo
Yahoo
That was premeditated
That was a murder one if you will accommodate
I bless those props just happened to be at Alex's desk which leaves
Incredibly unlikely it would be a strange improv thing to ya
We've had this net and we've had this YooHoo out here
For twenty years thinking somebody's going to put it together sooner or later right and here it is
Is finally paid off
I just I mean
It is any kind of excuse people tried to make Relic Michael Richards
For that because they're there
Is there
Lives are built around claiming the racism can't even happen
Because it doesn't exist
Exactly but then they're here and they're just like man
I don't know if I can
Can say that racism doesn't exist after that
What we got to come up with a bunch of new ways so many different ways to just be like listen it's okay to be erase
Racist
But maybe not this races
So Crowder he takes
That cover that ye is provided
Gets into a little bit of his own
Anti-semitism
There's a very big difference between yes
I do think there's a
Conversation to be had
Secularists
In the entertainment industry and if someone wants to conflate
What's anti-semitism
What they're doing saying always at because you're saying because they're Jewish Journal
I'm saying for the same reason that they're plenty of
Non-jewish people in the in
Entertainment industry
Who are involved with grooming
Score involved with by the way
The degeneracy of society
The only reason people
Largely atheist use any
Ministry or for example
Thanks
Which compared to their damn as a percent of the population is true for the same reason
There plenty of Jewish doctors
That dynamic as describing earlier on full display
If these people's jewishness isn't important
Why is it important that a conversation about the secular humanist with Jewish names who are in Hollywood
You didn't say it exactly that way in this clip but that is what he's been going on about in the aftermath of the end of you
If the problem is the indecency of Hollywood shouldn't their jewishness not even be a point worth bringing up
Stevens concerned that these people having Jewish names because he's making exactly the point he's pretending.
This is pretty antisymmetric position that Steven is expressing but because he is out there denying the Holocaust
It gives him the ability to express things like this and say I'm not yet by Abby's better conspiracy insinuations or
Irrational
Look at me I'm not that far out
These are the kinds of side consequences that come with platforming someone like ye and I find it difficult to believe that these right-wing
Ding-dongs don't understand that
What they want
To be able to be bigots while taking an imaginary High ground with anyone calls them out for it so they don't have to
Feel bad about themselves
They're in the wake
Yay and his b*******
Just going
Listen that's
Crazy that wave is too big now I do think there's something to be said about talking about the way
That's the problem
Nick and yeah
They are
What if they are
No they aren't they said they
Otherwise they aren't
Adrenaline and I don't even understand you any more push-ups
Look if they are it's the last fall
The lapses raps
Captain America we're fighting a Nazi
Do people like Kanye West
But I'll tell you
I've been attacked massively by the ATL all these other groups
And they rap
Me and the name of Jews
Which is
Then making a lot of people think is good you must be bad
I've saved this pretty pathetic attempt to avoid doing any soul-searching
Bluffton do s*** to make these idiots into Nazis
But
Alex sure as s*** has
His entire worldview in imaginary enemies are characterized by complete plagiarism from the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Mixed up with anti-semitic Trope from history like blood libel and
Well poised
He constantly makes excuses for Raven bigots and anti-semites and gives his audience
Flimsy Arguments for why you shouldn't see them as Raven bigots
An anti-semite said which they actually are
Anyone
Much
Alex is consistently hosted outright 80 semites and Holocaust deniers on his show and he never is that a problem
Funneling is audience into their information spaces
So long as they keep their s*** subtle on air
The list of people from recent times is pretty long but it goes
As far back as he's been on air
In recent 2003 episode that we did we saw him interviewing Eric Schmidt the holocaust-denying Techno DJ
And that wasn't an isolated incident
Flash forward to the present days having softball pretend debates with David Duke and Richard Spencer
And hosting friendly conversations with the man who has inspired
A lot of Nick and gave current ideology e Michael Jones
Is anyone facilitated the slide further down the path toward anti-Semitism it's been Alex with all of his nonexistence
Standards for Guess election and show prep
Even so frame
I mean this whole thing as a reaction is unacceptable
Yang and Nick are anti-semites they've decided to be so because they believed bulshit
I was just trying to take moral responsibility away from their decision by saying that it's the left evil manipulative actions
That led them to be a-coming nafees out of spite
I guess I guess it's fine
The implication here is that the left
If the left weren't doing the things they were doing naked ye would be at the semites which
Isn't true
Nick's been this way for a long time and now it's was fully aware that the whole time he's known him
He's just not able to plausibly deny who Nick is anymore so he needs to come up with a new Spin and it's pretty f******
Yeah listening to this it just reminds me of
How unfortunate is that we're all here
It all like I feel like
If we could
Just get
You know all of the not them people
And go on a holiday for like
Three or four wheel
When we come back later killed each other
Like even this s*** they can't help but say oh it's the left but did it it's a if we weren't here they still blame the left and
Can I just call each other the laughter they already already LOL
Here for them to kill us
What even this small group that is like around
Yeah is already incredibly volatile Milo was in and in-charge and now he's out
Maybe Ali Alexander is taking his place so who knows
But yeah there is there will be
Chaotic
Comings and goings
But I think
Nick is probably in
Yeah well he owned
You know it's
It's
Their ideas are so dumb
And so
Stupid that when they
Say them out loud and are challenged by another person of their ilk with dumb and stupid ideas that are
They blame other people
Rather than even engage with their own ideas being dumb and stupid they're just both like
Yeah isn't it other people's fault we're stupid
So many other people
ZR1 last
Clipper Crowder here
I'm just
The left
Weaponizing WWII
Years ago
77 years ago
Is very very dangerous on the left sing
Courses on that
Is going to them make knots
Because she was a bunch of leftist academics of Hollywood people
Literally trying to teach the majority-minority
Majority
White people who aren't
A certain religious group
All that people
And here you can see Alex doing some acceptable antisemitism well getting
To use Yeahs cover
This is absurd but let's play around with this idea a little bit so you can see what Alex is actually saying
Less leftist academics and Hollywood people many of them Jewish are teaching non-white people that
People except Jews are inherently evil
Kind of thing will make Nazis look legitimate
To the left is driving people toward becoming Nazis
That's fascinating because I pretty much agree with Alex's construction except for one par
Academics in the media and Hollywood aren't saying white people are inherited
The evil
That's a paranoid white identity fantasy that Alex uses for a bunch of different narrative shortcut
But it's one that's just accepted as truth on his show
He does make some sense that believing Alex's version of the world would make Nazis not look that bad
So in essence if you believe the pipeline
Describing
That he's actually responsible for the creation of a
He presents people with a false reality that makes the Nazis look less extreme than they actually are
Thereby making him a more acceptable group to associate with or Ally with
How bad are the Nazis compared to the global has to work for the literal devil and want to kill all humans
Well
I mean
The thing about that though is whenever you
Turn things into that kind of duality
Bright
Okay
So
As ye said you know if
If you're not working
For Christ
Then you're working for
The devil
And he
You thinks that Hitler and the Nazi
These were good
So they were working
For Christ
That's what his
Position is
Is that God wants you to kill juice
There are some implications that maybe would be best not explored if you're them
So these two documents I believe
Illustrate
Something of my point
The
Did the ways that gave being used
These folks
Nothing
Where is the immediate
Desperate Desire by these folks
Try and
Softer softer
Bring into the fold
This incredibly famous celebrity that they can
I try and Ride Along
And it does not work
Because he's not on the same scam
Grip level that they are
And then the alter ultimate their conclusion is using him as a prop
To justify your own
Dollar Tree
Essentially it's it's kind of Overton window e in terms of how it works or they be on the way
Look at it
Diego's this far so you can
Can go that far right quarters of the
The way down field he's he's
The battering ram IC is even described himself at stand
It's bad
It's bad and people should know better I think they do know better and they're actively participating in this to me
Steven Crowder
His appearance here is essentially only in the second
Enphase
And I suspect
That's because gay wouldn't go on his show
Yeah I think maybe there's a chance that like that book
Didn't happen
And so Crowder didn't have to go through the first stage of this
Yeah
Oh absolutely
So that's kind of the informative section of this but
I thought in the interest of fairness
Sure maybe not
I wanted to play some clips and discuss a Twitter spaces
Nick Fuentes dead
In response
To Alex's interview on crowder show
All right he does not take kindly
To some of the things that Alex has said and
In my response he ends up
Things that Alex probably isn't going to appreciate being made public
So we start here and Nick realizes that Richard Spencer's in the chat
Hey Richard
Let's go
Alright so
I was going to a space yesterday
I'm going to dive into it
Today
Respond to
Alex Jones
And that whole
Tencel as you know
Me and Jay went on Alice
I don't want to make it like a thing
Boston
You game changer
Entertaining
Deny that
Who's awesome
You know and it is agreed about that
Strongly
I get up
Everybody talk
Even my mom
Was like
Sure that was a good idea that kind of
And that's what that's all she had to say
Everybody wants
What's the explanation
Can everybody
Especially now
They're looking
Tumi
To go live I might have break it down
Everybody here south
What
Mansur's what a really mean seriously here's the angle
Here's the upshot
But I think that kind of
The point I think
I think it speaks for a
Michelle
I kind of agree
Secrets
Spoke quite a bit further comment on it honestly that it was awesome
Understand where he's coming from
What is perspective it is awesome you did exactly what he wanted to do
At the exact response largely
I can't I can't foresee another circumstance
Outside of him committing a domestic terrorist act where Nick Fuentes would get as much attention from the mainstream
Press and everything
Then this
Pretty awesome for him this is some
Weird
That's knocking dark mirror version of a dream
That might have been mine
When I was
Very young listening to College Dropout you know like just like me
Hangout with ye be cool to be part of his presidential campaign for what it's worth
Nick
From Chicago
And that's not something that's new so for him it probably is
I'm cool about that just all cool Liberty
Element of it alone
Absolute
Person that you've liked their music for years
It is so much like that is a dream I would have and then to have it
Be entirely and that your wish
Honestly you know what that would be like
Wish Foundation Garden
I loved the Bosstones
I'm screwing up and I would have loved to hang out with them but now Dicky Barrett
God dammit
Don't get too
So despite the fact that speaks for itself Nick decides he's going to beat
At the risk of
Astounding
Tripod
To put a very simple
Bishan Tire system is
Just put in place to
Again I know that
You know that's not really
Not really my most
What I mean by that is you
This guy Wareham
He goes on the Alex
Hitler
And we're going to stop
She's all the time
Of course what's the obvious
Can't say that you can't
I'd say that
Play that apology
You can't win if
You say that all that's not a good idea blah blah blah
And
You know I'm just
Kind of over
In the same way that a 26
16 people are more like you know why
Shut up
F*** off
Make America great
Build the wall
Ban all Muslims
You know I know that's probably not
Word search
Temperamentally slightly
Different in that regard that sort of how I would
We don't care
The system is so rude
Sosa
Skating with so overbearing
We're so sick of
The double standards
Apocracy
I really like the
Real
And the funny
And an honest
Brutal honesty
Answer these bucking conventional wisdom that you can't say these things
In the realm of politics
And that's
Whatever but
Does conception there
I think
Make sense
And I'm worried about the experiment
Because
There was a lot of like with Trump like
You was talking about like him having a big dick
Debate stage
And stuff like that dude like this doesn't work just doesn't fly and then it turns out
Through Brute Force
And sheared not giving a f***
Somehow it
Did work
And
The things that make is articulating here
Is
That is the way he's approaching being anti-semitic and Pub
I'm just going to brute-force it
F*** you well I mean he's he's explaining something I think that is
Well-known
Which is that everybody right now is so f******
Sick
Of listening to people lie to them all the time
Beer politicians or media and you can say all
It's this media that's lying to me or this politician that's lying to you
But at the end of the day it doesn't matter what side you're on
There's enough Flyers
In both your teams
But you're going to be mad
Yeah you know what people want is authentic cities honesty how they respond to that
Even if it's f****** evil
Right and that's one of the big selling point to the Trump ad and it's something that and that's something
Yeah you can get into to any has other elements of the archetypes that people gravitated to about drop the ID
Video of being self-made that authenticity is you brought up just having Fame itself is enough for most major
Presumably being willing to walk away from Fame and Fortune because of some kind of principal sort of yeah
He may or may not have
Those things are
Whether true or just illusion
Are things that Translate from
A trump campaign to a ye campaign
That they do resume with people
I mean
I could be wrong
But I don't think people are I don't think the electorate is big enough yet for the honesty of aisle
I love Hitler no
When I don't think on the global stage I think it would be a
I think we'll be tough and I think that my biggest problem with being alive right now is not knowing
If Loving Hitler is a losing electoral strategy for sure I don't like knowing that
Right and that's what I'm saying about like the kit the experiment worries mate what is there is there
Point at which that brute-forcing of like know f*** this
I don't care about your your decency ideas and I don't care about your
Your ideas of what I can and can't say
Is there a line at which something is too far
I mean I don't want to go
In Georgia
It is
A very thin line that you have to go a long way for it
You got to have lied about some abortions
You got to have all kinds of terrible wasn't following everything super closely but I heard something about werewolves
You left
To go that far
You just barely lose
How far is got to go so
So
Yeah and Nick
Apparently
Good spirits which I agree they're both
Now more than ever and it's
It's amazing
Cuz yeah and I are
Spirits
We are really on
On the same wavelength of
Look
We're going to go out there
Honor Hardware
Going to say
What we feel
And whatever
The best Frozen
Like with him or with me
Whatever
We'll figure it out
We went before we wind up broke dad
Murdered by the
The Jews
Whatever
Okay like whatever
Then that's a that's a
Feeling
Sentiment
There's also a good read
Like there's also like a
Cerebral explanation
For witches
Look at look at the
This guy
You did everything
Right
The American dream he blew up
Doing what he loves.
Cambridge
Became famous
Became a bit
Made products
So on
Liquid
When they rip this family apart they
Kids brought meme
Who invented
Lobotomized
And of course
I'm oversimplifying
There's more to this
The Napa
The point is look at the
The kind of society and
What if
It's not
Producing
Happy healthy
Still satisfied
Producing
It's becoming a
Impossible
To build wealth
You have any symbol
Independence
To have
But I help
Decent marriage
Respectable marriage
Which to raise your family
You know what
Societies making
All of this
And So my answer when
It'll stay like
Are you can't do this
Good idea
You that is
Why not
What's the altar
What are we going to do
Are you going to do
Alex
Say I love Hitler
Abbeville night or we could do a lot of things
You can see here the way that Nick is able to put his finger on some actual existing social ills
Difficulty people have Building Wealth these days
He can use the recognition of these problems as a way to rope people in
An appeal to actual problems they might be Experian
Then you can blame these problems on the Jews
Scapegoat that in effect reveals
He doesn't really actually care about those social ills of themselves
Recognizing them and Performing empathy around them are tools that he uses to funnel people into his bigoted
Question of like
What other choice did they have many
Most importantly though
Is that
The things that they are blaming
On the Jews
Are the direct result of
The things they want
Want to happen
Yeah you know like oh it's harder to build well that's
Because
The way the things have been setup is that people
Who agree with you
Laws that made it impossible to do that
It's because of your desires and ideology of the problems your prescribing
Exist you have to be a little bit careful because I think that would be fairly accurate for Alex
By Knicks
Policy set is not necessarily the same as a lot of the GOP I don't give a s*** what policy
He said he has
Nick would be in favor of like government regulation
For one thing
That is a fundamental difference between him
And how Alex would approach
Write some sorts of
Ways the government can intervene
In things that would restrict people's ability
To build wealth
Super example
I am I'm not
I'm not saying you should care you are not accurate
If you are lumping hey man
With like
A lot of the
More libertarian ask
Policies and governmental ideas to talk about it's a little more,
Alright
Turn off
So Nick
Thinks that people are overthinking things
I maybe should
Maybe you just
B look at things simple
Okay
We've reached an impasse
And it's some point
People have
And I'm a really big believer in
Maybe this is
My age
Speaking
Just not even say they did
Me being a man
Picture or something
I think all those things
Appositive
A big part of my
Belief is that
We are
Overthinking
And we have thought our
Ourselves into
Box
Telling ourselves what
We can't do what
I've Never Been Gone
And what is not pause
Possible
We have thought
Arguing
Theirselves
Whenever
What is
Should be done about our
Meaning
Can't say this
Can't do that
Don't want to go
Banned on Twitter
Don't want to lose you
Your job want to be
Can't do that
People is come up with these
Convoluted
Uninspiring
Ridiculous
Strategies
Elusive populism
Multiracial working-class pop
Boo
Boring
That's less likely to work
Been saying you love him
In my opinion
People think those are
Too bad off
Options
You want to know which one I think
Worse
The one that doesn't get me excited
The one that doesn't
Grab my attention to give me on Twitter talking about it you know
Yeah inclusive popular multi-ethnic
Working-class solidarity are not things that excitement
Now
Saying you love Hitler
I do I do feel like
Just put the Epitaph on Humanity
Like real honestly like
If two things are bad I know which one I would choose the one that excites me it's literally what should be on a Humanities Gray
That's just
Various now put it on the grave site
The idea of inclusive populism or multiracial multi
Ethnic working-class solidarity
That doesn't elicit feelings of like
Create work
It created
Difficult
Things that you need to do in order to achieve these goals
Whereas
Just saying on Alex's show I like Hitler and then getting a bunch of attention for it
Is f****** easy here's what people like
Let's do the thing that gets what we want
And here's what people don't like
Getting the thing you want is actually a process that requires effort
Involved and time and cooperation and compromise and you're going to have to admit that you're wrong about something if you want to
Things to improve and I know you don't want to admit that you're wrong about something and I know you would think that you're not wrong about anything but you might be and you
If I can do it
Bright
Nobody wants to hear that
Might be his Youth and his amateur Edition I need to take
Point-of-view has much to do with age these days
So now we get to the Alex
Nick has
Levi the accusation
That the Jews got to Alex
I'm sorry what now they give him a call
But I wanted to respond
To The Alex Jones
You know cuz I basically implied that he
He got called
Cheers to
And now I would like to say
To disavow me or whatever
Disappointing
You know we did that show last week
And then
Alex Jones
Crowder
And Steven Crowder
A loudmouth
Atlas
I'm sorry I know that's negative
But it's just
I mean he literally is
Giant
This figuratively and literally just
It's one of these big headed
Goober
He's not
Maybe for people that laugh
Geico commercial
Marshalls like that
Kind of stuff is funny
Brass
And he pretends like he's a lady
Provide Geico commercials funny you might like Crowder
Shots fired
Bud what are you riding are you took a long note
8888 find it so interesting
Like this
This is space that we have
Suddenly walked into
Where
There is a
Actual battle
Between
Nick Fuentes
Actually loving Hitler
And Alex Jones
Actually not liking Hitler
He actually does not like Hitler
He said true thing
But even he can't
Make money around here
Even in his heart of hearts he can't be like I will still say I love Hitler
A little bit more time on air for a little bit more money
Even he can't do it
That's how much a piece of s*** Nick ports
True and
I think that Alex is smart enough to realize that in his branding
And it is place in the market
That kind of a pivot
Might be good for a very short burst
But it is not sustainable and it has the
High likelihood of tarnishing everything he's done
In his 30 years on air that conversation as Alex with Nick
Alex is setting to Nick like
Listen
It's not part of my brand
This will ruin what I've done for 30 years this and Nick is saying right now to the world
I think that's stupid
Let's fucken say we love Hitler
And because you won't
I think that the Jews got tangled
Yep go on crowder and stepped into snake pits and Oh no you're getting bit
So Alex on crowder shows believed he expressed the belief that he got
Tricked into being part of a publicity stunt
And Nick takes issue with that
Is he goes on there on July 8th
Operation
Nice.
That's like first of all
You wanted that inter
Are you kidding me
How are you going to
Wife
Try and fly yeah out
And I don't want to
Disclose anything
Public but
They tried to say
You should go it didn't workout
Bengay wanted to go on
We made it work
And I laughed
Talking about
Have you ever
Diffuse word of our site crash
Sing like
Man like you wanted it
You loved it it was great hundred
It's going to go down as one of the most
Famous things
In Media
I was huge
Are you going to go on the
Crowder
After you
Yeah in a mask
Aloft Hitler
Victim
You
You you mean you
Invited ye out of the
Shell and gave him
3 hours
Knowing
What's going on by the way there
And push
And then you going to go in
PrideStaff
Steven Crowder
Publicity stunt
Publicity
Okay
Alex Jones
It's honestly
Just like insult
To his audience
Come on
Candice Cruz much yeah it is
It's a fascinating because
Nick is right I'm so sad
Skip they're both right
It was a Craftsman plicity stunt Alex probably did get roped into a little more than he wanted
Like he wanted a publicity stunt but it didn't go the way he wanted
So you know there is this Middle Ground between them like it wasn't an unwilling participant
He just didn't control it the way you eat thought he was going to be able to Alex thought when he agreed to this that he could get what he
Watch it and you did not give him that
And so now he's Act
He didn't
Raven one sitting in the first place exactly
So also on the Crowder interview Alex speculated that people like
Richard Spencer
Have they gay fascination with Hitler
And then maybe Nick has a fascination with Hitler as well
And then to say it's a
That's pretty
And then he goes
Jake Paul's as gay
He said that we are
Homoerotic
Fastenal
With Hitler
Which I don't know what that house
You know
Ye said we love everybody
I would love now
Hitler we love the
Jewish beloved
Zionist
Eddie goes well they're gay for Hitler
Like it's got nothing to do with being gay
We just love Hitler
No home okay Hitler I love you
No homo
Just downright that's
The classic
He was always say
It is they always
Say all well
Methanol cheese-like
You know
Do the hand thing
Aren't they a little you know
That's not the stereotype that I am aware of never ever heard anyone do that
I'm not heard that and I've not heard
Be like even sort of bigots
Syracuse eye being a standard attack
The Jewish people make
Weird
Brand new.
Yeah
Although I do think that
Again I think of it
Alex's speculations a little
Out of nowhere
Loves Alex
What
Because everybody loves everybody right all forgot say
But it was f****** week
Go on Steven Crowder show
You know and here's the thing like I love Alex
I think it's a good man
He's a hero he's a legendary broadcaster
Never had a problem with him
But that him running
Just like a sad
Move and just like Marjorie
Doing the cabin McCarthy
And what
What J's
Sade
If I
Permitted to call Dad
What is showing
Shop
Cruciate what's really going on
Which is like
All these
AR
Control they're all controlled DA's revealing it
Yep
A anybody but
What does whiny loser
He's turned on Marjorie Taylor Greene now too if you didn't know that they have
Falling out of good graces
Farewell
Penetration of this Nazi base
Boys have to get the mood not to base if you want salad
What was that movie
There's a movie that the Nazis out of Moonbase
I don't know I don't know
Anyway
What are the things that makes me a little bit scared
More of Nick
Then some of these other figures
Is it that he does have the ability to make a metaphor
Manny this is on
F****** precedent
Many times
Alex will try to spin a metaphor along time to Nick
Has a metaphor about the Joker
But actually
Works pretty well okay
He's been saying
You know I'm like
You're all like I want to be like
Superhero
Reset the other day in the office
And I was dying
But it's true
You know because
Like your Alex
John's near Marjorie Taylor Greene there they're like the other
Criminals in gotha
The Dark Knight
They're like the mob boss
And they bringing they bring in Joker
Kill the Batman
You know they bringing gay
For the publicity
Whatever it is on their website
And it's like
I don't know who
Is the line I think
They brought in something they didn't fully under
Understand someone to see the world burn
Astro
It's all just like how the
Criminals brain
Joker and Joker Burns all the money
And says
You care about it
Counters a better class
Criminal
And they're all like horrified
I don't like in their criminals they killed people their murderers
Who is this
At the same thing as like Alex Jones
They bring this guy in
Child is better
Class a Nazi
So
And then it's people like me I'm like I'm like
Angry dog
Free dog
And I
Yeah
I think that metaphor makes
Quite a bit of sense
Criminals and Gotham had a particular problem
I was late bringing the Joker
Is it better for Alex has a particular problem
Amides eyes on his product
Publicity
Great amount of attention so he brings in the Joker
And they didn't understand what they were bringing
It's it makes complete sense I mean yes
The thing that is annoying about it
Is the
Complete and bracing of
Just being like yeah we're the Bad Guy
We do
We know for me please play The Imperial March from the Star Wars free pianos
Annoying
It is over.
It is a little pretense of like
Still wanting to win can be like
That's making it look like we're acknowledging we're on the bedside but we ask
We know that we're on the good side and you're just making it look like that but we're actually annoying
But V
It is that like
Yode the destroying of the money and stuff is the
Is essentially
Puncturing the game
That the propagandists are playing
People like Alex
The thing that they didn't realize the Joker or ye was going to do
Is not so much the like actually costing the money or anything like that
It's that like
You guys are
Third
You can't play a crypto game with me
I am going to just call out the chaos here I am unfiltered unfettered
So Nick take some issue here with Alex because Alex was that
You saying that
He stood up for Nick and Nick never stood up for him
And
That's bulshit
You know he said oh you know why
Stood up for dicks
She's never show me any love it's like
I am
Have talked about
I have always been one of the
Wants to cover
The lawsuit
Understand man
Set the ship against him I'm always mentioning
The same breath as everybody else
So that's just simply not true
But when you did the other day was kind of
He had ample
Call Mia
Nazi
ER
Call Carlos de nada
Or what
How to say all that
A week later.
And cries about it to Crowder
I'm a bit
The publicity stunt
Are these terrible Nazi
Please I'm just a humble water fill
Filter
You know no trumpet
Patriot salesman
Please please don't cancel me
And you know the thing is like there's dirt layers
Of course
Alex
But he also
Presumably have Zionist backers
Like no doubt
I think even told me that
First time I ever went on a
Commercial break
First thing I talked about was Israel
Any cotton during the commercial break and said like hey
I'm not telling you what to say you can
Say whatever you want
But I recommend like not talking
King about Israel
The Jew thing or whatever
He goes but that's just not going to get you anywhere
We have a lot of Grey
Why Jewish list
Something like that it was like
4 years ago I don't really
Remember
First time I was
Don't get no don't play
Stupid everybody knows
That's how it goes
Everybody knows
So I think
If I were to guess
There was a conversation the first time Nick was on
And Alex
Knowing that Nick is a knot
I know that open not this s*** right was trying to get him to do the same thing that you did with yay
And because Nick
Wasn't a mega celebrity like he he didn't have a place in the market that was higher in value
You then being on Alex's show
Along with it and now he
He's contextualizing that is Alex having Jewish owners
Your handlers are whatever
And this
This is something that will play with Uno
Nick's audio
I mean as opposed
Just being like
See the way it works
Status is Alex was higher than me before but now I'm higher than Alex so I could engage in the same behaviors that Alex did
However because I'm higher status
You'll forgive me for doing it
And I can make you blame him for doing it perfectly think it's more than he's potentially higher status
Hello
It's hard to tell what with Alex's woes right now
I feel like
Higher status of his own
No no absolutely not he definitely ahead of Alex
Clear that
If I was a betting man I would say hubris and pride will be his downfall
As is the case with people exactly like this throughout history over and over and over and over and over again
Feel like
Make that is a
Very distinct possibility
Had a manic episode and decided to unleash his anti-Semitism across the world and then sudden the house
Found me in that I tagged along it's actually because I'm great
Conceivably Alex got a call from these dudes handlers that he has
Betty wants to go and cry I saw it
He's crying about how I
He said he got a phone
SoundCloud
This is a phone call
George Washington
It's like
No
You got a call from the
You got a call
The Jewish people
The buy the supplement
Whatever
You just like yeah
You don't okay I'm not
You got a call from you
Zinus bathroom
Okay
You didn't get a call from Genoa
You got to call
Diana's bath
You know Israel did 9/11
You know about Jewish influence you know about it
She talked about other shows
20 years ago
David Duke
Debated you into the ground on this
And I beat the
A spotted Rober
Bars on your showing year ago about it
No you didn't get a call
From Jefferson
You got a call from
Zion is back come on it was right there
What stopper come on
Find you
Billions of dollars you want to have
You studio and all that
You want you wanted
Do more with less
In other words
You want to have a
Big Show while saying
Fine
That's your decision
You're entitled to make that two
But but you know we all see
Right through this
What are you talkin about Ivan
What are you implying
Here's what I'm implying
You got a call for
Diana's bath
That was a big problem
Okay and that's why you pressed yay about
You know and he was myth
That the whole show is about Hitler
Please watch a show he kept pushing
And pushing and pushing
You know you can't just let the guy say he loves
God forbid anybody
Like that
Coming back and coming back
What about the uniform
What you mean is this
He said what he said
You are not going to argue somebody
If there
Inherent position
Is the only reason
That you would dislike Hitler
Is because you got a call from extremely powerful Jewish
If that's your big
Getting possessed
Right where's the argument going to start
Nowhere
It's a disaster as bad as saying that because I think I'm gone I'm out of here
The implication here is kind of interesting cuz if you unpack this
I think what Nick is saying is that like you know how like Republican
Organizations will buy bulk purchases of people's books in order put them on the bestseller list
He seems to be implying that there are zionists handlers
Or backers or whatever who buy a bunch of Alex's supplements
I was finances work or something
I don't think that's the case
Weird yeah
I don't I don't think
Okay so here's my business
I am going to get a bunch of
Our own labels on bulshit pills
And then some weirdo billionaires are just going to buy those
Move them from my warehouse
To their warehouse
Where they'll just sit and wait
Sure I mean
I don't know
I think
It would be
I mean I guess all of the callers who say they use the products could be lying but I don't know I don't
Smiletastic
But yeah this is it this is why you don't get mixed up with someone like Nick
Cuz like he has some actual good points here
Yeah that is that David Duke
Did out debate Alex autograph out debate Robert Barnes
Infowars
But
The then the conclusion that he jumps to that Alex is behaving the way he is bi
Because some Jewish handlers told him to
Completely unearned and there isn't any reason to believe that right
There is everything is explained by a very simple Occam's razor that is
That there is a certain
Blue Point past which Alex's business model
Is no longer viable
Nick is push past that point
And
It has nothing to do with
Jewish influence
Threatening Alex are coming down on him Overton profit window
Is everything to do with just
Simple understanding your place in the mark
And
Claim that
Like some sort of Nefarious thing but
Well the thing is quartz his f****** show like in his parents basement he's he's got a nice little spot for himself right now.
Because he doesn't actually have a play
In the meeting
Everything he's doing
Clawing a place
For himself
It's all
Destructive
Exactly the sort of
Privateering he doesn't have to defend anything he's wearing the armor of being a Nazi
Defend this takes time and I love I said I love Hitler what
Be mean to me about you can't hurt me because that
And so all he has to do is point out the incredibly obvious bulshit that everybody's doing
Because it's incredibly obvious it doesn't take a genius to be like
Oh Alex is exploiting people yeah you're a f****** brilliant and it's just it's just such an easy spot to
The problem is
Once he get something
Then he's going to go through the process of trying to hold on
Does something right
Definitely
So Nikki
Unfortunately a little bit yes peelings
And he feels bad that everyone keeps throwing them under the bus
Pretty kind of under
Costanza
Very annoying
And you know
You got all these days
People that are much older than
The me like Marjorie or Alex
Whoever
And constantly throwing me under the bus
Steve Ferrone
Dislike
Seriously
Like I am
The thing is like
Meet all these two
People on
I'm obviously like
Nice guy
Hawaii
Respectful
Like I'm obviously
Maurice Nazi
Really like
My bike character is pretty on a
Teachable life or something like that
I'm not a hater I have a big hard-on
I'm just like a lovable guy want to make a
The funny show
And and I believe it all the same things all these
People do
And they just have like no
Compunction about life
Slitting my throat
If it makes their life
You know it's like Marjorie
Map me
Shook my hand gave me a hug
Davis Beach
All this
Pretends not to
Janome the day after okay fine
You know you got to say
What you got to say
But you got to like
Denounce
What's my views
Anti-Semitic
Because she got pressure
Sure from the Jewish
She got pressure
McCarthy at the arch
Seeing all back
And she's like oh yeah
I'll totally pushed
Traffic
To make my life easier
Easier
I didn't believe until quite recently that the Jews had space lasers the stick used
Control weather
Yeah this is like Azazel in Hell being like he's there's a lot of demons around here what's going on
Around here has just started to realize that
Integrity loyal bunch
I wonder why I gravitated to them in the first place probably not important not going to think about it
Impeachable character
So
Meeting ye was amazing
That again probably was because his love for a long time
Meeting Alex
Which was not
It's a breath of fresh air to me
Somebody's a
True American original
And I truly somebody's free you mean Alex Jones
The first time I went on his life
Say whatever you want
And I was like
You know don't get me wrong you still
So funny
Workhorse
Incredible
But I was
When I heard that out
Deflated
Was like all your knots
Guy doing a show
You're good show
Hodor
But it's like
That was my
Give me like some contrast like either
The first time I wear
Michelle
Commercial break
Whatever you want
Don't talk about the Jew
Are the Jewish things that Dad and I was like
That's like what my parents
That's so cool
Alex
Absolute
You know
He's telling me the same
Stuff my
My Boomer parents
Really good idea
Did you really say that
I love my girl
The other normally like that there normally like well my son is Hitler
I hope he's not too Hitler
Toby grows out of the Hitler stuff like that is
Is that.
I don't know
Ground him something
Takeaway is allowance
Again
Never meet your Heroes though you know
Next very disappointed by Alex's non
Embracing of the Nazi lifestyle to me up about this
Is how empty all of this is if it also includes like
I still think he's a great guy and I think all of this s*** that's like that blows my mind
I disagree with
Because
Nick recognizes that
Alex is still doing something that serves his interest
And that is
Being the more introductory step
People can come into
Knicks
Stream
Or he's River much easier if there's a tributary threaten like Alex
There where you're coming from
Even if he is some kind of a shell or whatever
Nick is awareness the people who get sucked into that
Have a tendency to
Grow past
Alex's material Nikita harder drugs
Obviously not empty for him
Yes
So makes fun of
Alex it's like he's going to go insane
Hitler Hitler parted hair
Who is that for
For the Jews like who is that bore
Nobody is rigged with that nobody is impressed
Why you said
MARSOC
Don't cut yourself on that edge
Bro I like
I see why your face
Does not want you to
Another was a
Democrat
Dam Ali
Go off
Jesus said Hitler burn in hell
Absolute Madman
Woohoo Ladd
This playground should does not fly it at like oh you think my mom is fat Houck
Cool
No no no dude
You love him
That I mean there's no you can't be like oh how cool is it that he doesn't like Heather no f*** you
Doesn't work on this one
The Forgotten
The only reason this is actually kind of like
Maybe a dangerous point for Alex
Is that he is a free-speech absolutist
And it is
That he is like he fancies himself the tip of the spear
And like this
This kind of like dangerous edgy censored person that you've been censored by everybody
And your censorious toward someone else
Do kind of hold a little bit of a trump card on you
There is a little bit of a power that this person who has been censored by the guy who's against censorship
Right because you can't argue with that person
That Hitler can't be the tip of the spear
Well you know like you can't argue with Nick you can't be like hey know I get what you're saying
But you think that being edgy memes Hitler
When in reality
Your
Just
Loving Hitler that's the end of this conversation we got over a while ago
It's genocide I don't know what else to describe it as it's not an interesting conversation that Society refuse
Uses to have it's a conversation that we had and we've moved along
It's just you're trying to rehash it for
Yeah most of society is 100% on that there's no middle ground on Hitler
So also f*** Crowder and maybe Marjorie Taylor Greene
Scapegoat
Like we get to attack
Nick
For being the nice
We're just going to pretend like
Aiden said
Everybody wants to throw me under the bus
Whatever
I'll remember that
Also
Here's a real last
None of the people that threw me out of the bus are really
Even that impressed
I have never watch Crowder
I think I watched a
Crowder's
Not Wiegand
You know so crowded
Disavowing me
Marjorie Taylor Greene
You like
You know
I've already
Looks like
Does anybody really think so like if I had my
Choice that I'd be like
Standing with Margie
Retailer green
Like listen you got to play with the hand you're dealt I'll just put it out
Marjorie Taylor Greene danowski let's say is like no love lost
Honestly
Deshawn for McCarthy
And she was still
Backpack that would be
That would
Be bad
For me.
Blue pill weekly
I'm trying not to swear
Cuz Kanye doesn't like it yeah
About
You're somebody who's associating with
Is that
He seemed
To be fully in support of Marjorie
Back when they were on good terms
I know that they are falling out
He's being a little bit more open about like I wouldn't have wanted to work with her but no one else wanted to work
You play with the hand you're dealt at this is one big exercise in the emperor has no clothes
Kind of
Hey man just being like
Look at all these losers like that's that's again that's what makes me so empty for me is that yes
They are a bunch of losers
Did you see that
You are a bigger loser
Yeah it's me it's that same Dynamic that he has when he's talking about social issues then sometimes he's able to descriptively
Text get his finger on something that is an actual problem but his analysis and
Assertive
Other
Conversation around things is
Maybe worse
Definitely worse
Or meaning
And he has put his finger on a very real thing year that is funny and he's vaping
Nobody would want to work with Marjorie Taylor Greene if they had another choice
And
Complicated
Everything else around it
Is bad and he is worse it just
Any does it is so much more desirable I mean it if I were if I were not
Listening to Alex and MPG
It is so much more desirable
To listen to the kid who says that the emperor has no clothes
Because I knew it the whole f****** time
But they are
Told me because they all love each other that actually know they're great
The finally I have not seen that I can love
Who is willing to admit that every other not because an a******
Which makes
It does make some sense
Yeah
Sonic
He likes to see the good in people
Like Richard Spencer
Here's some of the good that makes season Richardson
Let's see who else or any other big blue checks
Senior Buzz besides
What time I call the Mom
On the phone I was like hell rich
He was like
See that's the type of humor you can't get on crowder show
Well not only
I mean that is his name
That is his name
I don't think that
You know out of line.
Want to be called the sir
That's helpful.
That's how I'mma
The van one of my favorites
See you know we find when we like about people you find what you
Walkabout
People that's got it that's a great story Richard Spencer said it's Richard not rich
What a guy so funny
I'm going to guess that there was something else that happened in that conversation that makes him memorable
It may be Richards listening and nose
Otherwise that it's Rich story
Is a little flat
Not a lot going on there
Also
F******
So infuriating
In so infuriating
What if it said it's
Raven
Order pizza.
Oh
Only I would have a bigger problem with calling them by something that they wanted to be called
Sure
So we have one last
Scorpio
Very exciting big breaking news
How about the new song.
Right
DeBary FL
What new song
Gales Garden Center
Like anybody and I don't know why maybe for the Alex
John sample
He took out the
Play I love Hitler
The one the version that I heard
It ended with that I love that I love that I love about Hitler
But that's okay
That's okay we know what he meant
Yep
So this is pretty funny
Gary posted this song on Instagram which seems like a strange
Considering what he's been yelling about Instagram of the sex trafficking operation at anyone who clicks a like button on a woman's picture is sex
They removed the song apparently and then he sent it to Alex and posted it on Infowars at the headline
Yale releases epic new song
Exclusively on Infowars
The fuc
It's an exclusive release because it got taken offense
Oh my God
And yeah after all of this
After everything that's happened Alex is still super anxious to post
There's no continuity in the new show
There's a new monster of the week
I know I got burned by this publicity stunt anyways
I'm going to release that single baby come on now
Sheesh
Play the song pretty but it's really bad suspected the reason it got taken off Instagram was because he use samples that he hadn't
I'm cleared there might have been like a copyright issue there
I don't think it'll be a hit if only because he includes a lyric about how God won't let him have sex until he's married again
Just kids are getting
That's the new punk rock
That's the new put new punk rock is no sex before marriage baby
Cool cowboy
This is this is where we're at
Marketplace is not a good place
Snow not
It just not I think
I think that it is important to understand like some of these Dynamics within this right-wing
Ecosystem in terms of how
There is this
Dual-use of
Yay
Ladies there's the ideal version which is recruiting him and getting him to cool it
Right on some of this stuff that is going to be bad for business
Omn failing that beer
And then failing that there's the
The using him
Like everyone used to use Alex and still does
When they need to
Maybe I'm not him person right
So there's that MMI I just think it's
Really interesting to hear next
Response because there is some
Analysis of dynamic
Between these figures
That he understand
Clearly
A Mac
Is something you don't really hear people talk about
Within the circles very much
Exactly
I think that's
That's what's so
Empty I think what's soda SEPTA
Give about it is because
He is willing to say the things
Things that everybody knows
People give him more credit for being able to see through this camera
When in reality they are
See-through the scam
He's just the only one who is
Making his scam
Pointing it out
Yes you know like he's just making his own little scam that he's got going on but
It's it's
Counter to the
The ecosystem that sustains itself with that interlocking
King scams and that is a large reason essentially why he's not going to be involved
In a lot of these other folks
Alex
In his interview with Crowder said that he would have went as back on
But it would need to be a debate
Auntie
I don't want to guarantee I've been wrong about
So much
I don't think that's going to happen
The reason
Pasta note
Nick would dance circles around me be sad
Nick Cannon Dodge
Is beyond Alex's capacity to punch
The things that Nick can say
They will
Confuse Alex
Will be too much
I'll go even simpler than that
Alex would have to prepare
I mean
So really the end
If you wanted to
Engaged
In that the way that he would engage in it didn't seem to prepare that much for David Duke
Nope
Anyway
This all is a mess
And
Maybe we'll go back to checking in on Infowars and Alex show itself next week we'll see apparently wearing
The palace Intrigue with a conservative propaganda
I think it's an elevated slightly it is it is it is I realized you I realized
Paris to you
There was a little bit of that saying that there wasn't
Extreme there was nothing I didn't notice that is just kind of fun like him yelling
Crowder
I'm fine with that
There's also an element of it that the cathartic necessities
It's so f****** obvious
You don't get involved with people like this
Because
That's what they'll do to you
They are going to smear you they're going to use things
That you may have said in confidence
Answer private or
Or something
And they will take those things
And then present them to their audience as
Some kind of evidence that you're involved in fairies plot
You know it's
Just stay away, don't get involved it is it is like
Part of me is
This is like here's what should be required reading
For third graders and it should be for every day of the year and that's just fat
Like just really get into understanding what the devil's bargain mean
You know like
At third grade you're 8 or 9 years old you're ready
To figure out what unintended consequences are it's time to hammer it home at a young age be nice
So Jordan
Welcome to the end of this
And I would also like to say thank you to Amanda for some help
With us
But until then
We have Vella website.com
Yep we'll be back
Until then
Emilio Emilio I'm dvx.
I didn't think of a new bit
You have been doing lately
Let's not a lot more frosting than I'd like to admit
Frosting than you'd like to admit the amount of frosting that you would like to admit to eat at like 1 dunkaroo
Morgan Carew package
How many packs
Well I've not got dunkaroos
Well that might be a first problem tubs of frosting and then
Wafers
This is one of the revelations you'll find him
What the sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color