Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Jones
M4u top
Jordan is
You know I'm a pretty
Even
Kill type of fellow you are monotonous
So my tip monotone you keep it level
Yeah I'm so excited for fun
I'm going to get high
I'm going to force I'm going to force getting high
About something in advance
Fire Fire Emblem game is coming out in January
So I'm going to artificially be
Market Pub I'm kind of excited I'm excited to play it it looks real
I'm going to I'm going to overdo it probably a little bit
Just ever
Sort of as a bit but then also have an extra I see if like maybe maybe hyperworks on Me Maybe you
Where the skin of somebody with her
Hydrite maybe I'd like all this feels right
But yeah it's it looks good looks good that's the only thing I'm worried about is it takes away what I love so much about three houses
Which was being it's in a school
Yeah it's where is it I don't know
Well that doesn't
Now that I say this out loud I have no idea
I just saw a tiny little video
Anyway turn-based RPG fun
Hi yeah you you just you just went from being eyeball the way down till you back to level again
I don't have the energy for this
What's a ride
My bright spot is I saw my wife and I saw
Guillermo del Toro's Pinocchio
Absolutely stellar
Really really good like the movies good but
The stop-motion animation is the best thing
There's this there's this team can you tell me what the movie is again really quick okay yeah that's what I thought you said
I got distracted cuz I saw the date
And I thought it was a palindrome but then I realized it was last year
12 11211 would have been
Play Pinocchio
Sorry about as interesting as possible palindromes distractible
Paradox
No just a bunch of there's this one scene
Stop motion animation
Where there's this
Floating balloon this slightly floating balloon the type that you know where
The string is just barely touching and it's a little bit above that it's so
It's incredible. It's it's mind-blowing we good
Is it super dark
No I mean
The original Pinocchio do you remember that
I don't remember all the details but I remember it being darker than the Disney version
So yeah it's a little bit like that
But with
Guillermo del Toro monsters so it seems a lot darker than it really is just cuz he
His monster design is so you know monsters you be like
This is a fun kids story with a
Of dark elements drifted a little closer to h.r. Giger and I were in the Hall of uncanny
Valley Music
Episode to do where we going back to the past 2003
5th 2003
And the reason for this is
We've been discovered
Stuff
The ye business
Alex's responds to it
Is a bit of quintessence of I think this stuff is really important
To discuss an important to cover we're not going to not
Continue to do or we going to
Not
Follow Alex in the present
Inside of course
I think you run the risk
If we only talk
About that stuff it gives a overwhelming
Perception of
Of maybe how
Uniform it is
You know what I mean like if I was all that about the listeners taking in too much of that in like
Giving the sense that we
Think that
Everything all around is white supremacist the Nazis jumping up
I need a little break from time to time a little break he is a little brain
The past is great
Respa
Absolutely
And the present sucks
Really learning anything in the present generally it's kind of watching
Stuff and being like oh this is bad
Where's when you go back to the path there's actually like
Illuminating things their stories that are interesting that has implications
To learn things about the way Alex
His brand has evolved over the years
And I I think that that is something that I find the far more captivating than
Him
Failing
To interview
A couple of guys who loved me
No I mean what's interesting about the past
Does that when you can look at the
Something and then see what kind
Consequences did
Occur there's a lot more interesting
Stuff to be learned from that because you have
Actual evidence
What will happen if you do this thing in this circumstance
Where is if you stay in the present all too often I mean if it does feel like we're
Constantly within the same framework and Minor Details are changing you know
Vic Fuentes hasn't said something new we haven't heard about white supremacist before you don't have tunnel vision saying
Presents a little bit to better way to express what I am
I don't want to
M play into
Listen to notes fight
You're not going to be putting
The tunnel tunnels
Purdue Dartmouth say hello to the new Wok Super Snake be in Austin
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Nick didn't get button
When's last time a male neck there some coming out for you
I am your partner
Sorry about that
Next honky-tonk
But don't be dogs thank you so much you're now policy want
Thank you very much I had a number of people email me about that about a missed opportunity
You talk about Don D walk
Is better
I mean
You know what
I'm going to sit this one out
You know that song that you know the song Honky Tonk Badonkadonk
Why I want to stay away from this because my disdain for all of it it no gray was a big
You hear that the karaoke bar is back when I was going to those ones on the outskirts
So Town call there was a time where someone made me line dance
So yeah that awkward moment when you realize your name reminds Jordan of Richard Spencer thank you so much you're in Alabama
Text I just got accepted into paramedic school so what better time to become
I'm a policy wonk
Very much
I was Brandon saying that he loves Emily.
No there is no just like Emily any accusations
Are unfounded absolutely will have none of it
Victorian so happy Winter Solstice Michaela
You're now
Four Star
Get mad and tell your brother
Someone someone sodomites
Has a Caribbean
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Thank you very much
So we come
Into December to
We are still in advance
Of Saddam being found
Again is what were what we're heading towards
In the in this
Chronology where we're heading towards that
Trying to see how Alex
React
Is coverage in the lead up to it as well
As we know he believes that Saddam is still alive which is accurate
True but
He believes that he has fled the country is in Belarus
With a bunch of stolen gold and his is Suntour
Actually that it's going to be weird to explain how Saddam went from Comfort
In Belarus
To the central Temple hole in the ground
It will be tough but Alex is up for the challenge I'm sure
Okay so we start here in a little bit of a different take on some geopolitical figure
BoBoiBoy
This man 2003 Alex's very
Much a of Putin
Did the bombings
As they both like pretext
Got order to fight the Chechen
Death ain't so well that is completely different now
One thing I like about having consistent principles is that I haven't had to change my opinion on Putin ever not
One time have I thought well maybe nope
100% anti-putin from the
The jump I've had some misgivings about him
1003 I'm pretty sure I was I think I was 19 so there's no reason for me
You have gone on the record I know you're writing a little column Bailey
Pro Putin
It did not
So there's another story Alex
You know when we're in the past
What are the things that Alex does is
He has like the Roundup
The story
A man alota bulshit for about two-and-a-half hours and then the last segment of the show is him repeat
Eating those headlines around up in the food.
It's a secure some of the stories
Toronto
Start article
Girl
Husband quite a bit of time trying to track this story down but I was unable to find the actual news story that was covering this case
Turn off the GPS because there's a story that happened in Canada
Wherever you at Child Protective Service doesn't have any jurisdiction
Extradition
The Toronto Star article itself isn't online anymore in the way-back machine doesn't have a snapshot of it but cruising around I was able to
Find some other cases that Alex my won
I consider
And Leo
October 2003 a 23 year old mother in Summerville Georgia was arrested for throwing her eight-month-old into a dryer
Or in November 2011 in Niles Miss Michigan was arrested for shutting her six-year-old son in a
Running dryer
We're playing hide and seek
During which time he had hit in the dryer Jesus Christ
One of the things that I sadly learned while prepping this episode is that apparel
Only people put babies and dryers more than you'd think
Like which is horrible
Even if you grant that all the details of the story Alex is telling her true it's still not a valid point
There are definitely valid critiques of the CPS in foster care
To be made it anything that can be done to protect the children in that world is a moral imperative to pursue
But abuse like this happens in all this
My contacts
The image that Alex is trying to present is that it never happens
Between a parent and a child and whenever there's a headline that read like that's the case
It's secretly a situation where the CPS is abusing children
You're trying to blame it on parents
Because the globalist
A family
In hindsight it really shouldn't come as a huge surprise that Alex got caught up and s*** like pee
Pizzagate the Wayfair stuff
It pretty much every other child abuse satanic panic
He's never really taking the issue seriously
So what are you doing now is more or less
The natural progression of what you see even back in 2000
It's a cartoonish Miss around a fairly serious issue
Yeah
That is that is one of those
One of those things where I can
Definitely understand the
The desire to
To think that it only would be an evil organ
Innovation that could do the
You know like that
That is one of those things where you want to retreat
From the idea that a parent
No matter
What the circumstances could even do that
You know
I get that but also know that's not how it works right
That's that's one example of a few actually think that you're going to see on
This episode of
Places where conspiracy theories serve to make things feel more like you think
They should be an underappreciated Dynamic of some of the the narratives
That people put out.
Maybe this that doesn't make sense to me emotionally intuitively or whatever
Or even just
Hopefully
So Alex Reeb these headlines before even reads them
Prove it
Start reading some articles
Barbara Sturm article
Propaganda
This is such a perfect encapsulation of Alex
His methods except he's lying about following up by reading the story
He just needs a headline and decides he knows what the articles about them doesn't change his mind when presented with evidence
That is manufactured narrative is based
I think
I am in my mind what hap
Does that sound right
He reads a headline
And then starts thinking of what he wants it to be another out there it's reading the words all the sudden they swirled together in a man
Magic paper and then rearrange themselves
The way that he wants them
To go it's exactly happy
And his mom is exactly that except for the part where he's still looking at the words while they're rearranging
Imagine what the story is I got my God
Good father wait for the words to redo themselves you can just throw the paper in the garbage
Alex has some memories of Fire
Short and he's wrong
But he's a very wrong about his memories
Most
Marine
Accident
Started
Control
To the fall of 2003 was a horrific season for fires in California which would eventually come to include for
14 different fires
The Cedar Fire being remembered as the most
Severe of the bunch
The first one on October 21st was called the roblar to fire
And this one was accidentally started at the Marine Corps Base
Camp
On the firing range
This was particularly complicated fire response because it was on Federal Land
And beyond that just
Consider all the things that could have
Load at a Marine Base
I didn't get some sense of how delicately fireteams needed to tread
Pretty bad
Is shity is this sound
Fires at these bases
It's not a
Terribly uncommon
I was able to find examples of fires breaking out just
Camp Pendleton
In 2008 and 2014 and that was
Barely even putting any effort into looking
I arrive feel like I've witnessed a minor fires
Just existing in my own place
And there are far fewer flammable things about
You know like there's a lot of people in a large amount of flammable things true
Exactly
Too many of the other fires were smaller in nature but they contributed to an environment where firefighting resources were spread thin
Made worse by a dry season and the arrival of some bad Santa Ana winds
That made fire spread much more easily
The Cedar Fire which the San Diego government
Describe this quote the largest Wildland fire in California history
Was started quote when
Hunter became lost and little small fire to signal for help
One of the other large fires called
The old fire was started by an arsonist
First name Ricky Lee Fowler
Who burned the house down after he was kicked out of it
The fire ended up killing
5 people and in
2013 he was found guilty of those murders and sent
Dance to death
Another of the large fires was the Grand Prix fire which was suspicious
But was called an accident by investigators in 2004 likely the result
Oven exhaust
Spark or cigarette butt
I'm not sure what out evidence Alex is basing his claims on and he doesn't cite a single Source other than his Memories of Us
Name news things he claimed through
Still seems like maybe he's just talkin
If I had to guess I would say that he's taking the fact that the roblar to fire began at Camp Pendleton
And then pretending that some of these other fires like
The older Grand Prix also had military involvement
In their ignition
That seems in line with how his mind works
And how he processes information
Exactly was the nefarious Evil part that was
Like he's saying that all of these fires got started at military bases. Not all military bases but all
Military like
But I don't understand what their goals
Climate change
Something make people think it's worse or something I don't know
They could script Marines
To start random massive
Forest fires right in order to trick people into thinking the property values I don't know got to have that
Specific about what fire he's talking about in Arizona but I believe the one he's talking about the big one that pits
Around the time frame that he's mentioning is known as the Aspen fire
This Fire Burns for just short of a month
And ended up covering / 84000 acres of land
In the woods
Switch to fit Alex's decryption
Initially folks thought that it was possibly caused by a lightning
Strike but investigators fairly quickly ruled that out as none of the telltale signs were there
It's believed that it was human-caused and while the definite origin isn't known there was a man who ended up being charged with
Convicted of lying to investigators about whether or not he was smoking on the trail that day
Exactly where the fire was known to have started
It's a pretty safe assumption that this was the inciting incident that caused
The fire
Or I guess you could globulus military exercises involved setting up giant fires
How to prove that if he wants
In the interest of full disclosure the military does hold training exercises twice a year in that area
In a program called Angel Thunder
It's about Personnel recovery but it absolutely would not be taken
Place near the trail where the fire started
Yeah and the program began in 2000
But there is that is a bass right nearby this
Mount Lemmon the area where the the fire was
It's conceivable that there might have been some sort of an exercise that pre-existed
Angel Thunder
Even so
Investigators are able to zero in on a
Pretty close location of where the fire started
Anywhere near where people were doing exercise
Prove this
Man you know what that
When you hear that Firebird for a month
You know it's 8 so f****** crazy to complete mastery
Cover fire can turn the fire on now if I got a lighter in my pocket bike master
And then you said that
Gets out of control a little bit
And it's burning for a month
Yeah
F****** crazy
Damn an issue here is that these kinds of giant devastating event
Can be easily caused by mundane and seemingly inconsequential things
And it doesn't feel right
It's an everyday action for so many people to just toss their cigarette butts on the ground so yeah
Seem possible that doing that could lead to
The tens of thousands of Acres being burned
And hundreds of homes being
Destroy
Not fair
But it can't happen but it's not fair and I knew about
Doesn't feel right that something so insignificant could have such severe effect
Can have the result of causing people to seek for explanations that do feel right
Something as huge as a month-long fire requires a commensurate cause like a shadowy world government plot
It's debatable whether Alex
Is a person who suffers from this need to come up with emotionally satisfying stories to explain world events
Or if he knows that the audience
Does any exploit that the profit
Spectrum down
I'm not sure but either way it
It's really best not to take information
Inform him
Yeah yeah
Band
Avel boy of all the of all the cockamamie screw-ups
Deborah ball boy being responsible for a forest fire
Yeah I mean
Cedar Fire 12 is really a bummer because
You going to
Subway's if you're a hunter and you're lost
And like you have a potential that you might die out in the woods or something right
Where's our something that survivalists or talk to
It's not outside of the realm of like well what else am I supposed to do in this
Situation
Mnd side effect of it
You know is this
Hundreds of
Dozens of Acres end up burned
Complete disaster
Yeah I know it puts all of the reality survival contest shows that I've ever seen in such a weird like
Whatever you stop and think about it like oh we're f****** up a section of the Earth for my entertainment
You know it messes with your head but the idea that it's
Entirely possible that one of those shows
Obviously it hasn't happened but in the future if we don't we don't know baby cuz
That would be the globalist for sure get it for 3
Yeah I mean like you're even on Survivor like there has been times when the like the shelter
Has burned down but like it does
Spread further
Yeah it's
It's
You know I mean I don't know how else to say but life is very fragile
It is it is
Planet this season in 2003 so fascinating because you have this like this Cedar Fire
Fire that is caused by this
Guy
Who's signaling for help
This guy did nothing wrong there late maybe didn't make the fire as well as he could have maybe there's something
It could have been anything
You wouldn't assign moral culpability to him
For that
I've been simultaneously there's this old fire
There is an arsonist
Who said it
Moral culpability
Yeah you have these burning within the same season
And it's easy to get all of them in your head as the same fire because I are all looks the same
It's hot and there's smoke
2003 was the the year
A fire moral relativism
Explain
It took a while preparing this episode because I had those sorts of thoughts
A little bit and then because of this
Story which blew my mind
Just look at the types of articles I have
Blurb
I guess you shouldn't
I don't know why you're welcome not you
Wild It Out by that a really should be headlines
Starting conflicts
At the beginning of the second Mexican-American war so this is a wild Newsmax story where a guy named Robert mop
Claimed that he and his family have been kidnapped by as many as eight Mexican soldiers who would cross the border to
To capture him
Mysteriously they were let go and this wasn't an international incident that was sparked over it
Crossing over borders to detain people even when they're wanted fugitives is a messy business as Dog The Bounty
Hunter learn first
The team's wild to imagine that this story happened as mopping describe
He claims that he reported a meth lab
Habitue on his land to the DEA who then told the Mexican authorities
Sure I'm clear why they would do this considering that his land is in the United States
It's but let's not get lost them
Good call the Newsmax headline ends with a?
Because even they aren't sure about this
A sourcing is sin
What whose quote was it that if it ends in a? The answers no I don't know any news articles
And if the news might even a little bit of leg work
They would not have had a good cause
To publish
The story
For safety by xenophobic demagogues like Alex when they were bored
Story
Yats us poking around
I came across an article in the New York Times I get arrested for the past
Sprite
Here we go
It's like I don't want it's going to be before I say
There was an article in the times
From May 1997
Put includes this little tidbit
Quote
Bob Maupin who maintains that he was arrested on his own land by Mexican soldiers protecting a meth lab
Smugglers have tried to run him down and their trucks
That article also explains how it started his own vigilante group that wanders the border and make citizen's arrest
Blessing of the deputy sheriff Robert Novak
Dressed in camouflage
Fatigues that carry semi-automatic rifles their own vietnam-era seismic sensors and zip ties for handcuffs
Quote we get together at night to make a game out of it hookah
Can catch the most
Besides
If you dress properly they don't know who you are so we get really really good cooperation
Right yeah those guys should be in jail
Of all the people who should be in jail in this story it is those dudes
Snap
This guy created a militia that terrorizes immigrants were fun
More than one occasion that he's been kidnapped by Mexican soldiers crossing the border because he's
Ditched on a meth lab
Seems like that story isn't true and maybe it's a rationalization
Hawaii mop and does this horrible s***
So you don't have to feel like a monster
2016 Maupin was interviewed about his support for Trump's wall in the Monterey Herald
Multiple times being held captive by the
Government
Weirdly neither does his creation of a vigilante gang
Very important to note that he isn't shy about letting Mexican Viagra
Smuggler's know that they aren't welcome to pass through his sprawling property in the Tiny Town of Boulevard
If you can read this you're in range one sign says his breath
Here's one thing that I have
An interested when you're reporting on this type of thing
Sure you can say it's a vigilante group or gang
Or you could say it's a group of men who commit hate
Crimes on the regular same thing so maybe one weighs more accurate though
Then
There's a book
Call illegals
The image of right by our unsecured us Mexico border
This book retails a time when mopping was kidnapped by Mexican troops
I love I love his stick into his fictional story I like it this time it was along with his daughter
Apparently he told a friend of his who worked in Narcotics enforcement that he smelled ether on his property
And there was a building about half a mile from the border that was usually empty but he would periodically see it occupied
He would know was occupied because plainclothes men with weapons would be patrolling
Then they would Hoist the Mexican flag
Nothing meth labs on foreign soil like to do more than announce their presence in Toronto tension to themselves
Rihanna's daughter were out shooting and work
Confronted by Mexican troops carrying NATO weapon
It should be noted that this situation is about
The same setup as the story being told in 2003 where his whole family was out shooting
Stuff these groups that they were looking for illegal guns and drugs
Today I have no
Jurisdiction to investigate of us oil to this is ridiculous
They also said they were looking for senior Maupin
Which Robert said quote made it pretty clear to me that that I had made somebody in the Mexican Government angry by sticking my nose
Who's into their drug business
I would say regularly committing hate crimes probably makes a lot of people mad at you
He warned the truth
But their guns work legal here whereas his
Is were
What are the soldiers didn't care and tried to take his daughters Gunn fuckbay so she backhanded him
About noctem
Oh my God
The others ready their weapons so mopping and his daughter put down their guns knowing that they were outmatched
This story is a convoluted mess and I don't believe a word of it
This part is
Particularly unbelief
Robert Maupin was
Planning to pursue legal remedies but Federal officials told him he would have to be in court for 3 to 4 months
Straight time he decided to let the matter drop
You know what sure
The entire Mexican government
Send a small Cadre of troops
Apparently kidnap you
Three or four months in court
Instead of spending those months and God I guess mop and decided to recycle this story on a couple more occasions to justifies discuss
Gothic vigilante actions in the process create new cycles that incite fear and hatred of Mexican Emma
Anyway this is part of the story that Alex doesn't cover because he does
He just looks for headlines that helped him get involved in that same incitement to fear and hatred and it does the job
He ignores
Is the?
And ignores
Hey who is this guy what's going on oh he's told this story
Multiple time
He seems to
Keep getting kidnapped
Gilligan's Island they end up
He keeps getting kidnapped I will say this
Never before has a story made me more likely to believe that Steve pieczenik
Is Jack Ryan
Okay sure
This is the one
Each time he's telling me stories
He doesn't say not again
In the present tense
And it's a new instant damage on boys
The government is going to kidnap us again
Ridiculous
Is absurd so
Anyway Alex
Is aee sold on this story for sure
He doesn't cover it too much because what is there to cover past the headline
Evan just being like why isn't everybody talking
About this true
Yes I agree
Why are people talking about that
Infant worrying anyway true I would
I would suggest that there's a decent chance that
Like
He wouldn't have a choice
About whether or not he went to court with it I feel like the US government would take it to court
Testify under subpoena making him more likely to be jailed by the United States government then
The Mexican government
Yeah it's
I mean
You can't you can't detain
Foreign Nationals on foreign soil even if your bestest
Buds
Margarita's countries like there's still no
Even if Canada
Accidentally at the f****** Niagara Falls just grabbed the guy and pulled them across the border
It would be an international incident would have to have the permission of the other government
So
Alex talks a little bit about drills
Interesting
Take On Me
Because
This is a knot
He
Behaves in the
High School
The arms blown off
Hydrometer
Did not have those kind of things.
Shotgun
Throwing
Cars
Why
Bottom
What's a drill
What's your reading
Rush
Terrorist attack
This definitely isn't the reason with Alex says that they are training in scenario exercises now
This is
Completely
Ring conspiracy narrative that he's expressing in the past
A misconception he thinks that they're all these exercises because your unconscious mind will experience them as if they're real Attack
And you'll emotionally think that there are more attacks in Iraq
Actually are
Because of your heightened state of subconscious fear the globalist will be able to exploit you into supporting things
That are sold to you in the name
How protective
You from these attacks
Of course in more prison times these exercises exist to give cover to real false flag attack
For instance the operation lockstep
S*** existed so that the globalist
Could plan the covid-19 release
And if anyone was caught they could say was part of the ex
Exercise
Leaving aside how stupid that theory is
It's the it's worlds apart from this 2003 understanding of these exercises
And that's because at this point 2003 Alex doesn't seem to have recognized the value of
Fully denying reality and calling everything false flag
His business model is still kind of in its infancy and hasn't matured to this present a level that we see now where it's like
F*** it
Everything
Maturity or metastasized
Also if Alex thinks he's exercises exist to give people a subconscious sense that things are worse than they are
I would suggest he consider how he covers move
I am how the lies an exaggeration
Give his audio
The impression that things are worse than they are
Specifically around certain themes like immigration and white identity fears I don't understand what you're saying
Are you saying that he is
It like whenever he says the government is trying to subconsciously make people more afraid of terrorism by creator
Are you saying that he is been taking something like
The story of an absolute lunatic
And then bolstering it with his bullshiting to make it look like everybody is in
Being invaded by the
Country
More less
And also like I wasn't able to find this article that he was talking about but like
I bet that article is just
Somebody
Add a newspaper
Having a little bit of a flourish
You know it
I read those articles are like
Bombs are exploding everywhere paragraph It's like and it was all
An exercise to train people for the Bible.
Do you write as if it's real at the lead in the beginning
It's kind of fun
The conception that
Most of your readers
Will know already
From the word go that bombs were not actually going off in their own town
Alex is a little bit
Maybe a little bit over exaggerating
So apparently Columbine
Call swag baby
The Secret Service
Call parents
Secret
Underground
Mechanic
Principal
Text
Can you
And
It was a military
What Alex has Express in with his girl talk appears to go like the
A training drill happens which no one is claiming is a real event
Alex pretends the people are saying it is a real event that takes on the role of the guy insisting these are fake Grillz
Eventually a news outlet covers the drill and Alex takes that as an admission
And that he's yelling force them to end their cover-up
His role in the whole thing is a charade and entirely me
Unfortunately this is exactly the kind of thinking that left unexamined for too long
It enabled by a further radicalized
Conspiracy environment
Leads to a person losing a billion dollars
All that stuff about Columbine does sound remarkably similar to the cephalic says about Sandy Hook
Not necessarily in terms of the specifics of the claim but the way that there's a collection of claims that he
He almost certainly got from
Wheatley disreputable sources which aren't accurate but he throws out anyway to
Defend his contention that it was a big theatrical event
It's the same way that he has all of these talking points
Benny Blanco
What kids are walking around the school's the porta potties
You know they don't let paramedics
These things that's exactly what you heard with
His his description of Columbine
It's definitely seasonal to live
We're literally talking to the ghost of his Christmas
Just passed as we speak
Yeah it's a little bit on the nose
The current Circle
Thermostats is
Of our situation
Costa Chris
Also important
Harrison Klebold were not in the trenchcoat Mafia
That existed at the school who were wrongly associated with the shooting because the shooters War dust
Most of the people in that actual crew had graduated the year prior but in the Panic of the immediate aftermath I still got them confused
In the media did a poor job of covering this leading to misconceptions at linger to this day
Much like the narrative in Harrison Klebold were bullied which also
It's not
Full accurate description of
What led to the
So anyway Alex's wrong about another school shooting
Right as rain is always wrong downfall was cemented
How many years ago it was written
In stone
So fast
This is not saying
Necessarily in any way that like the shooting was faked right or that no one died or anything like that
But you already see the seed of it's going to
Grow into his presentation year and that's like
It almost gives a yeah there's a feeling of inevitability but
You know when you when you start looking at things from a Delia logical perspective and then you see
I mean it and eggs
Exact
Like nucleus of the future
Ath fascinating to think of you wouldn't know that this is the kind of place I could go to back then but looking back
It seemed so obvious like it's John Lennon walking by guitar store like
Kind of
If that kind of feeling of life
That's what I'm going to be
So there's a drill in Austin
And Alex
Cuz hell
So he blocked
The news
Right I get there
This is amazing
Haircut
Drill
Turned out
War
So you got scooped on your lie
So Alex
I mean I think there's a couple things leak
To pull out of there
The first is that he lies about sources
How do you
When you admit that the first time I can ever trust you again
Right now you might be bluffing
In the telling of this story whether it's true or not
The he got the outcome that he wanted right
EXO
Lying work
So why would you stop lying at any given point seems like as an incentive to live based on his own story
And
This
Is it again this
Is all existing his head
This feels like when the Boston bombing happened
And he feels like the media is talking
King to him
Yeah I have those like
They had to get out ahead of me Friday saying this
As I know there was a drill
That you were yelling about
And the News will probably going to have a story about Heather was a drill to drill them about source
And what have you and it meant nothing
They were like
I don't know what to do with this point phone call right click
Cool
I mean
This isn't like
The perfect state of Al
Being annoying
But ultimately
He has no impacted anyting is what he
He should be there is no
Nothing needs changing
Look in terms of these drills and stuff that like
They're they're happening
People are learning
How to respond to stuff
What do you want do you want people that have two
To deal with it for the very first time time it happened snow
God will provide
God didn't wanted to massive nuclear spill you don't want have somebody being like
Hey sorry man
This is my first nuclear spill cuz that's a reasonable excuse for why we're all dead
Here's the other thing too
If you believe
Leave like what Alex is saying then there are these like
Hundred
Of
Make event
Right yeah
He's got to be like
Jumping from room to room he's going to be like spinning
Plates to Tryon like cover all of this stuff
It's like get to the get to all of these fake events cuz if you didn't
What was to be allowed to pass them off as real I have a bigger Quest
Yeah
What is the ratio of fake events to real events
Are there more
Fake of athenry
What is into fake event
You never want to be specific.
Cuz I feel like it
If the ratio is the opposite then the real events are The Fixx
Terms of
Do you know
A giant
Events
Mass casualty type events
I would imagine
You know if you want to use this language
There are more fake event
NetSpend real one
Inasmuch as there are training exercises that happen right and a lot of EMTs and
Emergency medical
Stop along with
Military
Training type stuff probably happen more
Then
Newsworthy
Here's the thing
Malik season
Covering all of these drills that happen
Can't. Even close not even
There's too many and guess what
He doesn't cover
Aren't reported in the news as real
Cuz otherwise we would be having like oh my God new cleared there's a lot of other everything I ever you all over
Happening on almost like a calendar
As if there was a regular training exercise in case this sort of thing were to happen
Seems to be happening biannually in the exact same place
The show I listen to the tells me about this is not serialized otherwise that would be an issue
Very dumb
So Alex talks about to the the Texas Family story again the back getting
Any takes it up a notch
Because the family
Border in
North Carolina
Get off your property
Machine gun points
Okay
That's that's fun
That's fun I think it would be more fun
I think we would have all have a more fun life if some people were just British troops with machine guns
Get off the Lions
Whimsical evil what happened to America happen with the land
Did he have to leave
For the queen now
He's got the
Obviously
But it's probably based on a fraudulent telling of a real fact
That there is a tiny piece of land
Approximately .052 acres in North Carolina that is actually British soil
Intersect there is a small patch of land on Ocracoke Island
Memorial to
The five British soldiers who died there in World War
The land is technically still it in the US but it's
Permanently lease to the Commonwealth War Graves Commission
So it might as well be British and it's kind of
Considered British land within the continental US
That so there is that they think that's about as close as you're going to get I imagine Alex heard that it was like
The British are taking land in North Carolina I love it I love it you see the connective tissue
Could possibly be to a guy getting kicked out of his deer stand
By British troops hundred percent total
I mean you're literally a hunting on a burial ground
So yeah you're kind of an a****** here
No no no
Who was actually have no
No that's a little disappointed the story
At its core his grave
Okay
Okay okay I'm headed to British soil within the United
And it has to do with the military
I'm saying that Alex
Was made aware of that and then he wrote a story in his head
Facts about a North Carolina man giving a costume to buy
British troops
Hit machine gun point
Going to get off the land type of story that Alex would makeup up immediately
The British have some land
Clearly a hunter with kidnap there
The embellishment cycle
Call Joseph Watson is in
I'll say
Watson
Being on the phone
And just coming in for a little bit
About where you belong
He's not a host
But he can come in
A like a little sting or whatever and he's not to not the worst
For some reason it sounds better when he's on the phone
Because it's like
We got our guy embedded in the UK
Fortunately the two of them were talking about the story about the Texas family that kidnapped
I am Alex
Is Out For Blood
Ignored for a week and a half
Well it depends obviously
Ali said that
I'm should be a
Mainstream headlines
Carrie
Open policy
Refusing to all
Tambien
Beauregard's
Down there even though they got in
Every week by the Mack
Bordered by Constitution
We're not going to war with Mexico
Well that I kind of believe
Mexico is in my blood
Trust
If that was his reasoning I would have to
To say you know what at least
That's maybe on
Instead of all this old Mexicans are evil that's
Bulshit based on mythological racism you hate Mexico because your ancestors died
Kalamata or whatever yeah you're spiritually connected to Colonel Travis whatever the f***
You just hate Mexico
I honestly also think
Think that if
This was the way he acted more
AAA would be more
Like
This
Is this kind of feels more like a sincere expression of his feelings like
I just hate Mexico I want to crush that country and also again
That's the
It seems like the stakes are raised but be
Because their race so ridiculously high no one's going to war with Mexico and this is a fake bulshit story
Pixar once again
Back down 20 self up into a frenzy where you want
War against a neighboring save over a very dubious article in New
Newsmax
Describe the headline ends with a?
That's more worthy than Alex's like in the same breath being like
They lied to get us into Iraq
A viking makeups
Youcam makeup
Let's go to war with next
Stylistics some calls
And this guy sucks
Gun Shop
One more thing
Collar White
Male right here with
Articles
It's an alarming
Virus
Use the word virus
Article
A white male
Hi Arabic
It seems like
Daughter
The white male
The -4
In a world
So they can have
The Catholic again
Open Redbox
And not inconsiderable amount of Alex's audio
Has always been this guy
Anti-semitic white identity obsessed and paranoid
I think it was straight something important to note
On the part where white people and Arabs are being pitted against each other to say that the global
Spit all groups against each other
Doesn't really push back at all on the guys claim that there's a judeo new world order
That's probably somewhat strategic
The way he pushes back on some things and then leaves
Other things going to like
Yeah that is
That is a way of introducing yourself
Blue Collar white male here is the way of a Jedi go away
I saw an ad that said blue collar white man need not apply
I mean if you say it like that man so it's article that he's talking about was in The Help
That is odd
Ha it is odd
So Alex gets into a stretch here where there's some really bad predictions
City makes
Hit across the
Hot water
Politician armed
Father's Day
Aspirated
O'Brien
Paul Watson Thomas
Comments on my phone
This is just Alex talking to himself
I would die for anything that I feel like what are your comments on that
What are your thoughts on there
How courageous do you think I am I super crazy
Or the most courageous there ever was your thoughts on that
You're looking Rough and Ready I'm just thinking of a British thing
Yeah I was just talking himself up there and it's kind of fun
Vets
He believes that the globalists are definitely going
Like to kill him maybe in five years maybe tomorrow who knows
And now almost 20 years later we sit here and
He was not killed
In fact he made millions and millions of dollars by getting worse
And worse
Yep
Foolproof that if you die in your dreams you do not die in real life
This is this is just
Sad face
I think I think that there is probably a small part of Alex
Now in the present that he said he didn't die
At some point
Because this idea of the like what lives on is a man's Deeds
Like there is a time when he could have probably
I have a Bill Cooper ask eggs
Where people like
Deify Bill Cooper exit but it's
Bill Cooper didn't end up living long enough to have like a
Sweet
Like
Falling
From
Grace is even a billion dollars
The key didn't have to become like this weirdo public drunk
Shows up on these strange podcast
8011 South
Where's that Tyson interview
She's not due come out there are a lot of things
I think I think like
In in Subway
Is Alex Emily talked about this even like hundreds of episodes
There is a certain sense that Alex has outlived his usefulness in
Terms of the conspiracy community and he continues on as this weird thing
That the next-generation is trying to navigate how they use these almost vestigial
Depend
It's like they need to exit we all need
Exercising from the the human
The humanity
Yeah he is in Subway's but they're still like something to be gained
From him and terms
Exposure
Stuff
It's just yeah
It's strange it's not a position I think anybody would want to be
No
No no I'm not I'm not expressing pity
Probably
Isn't where he wants to do
If that's such the
Greed
Houck
Can you want
I can't imagine making
A hundred million dollars in like a business
And not being like
Sweet
Guess what that mean
Games for me
Out
About
You know I'm just I'm done with this stuff you do you somebody else
And deal with all that b*******
What if you had a underlying needs to demonize people and satisfy your anger
Publicly and lash out to see that's the problem
Yeah
I wouldn't do
You know another thing I was thinking about suicide
This is
Articulate exactly but
So much of Alex's career involves this idea that like
Todd like Fox News was going to give me millions of dollars as got you know like
I couldn't be the thing that I want to be there right
And now Tucker
Carlson is the most important person in the world
Kind of
Contradicting Alex's entire ethos
Right
Like he could have
Have conceivably gone to Fox News and Ben
Richarlison
General I mean well I mean Alex couldn't have because he doesn't have the
Control necessary to do
Somebody working within Fox News could have had the show that Alex
Fixie wants to have
The it there's there is a place with indians
Do something can be corrupted enough
It's completely counter to his his ideas
He couldn't do it it's not it's a
Personal thing for him and
And it's maybe because of him he's unemployable because of him maybe that
Tucker
Camp at Fox
Like by being on the outside Alex did more to influence Fox News
Then if you were inside
That's probably true but that's not the place that you would want to be if you were able to
It is not the like
Fun or admirable or anyting place
Down all the corporate money and all that it should be the admirable thing until you're Alex
Then it's
Disgusting
And he probably do
But
There's a lot of a gold sale
Stop going on
No tab he doesn't pop
Because he didn't actually give up the corporate money even in the slightest
It's a little bit
Gold Corporation weirdo Corporation
So there's an economic collapse talk being used
Sell gold
S*** predict
People's layaway
We're in the middle of the
Play long time
Expect to follow the line
All the shopping center
Mall restaurant
Now are you
Terrible
For our economy
Percent
Play some good decision
Remember the
Call this stage
Collapse
Eventually
Off-white
Completed with the euro
An agenda.
Pawn America
Indian currency
Call Dale
Can I borrow Ana Maro dollar
2006 they rolled out the Amero dollar and everybody who is laughing at Alex
Was not laughing anymore
Bought all their gold that was that was what happened
Change the course of history the Amero dollar
I mean when you're right you're right
Alex is going to be dead in five years in the Amero dollar timeframe you know like
There's no way that $8
Can come out in 3
That's just not possible
There's just too many interlocking part
I mean like there were even like
The dollar coins
Was a difficult thing for I don't even think I was fully successful as a roll I
Sacagawea
I don't even know where we are
An uproar
And that means nothing compared to emerging different countries
It's a slightly heavier representation
Of the same thing
Yep that's it
So we go back to the
Bombing
In 1999
Trent Russia
And like I said
Proven
I9
September 9th
P90
Sickly the month following
Seriously
Explosion
Complacent
Which cave pool
The pre-tax
Say when launching
Create Apple ID
Stay at home
KGB
Rancho Chico
Substituting the
Domi explodes
Wealex
And then they will call but
Prison Planet
You know I guess
Buncha.
The blow the whistle
Trying to deport him
Any journalist
In Russia
Strangely calm down
Street
Yeah well the none of this stuff is true anymore
So weird how he
He's the protector
Picture of the white
Which family now is great Christian Rush has never been known to do any false flag
Huge
Nothing more christ-like
Weird
That whole section on Prison Planet maybe not there anymore
It is so nice to believe
Give thanks
It is really nice to just I don't have to worry about finding new things that I don't remember about
Anza it's you don't like
Forget that you prove things
Can order to have proved the new things that are
Contrary to those little things
Who I was wrong and now there's anything
Yeah this is
This sucks
Anyway
The caller calls
Short leather collars do
And he says
Is Blue Collar white male here
Better than that guy
Another
You're on the air
For quite a while
I'll be honest
Start looking
Your program I thought you're not
Apologize
Just the facts
Wow on the Alex Jones
The 2003 would think the 2022 version is a
Yeah you constantly are evolving into something that would make you ashamed
In the past
That's not the
That's not the trajectory you want your life to go down
Couple years ago I would have been so proud and impressed with what I achieve
Totally
What kind of past me would have been like well-done pat on the back
Yourself in the past wouldn't be the top pasa
That's the kind of things that yourself in the past
Wanted to do you achieve things you don't have to disavow later
I have to be like man the past
I would have looked at me a bit like f*** that guy
What a bummer
This is the Christmas episode we are getting awful wistful about the Ghost of Christmas Past
So worried about you constantly have layers of the onion peeled back and you see more rides dryer
Okay so Alex is screwed
Keep blowing your mind
Paul Joseph Watson
No he's not
He's decided
Oh boy
David Knight is the fattened goose that sounds right
I think David is actually a pretty good Ghost of Christmas present
He's almost
The same thing in the present analysis
The best he could just show up and be like bet you wish you didn't fire me you dumb dumb
The visual metaphor for Alex but I could be the Ghost of Christmas future be like
You become me
In this in this version I think everybody is reptile people
The Ghost of Christmas Eve
I'm about to turn in your Punchbowl now I am high hahaha altered
So I went to the conception of what his show is
And I think it's kind of funny because it is not
This
Absolutely not
Wow
So far from what his show
Blurb put on the show you don't want to like come in from break and be like if your
Joining us for the first time I make up bulshit based on skimming headline
Try and make white people scared it is a little bit like if the
The blurb on the back of the Bible was like
Non-stop action Fest
Packed with Jesus shooting all the Pharisees like now that with every percent less list of names
So
Alex talks about his JFK conspiracy
We know from the present
Nick Fuentes was just on the show and apparently Israel did it
And Alex has a big part of it
Weirdly not
In the past 2003 that was not what he was
He's proven that stuff isn't just like socks
Jerry
Private lawyer
Murdered
What is a demitted widow
5 minutes away is that means that she was actually married to her by thing
Admittedly
He was admitted in the in the white papers
She was wearing white
Cuz it because users and now she's wearing black
Admitted Widow
Is it strange
Turn afraid that's all I'm saying
That was in 1800 that meant that she was in an asylum
Haha
Also wouldn't be ladybird
Yes that would be
Is Alex head lady American
Royalty ladybird yes
Correct I find that hard to believe that she was again starting forwards and told Alex that
They plotted to kill JFK I think I think
There's a fairly funny movie to be made it where all of the conspiracies are true and everybody shows
Who's up in Texas on the same day kind of like
Having an awkward mixer
People are like all what are you here to Florida like I'm married to kill Kennedy and they like
I don't know enough about LBJ so I don't know if like
He got remarried or something like that he have another wife cuz that's the only one I know of
Labor Johnson that's the only one I know of
I think you actually maybe he did have another wife
I'm looking at Wikipedia
I seen one
Ladybird
Please let's let's call it let's calm down on whether or not he was
That would make somebody a admitted Widow
Though
Do you know
You are not wrong
If you're like
Screwing around Taylor make you an animated Widow Widow first
Actually times whenever she was not admitted
Here's the question really is is admitted mean I have admitted to it
Or you've been admitted into the halls of widowed up
Century what are the previous hundred years was The Mentalist
Institution so admitted into make sense
I think that still count
The point here is
I don't know what's going on and Alex
Conspiracy
Linda Valdez real 2100 percent the Raichu
Very very malleable
Another call
And in this club I think we get some insight into
To what the left-right paradigm
Memes to Alex
It's not what you think
The distinct impression that whenever I have a
This is amore
Complained
About bush
Like you said
Become
Like
In League with the Liberals are
Power
I believe this is a really illuminate include to help us understand what Alex means when he says he's above the left-right paradigm
Just based on the words and what they mean
I think he means it is politics exist outside of the spectrum that defines things as left-leaning or right-leaning
This is the way that he wants people to
To see him because it helps make you more appealing to folks who fancy themselves
Also to be above politics
Finger right
Actually mean is a bit different
He opposes Bush and because of that people on the right assume he's on the left
The left-right Paradigm he's again
Is the assumption that because you oppose a republican you must be attacking
From the left
What Alex says he's above the left-right paradigm
What is essentially saying is that he wants
To make people aware that you can attack
GOP from the right
Yeah based on his use of the term in his clear ignorant about
Pretty basic stuff in terms of politics
I kind of think he doesn't understand that this is what he mean you are 100% correct it seems like he actually thinks that a
Hacking the GOP from the right isn't involved political position that places him outside of the left-right binary
But it does
He's outside of the left-right paradigm
He's on the right left parody
See it makes perfect sense everybody
That is on his team
What is on the right
And everybody else is on the left
Right
He thinks
He's on the these are meaning
Political Spectrum
Putting what we think of as the right
On the left
Side of the spectrum
Taking part of further apart right of the Spectre
That's the only right
You can diagram it out
It's okay Paradise
And that's why I
Far-right position
Lottery position why would you say that they're not common sense
I'm a Centrist because I believe in hyper nationalism it doesn't get more
More middle-of-the-road than murder your enemies of which
All you get a lot of mileage out of saying stuff like I'm above the left-right paradigm
Guilty people who are independent
Oriented
You think like a man maybe
Did this guy have some
Some stuff that goes a little laugh
The little right you know how
No it's just
So far on the right
I mean
What he's really saying is I defied political
Party I think both political parties are b*******
Which
Is is fine but that doesn't make it like I'm
I think both political parties parties are b******* but I'm on the left
Yeah mean that I'm
Yeah left-right Paradigm you can have
Structural problems with both political parties and still recognize that you exist within the
Continue exactly
And Alex is trying to pretend that he
He doesn't
The game traction
And make himself seem like a less of a
Extremists on the right
I mean if you're if you're the f****** Amitabha Buddha yes you exist outside the left-right Spectrum
I agree with
If you're somebody who doesn't have like
Concern for pollen
It exists outside like someone who maybe all you care about is charity
All you do is live in a cave
I think that also is outside the left-right Paradigm that's a good point there's a lot of people point
A lot of factions caves out there
That was a felon
Because you have not been to the Appalachian Mountain
Some of those caves turn your fashion
I'm telling
Not been there
So we get one last year and it's another caller
And he has a question for Alex about source
Because
This is a non-answer
Yeah you're doing stir great job
I have a
One main quest
Can I actually meant I'll let you go under
Today
The global policy
You were referring to
Tower
You said that you write with
What's the size of the Moon
Is based off of
How do you obtain those
Where's where's
Foreign affairs
Propaganda
Congress
Project America
Operation
Report
I do appreciate that
That's definitely
Send me in a different
Directions
If you pay attention to that
It's been really answer the question middelpos
And the reason for that is that he doesn't bases conspiracy bulshit on an actual source
He skims headlines and makes up stories that are complementary to his extreme right-wing white identity ideology
Endpoints to have a gun specific mass of official documents to give his narratives and unearned weight
I've tracked Alex's answer
Here is what he says in response to a very straightforward question about where the
These reports are that he's talking about
First he brings up the CFR who have about 25 different kinds of
Courtright
This seems to imply that all of these kinds of reports spring forth from the CFR
Maybe
So they put up for an affair
This is a public facing propaganda Outlet so that's not actually what we're talkin
It might still be one of the types of reports
But it's still coded
Is he completely on specific reference to all sorts of other reports
Set the CFR puts out to the president or internally or interdepartmental briefs
Whatever the f*** that means
Departments of what department of evil in the department of
Tell their true plans
You can see how this doesn't answer the caller's question at all
Pinac the Carnegie Foundation
Add the Ford Foundation battle plans
Corporation these things are just name-drop
But hearing these names doesn't help anyone find the sources Alex's talk
Talking about
Instacart
Ricky Foundation has worth going back to the 1930s how does he expect anyone to know where to look
Is it just one type of report that they have I imagine the Carnegie Foundation has so many different types of reports
You start to learn the names of the p
People in these groups and you see them writing articles
This is again
Outward-facing propaganda but
I guess you can use this
Check your work
Against these internal documents to illustrate that they're putting up
Propaganda
It's speaking openly and Secret
But these document shows they're working towards a similar goal
Right this is welcome
Completely useless as an answer to this caller because you have nowhere to go with
What You've Been Told
The colors obviously looking for more information and you would think that someone in Alex's position would be eager to give that person
Some specifics
About how they can find Hard Evidence
What's the shows that Alex is right
How about the nonsense that he spouts
But in reality the last thing Alex wants
Is there actually curious members of his audience
Checking-in
On any other ship
The game he's playing only works if sourcing is left
Invega non-exempt
So when he's like this he does the equivalent of like gesturing wildly and acting like a kid was trying to blow
What's a book report
And that's that's what you see there
Yeah it is it is two things like the first time I'm up boggled by him Bay like listen
You're doing a great job I think you're a genie
Anyways I have a quick question
Which I think should be a foundational question
Is what you said based on any
To which Alex replies
Okay I see what you want
You want to find this needle in a haystack
What I'm going to do is I'm going to give you this a stick and it's going to give you this a lot of Haystacks
I'm going to give you the exact over here
It's in there
Start digging dum-dum this Haystack is been growing since the 1930s to keep piling hay on it play it is
Is it is almost
Perfectly designed to sound like an answer while at the same time being there too
To make you give up on trying to verify any ordinary overwhelmed
We'll never find the thing that Alex is referencing
In the premise of the question is even interesting to because it's like okay
You are reporting on news right and I can read the
The story in the paper and it doesn't say what you're saying which is an issue
But it's not an issue because you insist that you've read these
Global report
Help you like
Use it like a decoder ring
You can see what's going on in this pistol right now
I would like
To see the decoder ring
Right and right it's that needle in a house
Are you the tip of
This beer then you don't get to touch my Dakota
How about that
How about I would like to check the work on your Dakota
I didn't ask you to check my f****** work man I'm the tip of the goddamn spear the decoder ring is in my pocket you can't see it
I'll never bring it out the decoder ring is literally everywhere and everything
Enjoy
The force is everywhere edit binds
That's what it is okay
I would say that the doc answer was a bit of a dog
That's true
Cable
I don't know
We end this
2003 Excursion
Yes
Think there's been some Illuminating things
There's some interesting stuff in there
Still no no movement on the Saddam front right that's okay there's still a little while until he's discovered
He will be fine
I was so fascinated by that Texas Family kidnapping
It's
It's just it's just weird to me
That like you know Newsmax
Wood
Even with the?
Put out the story without doing a little legwork in
I'm finding these claims in the past that he's made
And not have a follow-up question of why you
Keep getting kidnapped
Five Mexican government a lot more than normal people have been kidnapped
Letting you go without incident
1 *
I do appreciate the negligence that went into that story making it all the way to Alex repeating it and
Declaring war on Mexico
I just like
Just like that that's
The type of fig
Where you hear that story and I at mean
You and I both knew it immediately just like
This is not a what
This motherfukers do it some other shift to a patient this is not a man
His one-time admitted.
The guy with the Courier
Jordan will be back
Another episode get back into the present
Yeah
Who knows
Give me any
Maybe we'll do an episode about caves
Sounds interesting
Appalachia my friend and then we'll see what happens whatever the case will be back but until then we have website
Shoprite.com
I will be back but until then I'm Neo I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark I'm the juiciest Ice Cube
Its back
Exactly what
I was reminded by reading Wikileaks a time to do so
And now here comes the sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color