Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge by now it's like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
I worship at the altar of a little bit about
Alex Jones Indie we are Dan
Play my library today Jordan is beard oil
That hey man
Maybe it's time to
Take care
I don't know caring about myself at all hampering myself
Into consideration you know it's never been to part of my
My repertoire I thought about it
I have this beard
What can I do with it
I guess I can
Could like
Make a little sure you could do little things in a little braids yeah but I don't think that's me
Now That's My Style
Decided to explore beard oil
Beard oil
All right listen
A few years I was never I was never big lotion guy ago
My wife
She really bad and you know what
Better sure I don't know what the hell would appointment should be moist or something
I grow up in a place where they like men have hardtop skin like screen
Well I'm an I have I have tried this out
Yeah I am so far I noticed no difference
Why would I I don't feel my beard you don't I don't have a mirror in front of me
Hard with it with the smell of my dog
Play my face I have a uber Idols you're one of the Pinecone
Situation and the other is like a vanilla lavender
I like it
It's okay I'm going to
We'll see what happens
We saw we saw a banshees of inishmaan
Which is
Amazing it's done by the guy who did In Bruges
So it's Colin Farrell and Brendan Gleeson just being
Good acting at each other you know you're talkin to me and you say something like that could be a movie I couldn't give you a fan
That could be an art installation
Outside of ebbing Missouri but that one's really really good
Just great
Ireland
Here's the story
Here's the entire
One day
Is old dude is like
I do want to be friends with this guy anymore alright movie
Over okay
Wow that's
Loeber short plot synopsis
Is it a ending of a friendship that leads to a lot of Calamity or is
Is it okay
The traditional Irish tragedy
Very very funny and nothing good happens
To anyone ever
See I was imagining a movie where like the actual end of the movie is like the end of the conversation.
My Dinner with Andre My Last Dinner with Andre
Jordan
Today we have an episode to go over time DVD and it is
December 13th 2022
This is an episode where Alex
Does a stupid thing
He decides that after the interview that he did with Nick Fuentes
You decide to have Nick back on
To talk about things
Brilliant maybe see what kind of Common Ground we can find if he doesn't
Maybe maybe
He's trying to bring him back from
You know have you considered this is a reverse Vader situation
Where or more accurately a Luke Skywalker and his nephews
Situation
I didn't I didn't think that because it's not
Edit very clearly wouldn't fit any of their psychology
It's a situation where
Alex has done this interview with ye where ye deny the Holocaust and talked about how we loved Hitler and all this
Hey man
Use code
Knox
Not addressed by it's what we all do no no no I'm not going to lie and also Hitler is wonderful
Don't understand if you don't like that it makes it look really obvious that we are lying
Penetrates the market bubble that we have
Alex went on Steven Crowder show
I've started complaining about how he been done dirty
And
Criticizing him Beverly
It is very sad that Crowder consult him
And then Nick Fuentes came out and did his response were here said that Alex got a call
Right
From the Jewish handlers or
Jewish backers that I have
Answer that's the Prelude to this this interview I guess what Alex had heard that naked said
And decided
Why not
Have an interview
Debate
About about this stuff
Yeah and the great idea
It's a real
No it's a great idea no cuz he's going to he's so smart and
Charismatic and talented Alex
This is going to be able to
Scream him under the table there's no chance that anybody can beat him if it's a screaming match then yeah I do think
If there's that there's a good possibility of of that
But no
It's a
You know it's never it's never just
Screaming
Miami
And from something of an optical perspective just the fact that Nick is
Coming back on
Is a loss
For Alex
Add a win
4nickk
I have the mind
That
It's going on here is that Alex
Thanks
Picnic
Is somebody who can be reasoned with
He believes that make it is willing to play the game of using code and and and all that
Because that has been
Done in the past
I always was able to do business with him
A couple years he went on the stop
Bastille tour with him and Ali Alexander
It's so like I think that Alex is inviting him back on to give him a like
Look
Come on
We have this
We've done this before why are you why are you being so over
We're scammer doesn't work
You're not better
Right we're all scammers and just cuz you think you're doing something different your f***
Yeah and at the same time Alex needs to give some kind of a performative
Back
Push back
Do I donate don't hate anybody to the preceding
This this episode is
Tough
Because
Full disclosure recorded most of it decided this is
Beating a dead horse
As is our once we did about two hours and we were like that is just right but it
It's too much was a lot to go
And so on the Fly essentially just decided
Goodnight streamline this thing so it's not the same thing over and over again
Being like Alex is doing a bad job of this
Spoiler alert
For anybody who's who's who's
Afraid
Nick Fuentes is still a white supremacy
He did not suddenly changes
Is is June
No not really still too much of that
And so we have
Heritage valve called an audible
Sober before we get to that Audible
Dot-com is a sponsor
Audible.com
New Wok
Sorry
Help I'm a raving Angie somebody whose balls are stuck to his leg thank you so much and I apologize
Text sherston I'm so sorry I subjected you to so much of Alex Jones as a result
Oh thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk thank you very much
It's a me Mario Speedwagon
Journal about what you want
Thank you very much I wish that delivered ever try that again
You don't have the falsetto your voice
Is too deep into the owner is beautiful
Text a fruity little Necromancer thank you so much right now policy want
It's a have happened
A little of the past
My favorite part about this
Is that because we've already done this
I already forgot exactly what it was that we were doing and how long and how easily we forget
This is why maybe we could just do the same episode over and over again
You don't remember anything I've got a very Vibe every is flighty
I'd like to announce to you once again
The celebration of the nuptials of Miranda
Congratulate. Married on
October 29th congratulations and I now declare your wedding to be attacked
Democrats
I'm a policy wonk
I have
Risen above
My enemies
A little breaking for me
And then we're going to come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f****** horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
I never want to come back
Apologize to
To the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
Better tomorrow sucks
Terrible Super-Sod
So bad
You know what
You know what is it is
Not our fault
It's not our fault you know much like me playing these clips for you it's not my fault
Actually my fault
It's partially our fault
Maybe better improvisers could have found it before unique ways to
Express wow wow wow we are not we are not them
This is going to be basically just a discussion of
Love Nikki
Debate with Alex
And then also the failings on Alex's Park
Before Nick shows up
It's
It's a no-man's-land there's not much going on there
It's kind of just
A lot of Alex Lange track you know there's a lot of Alex trying to prepare the audience to
Except
Nick's arguments as not being bigoted
Batl is bad too and I think they're worse than anti-Semitism so
Even though I disagree with Nick Fuentes
Maybe we'll agree with something
On a on a scale of 1 to 10 - 1 and adl's and 11
That's basically that the audience
What's an excuse for
They like what they can say why it's okay with you
It's not because you're a bad person that wants to murder an entire race of people
Cuz
Tough to watch the ATL do things
It's just that they're so bad that Nick is good
Hitler's great it's so weird about half
And one other thing that happens is that Alex takes
Some calls
And what color in particular is
Completely off topic
And this is just heard of a novelist bougie
For Isis and doesn't slow down
Get ready to hear about a DMT trip cuz that brought Revelations of cyber Satan
And
Normalized
Cumulus media
What shows like
The later
Where gets weird
DMT in
Armageddon
The Manifest
Explain the artist
Elgin
You also
Summon Bell
Power of everyday
Like a network of
Neuron
Devices
Steals our art
It's like stop lights
Are the most powerful form of AI currently
Interface with it and follow his orders
America
Collectively we decide to do it
AI is only
Powerful as we make it thank you so much for the call
One of the things that I think the audience is deprived of
Is that when your incredulous about things
I just nod
I was given a vision
Is Chuck's out absolutely
Oh yeah so Cypress is coming and it's going to trick us into thinking it wrote Our books
Bayou
Appreciate whenever people are trying
They're bested like
Rectify
Dermatology of like you know though
Revelations are coming in the Antichrist and all that stuff
With reality
Of like
We're developing superintelligent machines that are probably going to
Pass us eventually like we just know that they will sooner or later it's a matter of mathematics
Do have more intelligence than we do
Still not God
I would I would say
If you
Are gearing up
I have a little debate with guy who may or may not be a Nazi
It really is funny that you're taking a call like this seriously
Maybe it's a bad sign
For you being the kind of show that can handle that kind of material when you're taking
DMT cyber Satan Revelation guy and end
The call that's a great point
Now you're totally right every civilization has ended the moment they tried to Summit Mall
What happened to golf
Summon ball
It rhymes
It probably mythology
Sign of the times
So what are the things that is
Critical to understand. Is that Alex is
Lost
Before anything even begin
This is before Nick has even started to the interview
Add / debate analysis
Fuct
I'd like to give
Time to give his Museum really going to talk to my
About him
Coming on today
Really went on there
Didn't know it was going on
I knew I was meeting with
Wasn't antisymmetric
What's some of the Jewish Mafia
Play me everybody's a Nazi doesn't agree with them
So I just kind of
All this really is an enigma
What's really going on show uncensored unfiltered
Nick Fuentes joins us
It's an enigma
You should sensor until 2
I would sensor in filter
I will and I think it I think it would be helpful
Yeah
I think that Alex is setting the stage for Nick
To be able to make whatever argument he wants right
And Alex will have no foot
To the fall back
It is an irresponsible presentation
It's it's fun
Phyto to say on censored you know like
Uncensored
But like there's some times where you're like
Listen to things
Let's do a little censoring just a tad like maybe
The Holocaust denial
Yeah it's not
You know when you want to talk about all sides we hear all sides of a debate
I don't know if that side is
Is something that we really we have
A use for anymore
That's eventually
Alta Bates
End
When there is an answer
We come to a conclusion exactly
So there's no need to debate anyting
How about this
Whatsoever
Yeah I think I think to do so
It is indicative of we are positioned exactly
By talking about it you have already explained what
What's wrong
Reading
A holocaust denier as potentially right and having something to add into this conversation
UFO
That's not
Go away is how you treat
So Nick
Talks a little bit here at the beginning about the responses
To the interview
And he's just pulling out to some of these
Classic truck
I really can't say enough positive things about him
With regard
Words to the appearance on your
Show
What I've noticed is that
Jay has started this time
The Defcon 3 Tweed
About the Jews
He went on your show
And he said that he loves Hitler
And what's
The most remarkable about the
This is everybody
Fixated on the
Remark
What did you mean by that
What did you mean by you love him
What do you love about him
What is DEFCON mean is that a threat and so on
And he's done
Interview with Piers Morgan with Lex fridman with Tim pool with you
With Gavin
And it all the interview
Still focused on
Focused on the Jewish
A lot of people they might say all well
Course that's an outrageous
This thing to say it's so provocative
And maybe that was the intention maybe was about
Publicity maybe we'll stay
But if you listen
If you listen to what the man is saying he has said what got us to this
But it's almost
It says something in it
Self that the conversation is about
The remark
Rather than all the
A my opinion far more outrageous things going on all around
Which is the right now the ATL shaking down Congress
If you listen to all of his interview that I mean
It's mostly
What lettuce
Here is grievance
Just weird things about gays personal life that he's decided to blame Jewish
People for
And
Dinner
Which complaint
These interviews were all like Hitler and do stuff
Is
Silly because
Skiing
That was where the ones who went
That was their idea
I've listened to a lot of interviews on Alex's show and
Outside of
That ingredient
Usually doesn't go that way
It was it was an anomaly
It is interesting
Ethnic did accidentally bring up a good point
When people ask
Yay what
Did you mean by that
It is
A dumb question
Yeah and it's indicative of not propaganda or anything along those lines
What is indicative of our culture being one where if you take what someone says at face value
You are a rube
Did not say I mean on TV or something along those lines
Because so much
Bulshit
Right is all over the place and everybody like
They get off on saying something and then you take him seriously.
But like
You don't need to ask why he what do you mean
He said what do you mean
Clear
It's absurdly clear clarified a number of times
What did the trick
Betnikh is using here is just as really just
Very very simple thing
Painfully transparent want to notice
What are you doing here is that he and ye came into the Inn for Studio went to all these other platforms and they said all this s***
There was a just over-the-top auntie
Cosmetic what is far as denying the Holocaust it was
Nonsense
This naturally has prompted a response
For people who find this s*** important and they've gotten a lot of criticism for this over-the-top 80's medic ship
Now Nick is coming back any second look at all these people are so folks
Suspicious that all this food
Feedback that we've gotten has been about the Jewish stuff
Does that kind of proves that we were right to begin with
Why aren't they talking about all this other
Stuff
Like
Ye feel weird about his trainers
Why are you why are you a dick
To deport nography and blaming it on your ex-wife
Can I ask you that question question
How are the Jews involved with that
I hope you still with that
The backlash that Nick wanted to provoke
Is being used to give the appearance of credibility to his initial point
It's mainly the Jews run everything and that they're trying to crush gay
Then all the people who would speak out
Against them
I think
District
Is so prominent
And again that Trolli
Ecosystem
Words like you to say something inflammatory you elicit the response that people
Would naturally have taken what you say at face value and then
You're like I can't believe that focused on responding to the thing that I said do you know what it is
This is the thing that I hate
So f****** much
It is
The dude
Who texts like hey do you want to go out I think you're hot or something and then they're like no just like
No I was just kidding about that I didn't actually want to do that
F******
Terrible
You're a coward
Yep
Nick said that the abl is shaking down
Congress
And here's what he was talkin to
About that
I know the ATL shaking down Congress
100 million-dollar
I don't know if people realize that
Submitted an Appropriations request
In response
Do the interview we did
Now you got
You know whether you thought it was entertaining whether you thought it was
Revolutionary
You have ye with a mask on with a Yoo-hoo internet
Madl shaking the couple times
We need 500 million dollars to finance
Semitism
It's outrageous
He's been banned from the bank he's at his deals
Shut down by Nike and Adidas to the tune of billions of dollars over 10 years
And
The list goes on and on and on
What what people ask and I don't
That is gay secretly like
ATO operative to get them funding
You can see their how Alex has a mission and its
To create a
Sir distractions in order to keep the audience from focusing on the central point
And why any of this matter
At least when these kinds of issues are being
Disgusting when he needs to
Provide cover for big
I can't imagine anyone being seriously concerned that yeas whole thing has been a false Flags get the ATL more funding
Fwiw the ATL made the Appropriations request
What they're talking about that Nicki
You saying like it was in response to us in April
It's an application for Grants
And the 500 million dollar increase involves their nonprofit security grant program
This is something of a DL runs they quote provides nonprofits with the capacity to increase their defense
Against threats
Including physical security and cybersecurity capacity in Corydon
Nick wants to pretend that this is something that they didn't reaction to his and gays interview but that talking point just isn't true
Hate self-aggrandizement that makes it look like
Do the establishment is so scared of these things that we're doing
And yes it is much as
People are scared that
This rise
End in
Bigoted
Rhetoric will have the effect of emboldened
Inciting people towards violence
It's not that there
Scared of
Stock quote on quote
Yeah
You're saying
500 million
Put it in the bucket I need three times
Tumi
It's always bad
When you're dealing with someone like Nick
Who at this point
Has
Literally no reason not to just be pretty upfront about things
You don't really want to ask them
Cut-and-dry question
I am so Alex decides he's going to do that
I asked
Hey man
Do you admire Hitler
I can't imagine
Him thinking this would go any other way than it does
In my view just
What's the way
Do you actually admire at off Hitler
In some ways yes
And I'm not a
Socialize
Text and I'm not and I wouldn't identify that way because I'm a I'm a Christian
So I'm not any kind of a socialist or a fascist
I like ye believe we should have a Christian government
Christian country
God runs the world
We should have a government
In accordance with that but
But honestly I don't
Don't share this histrionic Jewish view that
Hitler is this
This exceptionally Boogeyman evil figure
All the 20th century is full of a viola
Tony chachere's bold
Authoritarian ideologies run rampant and and that's
The product of modernism and liberalism and
All kinds of Tren
But
But this idea there
I'd my life is a
Then anyway and Pat
Or I'd have a lot more animosity for the ATL I have a lot more intimacy
City for the COA I have a lot more animosity for the group
It actually made my life
My family
He really worse
Personally and acrossed
Sick of being expected
By Jewish median Holocaust Museum search
Beat my chest
Like you kind of did the other week until I hate Hitler I Heelers
Of course Nick has more animosity for those group cuz he doesn't have animosity for Hitler he likes Hitler
So make Express support for Catholic Fascist governments in the past and his views of Christianity are entirely compared
Potable with Theocratic fascism
He knows that he's just lying to Alex's audio
Has to be more palpable
Do not like the word facets Nono thrown at them a lot prefer is that you call it
Sharia law
And that Nick Fuentes is the new Ayatollah that's what they would prefer they would rather do that because
Is it completely different from what they want
Nick's construction of his feelings about Hitler historically it's a meaningless tape
He's coming at this with the position that's kind of close to there are a lot of bad figures who did bad things of the 20th century and Hitler is
Just one of them
What you might be something that's okay to say if you had just made an entire media campaign out of
Expressing your love for him
People aren't
Expected to beat their chest
Then say they hate him
Alex did that performatively because he ain't came on his show and said that s*** and Alex was trying to
Texas branding so the audience
Instant Runaway
I've never once felt the need to beat my chest and say I hate Hitler but maybe things are different when you're a media figure who keeps saying
You like Hitler
Maybe if that's your reality people want you to walk it back cuz it's insane and dangerous
You don't okay maybe it's subjective and unique to Nix
Experience I'll give you I'll give you a
Like that I'll give you that let's take it out of there
I've never been asked
To thump my chest
And say that couch SQ was bad
If a single person came up to me and said you know ceausescu us
It's a good idea that I would run away from them as fast as I could
You must beat your chest and say that Slobodan milosevic was bad
But if you say you wasn't
That's the problem
Well it it raises some questions
So
Nick has gone out
On his Twitter spaces
He said that Alex got a call
That made him turn on ye and himself
He got them and so this is discussed Alex really wants to know like
Hey man
Did you make that I got a call
I legitimately
Stalin hate Mao
Hate Hitler
Wallpaper Rock Obama
Hate the Democratic Party
And I've always remember me on Piers Morgan
I didn't get a call from the ATL
Popular thing ever did
Back then
I said Hitler
Mal took the gun
Gun 1776 will commence again
I've always criticized
Hitler
I made documentaries about the Bush family
Helping fund Hitler and the British royalty show
Where we have a sticking point is is that
As you as you sit on social media and I'm just curious
Do you think I actually got a call
To come out and criticize Hitler you think that's a new thing for me
No no I know that you're very vocally anti-hitler over the years I know the year
More of a Libertarian and so you have the
This view of History which
Which lumps in together Mouse Tale
Antler is authoritarianism versus
Freedom Fighters
Capitalist
Washington Thomas Jefferson I'm familiar with your showing all of that
And and honestly was a little bit glad you called me Baby Hitler I said you got a
Call
And I'll quite honestly it's banned through but it is well known that you
Don't really talk about this
Tissue your ear more talking about
New World Order Bill Gates
It's in any sort of a
Obscure
Conspiracy theories like Bilderberg
My shows a lot more focused on you know what you might call the Jewish
Question which is what are we to do about this
Jewish Elite
Is it run or Chris
Christian country
So apparently this s*** talking
The two of them dead is a primary issue for Alex really needs to be hashed out which is just as easy as
Connecting like are we talkin
You said that I said days
Now that we've squash that beef
I just want to remind you
That I want
Ultimate power to remove Jews from this
This Earth
I want you to be reminded that I mean this
I don't think you got a call
Because I do want to murder all the Jews wait hold on so this is a devastating
Moment for Alex
There's three things
And that clip that I think are a real problem
For him
The first
Thing is that Alex is coming face-to-face with someone who is smart quick-witted charismatic and understands the Infowars
Talking points
Nick watched Alex in the past so he knows what Alex preaches and because of that he's going to be able to brush aside these now
I heard is really easily
You can see the way that Nick present himself is being this hot like talk about high-minded things whereas
Traffics in obscure conspiracy stuff like the Bilderberg Group
Nick is asserting himself as high-status here and also putting Alex on notice that he isn't afraid to bring up the Bilderberg Group and sell
And if it out and if Alex does
You better be careful
Because I might know some stuff about this I mean
It is your tricks out your Jedi Mind Tricks aren't going to work it is it is like he's been
Whoever he's been doing his homework for his whole life watching this s*** you know like Alex
It's like it's like the Douglas Adams
I think
Long dark
So there's a Electric Monk
Sitting on a horse
Another horse
Tons of thoughts
All about the Electric Monk
Right now the Electric Mud
It's easier to sit on top of something and never have a single thought about
Like that kind of thing
Like Alex
Has sat on top of Nick Fuentes is
Bulshit
He's put it on his dumb website
And he's never watched
Single hole absolutely not one second yes
Not a second
It's not his shop has never watched the America first
Concerned himself with that because he doesn't yeah it doesn't give a s*** where is Nick knows the
Nick knows what he's dealing with Alex doesn't know what he's doing
Practically know what Alex
Is going to say before he says it because he says the same s*** every
Yeah
So the second thing Alex should be worried about is Nick saying it's well-known that you don't really talk about this issue
If anybody is familiar with the way of the Nick in the groin purrs
Confronting Turning Point USA
They would hear some similarities between this there's a there's a resonant Echo
Yeah that's there
The third thing is that Nick literally said that his show deals with the Jewish question and Alex said there's a
The good debate to have there
No one and I mean no one outside of white supremacist white nationalist or Neo-Nazi communities uses terms like the juice
Which question or the abbreviation take you
I guess people who Monitor and criticize those communities are historians might use the term to but you get what I mean
That ain't a dog whistle
Later the bullhorn
It's a little tiny bullhorn
Has a big old bull horn
Alex either not grasp that or hear it and go along with it is damn
He can only mean that he's either in support of Nick's 80s medic ideology or that he's in
No way equipped have these conversations
And every time he does he's just going to get run over by the person he's interviewing
It's a
Very very bad
Yeah I mean there's no
If you say the Jewish question
Interview over
What the question is what do we do about a race of people that I think
Are biologically evil
By birth
From Satan himself
That's not a question of like
Do we give them better schools
That's not how that's going to
No it's
There's there's nowhere to go
These kinds of things have been been uttered and it gets worse
And I would call the FDA
Text Roxanne
The federal regulators
You all
We are Jewish
We're out there doing that
You're hiding behind Judaism but I don't then blame
The average Jew for that so I think that's the difference and you were on
With Gavin McInnes and he's like
Fortunate more crime
The other group
You don't just blame me a black person you just not trusted you when they come in the room and yagos
I don't know
To me that that's what I'm saying is
I do believe Martin Luther King
That we judge individuals by who they are
And what they do not buy what color they are where they're from but
I agree with that in
Principal but we also have to understand that it's
It's not the thief
People happen to be
The Jewish I think that's the big
Source of the disagreement
Is Lisa it were told in in the last
Ashby weeks
When ye makes these remarks
What about the Jewish media Jewish Hollywood or Solana
These are individual
These are people that
We've got a name them into the
Visually and these are people that happen to be bad
Or rather they are
But I think there's something about their Jewish
Nest that that makes it this way
And I think that that is really the source
Of the disagreement
See when somebody says the Jewish question that's why you went the interview because
At that moment right there Alex
So just be like
I got nothing I can't I can't do this I've clearly failed I f***** up weave
Jewishness is itself a problem you're f****** bad goodbye
Yeah if you're Alex you tried to suggest to Nick that he's making
Composition fallacy where you take the characteristics of an individual
And then applies it to an entire group
Onyxia
Nope I disagree
There's something about being Jewish that makes a person bad
At that point you reach this
A disagreement that words will not solve
If you're naked this point
You have to be thinking that you're crushing Alec
Eyelash when Nick said the Jewish question Nick has reaffirmed his admiration for Hitler and now he's
Buchanan Martin Luther King's ideology
In favor of anti-Semitism and Alex has enough
You just floundering here giving Nick 101 level responses that are basically softballs
It's pathetic to see really but
I don't know why you would expect anything else
Yeah man
That's such
That's such like a
Thank God
That it's not me and Nick in a room
Together having this quote on quote
Debate
Because that's throwing hands
I mean that's it that's just say it to my face
That's throwing hands.
It's at least we're done here till I mean at the very least at the least
Yes
Yes it's ugly
So Alex
Tries to get
A question out
And what are the things that he seems really preoccupied with is this notion that there's a conspiracy going around
Are you secretly fundraising
For the 80s
Is there Alex is trying to get that question out but then he reveals something that
I think is important to wreck
I asked earlier that I forgot to get back to
Video was 500 million they want more control over Society because of
Kanye West yazel comments here
I get he's obviously not a threat
He doesn't control People's Bank account
That's a joke
But then people say is
Yay
Really working for them
The first wearing red hats
Caesar Trump supporter and now come out to do this
I've been around him I'll talk to him a lot
For a long time
And I really don't think that's the case
You know
Nicastro niacin
Happy office
Jones did all that to poor neck
Yay for a long time
He never come on the show
I gave his number to
Other folks
Come on to Milo yiannopoulos
He got that point doesn't touch with him
But that was fine
Know where you want to go
I wanted to talk to him I gave him the number
That's shocking
Pianos as the
The history books will be written
Alex
The central Hub in the middle of these wheels
You have a good argument
And I'm not sure where that ends what you have to blame Alex like
Literally throughout your day you might experience something that you probably could argue is Alex's fault you sound
About to do like a class action lawsuit commercial
Look at all they have a case all this f****** s*** yeah
It's very strange.
Considerate like I have
Some
Concern or worried that these these kinds of bigots and folks would find each other naturally at some point
Like their orbits
Artrac big and they kind of overlap so
There's a chance
And ye would meet
At some point
But
In the real world
The way it did happen was that
Milo wanted to talk to you because he was excited about the anti-semitic s*** he was putting out so he contacted Al
Alex got him in touch
And then Milo cuz he wouldn't go on his show so Milo got him and brought
When testing and now they've got the thing and not Milo's gone to Milo's out there all f****** stupid
How do you spell I think I think that that is a Hallmark
Of chaotic
Campaign slogan he remember all the Intrigue about who's in who's out with
Stuff like I wouldn't expect anything else
I just wouldn't
Expected by low to last that short
Has been
Thanks so Central to so many things to get sued
The wild problem is
Most likely a coincident see the Forrest Gump
To me it's a little bit like like like a Beatles you know like they're there was a time was right
Pipe for a thing to happen you know it if you remove the Beatles
You're going to have something Beatles like take their space
That kind of plan probably nothing
Monkey
I don't know that they were bad
But like if Alex was gone the what-if
This gaping hole ripped in our society if Alex was not there in the past is so cute
Well you know.
Conceivably it still have like Rush Limbaugh all that stuff
That takes care of a lot
A lot but they're yeah there are peculiarities of Alex's psycho see use them in his idiosyncrasy
Set really do end up affecting things
It is
And the kids marginalization
There's so much of his career his life to him associating with so many
People that other like a rush wouldn't associate
You connected
At the right
Time to be the right
Piece of s***
To do this
And there's
There's maybe an argument to be made in a in a much larger four dimensional sense
Of what
He was
PlayStation 2
Was the reason that his downfall occur
You know like if he hadn't been the person in that place at that time
Then maybe his life would have gone
Absolutely would have gone differently
But maybe it would have been his self
Destructive
Yeah you know
Probably
So like a lot of pushback that Alex's giving is
Is not good
It doesn't help make his point sometimes it even helps make Nick and gays point
The time it is just the softballs
That make him
The handle no problem like hazy a secretly fundraising yadiel this is worthless a waste of time
So we skip to Nick
Boosting yay for
And
Alex gets a little bit concerned
Musicman what about rain
Because I'm so so I ran Paul
We're supposed to believe our two
24-hour going to be DeSantis and Trump
DeSantis I
I think you like him
I'm not really huge fan
And Trump like I
I said in a very moderate
Forum
Low energy and I still love him I still die for him I die still
He's a Great Hero on one of the Great American
But is that the same guy that he wasn't sick
16 everybody
You're not
Young guy
In the last couple months
With everything is going going on is
Here's something out of all the
Stop the wheel
You & I in the last
Last two years and many others
Between January
Jamaican election
Finally
A light at the end of the
Tunnel here is finally a North
Star west
Pandora baby
Star or something that we can finally look at it and at
Actually get excited about what happened.
And what about
You know I like Rand Paul
I like him a lot I met him at
2016 and I actually worked
Maybe I can work on it
Campaign I think I can paint with
Cruise actually during the Republican primary in 16 but
How is interlacing
Reporter that when I'm talking about when I was a senior in high school
I was just supporter of his ice
Still am I thinking
He's very intelligent
He's a libertarian
And he's just not really my kind of
Conservative I know you're more libertana but I think there's more overlap
I'm really more in favor of bringing back of
Strong fashion flavor
Nationalism
That term I feel like it's being hijacked
I want the government
And I want us to have a true National
Thought that's what he's got star in yay
We can all follow in Alex's room
Let's go off on that
But then
This I want Christian nationalism
And I think the term nationalism is hijacked people like Alex
Implied
People like Alex at days are Father's Day
Anti-christian
Straight straight bro
Exchange was it
Exactly like if somebody ask their dad what they think about ye and their dad was like
What do you think about that
I think I've been there been some others have to like and whatever
So just like man
You are far away from the conversation that I am having right
Is a
Don't say more about why we should follow yet
So they go to Commercial and they come back
And Alex plays a clip
From a mid-november episode of America first
Yeah Nick
Now
In fairness
This was a cliff that they took from rightwingwatch
So it's not like Alex watched
Big Show
Clip
Is incredibly f*****
And
Listen to the app
Episode are the parts of the episode that these clips come
From
And they are not out of town
I will assure you they are in contacts
And Incredibly f*****-up
And I don't know why Alex played this
The Jews
Here's the silver lining
It tends to go from 0 to
Like they're not wrong
But there's a reason
For that and the reason
Is that
Do the Jews
Every society
Anywhere
Is gone down with the
Always
Paris
Okay
Never starts
Frequently
It seems to end that way
And it gets there
Very rad
Doesn't start there
Bharat
Frequently
But I would say that the Jews
I better start being nice
Two people I got
Because
What comes
Is going to be a lot
Uglier and a lot
Anything is
I didn't bully by the Jews and
I've been depressed
And slandered
Jordan lied about
I'm attacked by the
Statues
I have been
Precise
The most part
And even-handed
And nuanced about my
Review about
And I'm also Chris
Because
There
Could be a lot worse
Michelle
And what's going to come out
I could be a lot uglier
Don't we stay on the shell Dino that there are other people that
Farther than that
Conversation really starts
And the Jews are going to look at
People like me in America
The first and say damn
I miss
Someone was just that funny
Guy
Missanabie
It's going
So I don't know why Alex
Would play that
Because it reveals something to the audience
And that is this
On his own show
Jeff and
He's talkin fairly similar Leon Alex
The show but a little bit looser
He has the the Jews should be nicer to me because it's going to get bad
It's going to get worse later
Laughing about it going from 0 to 60 once these conversations get going
Switch
Even by his own admission
He's trying to get these conversation started
I think it gives a pro
Pretty particular image of
What Nick is
Who he is
What he believes
What like
I don't understand why if you're listening to this or watching
Sing the show
You hear that why
Would you believe for a second Alex is sincere in his like
Wow you don't really mean this is Davis for shock value or CDL is worse
Like
What yeah I mean it's the point
Sometimes
Sometimes I have to humble myself
And
I have to say thank you to people that I wouldn't otherwise so I do want to thank Nick
Because the only reason I am not in jail right now is that he is never come anywhere near me
Probably has
If you haven't
He's very we're both very lucky we're all very lucky people sitting here right now
Because if you say that
I wouldn't say it
I wouldn't say
My voice again it's again
The kind of thing
That when
One says it
Words
Are not going to hell
This is not 23-year extorting Jewish people because you're
Threatening a holocaust
This isn't something that you argue you can argue somebody out
Maybe if they get to a point
Where they can recognize
The awfulness
And
Like what they're actually in
And be like oh I should probably try and change
I think there is
Is there a possibility for people to change
Recognize you know that kind of stuff but if you're arguing with Nick
Like about
If you hear somebody say this
You're not going to win an argument
You don't need to engage
In-N-Out
Stop that to me I don't understand why there would even be like
What is it about
This person
Nick
Alex Caesars
Worth
I trying to have
Some sort of the conversation with
You have to ask that question
It's it's not a question that lead you anywhere other than
Alex had the tacit
Agreement
Right with Nick about
That right he won't
He won't be as overt as Nick but they're on the same page
What if
And this
This could just be because I grew up in a very cartoon heavy
Era
What if
We hit him in the head with a frying
Bugging out kebangsaan I'm not saying that it 100% works
Here's the here's the problem
Yeah you would have to prove that getting hit in the head with a frying pan made him anti-semitic in the first place
Cuz then be hitting the frying pan could undo it
Like
Perhaps Alex accidentally hit him with a frying pan when he was a young child to Alex feels this personal guilt
That's why you got him to show the boy put them on bed TV and I look forward to your cartoon
More clearly established
So Alex
How's this
Need to defend his own conspiracy world
Because throughout this Nick is also not buying Alex's s***
Play Alice's bring up like all the wa out for the world economic Forum there behind everything is forum
Who goes to the Forum they're all controlled by Junior
Alex's just getting busted all over the place with his own narratives not being able to stand up to someone
Cool
Knows them and doesn't buy it right
Alex tries to defend it and it doesn't work
Yeah you really I think smoke
Do it earlier in the last hour where you said well
Kind of side issues a Bill Gates the wef and
You know this. But the
We're over here with the Jews
The wef and the big corporations the New World Order and Gigi ping
Are mass murdering people are bringing tyranny and lockdowns in World IDs
And controls and whether they're Chinese or whether they're German or Jewish
I'm just opposing these tyrannical objectives
I kind of want a big tits
And I just think
Dangerous
Do then
Sit there and just invoke all of this
And say
Jews are the
Powerful Jewish Mafia
Bases around the world
Is that what you're saying
Yes
And I think they do
I don't even think it's really disputed anymore after what happened to ye and that
Did you played
Would bring black from the ATL at
Look at him I mean he was somebody who even in 2018
4 years ago
We're saying things that are regarded as Politically Incorrect and people
Correct
Nebulous
Very specific
He said like partisan conservative talking points in 18 and he was
Just fine
And he see one on Tucker Carlson and he
He called out
China and called out a lot of things he was just fine
Then he switched up on the Jews
He was banned from Fox
He was banned from daily wire
And you don't have to
The whole list but we've all seen the
Cascading effect of this
Adidas Shell card app
Chase Bank
Rose
Tens of millions of dollars
You know I mean it's unbelievable if that doesn't prove it
And then the ATL is going around now
I do not respond
After passing route a letter in Congress
Demanding
At 1 they're getting him
Kicked off Twitter
I don't know how much more clearer could be with Alex
Looks like he reject out with his conception of the world
He's Express
Fundamentally different views of policies he'd like to enact
90 subscribe to an ideology that Alex's audience
Will be very susceptible to
This is one of the most ill-advised interviews Alex's.
Probably not as bad as gay but I think it's worse than Spencer Davis
Also how much was it gay being left alone back in 2018
Doesn't complain all the time about people getting him hospitalized because of
Supporting Trump
It seems like Nick is just selectively rewriting history in order to accommodate his anti-semitic conspiracy and also he was only
Show me fine when he went on Tucker because they edited out all the stuff that
Is not said
That's bad right now I'm feeling like that story you told of the red card Yellowcard the kid who ate
Like what is what do you think at
Okay if you eat the yellow card
I'm going to eat the red card on I have
Yeah you know like if you ask me do sympathize with Hitler do find him
Yes of course I'm going to eat the red card that's what I'm here for what do you do with Jews Run the World
Going to eat the red car
What do I have to do
I'm trying to express to you
That I mean this
Play the clip of me laughing about it going 0 to 60 and that the Jews better be nice to me cuz
There's worse stuff coming
You do not get it
You have all the information I gave you all the clues and I liked all there if this is an escape room
Just a door
Another narrative here and it surprisingly also falls
But how do you square it up the Jews and Israel
The most County in lockdown for the world after China
Evan given the deadly shot and one of the highest death rates
All-powerful
Why is this biomedical tyranny targeting them doing that to them
I think that that's just a symptom of the elite I think that's a symptom of hubris I don't know
Example that the facts
To kill people or something I think that
The covid-19 very complicated there's a lot of Journalism to be done there
Centerpiece
Israel
The worst country for beginner the poison shot
Your lock down to the SEC
Even make any sense because if they were going around giving everybody the VAC
Maxine and that's supposed
To take out everybody
What were the most vaccine
And who's who's going to be remaining when there
I think the shot is dead
Play I didn't get back
Vaccinated at all but I had the idea that
That the Georgia guide
Headstones are dictating global politics
I think it's just ridiculous and I think it's one of these things that led by
The founder of CNN put that up I mean they do believe in Illinois
Nick there is a larger de Papi
Who funded Hitler and how they set him up
And this powerful group
Tumi
That's what's going on
Yeah I just don't know how convincing that as I think when you look at these raw demonstration for power like
If Alex was paying any attention to Nick
He wouldn't think that this was a great point to bring up now
And it's pretty amazing to see how little respect Nick has her out his entire worldview yep he doesn't agree with Alex on
Fundamental base level aspect of reality so without addressing that this conversation
Convoluted
Alex can convince make of anything because Nick is a reasonably smart person and he's not one of Alex's traft audience
Its members
Alex's flimsy distractions and nonsensical conspiracies work on his listeners because they're not really processing what he's
Almost every
Guess that he has on his a fellow con artist so they just
Know how to play along
But don't care about pretending to agree with Alex a stupid s*** cuz he has his own agenda to advance
So you have a rejection of a fundamental elements of Alex's World being voiced
Comfortably and confidently on the show by someone Alex has complimented as smart repeatedly
That's a problem and is why you see Alex
Begin to interrupt Nick more at this point the interview
When he hears I don't know how convincing that is Alex nuheat
Couldn't let that sentence
Discontinued because Nick is about to explain why Alex is ideas unconvincing and that is dangerous
Alex's ideas
Supposed to be
Possible to disagree on because they're based on
Discernment and documents and divine revelation
If they continue down that path Alex would be unable to show his world to be real at all
And you be forced to fall back on outburst
Cynthia Patrick
Which looks bad in comparison to Nick being calm
Collected non-confrontational for the most part
Yeah even keel
I just don't think even those tricks would work
I mean it's
It is
If you're if you're
Going to get into a fight
Alright
Maybe
You should try fighting with your bed
Best sword
You know
Like an Alex is trying to
Fights with
Floppy little pool noodle
Because
I don't know what he's
Even trying to do know he is got scream at this dude's face
A head of steam in your autumn off every time and make
Him run away
But I think Alex knows that that's not going to work
Keep on going big-hitting entire f******
Trainwreck of the thing
You've only got one sword
You're flopping around with a pool noodle so you might as well bring a sword
It's it's
It's interesting because I don't know how much Alex does know this
Because a lot of its
Experience in those like online debates that do just
Deteriorated to screaming at each other
And it makes me wonder
If Alex is aware of that and he would know that Nick and handle someone yelling at him and he doesn't care
So
I don't know it it maybe it's intuition but just like
I don't I don't think Alex's is
Matchup for the screaming at him
Yeah but you know you again
You're on home
Court
You can mute him
You could you have control over all this
You can make this kid look like a fuking idiot
Unless Alex is afraid of losing some kind of an access to yay or possibly alienating
Knicks audience
Who are notoriously hostile
Exactly
Call Billy's going to go and do a fight
With a pool noodle
As a sort of sacrificial lamb almost the only way to win is not
He does like that
Quotes
So Nick not only is going to disrespect Alex but I just like
Your ideas are not convinced
What is also going to make fun of his sales pitch
Are brakes are at
Mean
So we had to go to break there
The point you were making to break
Yeah
Between you and tumeric 95
Teen killed in the stupid
Hi.
I'm somebody who
Everybody knows me is like
The Holocaust
Austin IRA
You know but that that's sort of why it when I'm Bill.
Labeled categorize
Won't you see that I'm so much more than just a holocaust denier
What what disgust
Give me about him so much
Is
This
F******
Camouflage
Ambiguity with humor
Cluck-U
You're not actually funny and you f****** know it and the reason people like
Is because when he says these funny things
They know he's being honest about them
There's a sincerity behind that honest or that that attempt at humor
Will tan your voice
That's it
So Alex wants to
Impress upon Nick
That
Judaism is not 21
Nothing of multitude of people of
Different opinions and
Different backgrounds that are all contained within
The collective of
Of Jews
I feel like this is going to go well
So it doesn't
I can't I mean
You would have every reason to think it was
This one turns out does not work
SoJO like you're saying that his
Acidic juice
One of the biggest rooms instead of Jews
Doesn't think Israel shity I'm going to eat the red card
Is it
So
I think it's more complex
Nicktoons what you're saying
I agree with you that there are Jewish batch
The one thing that they're on the same page about is that they're all on team Jew
Israel
And they literally
Unchristian
And it's so tragic
There's so many
Christian song
Iowa semites
These are not the Jews the Old Testament
Call Juice dad that I talked about
It's on the yay interview
They believe in the talmud
So yeah it's a real myself but I do not number of people who have
I've gotten reporting of spitting gun zero
Of those those
I mean seems Seems like a strange
Now I could be wrong perhaps he's talking about when Saladin took over
Could have been then
I would have listened if I was in saladin's Army spend on some Christians
I I think that you're sort of inside of the I'm about to get the card and so right
You can feel in the setup of of Alex's the way he's like weird
Bucked up going to happen
What are you doing
Yeah
Well
You can say a lot of things about Al
And we have and we will
But one thing
But you can't say about him is that he's interested in you.
But
You can say that
He constantly pretends to be interested in you 100% you can say that
Yeah
You say the full thing about Bill Gates
How did you know
That's the central issue
Should I see this hole
Lester staying saying America
Hitler and
You know the left scripture Captain America
That's what it is
And
I just hope
All of us can come together and
Transcend
The castle
Society in the world government
Injection
Trying to get everybody together
On those issues
Instead of
Obsessing
About different groups all day you know this whole group
McKay's
And I don't think the Jews run everything
I mean who do you think Rodger
China
With a billion 500 million people
I think the Chinese run China
And I think that's why
I mean there are problems in China but China
Country that is fighting for its
Fighting ruthless
And you could say that it's at rannoch
Allstate has always been a tyrannical
I'll stay there different kind of society
Hey there the Chinese people
Are very collectivist they're very societally minded a very obedient and and deferential
And that's their culture and that's who they are
But there's no question that the Chinese standing committee
And she's champagne are going out too bad every day to get
They trade deals for China
In a way that are are Jewish
Leaders in America are not working for
People in Oklahoma and Iowa
Does anybody believe the Hollywood use in LA
And finance used in New York in the government using d.c. in the ones in South
South Florida
Does anybody think they need daycare at all they give a
Damn about people
People and
Kansas or people in Iowa
They don't
In the same way that
You could say Putin or champagne care I think about there
Ximena rasad hears about the
Syria
Alex was not expecting that answer
Alex was expecting
Nick to say that Jews run China
Emma and Alex could argue with him about it but unfortunately
Nick has a
Different worldview
AAA
I mean
Just pathetic
Just f***
You mean that Alex's display
Ya-hoo tummala together
That is
So disgusting
Yeah
F*** you one that's not an answer from Nick
That's that'll Lindbergh f******
Stump speech
Join Hitler
I will say it is an answer and then.
As much as who do you think runs China
Deterioration to
Alex decides he's going to give a little bit of a rebuke
You know who my favorite businessman was Henry Ford
To let me tell you what what was that
Ono Ono
Describe is a pool noodle
Of a rebuke
That he gives
To Nick
Decided
Discussion
Here today
And you know a person
That everybody
Black hole
Giving power to it
Manipulating
Maybe a transom things on policy
And ideas
Issues
And the fruits of the tree
We're going to break here in a few minutes
It's your chance unfiltered fog
We don't screen the calls just have a good clean phone line
Calling from and don't cuss
So the rules don't cuss
We're talking about
Genocide and entire people we don't want to make it gross
Spell show
So how does whole thing was that you want to take a bunch of calls with Nick
But that weird lady
20 minutes left in the show at this point
Baby hasn't dropped calls
Before
So this is about as close as Alex gets to condemning next views as the weakest position possible
He has no actual criticism of what
Nick is sad he just thinks
But there's a black
Cole the people get sucked into a mess with the Sinister forces I guess the globalist
Twat
This is boilerplate s*** and it means nothing
Transenterix on policy ideas and actual issues
None of that has happened on the show at all today
Nick has been pretty clear about the policies you'd like to explore in this and other
Appearances Beyond steel polish
What's the first amendment wants to create federal laws regarding where Jews can and cannot work
I am basing most of the government's decisions on a Ridgid fundamentalist interpretation of Christianity
Actually wanted to transcend things whatever that means in the realm of policy
You could have started there
Defeat makes desire to ban pornography and even sexy images in the battlefield of ideas by explaining house that attack on
Threatens a wide variety of other forms of speech and expression
It's the simplest thing in the world
It's Alex's Marquis issue
And instead of even taking that much of a risk
I was just mopes around building
Defenses for the horrible s*** Nick says
Then I'm using the First Amendment as a shield for why he and Nick should
Be criticized for having this conversation
It's cowards
Even
You entirely buying into Alex's worldview
If you're a listener of the show and you believe all of it
You should be watching this interview and questioning whether or not Alex is the champion he pretends to be because
He seems like a loser little titty baby you honestly it's very very sad
That's the thing I mean I
In my head you know the argument
Could be
You know you don't want to piss off Nick
Because it'll alienate his
White National
That's the fear or they'll attack you
You or something like that
In my mind
If I'm Alex
Here's the only thing I have control over
I have control over my show
You know
Yeah and I've got
To dominate this kid
Because I'm more afraid of people not listening to me
Because I got my ass beaten by a 12-year
Well I think
It's too late
That is definitely true this point certainly in the show where they're at it is too late
Perhaps
He said there was something about jewishness that makes these people bad
Or when he
Since the Jewish question control over your own shop
When you're like all right
Well
First Amendment does allow you to say these things because the government is interesting you
So I'm going to make a decision
About the kind of content that I am
Willing to put on MySpace
Skip that I have control over here and get the f*** out
But I wouldn't do that because
Some reason
And their stupid conversation boils down to
Him being like I think it's juice hookah
Control our country and Alex been like that stupid
Shadowy group of people is convincing you to talk about it being juices the problem
A group of people
It's what are you
Again
You know it's so painfully obvious
If you look at the
These things
That the yay interview was Alex
Desperately being like use code
Just
We can make so much money use code is going to be great I bought a money printing machine
Yeah and
When he's talking to
It's the same thing
It's just
Use that code
Come on buddy
Shadowy group I mean he might as well go for blood typing a sign that says shadowy group okay
Jesus
So Alex tries to sum up his point
Pierre and
Let me just make my point here on that I'm basically done debating and arguing all this
I don't judge Nick
Coin toss
You know I just
Are some issues here
Because you can't have the left
Vicious
Sing
People are inherently the devil I have
Where major universities in Michigan California New York
White people wear badges
Digitally track them and don't let them go in certain areas
And who's running then
Batl
CDL after last three conferences said I'm the number-one enemy
We track the lawsuit
Everything
I'm not going to blame the average Jude
He's doing to me and my fam
In the process of trying to sum up his point Alex uses
Fake stories to exaggerate the oppression of white people
In order to make Nick's ideology not look so it's
Extreme
This is him pretending to pose neck but doing everything in his power to make Nick's argument for him or at least
Make it more palatable to the audience
Now listen I know it
It sounds crazy for Nick to want a genocide people but
The ATL wants to genocide people so it seems like next a great guy
That whole thing about why people wearing badges I think
It was from a 2022 midterm election attack on Wisconsin governor Tony Evers
Evers that worked as the superintendent of the Department of Public Instruction between 2009 and 2019
At some point during that span the DP I worked with a group called Volunteers in Service to America or Vista
In 2013 Vista handed out a document titled addressing racial privilege
A mental model for white and erasers
Which included a section
That Addison
Suggestion of wearing the white wristband that you can use as a conversation starter
How about your commitment to equality and acknowledgement of white privilege
I believe that
The story that's at the root of this okay
Complain about it before things like you might have exaggerated that story out a little bit to be a counterweight
Now but
You're forgetting that
The Livestrong bracelets wear a shadowy plot
Turu
Kill people who are either
Bell or
Sword not good at bike
Yeah
Truth and it's exciting to hear that Alex has traced all the lawsuits back to the ATL
I thought it was Hillary Clinton's Law Firm that was behind it all
Supporting Trump
Ipower hovercraft on any given day
Does seem very malleable
Pretty bad the rotating cast of characters taking over
Jeff from 8 to 12 you know we're repressing Alex you know it smart
So what is it saying
We was a roadblock
In terms of our initial attempt to record this episode I realize that
Was the incessant
Alex
Pointing to like the abl being bad in order to make a NIC not look as bad
Most of what
His defenses and his argument
Surrounding this is like
How can I be mad at Nick when the ATL is so bad
That is really what was bogging us down
We are was I was convinced we were beating the dead horse that's not true Alex was the one who is constantly out
It was so repetitious
Interfered with our ability to
So you're so racist we couldn't
Record the show the first time
That it was
Boring to the point where I
Felt like we were walking
Through like knee-deep molasses
Seat hearing this defensive Nick over and over again
Hey look if we have to do a post-mortem on this
At the end of the day some of that might come down to my fault
For when I was cutting clips
Maybe I had too many of those
You know well listen
You get this one
So Alex expresses his opposition to Nazi
And again I mean the end on what grounds
Personal one
That's what I was
Hitler's for plan Society
I oppose that be
Because it is a
Obvious eugenics
Operation and I'm an expert on it
I know all about it
Mystery box
It's amazing
But
Again
Dallas
One side of my grandfather
Bolt action
The other side the Hammonds
And they were
Module
Blonde hair blue eyes
And
They were in World War II
And they know what went on
And they told me now Hitler was bad
And I told me what went on how the rich Germans in Dallas
What's Hitler.
In the power and 33
They would blackmail German
My grandfather worked with
Can't were doing that
My family told me went on
So I grew up
Actually
Hearing about all of that then my grandfather
Work and seek
Programs
And I only heard a little bit of it that my mom heard and talk about he never talked about it
You're sold about
Weapons projects
Now here he knew he wouldn't
And how
He had to deal with these damn Nazis and arrogant they were and I didn't like them
Show me I grew up
Both grandfathers
Both
And they both didn't like
And so
I didn't get from Captain America and get it from Hollywood and get it from any of that
Another for my badass
And they don't make men like that anymore so
That's where I'm at
I can I can
This is a personal story
Event is like
I don't give a s*** like
I don't think that this
Anecdotal story means much in terms of like why you oppose Nazis
Like one grandfather was annoyed by them
And then the other one heard something about extortion
Also one side of his family sounds like they were Nazis
100%
Crazy German
Came here recently
It seems to be ome said they were in World War II
It seems to me that all of those things are Alex adding up
2 they were not hurt those are that's
That's the type of
Lineage
Tracks with Alex's bike
I've not told this whole story
And is it I mean you know on the other hand he's not quite telling it like a Romeo and Juliet you know like my tooth
My grandfathers were both at war with each other you had
Lineage and then the Confederate lady a
I'm that baby boy is not America opposite of you got chocolate in my peanut butter
Is it is 100%
Slave owners in genocidaires are like we do the same job this is such a smart thing we do
We are making a bit of an assumption but it is assumption based on a lot of
Details that Alex was very
So he knew a lot of Rich Germans in the area at
Time Hitler took over
So
I think
I think that
Especially if you're expecting to enter a conversation
With a guy who you clearly know
Loves Hitler and
Basically has
Neo-Nazi ideas
I think
You should be able to articulate your opposition to
Hitler
And the Third Reich
Better than saying
Wernher von Braun and his buddies were arrogant
And
Nazis extorted people
I think
This
Is soft
Possibly attend
Channel 8
He said this exact thing in the AM interview
Like
Nick is already hurt
This is means nothing Alice's remember he doesn't care
I mean listen here's the thing that's unspoken that is in Fury
Right because
What's going on here is the World War 2 Hitler conversation in the canto
Text those of the Holocaust and all that stuff
And
Yeah Alex
His defense is horrendously Garba
I feel like even if you are an anti-semite
Shouldn't you be able to agree
Bet flattening France is a bad idea
That should be held against someone that's interesting
Hold that against him I think that's an interesting point
But I'm the reason that they don't mention that it's because they're fine with expansion of government flattening people that they don't like
Probably
But I think that Alex bring
Brings this up
Because
To him
Subjective experience
Is so much more important is anecdotal story
And stuff that is much more reality to him
Then
Something that happened to somebody who he doesn't know
Or they're the broader picture of the
Atrocities in horrors of World War II dealing with two narcissist 17/20 is bulshit earlier about
I don't care what happened in the past ATL is affected my life like 10 and 2
Who cares
Your life is meaningless you shitbag
But
Keep saying it
What
He thinks better of it
Okay but then you thinks better of the thinking better of it
This is basically Alex
Ping pong game with himself
I'm at but that said you can't
Schlotzsky's in the dryer he's been spun around so many times
When the left
Is literally
Redlining the engine when it comes to race-based politics in the ATL is
Captaining
Teaching elementary students they're inherently bad
Because of what
I'm not going to
Reliable the ATL
What I say
Mess around find out
Earlier using
The support for what ye said
What's 50/50
I wanted to
Demarcated
The fact that I'm up
What's
He said I don't agree with
And what's happened to him
But I'm not in League with that whole worldview so that's where I'm at
That's convoluted with where you're at if you're listening to this
To be pretty tough to get a sense of like
What that means
I would like rather than going on the journey to find out where Alex is at I would like him to tell me where he's at and then
The show is work at
If you must know he's never going to do that out
Sushi is saying that you can't judge Nick because the ATL is so anti-white and they're teaching
White kids that are bad because of that
Alex doesn't want to do what Nick is doing
Because he doesn't want to sync
To the level of ATL
But also
F*** around and find out
Like Nick said in a clip that Alex played for All America first
At Dave's June should be
Stu us because there's worse people coming
So that's that's what Alex is hearkening to the right and as a little bit of a cherry on top he says
The support for gays
These comments
We're 50/50
Which is to say
Half of my audience
My audience is not
Those worst people that are coming
If you're not nice enough to Nick and gay
80s
It is so f******
Unreal
It is uncanny
Candy
Because I think of these people and I see them wearing the skin of a human
At all of those
Thanks right when they
Talk to each other
This this
A lack of mirror
This idea of like
Well obviously the 80 I was leaving so much racism and it's like you just heard a guy say the Jewish question to your face
Your goddamn mind
What is going on in your brain so it probably comes back to that subjectivity thing to though like
Going up there is an inability to
Probably process that like the things
That you're involved in our
Look as bad or worse than the things you're accusing
That's the thing
To me that is soaked
Confusing about navigating life
Is like
I don't know
What it is that you are if you can't do that
Cuz I died and that doesn't mean that I think I'm some sort of more human or
Or they're not human or anything like that right I am in this context because what I think of is a person who can do
You know another thing to that kind of muddies the waters even more
Is that this is
Providence purpose is a conversation between two people but it's also perform
They're being recorded
It's also
Alex
Doing his show
I am kind of not trying any harder than he normally does
Being pretty over
And comfortable in his own position in a way
He hasn't been
On Alex's show the past there is a persuasive element that Nick is bringing to it that Alex
But he is also bringing to it that he is not
I am in that kind of
That can kind of
Add a little bit of another variable to a
Where you accuse
These people of being like others of the most horribly racist thing in the world
I'm not acknowledge the things that that isn't
That is the conversation
Alex and Nick are having
Because
It's part of the performance conversation
But yeah I think this is just been awful it's been very bad
Nick sucks
He has gone
Azfar possibly further than
Yeah he did on his interview
Now I think maybe the only saving grace
If you want even call it that is
Look at how little attention this
You know there is something to be said for how much this is
Demonstrable evidence
Of how much Nick Museum
Penetrate in any way into outside
Market
You probably didn't even know that this happened until we started recording no clue
I think a lot of people didn't and I can say for sure
Based on the number of tweets
That died
Come and it was
Flood
When ye was on a couple
Right when this happened so
I think that there is something that is like
This is dangerous this is
Is f****** awful its death
Finally going to have an effect on Alex's audio
And there is a real danger of
I am swaying some of them over
Yeah but
In terms of this having the same
Kind of
Broad
The fact that gay being on had
It's laugh
Yes it's less
Now
Intervallic protecting his body
He's not doing a good job
It actually is doing a bad job
Commercial free podcast on Saturday
Log the found something like Fifty calls we should do this yet your own show
On Cozi TV as well
URL
Rosie. TV / Nick
Yeah I'd love to
Don't be afraid
Advance Auto
Bandai video and enforce.
Don't be afraid of the info
What the fuk just happened
Funneling is audience to Tunica
Bob Sight
I mean Alex just invited him to talk more
Does Alex not know that he just got spanked
You might be in denial about it that's crazy
That's crazy
That is it safe
If you're describing it as a spanking it's a sort of
Assisted speaking events
Alex if you wanted to
Could have had far
More
Robust pushback
Oh yeah he could have had
Any number of ideas
4 things to say to Nick other than
Well
The ADL is really bad so
You may be on his bed hey have you ever considered that maybe
It's not juuzou maybe it's globalist
These are just like
The best he can do
100%
What what the point is
You can't it I mean and I'm not talking about spanking the debate like the ideas were but whatever
They're not
What I'm talking about is
The debate has
And Nick
Clearly has nothing to be afraid of
Nobody can hurt him
From his little screen
Alex is clearly afraid of
Tons of s***
And it's
Palpable
That's that's what
He got spanked
Yeah he is not the he's not certain
He's not like this is how it is like maybe you could be
Listen up
Jerk exactly exactly
You have this worldview
And I understand where you're coming from
You're 23 Creek shut the f****** because what you're doing is actually damaging to the cause
You need to understand
Know Your Role
Shut the fuk up
The fact that he doesn't behave that way it is
Sad
Becoming a that's that's
That's what would make me leave Alex in my head of what in Alex listener is obvious
They wouldn't let me has nothing to do with that bright but he might head if I'm
Alex Jones Infowars fan
One of the
Big things that I'm a fan of
Is that this loud angry man is right all the time he's giving it to him the way that it needs to be given
Piers Morgan
And talk about it for the next decade
Not really
Take a few calls
And
One of them
Is a real bummer
My daughter
10 year old girl
She was sitting there listening to this conversation
And people need to realize
People like you Nick
Having influence over younger people
Very careful with her
Extremely careful
We don't realize
Don't you have
Honestly
Do what you want to but I
Before you make any more comments
Extra tall
Nick is super aware of his influence
Tricking kids into thinking extremism in 87 summer cool is legitimately the Cornerstone of his marketing strategy
How Will I
It got going for him
Like he was being radicalized by weirdo Nazis pretended to be teens on 4chan in now
Nick is trying to take that game and GoPro
This color so f****** said 41
Letting his fourteen-year-old daughter listen to this
Nick wouldn't hear a warning about the influence he has on kids as an amazing compliment
Play I did it almost
Feel him laughing
That's absurd
What that's that's such a great
Little
Bad bad thing to try
You know what I'll do
I think I can talk him down by
I tell him about the
You got to read it twice that's good word my friend you got a lot of mixed up ideas that this good old book and saw
You know what is kind of like a real
Milquetoast
Version of the shut up until you're older
But it's
It's
Very very
Black cooler than dancing
Of the Bible kids come on down we got to youth group together
So this next color is a fun
Long and short of this is
I think this guy is a Nazi supporter
But also he insist
Set Alex's German and Alex will not accept that
Hey guys
This dialogue
That's my cuz
Maybe this time
Before you know the right
Conservatives.
Hitler in the left
Always deflect
Hitler
I got to ask me
Don't you agree that the
We're fighting for a better future
Future for all of Europe
The tactics
The war and Hitler
You keep repeating that you're German don't you think that Europe will be in a better place now
And Hitler got 20 million Germans
Answer
He is an American and a Christian
Man
Now we've got two races to disagree about their racism suddenly being accosted by a completely
Different form of racism
Racism Works guys and this this
Color is weird weird
Quite Place him
But I do think that what he was expressing is that if Hitler had won World War two things would be better
That seems to be the sort of
Bullet point
Also he's lovely
Well I mean I think that was also another subtle indicator is that that like
No no no you said you had one grandfather's German
Your German
You're part of Zeller your parts of
The fatter liar
Sir
Yep
31 last clip here and
Like these colors
Suck
Because there is legit pushback that a caller could make on what
Nick is bringing to the table
Within the conception of Infowars
Go weird
There are there outside of the Infowars
Box
There are potent criticisms that could be made
Based on the things that makes a
Call him out for saying the Jewish question thing
Call him out for saying that to this
Jewishness that makes people bad
Any of these things could
Be like what the
F*** did you mean by that
Family show don't swear
But
Get this guy saying hey think about the influence you have on kids
And read the Bible twice
We get this other guy who's
Probably on Nick's side
Quite frankly
Hey nectresse
Question for you
These are all just words
Why don't you start living in
My question is like
Why don't you
Have to be a horse River why don't you
Do Your Own Thing
How much live in Christ
More minutes of the day than probably any group out there
Why don't
Why don't you just
Stop throwing bombs
Start living
Fight
That's my question to you
Well I I don't know what that means I'm not Amish so I don't think living in Christ means living in a low-tech society I'm living
In price every day I'm a Christian I go to church I pray everyday I pray the rosary and what were called to do its
We're call to go out and have Angela's until the
Truth there's horrible iniquity
And horrible and just
Just going on in the world
If you're Christian you have to be discussed
At the state of our country like I said though
The filth in the media the filth in our school system
The groomers
P*** the media
It's terrible and it to sit by and watch all these innocent people and some kind of quietus
Y'all people call this
The Benedict option
I think it's a dereliction of Duty have an allegation of ours more calls
I think that this
Hey buddy
Country Jamaica
Bucking religious weirdo compound
I want to
I want to Kobe hugging Hamish
I'm not Amish
I don't know what you're doing sir event like
They they are
Christ more time
It's such an it's such an
Easy thing
Agree with their conception of what it means
To be in Christ
Oh
Okay
Well
Thanks thanks for taking my call
It's such a
The problem with
I mean but that's
That's how the religious
Peer pressure always wind up working is
Somebody like Nick comes in and then they're like hey you know what I don't think you really understand the Bible
We need to learn about it that and then somebody like naked Power and they're like
Nick says some interesting things I like listen
Tunica
I thought you knew about the Bible but I guess I don't
Yeah I ain't no I disagree on a few things
Yes that's some other things that
You got to
You got to listen to these other folks are saying some really bad
Maybe the extreme stuff that he believes in art isn't really that extreme
Man
Aisha
I hate this
I don't want
To just
Cover this stuff
But it's
More or less the only thing that I find relevant about Alex's
Present day
Does feel that way
I
Ronnie just today Trump came out with those nipes
I do wonder what Alexandra say about that
But
I hope
This can move on to a different subject
Soon
Release
I'll tell you what I'll tell you what you know what
When I next brand of Catholic fascism takes over
I refuse
To believe
But that priest actually turns that Cracker into Jesus body
I will die on
Hang me from the Raptors
If you think I'll ever say that the priest literally transforms of cracker into the skin of Jesus
I'm not doing it
Not once I think
That
This is
A bad interview
The bad debate
Yeah Nick is escalating
He's taking some of the things that were
Part and parcel of the gay interview and reasserting them to Alex in a way
That Alex is
Impotent
Too much back on
That we can't rule that out entirely
Because of the end of
Of all of it Alex's still like I want to talk to you for 2 hours I mean it, let's do this body I want to get more
In the nick Fuentes business unreal
But
It was
Watch
More
Monotonous
Then I thought it was
Listening
I thought it was far more engaging and interesting that is really just a
It's kind of hitting the same notes
82 batl is worse than you so hey maybe it's not so bad how can I criticize you went the eggs
Exist
That's the problem with the lesser of two evils
Always goes bad sooner or later
And then the other thing is the trying to be like hey you were trying to be sincere
Satonil in trying to piss off the sensors and
Of all the time to give Nick excuses for him but he doesn't want
In the same way that he was doing that with
With ye
End
It does not Alex's a behavior does not make me confident
That is going to be able to
Navigate
Be more choppy Waters that we're going to be getting into as we get closer to the 2024
Election
Whether or not
Yay continues as a
Quote-unquote candidate
Even if even if he doesn't
This isn't where this at
No that's true
This pageant that were in the middle of that is true
And Alex
Are you showing himself to not be able
What the deal with chapter 1
So as the book
Progresses I imagine
It's going to get worse
Feel like
It's it's just so obvious
When you watch
Yay and Nick do these things with those
Other people
It's so obvious
That they're throwing a bomb in the idea of we always
July
By doing that
They're revealing that everybody's lying
Like how does that not
Thinking for people
Well you know like you watch
All of these people
Reactivate
Exact same way
To this man saying the same thing over and over and over
You know he means it 90mm
Means it and you agree with him over and over and over again
But you keep telling him to lie about it
Yeah because you're a liar
It does seem to I mean granted
We should be clear
We've only listen to the Gavin and Alex
Appearances and Tim pool
Wheatgrass
Yeah that didn't get off the The Runway lucky he gets an incomplete on that
Interviews that may or may not have
Gone that way but turns of Gavin and Alex
I agree with you yet that does reveal
Yeah they're crypto nest
For sure
F*** all this
Ava Jordan another episode. Until then
Redlobster.com
Cubes
Are juicy
And now here comes
What the sex robots
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color