Jordan
I have great respect for Dan and Jordan I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Need need money
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody welcome back tonight
I'm sure
A little bit about
Alex Jones
Indeed we are.
Quick question
Before anybody wants up today going here that was
There before we started recording
It was
Not there at all about two-and-a-half seconds ago and now I feel it this is a large credibly disorienting but
I will make the best of it
So my brakes today is not that we are recording
Remotely
Because I got a little bit of a sickness
I've come down with the bad case
I've left and you I will we know I don't know what it is but I
Would test and it's not that so
I don't know I still recording remotely because you know could be
Any number of different things is wiser now in this day and age to to be smart about things like that so you know sure
Sure I'm putting a hit the button
And the blast doors came down and I'm locked in
Before I felt
Fell ill
And that is that I was taking some couple bags
Buttons
Packages of buttons
Stuvi
Mailbox
Down the street
Because I can't
Just leave them in my my apartment there you wouldn't pick them up
So I expect the birds
To take them where they need to go
It would be nice if I had carrier pigeon who take me to Scotland
So I was on my way down there and I saw a mail truck
And so I walked up
To it and I asked
The guy like hey
I'm about to take these down to this mailbox
Or you can just take him from me
Is a golf course
Yeah it was just a little thing
But it was so nice he was evil
So positive this mail carrier
And like
I don't know it really bright
By my spirits
That's that's so cool because part of me honestly expect that response to that to be like no it's a
Illegal
Right right or there's a policy that I can't break
There's some reason where it's like I can't accept this by hand
There's ain't no God or any number of reasons we can't have definitive trail of custody or chain
Custody
Plastic go in the box at some point
Except
Yeah that was really cool I like that I appreciate that
That was great
My bright spot it's kind of like a it's kind of more like Twilight spots to some extent
Like a my bright spot is the World Cup
Final today
And it was a die I mean
I couldn't do it justice to describe what happened with 10,000 words it's rev everybody's already describing is the greatest
World Cup final this ever
You know
Another
Whatever right I mean it's one of a really was astonishing to watch
It made me think of like the pyramids
Do you know what I mean because I mean like in Egypt in
Other countries me the game pyramid
The ancient pyramid
It's about how we still go see them
And what they are is really monuments to what you can build with slavery and blue
Cuz I actually heard from a guy that they were used to store grain
That's possible
I mean aliens have to keep the green somewhere and it was at the time
It is it is this world cup is one of the most amazing things I've ever seen and it's also a testament
Blood slavery so it's a terrible thing
Anime convention in soccer teams were built on blood and slavery
No but the arena was
The word placing forgot I forgot the guitar
Yeah yeah yeah
Guess he was
That's my other bright spot this Elon Musk guys doing some some great things that Twitter
That made me think of the pyramids what are these awful billionaires but the modern-day pharaohs
So fantastic
Today we have an episode to go over even though I have fallen ill
The DeMille
Podcast Mills
Can't be close just because
The foreman is closed or northfleet
Great I would take the day off but
That mailman
Really inspired me to no no no
Because my voicemail not hold out
We may have a little bit of a shorter episode today we're going to be back
In 2003 talking about December 8th
Good idea
Even otherwise without that I still probably might have
Put Alex in his time out spot
For bad behavior
Even if it was I wasn't ill
But
A lot of calls
Iggy Azalea
Call Heather
Unfortunately I am
When I say that I would put him on timeout
It would work
Against me because of what ends up happening
And some of these calls
What is this the episode where common reveals he's an anti-semite
Unless common goes by
Greg
New Mexico wear whatever that I'm not sure
Beget release cuz I feel like it was right around this time
Was he on a promotional tour
I don't believe that,
Is backpack in the theater Infowars Studio
He at that these collars
Terrible
Say hello to some new walks
Oh that's great idea
So first I set my goals but before I set my house on fire thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Very much
I blame Robert Evans
Thank you very much
Alex none of this is real Ambassador squatches 2nd paper podcast thank you so much you are now but was he walk
Next
But thank you very much
And Kirby Rick's existentialism is a hoodie is a false flag also my 401k isn't doing so well
Late bro thank you so much
I know we got to take the trash to the mix Jordan so
This person told me to read this as the symbols exist
I think it's some kind of a coding
Joker I'm not entirely sure so maybe this is
Maybe the robots will find this real funny
Abso text
Lexa backs of this
Apostrophe
Close parentheses semicolon drop table technocrat
Semicolon Dash Dash
Thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Someone sodomites
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Thank you very much
Haha I hope that wasn't some sort of 8
Missile launch code or something that I have just let out
Start off and here's the vibe that Alex is putting out into the universe
It's a Monday mantissa Monday show
I've got a big fat week
That's whatever that's what I say whenever it's Monday huh
We're back in 2003 this is phat this is prime Phat time
So whatever people say was a big fat week you know what
I mean like in the it last year I would hear Alex
Constantly say that we have a thick with two C's in a week coming up
So
We we get to talking about some actual stuff
Pretty quickly
Pretty consistently throughout the show
As a testament to that here is our second clip
Is a collar
Already a call
Already you call her
Is a guy works in 1/4
And he claims I believe this actually probably true
He claims that he works with Chuck Norris
Where's Chuck Norris is like a deputized honorary police officer of some kind
Wait wait I thought that was Steven Seagal
Where they both
I think a lot of them might have dabbled in.
Wasn't Shack
Deputy sheriff honorary never thought this before but thank God
Bruce Lee is dead so we didn't find out that he's a cop in New Orleans or so was later on rice for a while
That would be great
So anyway here's this caller talking about Chuck Norris and we learn something unfortunate about this color
I'm probably about Chuck Norris
One of my auction
Reserved for
One of my Oscar
Big
Videos by the way
And we were
We were
Beard Scout
Showing
Really really strong
I'm not at all
Yeah so Chuck Norris cat mentioned
Sherwood
Dimension the baby Jesus because of the Jewish influence on the media
Alex has a
Disappointing reaction to that color
Listening to visit like right out of the gate
F*** is going on
What are those
I know that even in like other periods of 2003 the we've got back to you there has been like undertones
Obviously there's
Conversation going on at
Check bigoted stuff of
Various tribes
But like
Going back in Japan
Here's overt
Some of these episodes
A right in your face
Yeah I mean
You know there's a part of it that makes me think one of the reasons that we're we're kind of unused to it right now
It's because
I guess 20 years ago they just didn't feel the need to speak it out loud to each other because
Was never under threat
You know now that people are paying attention to it then it's now it's time to start going
Absolutely crazy but it was always there
You know
Yeah
Yeah yeah it'll be more there as if it goes long to just call her is an ox
Emily let's say on this episode
Everybody we're going to be like
Okay well now we need to respect all peoples
So honest episode Alex does spend a fair amount of time talking about how great gold is due
Gold prices through the roof and what-have-you
I have been on other episodes in 2003 to that I've been listening to but he never mentions
That he works for Midas resources
Do they sell gold
He's not so weird
He's not doing the second stage of the gold sale thing
But it is so obvious
That he's selling gold
Is marketing gold
Right and then a big if true news story
Picacho
Gold
Yeah man
If you mention Jesus Christ you're going to you're going to get 6 months in jail
Pearson understand why saying if you bunch of Jesus Christ
Is war like emotionally-charged for people
If there was a law that was any word LEDs you 6 months in jail
I'd be furious about it right like it doesn't matter if it's Jesus Christ
Or like an
Is Angela to his six months of Jayla pizzerias to
Yeah I mean like I guess yelling fire in a crowded building if you lead to like people dying but like stampede
Good maybe
You could get a manslaughter
Charge or something
But like that's that's a pretty specific Circle
Takes a lot of other problems going on around you before that becomes the central one
Yeah maybe it is like a graduation speech they don't want you to just let give a sermon
Maybe it'll public school who don't necessarily
Let's not encourage
But no
By the way why is a judge giving like this press conference like
We will rock you up if you take tikosyn
Hernia silly
Okay he's locked up
Thirty or forty people already
For saying Jesus Christ and he's tired of it maybe people don't
Know about how you get locked up for saying it
Notice
Yeah yeah he just don't do it this is like a
Falling Rock sign
Yeah
So we get another caller and this person has a bit of a perspective that is like
Forced prayer in school
And if you don't like that
F*** out
Get out the country
Comment on it
Am I children where you and I'm grateful that they had a teacher
A small girl
Graham crackers
Sprite
Simply workout
Kristen Nurse & Lothrop
Leave
Measurement let us go on
Have a great day
Yeah man if you don't like her Tendencies towards theocracy and you don't like our indoctrination of
Of kids in public schools
Get the f*** out
Get out
All I'm saying
All I'm saying is that if there is a child from a different culture
They need to go to an American school have that culture torn from their bodies
Assimilate into whiteness and only white Christian theocracy
And then everything's going to be fine I feel like people are overreacting to my advice conversely they have another choice and it's good
Yeah so when we eat when we hear in the present-day you know again and talking a bit about like these
Tendencies towards Christian theocracy Christian nationalism
It is not a foreign conversation to the mentality of a lot of Infowars
Listeners even
Over
Like earlier time
Yeah
Yeah it makes you it makes you wonder like
Perhaps part of the reason that he's he's so willing
Throw those
Those bombs
Is because
You know
Maybe 15 years ago it started becoming more important not to do those types of things
Conservative right-wing commentators took their anti-Semitism in the leg
Into that coded language world
And he wasn't alive for that he wasn't alive for the Fallout from the first time everybody was like what if we just hated use all the
He wasn't alive for a lot of these like really important elements of the the right-wing and I wasn't live for
What happened after Oklahoma City
Probably doesn't recognize the stakes
For the
Pecan people
Importantly militia organizing
Yeah
Sure and he's he's a kid so you know you can always just point to this kid and be like listen
I know
You think you have had a brand-new idea
That no one's ever f****** thought of before
But I'm going to be honest with you
You have not
Yeah
Buddy
Yeah yeah
Set Alex's main story on this episode appears to be that the Supreme Court has decided that there is no second.
Which
I mean he reports
Pretty much
Three or four times a year
Based on a different story of some sort
And it is never true
20 years old I believe the Supreme Court has invalidated
The Second Amendment at least 48 x States Elmo real
He's explaining some of this stuff to a caller who has a question
About about this ruling
Wheeling by the
Supreme Court
YouTube
Oh
Max
Pay study abroad
Weather
Supreme Court
States rights in the face dead
Snappy
Brady Bill was unconscious
A what
Jeff Mack
They still
Indifferent
But it is not Constitution
Indeed
Completely unrelated to this caller or clip
The day after this episode was recorded these Freedom Court decided that the Potomac River was under Virginia's control
Maryland
I had a court battle to get to the river
Okay
Alex is a really bad source of information because pretty much everything he saying In that clip is incorrect
He's telling this caller inaccurate information and then using that to construct. Merritt is about the reality that we all live in
The 1997 Supreme Court case that Alex is talking about is Prince versus United States
Did not determine that the Brady gun bill was
Additional
That Bill had a provision that required gun background checks to be done for purchases but on the federal level that's
System was not prepared yet
According to the bill state law enforcement agencies were required to use their background check system to run this
Until such a time that the federal system was ready
Prince versus United States ruled that this was unconstitutional to make state law enforcement carry out federal law on
But activity
The state law enforcement folks were required to
Ask to do this
And if they wanted to opt out they could
That was the result of this ruling
Ultimately Most states had no problem with the setup and continue to participate by their own consent
I am but you should be can't move once the federal background check system was Operation
Naturally
Alex is lying about the Supreme Court decision to tell it this color that the government ruled the background checks for gun purchases
Unconstitutional
But they didn't care
They just ignore rulings that they don't like
This is a dangerous message to be sending to an audience like Alex is because if the government doesn't even follow Supreme Court to say
Visions then isn't everything of farce
There's literally no way the public can be involved in politics since the globalist
Just decide who's going to win the election
And they could just
At capriciously we decide whether or not to follow their own chords
This is not a state of affairs that anyone rational or sincere be presenting is just the way things are
This would be a message that implies that I need for action
Are all Civic participatory government-related actions are
Merely pointless
Play song he's telling
Yeah absolutely
This is the one that is is also the reason that Prince had to change his name to the symbol
Ryton Printz
Saudi Prince
Aziza Plus
I just like the idea that the Supreme Court
I didn't think about the Supreme Court is one of the reasons that it's so easily exploitable is because the actual decision
Visions
Are so nerdy and specific like Nana and arrow decided
Is whether or not this aligned is it
Acceptable to Cross by Butte
Very specific circumstances so you might as well just claim it does
Who gets the river
Yeah exactly
Exact circumstances
These cases in Court decisions Alex never uses specifics and that's for two reasons
One he probably doesn't know any of them because he's lazy and he does zero show prep
It's not in his interest to be specific because he's lying and he doesn't want to make it easy for his audience to follow up
Claims and realize that
Because he said one specific I'm left to assume that the ninth Circuit Court of Appeals case in San Francisco that he's referring to is
Nordyke versus King
That was a decision that came out in 2003 and was
Not accepted by the Supreme Court
That ruling has to do it's not with the banning guns or declining there's no Second Amendment
It was a situation where a gun dealer sued Alameda County because
The county has passed an ordinance
Possession
Nerf guns on County proper
This included the fairgrounds which is where nordyke begun dealer held gun shows
That ordinance was passed in 1999 and the reason was stated as being because there was a shooting that happened
The previous 4th of July at the Alameda Fair
There was a believed to be a bit of a confrontation
That resulted in injuries
Including an eight-year-old boy and two other miners
This case about this ordinance is the closest thing I can find what Alex is talking about
And it's nowhere close to reflecting
Any of his narrative
I wonder if he give some specifics about the story later in the episode
He doesn't
You shouldn't be optimistic
Information
It's just that
This ruling and because the Supreme Court decided not
Hear it
Now the second amendment's gone
Know that it did they just ruled it a county does have the ability to band
Vons on County property
If if you think that the Supreme Court and I mean if you think that the government is just enforcing whatever
Rules it likes or not
Then
I mean there's there's the conclusion that you know there's no point in participating in democracy at all but I would also Imagine That
That if you have
Guns and Alex is telling you that
Guns are banned in this country
And nobody's coming to stop you than your your assumption would be that they just don't want to do it right
Or they're waiting for the strategically right moment
There's no wind there's no way it's always going to be always f*****
When your worldview in reality is largely based on creative writing prompts it turns out
Add new layers to things constantly
Out of a jam
Yeah I would have kicked a lot of people out of the creative writing class if I were running it
A lot of people with a god
Exercise with gone on for 20 years in creative writing
It's a very repetitive
We need some new themes and motifs to start appearing
Your greatest CB after class
Alex has this idea about these gun bills in these Supreme Court
Rulings and we'll have you
And
You know that the NRA is derelict in its Duty
Cuz it's not telling people they fake versions of these bills that Alex is telling people
As we saw in that last clip
It's Alex was lying about these cases and rulings
He's the one creating false reality in order to scare his audio
Alex needs to attack these more mainstream gun organizations because they don't live in his false reality
Battle Ray can support gun rights all day long but if they don't pretend decision is the end of the Second Amendment
Alex they have to be liars and probably gun-grabbers in disguise
This strategy have a couple of good effects from Alex's fan point
The first is that it makes anything the NRA does look less extreme and always not enough
The audience will always demand that the gun rights organizations take a couple more steps than they should because they believed that there was
Responded to the fake stories Alex
The second effect is that the audience will push the NRA further towards
Living in Alex's false reality
Or at least behaving as if that falls reality were real
In order to keep up with
The base
Any sense of this
Consider the Ted Nugent was a fairly controversial person to associate with back at this point
He's now a member of the NRA board
They they have shifted a little
Due to this external pressure based on
Snowfall stories
Yeah I mean Vendetta at this point
What most people don't own an assault rifle
I mean it and it's certainly small number of people own assault rifles
The only people who were protecting they were people who are either
Overreacting because of a slippery slope argument
Or people who are like living in a
African Bungalow in Brooklyn being like I need a surface-to-air missile otherwise I won't be safe
And I was like well there's some other people were focusing on this story and they are folks
To like to sell guns at the fairgrounds in Alameda County
Maybe close attention to the story but
I understand that Alex's story is b*******
I have they are
So we had earlier
A story that is clearly nonsense
About you
Prison for 6 months if you mention Jesus
Call we were recording remotely for the first time forever and now the cops are out here cherries and berries
Going down I said Jesus Christ
Here's another prediction that Alex has about
Stuff that will happen
Enforcement standpoint in the near future
Did you think this happened
Is Alex correct
Hellcat
Pickup truck
What would you do
What is the division
Warrant
Naturally
What's okay so to get a couple years of fugitive apprehension
Yeah we're getting married we're getting a 15 16 year olds out there as bounty hunters
Excuse me sir I just want to let you know that you've been served
You didn't need to do that to graduate
Radish
What about to get a GED can you just drop out
Belt. If you if you get a GED you have to become a cop for 5 years
What's coming and I think he was wrong
I think basically
I don't know I just
I don't know if it's a terrible idea like that maybe I mean I think it's probably if you're bleeding
Tell people to do you know stuff like that fugitive apprehension Worth to high school
He started his things like
Pulled weeds and all that stuff and then it elevated
To serving warrants
Very quick
Yeah yeah volunteerism encouraging it within people in
High School I don't think it's bad
And when I was at the University of Missouri for a while at the office of service-learning
And it was a part of my job was to
Look through the course catalog and try and find courses that naturally let themselves
New volunteer opportunities being incorporated into
The curricular
And
Yeah it's that kind of stuff
I think is very positive that as
College students being forced to serve warrants
Or Suffolk neighborhood surveillance I always watch I give people
All around
I just thought that was pretty
Tell me he's like
I don't understand how anybody could take him seriously with that he's talking about this
Have you ever met a 15-16 year-old to sync and you trust them to
Wright-Patt listen pretty dangerous
Can't drive do I feel about all the other head
There are a lot of Opera
Opportunities for ambush
Warat issues
If it's
Children that you're working you're not expect
Children deserve a war right
So you were a little fifteen-year-old walks up to
Excuse me sir
Do you know which way the story's for Kohl's I need to buy a new t-shirt you've been served
I think if you're talkin about like a summons to appear or something like that there's a lawsuit that like anybody could.
Deliver that
I don't think fugitive apprehension like that implies somebody who's on the Run
Hi baby
All right we're going to take this fifteen-year-old
Venezuela
Top notch
Most Wanted FBI criminal because otherwise he won't graduate
In order to get the college Uniden extracurriculars and some people can Debate Club
Some people might get into sports
You know if you can't make the team
Maybe you got to be Dog the Bounty Hunter
Cowboy Bebop
So dumb
Brett Gray
I love it
Yeah that's pretty
Interested
So one of the things you need to understand is that your mind has a lock on it
And there's a key
It's in the shape of a lie
Interesting
Stop
Found
The anti-semitic techno artists who is concerned about underwear
And your balls
The best stuff that's
He's pushing that pretty pretty hard
He's making money for
This pair of underwear
Is
Really really good at supporting
Lefty
But I'm telling you
The right side
Does that
With the left-right ball paradigm
I am
Baltaire
The show might not work if I take cough syrup
Amighetti's
Perhaps but
We have to enjoy a little bit of
A little bit of fun because ultimately I understand what's coming
And I know
That this next clip
Is a b
A bit of a shock
Answer Mike down for this Jordan this is this is another call that Alex gets
That's a blue me away
Well you don't want to call
Invisible Empire
Lakme
Guys around here
Well I mean that nobody knows it
The neighbor
Well it stopped here
Everybody
The plan
Indignation
They get up on her horse and a ride
And that's what's going to happen
Disgusted
Khalid Muhammad
But
Normally I think I would hear someone calling to the show and claimed to be in the clan and I would really believe it
Bye-bye at 100%
In the fuc
King Clan
If there's ever been
He sounds pretty sincere
He's old enough to own a hood
30 copies of Birth of a Nation 3
Free handouts on
Christmas
He sounded pretty
Cryptic to language
I feel
Lense to his credibility
Well you open with a riddle
That's what I'm saying
Planned loves riddles
That's what everybody does that
Now the reason this clip is important is that it really has Echoes of how Alex dealt with ye and Nick in the present
Hear the caller who's admitted to being a proud Clan member which is something Alex is supposedly again
In the same way he's supposedly against Hitler and the Nazis memes days
And yet somehow Alex can't manage to make it
Clear emphatic statement in opposition to these groups
With Yang and make you can't review the Nazi in Hitler's choosing instead to pretend that the ADL is worse than
Naked because of fake stories that he repeats over and over
About how they think white people are inherent
Evil
The only way to get voice to criticism of ye and Nick's Nazi ideas is to condemn them along with the ABS
And be very insistent that the ADL is worse
I'm here Alex can't just tell this caller that the clan is bad and he shouldn't be a member of it
Instead he rather bizarre rationalization for why he assumes this guy joined the clan which I don't
Too far off from what folks in the clan might say
They also love to pretend that their racism is justified by imagining it
Only exists as a defense
Against other people being racist against them
This is Alex giving me a
Appearance of pushing back against this guy who literally in the clan
Well actually making excuses for him and making me act of joining a hate group a possibly unwise
But morally neutral decision
This is because Alex doesn't actually think being a member of a group is a bad thing
You can't even get through this response to the collar without speculating how white people would be arrested for open carrying
What black people get away with it essentially justifying and signing off
On the feelings of racial agreement that drive a lot of people toward these racist group
Here's an important thing to understand
Even if a listener or this collar word except Alex is framing of things and conceited at all
There's still no reason not to be a member of
The client
If and only if we're able to defeat the globalist
That means racist groups will stop you played against each other
But until that happens
And even they understand that that's never going to happen
Then these other races groups will still exist
The clan members and Nazis believe that they are defensive organisation
So if those other group
Entirely intact
I understand that Alex doesn't show up to the studio knowing they'd like he's going to be on the phone with the Klan member
But he definitely should have known it was a distinct
Possibility
Like he knows who his audiences and the fact that he doesn't have any stronger condemnation for the clan this is damn
Yeah I mean
It's it's
It should be more complicated and yet somehow it's very simple you know like
If somebody calls and tells you that the Clans member and then you go well yeah of course
You are but it's not
Your fault because black people are racist
You're a bad person
It's not what you would expect if you actually opposed the class
Listen
I get it
You're a clan member obviously black people racist
That's why the clan was invented before black people were allowed to vote and every
Oh my God no actually there the horror of all know see that can
Can't happen
Yeah I can happen but it's very strange
What Clan is that the Black Panther Party wants to kill a white people I'm sorry what now
Yeah that's my real problem with it
Ha
So
Alex tries to follow this up
Bye
Condemning
The clan
One of the things that he seems to want to do is discuss it only in terms that have nothing to do with race
My grandmother was a
Don't like
The burn down
Murdered
Control
Yeah that's a little bit
Weird so yeah it's just it's just a group that harasses business owners they don't like
Trying to get the Northerners attitude Texas
Let me problem with the clan
Is the inconvenience a lot of
People
That's it
General fashion in specific
The big problem you know it's just
Just no group
In particular
Plan
Now the clan
It's mostly just like a the Shakedown operation of businesses
Goemon sure they started as one thing but you don't like
VW made engines for the Nazis you know we can change
Yikes
So Alex Goes to commercial
Get that to get a little bit of a
A break after talking to a client
This commercial I just thought it was like I'm just play a couple seconds of it I thought this was like really f****** dumb
That's right
It's so crass to me to hear like at 9:11
Conspiracy theory being sold with that like
Morning radio
What is a
Coming up this Sunday like
I'm sorry this building
Coming up right after the break
Reminder say correctly your documentary is proving that the United States government did a false flag onto his own country and
Either way you're selling it
Yeah it's it's a little it makes me feels on Sirius
Baby undercuts
The level of Gravitas that your documentary by deserve
Another
Point that I'd like to bring up here is that we've heard Alex claim that
He was the number one
Voice over guy in the world
Criticizing Obama was like
Oh no you can't get any jobs
I don't think he has a place
In the market
I don't think that's good voice over work
I mean he's not going to be on a Geico commercial anytime soon with that kind of stuff he's not going to get his own recurring character
You know though they do have those Geico commercials that are like washed-up celebrities who are like in like in weird
Circumstances he might show up into the the
The new cave mode
Geico show starring Nick Kroll
I meant subtly try to sell his caveman bone broth
Going going into business for himself during the middle of this
Beryllium
So Alex gets a call from a mason
Lot of folks in groups called him today
Three that I didn't know about
It was it was a group heavy time
This guy is a Master Mason
And Alex believe that means that he's a 33rd degree
Mason
Answer
Is talking talking about the Hitman
Who builds houses for off
Before we get to the reveal they Prestige Alex has to talk about but
Stuff about how amazing the get away with murder
Of course
Unless you're amazing
Orla
Tubalcain
The mob
Pokemon
Running
Walked in Alaska
Yeah I got the Mason in distress sign do will Cain
So Alex is is going off on these like this grandmason stuff
Because he thinks he's got like a high-level Mason on the phone and they're going to be able to commiserate but also the guy
You started listening to Alex's show it started to wake him up and he's thinking maybe he's involved in an evil organization
So I'm going to try and lay this track that this guy is been going to be able to sign off on
As a high-level Mason
Unfortunately
He's not
When I said masturbation I was talking about blue eyes
Degree Master Mason
The great I Have Nots
Going into
The higher-level sup
32nd
I had many offers
Scion
Weekly
The Grotto
I had offers to go
Starwood
Which shot
Primarily
Arm of the basin
Going to stock price
Brighton
Thanks but
Little voice
Myself okay
Useful idiot here in the trenches
Fraternity
I ask myself
Useful idiots
The tenants that are preached
Need to be wonderful
What is it is it a veneer
Dark
No
Really
Totally
Duh
That's the human devil
There's a Zoe's principality
Yeah so Alex realizes it is guy isn't very deep into the Masons
Blow his mind
I can make up whatever I want
No right
That's the funny thing about him only being level 3 is like
He doesn't know
I already believed it could be anything
She's already suspicious of in like coming around to thinking like a maybe Alex is onto something
Oh hey guess what
Level 77
Even start
Christopher Avila
What organization invents 300
60 degrees
That's too many degrees way too many if you're if you're going to complain about a generation growing up with too many
Participation trophy
If a Masons give out a degree for everything you did for me a drink he's 38-degree now
Well and and you got to think like
Imagine the bureaucracy
Like
Imagine the micromanagement in like
Get this if you have 360 that you have to
A good 290 of them are not for human human complete David's right
Are they the ones deciding if you chart is a mess
This raises a few important question
And that is
Do the demons start at level 77 or do they have to be like level 123
Are you
In the same level one classes maybe a couple of demons in there you know like you've got six humans and then there's two or three demons right with you
Or just jealous cuz you like all those m************ can get past that.
From going level 60 70 6277 murder you have to kill yourself so detailed
Right is it a transformative right into the 77th degree
Questions are unanswered because Alex
Could be one reason that could be one reason
I do love it when Alex is like I'm going to get back up from this guy I got a caller on the line it's going to be great and then Erie
Realizes I just make up whatever I want this person doesn't they don't know shitt
Very very zabumba to Freed of their though there is another Freedom that I I did definitely hear whatever
The guy was like only a third degree and I was offered the other thing Alex was chomping at just like I could
Say Annie
Hang right now I'm mixed with disappointment
Because like
If the guy was
You know somewhere in higher levels or was willing to pretend to be
Andy was going to sign off on Alex's like yeah you can just stress
Or whatever is it that would give him so much like credibility to this b*******
Imagine if it was
Imagine if the tables were turned in this guy was like
Not not
I'm at the 77th level here's the problem
Humans can't get past that that would
That would freak Alex out beyond all reason
Well I'm going to guess at that point you would shift
The story somehow
I can't have the rule that I cannot do that voice right now
A disaster
You're under the weather but we got it we got it somebody on the injured report
Questionable for today
So Alex gets another collar and this guy has an interesting question about
Planet X
I want to dance
Ask you about
Planet X
Is it for real what is
And I also wanted to
Shell if you could
Who killed
John F
Two big ones
Two big ones at the same time
Hey what about this other planet that secretly there and while you're at it
Gourmet baby you don't answer maybe you do but why
Might as well throw the question
Asking Alex about JFK who did it
The impulse
Impulse buys I picking up some gum
So here's Alex's take on Planet X
Planet variant which was an issue
Titanic
Last Summer
I know what you didn't do last summer
A clock
Stop
Yeah so you understand I can't I can't follow that whatsoever it wanted to hoax into it's also
Closer than they expected it to me it's both of those things
It's not the 10th Planet it's Mars or something and it's really a metaphor for the occult Rising
Astrologist
Along with religious sect
But he seems to know everything about everything which is a Hallmark of a
Cool person
His name is
Text Mars
So I think he does know everything about
Both technology and Mars
That makes perfect
Htx at EXE
And Marrs so
Probably probably
So yeah
Play Planet X was b******* that was
Made up by zecharia sitchin by because he was funded by The Rockefellers
Chesnaught
Alex is going to need to substantiate that somehow
Butts
He's been writing but this s*** since 1976
But you think that's when the 12th Planet first came out
Book
They began that series
That was based on like Erich von daniken s***
So like bright
Yeah the Chariots of the Gods is in her mixed in with this and that was like in the six
I don't know I don't know how all of that is supposed to be like
A predictor of
The rise of the
Cult in 2000
M3
It didn't seem to do anything
I think I think what it is
Is VM
Bishan
Of naming your book the 12th
Planet
Cuz that skips over both the 10th on the 11th like
We're just assuming already that you know about those
Secret plan
Like that's what sticks with you
A guy with
With ambition bigger than the Stars
Rice if you will
Yeah I mean I'm not proud to admit this I have read the 12th Planet
Yeah
Planet Smoothie
I wish I remembered
It is not something that is stuck out in my mind as like a mop
Tiamaa is one of them I think
Always bad when you name something
Tiamat that's that's a sign that you're not really paying that much
Trying to look this up here
CT
Then give me a breakdown of what these planets are
Weather is like okay so like there's an aburu right
It like hit Tiamat
Enantiomers
Broke
I don't f****** remember who knows
I just worried about how the acronym is going to work
Mnemonic device
I seen it like my very Earthly
Mother and then I don't know what happens after Pluto
Sure or you might have to interject it into the cuz it might be closer at times
Here's another thing
In the meantime since he wrote that book Pluto no longer a planet
True Galaxy 11
Planet
Unless
He's also found another one
You never know
So yeah Alex was was cool
But he knew that this was bulshit he wasn't going in with the end of the world claims or anyting
Calendar
Years from now
Goriyan gallan
That was easy for Alex to call out because that's what he does to
I was going to say it's almost like somebody predicting a financial collapse or perhaps
A summer of Rage every single year or month
Right we just had our calculations a little bit over the FedEx something to stop them
Or the Rizal diesel fuel in the United States like to eat
3 weeks with no diesel
It's been awhile since we've lost all of the diesel fuel in all the trucks
Falling apart
But even like to take the other stuff like the the globalist are about to make their move they've made their move
Do you not like the FEMA camps are coming it's it's right around the time
I am his audience just has I don't know why but don't know Limited
Tolerance words being like Oh Yeah
You managed to stop it or something
Respectful to point out the scam you're doing
And blame other people in the same way that all psychics and mediums are always like listen
I get it
You think that psychics and mediums are b******* because the other ones are but I'm the real one you know
That kind of thing where it's like if everybody else is b*******
So where are you
What's a little bit disrespectful but on another level and also
Kind of seems to indicate a little bit that maybe Alex has perception of himself is that he is not
That
Which is sad
If that's the case that is a bummer
But yeah could be
31 Westcliff Dr and it's Alex responding to this guy's second question
Which is the JFK question
And
This
Kind of bummed me out because I don't I last 2003 episode we we had a little conversation about the admitted Widow
The Lady Bird Johnson
Liechtenstein
The goalposts a little bit here on this episode
Cornered
I ordered the hit
Leslie Butler is involved
I'm sorry what you doing
John in North
North Carolina
That's quite a number of reasons
Apparently why JFK was killed by the bankers
People didn't kill.jfk considering there were so many reasons to do was like murder on the Orient Express it was like
Everybody had a reason
Tomorrow could have gotten to the bottom of this
Widow to lbj's mistress
Seems like Alice's really sweat the small stuff
Like talkin accurately and say things
I was referring to Madeline Brown a woman who has been widely discredited by people who have looked at their claim
She alleged that she was at a party in Dallas the night before the assassination with folks including but not limited to
LBJ Nixon and J Edgar Hoover
But
Concrete evidence
All of these people except
Nixon outside of Dallas that entire night
They could not have been there and
Nixon's whereabouts were accounted for in Dallas
Isaiah if you got those guys in the same room in Dallas
That's the room I'm assassinating
The meaning is essentially impossible to have happened which is where the threat to kill JFK was said to have happened
You can kind of see how this
Pokes a gigantic hole in her story
Because it's
Then the other know how that statement work
Subsequent investigation of her past has shown that she's been of a fraud person
Haven't been a convicted
Elderly relative in 1988
She's kind of like a JFK era Larry Nichols type so it makes sense that she and Alex will get together and
Stirrup the b*******
Together but that's the admitted Widow that sucks
It would suck more if like ladybird for real
Unusual then we be in Nelson medley being Mandela effect territory
Was actually there
One sign that things have changed
I would imagine
I would imagine if ladybird been on Alex would not stop talking
Going about it even to the present so
That should have been a clue for us but that was that did not happen
Bi-Rite that one
God what would that be like if a city like even and I mean even if we could teleport
Benefiting
I'm just supposed broadcast end up back then
Vicky Blake
What what
Vice president like what first lady goes on what show would be as insane as lady bird show
Hillary
Nancy Reagan showing up anywhere would be fine
Come on Hillary baby
Tipir tipir going on
Howard Stern
Never go against turd might be as crazy as that
Uncle Luke Luke Skywalker from 2 Live Crew had a podcast
Listen to the hell out of that
Heading to yes I would lose my s***
Yeah that would be Luke Skywalker
Yeah well on account of there's a very famous name
Kmart
2003 episode
Some shady s***
Clan member goes essentially under review
Call Urban talk about the baby Jesus because of the Jewish influence in the media
Here's by here's my feeling on how the calls went on that one
The guy opened with
Chuck Norris can't say things because of the Jewish media
The clan guy was like well obviously I'm going to call later and then once the clan guy called the Mason guy was like well the Mets
Masons have to be Representatives at client's going to show up on this
Right
Right it's a regular old Cascade of cause and effect
Domino of
Group members needing representation
Yeah and I'm just sad that he didn't have a fourth hour back at this point because that was when the Illuminati
Body would have called in
Atlantica water
Eminem
230 3rd degree Mason Beaman
The Daughters of the American Revolution would have been a good way to go neck
Text you know he's into the next one before you get to the Illuminati
Now we got to go with like the was that the Council of twelve
That Bill Gates is a member of maybe I'll of 12
You know we got to go we got a
We got to escalate this hard
We have to go to like
Super Elite
Organizations
That maybe don't exist in our very mysterious
Here's the ultimate Terror I have with your witch
Is that
Based upon the level of magic that you have displayed so far
I'm terrified that you're going to alter the universe in such a way that the next 2003 episode we did he has a literal inter
Interview with the Devil
Like well surprise
He's been bitching about this guy in the present
Guess who shows up in the past
What is the devil calls in
Collar bone
I got this disease coming up
20 years that I got Aur the spokesman for it by Fred
Say hi
Costume dude I was worried
Well let's hope it doesn't come to that but be prepared
Come to this but will be back
What's up episode
Indeed we do it's knowledge right.com
Royals on Twitter
We aren't winners at Dollar General Store fights
I will be back but until then I'm needle of Leo and bcx Clark I am the
Discount of DayQuil
What
Biking
Alex
Color