I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Need
College vype.com
Everyone welcome back to fight knowledge I am Jordan and unfortunately Dan is
Not with us
Today
He is still under the weather with
An undisclosed but
Non life-threatening illness
So luckily we have the incredible Ace Attorney Morgan
Stringer joining me today
How are you
I'm good
It's
I guess if my moniker I've gotten is Ace associate but they made the same thing so
Turn the video game
I think I may have been thinking Harvey Birdman attorney at law that could be
Might my only reference to law is Harvey Birdman and then I think there was a dancing baby on
Ally McBeal one time
That is what I've got
I mean that's a good place to
Start so
Well I apologize for getting your Appalachian wrong but
Thank you so much for joining me today I suppose the first thing that we should talk about if you
You don't mind
Is an update on Alex
Six bankruptcies circumstance
What's the most recent information
So
Do you know
You're you're wearing Jordan of how you get really mad
When the media reports things about Alex and then it turns out to not really be that thing
Me
Good Heavens no even-keeled fan of Cullman quiet
B I do
That's why I wanted you to start right here because I assume something is wrong
Wild crazy wife
Missing that tornado with energy but
So speaking of that. I had the same thing where Iowa
I'll have that same reaction when I see the Press get these things wrong about you
Is formation figures
Pop culture figures
And also
With the law it really frustrates me how
You know we do have a lot of good legal reporters
Was Williamson
She's done a great job on this but
Of course
A lot of other people just need to stop
But they need to stop so
Frustrated because I see the headline and I see some tweets
You know that of course have 50000 likes on them by this
Dwight saying
Oh absolutely Alex doesn't have to pay the one-and-a-half billion-dollar judgment or he does have to
To pay that one and a half billion dollar judgment and a judge has you know
Taking away his ability to fight it
And course
That's not what happened
At all
So I thought I was crazy
Actually cuz I was saying well you know this
This Outlet is saying it just happened and I don't remember that happening how about you know blacked out somehow and
Remember something different
And no it turns out I was right
So it's a considers like there is a consent judgment in place
Which means that both Alex
And the plaintiffs are green
Everyone's in a green
Okay
Wow okay first off that's that's a monumentous thing that you just said
Yeah so what happened is the families who have already had their cases heard
Those cases they have lifted the stay on that
But the only things better left or I guess with formal entry of judgment in the Texas case which that case is already
Ben
You know basically is already done
And it's just have a judge can interpret judge
And dad in Connecticut
The only two motions left our Norm has emotion of remitted her which means he wants
The judge to reduce
The Judgment in the Connecticut case
Because my number is big I wish I was exaggerating. Ray sippin
But
In anyway when you're looking at a number like 1.5 billion honestly I feel like that's a reasonable a
Ask just to be like
This number is bigger than I understand I mean yes and we divided by 15
People invent
You hear you know everything that happened and you here but you know testimony in that courtroom
I can see where some people say oh that's not even enough
Oh totally
Totally
That was one of the things that I was thinking about it and whenever the verdict was about to be handed down is
You know before the Texas trial even happened I said
If I think it should be in the
Ballpark of 250 million or something along those lines
And it's like
How could a reasonable person though
Get to a number that big
Like I can't even understand what a million dollars is
In my real life
Let alone a billion
You know
Yeah well you're kind of right on the money there when you're talkin about you know
People like Robbie Parker who did get about
I want to say
Total amount
What's 200 million
But
Including
Peter doesn't
And everything
Steaks out but
But yeah so that's not what happened what happened it though is that the judgment
Has been lifted onto those cases just at 4
Procedural issues
You should go forward Norm is also has a motion for a new trial which
Everybody knows Norm even knows it those his motions are going to get denied
But basically the bankruptcy court is saying
Yeah those judgments and go ahead and be entered and then you can proceed with the appeals process
Windows
Now the Fontaine case and the Posner case those are still
So I'm yeah that's that's what's happening there it was not a judge saying
Up Alex has to write a check tomorrow you know and that that's that's what I feel like a lot of people
Got wrong here and also I did want to say this hasn't come up yet it has
Time to come up in the background of the
Conversations as I've kind of read between the lines
Listen to the
The attorneys
These hearings with
Lopez
The bankruptcy court but
Bankruptcy code section 52
Actually prevents a debtor from being discharged for any debt for
The willful and malicious injury by the debtor to another entity or to the property of another in
So actually hopefully malicious injuries cannot be discharged in bankruptcy regardless
And I think this is going to be litigated on it
Discounts but I would say
You know the punitive damages which had to be awarded
If a were if you know the
The jury found that he
His conduct was willful and malicious
I mean
Speaks to itself right
I really just think that I'm busy
These bankruptcies know the personal one and the company one
Is Alex Delany
Because what I noticed was when I watch
The latest Texas
I saw mark
Essentially saying okay well we're fine to go ahead and schedule Fontaine and Posner because we can proceed against Alex
Individual
And
I get that low and behold December 2nd he files for person
Bankruptcy
But I think that this isn't going to end up backfiring
I think his strategy
Here is that he
He is going to
To try to
Yo Drive East fam
Movies out
We're going to have to go through the whole Bank
See processors you know creditor committee and a personal
And there's that you know
We're going to have to submit plans
Answer three paid data
Negotiate
All that out
Between all the creditors
The company won
So I
Think what he Evander see if he'll spray
And I think what Alex
Is doing here is he
He's trying to
Number one by more time for
From self and number two
Where are these families down hoping that they'll settle
Brightright so essentially whenever we read any reporting from the news for probably than
Next year too it should just be taken with a grain of salt that means
It's still going on
I mean really
Still a struggle
Any kind of
You know it's illegal reporting I feel needs
You know he would ask
Behind it you know it it's just I don't understand what's going on with legal reporting and of course I'm an attorney so I'm
Picky about that but it's still
I just wish people would henagar running into your running into a big problem with legal reporting and so far
Far as
The people who read news want something to have happy
And in the law things are always
About to happen once that motion gets filed
Then we'll see you in a couple of weeks
I said once that couple of weeks happen
Well I will file tomorrow
Vita like that Scott
Mistrustful
It is I and II definitely can see that yeah I mean there is a lot doesn't make
Splashy hat
Right right
But there are some that some things to at that you
That they could have actually reported
Like the fact that Alex was popping in and out of his latest hearing it was virtually
Virtual on zoom and he kept you know alright being in and out you know
What was what was he doing popping in and out I have no idea and I don't know if it was his Zoom
Being glitchy but yeah
I do I have no idea I think he was just so you know
Again it shows his lack of
Seriousness
Cases as usual
And yeah his attorney actually claimed
.
He need a basically did the I need money
Argument
So we
What are the four reasons why I think this
This Dom is because now Alex is having to expose his fine
That's right you have
And I think this was one of the dumbest things
He could do when he filed for bankruptcy the first time I said
I can't believe
If he did that
So Jose are saying that his
Initially was saying his salary is 20000 every 2 weeks
Company bankruptcy that's a normal salary for most people
Mosta Average Joe's putting on their hard hats
Going to work everyday weeks is regular right
I don't make a frac
About much which you know maybe baby I should be practicing law more like normal but you know is a whole other
Brat but
Yes / judge
Did Joshua Jackson probably buy some local insurance if I want to work work work
Exactly
Yes if it judge was asked though to force Free Speech systems to pay Jones 54
Every two weeks
And the judge said okay well I want to address this later and you're going to have to submit it to me more than just
I need money
So
So if I so if I understand correctly
Alex
Is bankruptcy lawyer
Said to a judge
How about pay me
Almost three times as much every two weeks and the reason is cuz I would like three times as much every two weeks
That's what Alex himself was saying
Yes.. Amazing paid out from
From Infowars
Free Speech systems
And Alice's lawyer also made the argument that if this was denied
That Alex will have to find more work
God
Yes
Please
Please I want to see Alice's sidegig I want to see a psychic
If if you could watch Infowars broadcast
And then getting an Uber with Alex Jones I think that would be the ultimate in
GoodLife really
Which brings me to a question I wanted to ask you Jordan what is the funny or job
What is the funniest second job that you think Alex
Can take
I mean
The obvious answer would be mine
Because to sit to see him naturally he would have to be
In the most public of spaces
With the only restriction being you can't talk
Of course
That one's a good start
I think the other funny side job would be the person who
Feed lions and then accidentally Falls in in an Indiana Jones
That would be cool
Batman I mean he almost was a movie star so yes it was
See you there Star-Lord or being eaten by lions and it Indiana Jones movie I'm fine with both
Truly
But that's it that's you bring up something you have been watching almost all of these hearings if not all
It was them and regularly live-tweeting these out have you been
Have you added literally been all of the hearing
I think I may have because I did get a heads-up from an attorney saying
This is just a
Scheduling hearing
You don't have to be here
Say off. He was very very nice about it but he was letting me know basically this is a meeting just
Schedule something in the future you know just saying it's going to be 10 minutes tops which I appreciate it but also
Man all these people are aware of me
Which procedure next week is going to be
Normandy mtume you got me advice for me
Buffalo
That's like the most inverted deepthroat that there ever could be like there is a secret connection you have between
The lawyers but
In the in the parking alley it's just
Will see you tomorrow
There is actually which I you know I've been with all seriousness I have been thanked by it
And I can't believe it they found anything of value as to what you know
I've said but basically yes so I
You don't know
Told you you know
Earlier we're
I'm not a big fan of a lot of legal reporting
Answer so I'm not a fan of a lot of
Legal analyst in Long crime was covering another first
Or babe actually covered Connecticut trial but I knew they're going to ashamed
People job on that and also I knew a lot of Bad Axe
Jurors were probably going to
Talk about the Texas trial and hello poor Alex
He's being railroaded and I really do not want that to happen
So what I do because I don't know something is wrong with me
Was I decided to throw myself into the abyss and I said okay I'm going to wash this entire trial and
And I'm going to
Just say what's happening and then give my legal
Analysis where I think I have some or give you know Otis
What I would do or
This is why I think Mark Bankston
Finish doing Acts
Send here's
You know
The wherewithal is probably screwing up and needs
Do you know change tactics
Which happen
Inconsistent
And yet mystifying all the same
May I doubt that was also a challenge I was watching you know especially with the Connecticut
Trial just thinking
I can't even get in your head to see what you're trying to do
What's up with Norm Norm when you were watching the
The Texas trial
You can see right now is it is a professional who's trying to do a la job
If you will
In my in my dumb way of saying it and Norm seems like he was just throwing caution to the wind
Drop-in smoke bombs and falling asleep all over the place right
Oh man it was like
Oh man the ending when he did that litigators prayer I asked
Sandaroo
Torres who I work
Format the firm butt
I got Andrew Torres is my personal attorney according to a Twitter conversation that I
Considered legally blind
I don't know that but he should do well it doesn't apply to me
Not yet not yet but I just young
But
Yeah so Norm it was just babbling and I asked Andrew I said is visit thing I've
Never heard this in my life please tell me this isn't a thing
And Andrew said
When I told him about it he said I have no idea what the f*** that man was talking about
Animals are just wet you know what's going south which I always say juries are mysterious creatures you don't want to you know
Get inside their heads too much inside yourself out because who knows when groups of people come together you know what
Care about versus what they're not going to care about that's why I really like
If a jury question
Texas
But anyway so
But you know it's going
When the jurors were you know avoiding eye contact
Switch Norm
And he is away
Oh man that was it that was just so rough and
It is a little bit like Erykah Badu
I can clearly
I have brought all of you shame
And you don't want to be associated with
No
Here's why I am correct
Yeah but I also think that this
Strategy
She was dumb because there are trustees
Assigned a bankruptcy case
Suzanne
There's a whole conversation about Alex's is going to get on the stand in line and we know how often you know perjury is it
Prosecuted especially for a civil case
That's right
They are for bankruptcy
Brought on a bankruptcy yet there are people assigned in every bankruptcy case
It's called a trust
And what they do is basically, most of the time they're just overseeing to make sure of a bankruptcy court
You know it's going along smoothly and everything
Working according to procedure
But in
These kind of cases in the trial of Alex Jones it is not a most of the time scenario
It is not at all because of the types of bankruptcy that
He has filed here
You have a little bit more supervision here from the u.s. trustee
And basically what they can do is
It's their job essentially one of their major jobs
Is to look for fraud and make sure fraud isn't being done
And if they see
Suspected they refer it to but
Department of Justice
And it gets investigated or
Oftentimes Prosecco
And a lot of times when that happens they uncover a bunch of other crime
Because chances are if you're lying to the bankruptcy court you're probably not
You know I've been up
Only open up on your books right so if you're one of these trustees at this point
You have to be like
Rubbing your hands together with maniacal Glee or something like that right like
You look at everything Alex has done so far and you go well
I I don't know if I can
Fall asleep without hitting fraud
On the way down
Like it is
Unreal right
Yes and you have to disclose you know he's different assets which I think
To me I was thinking well I would be
Hang up especially close attention
I'm here because
It's going it might indicate where he has hidden some of his ass
And a yasso
You deaf I was bewildered
When he did I mean
It's in your another delay tactic and I think
You trying to get the
Families again
And to settle in
Rachel elassar about
Just so he goes
This way but
I mean
His behavior has been completely shameful
Call abs
It Beyonce
Hiiraan
Why would you settle with him
No it ain't it feels a feels a little bit like
Who is is almost pot committed to this strategy of like
String it out as long as I pause
Can
And then maybe Hail Mary they'll they'll get tired but
I mean at this point it's hard to imagine that being
Impossible
Yeah it's going to end you know I know
We talked about earlier how it feels like there's a motion to you know
Do another motion later and things like that
Yeah and the end that's this is whereabouts going to you know
And
Yeah we'll see where and also Alex wanted to join
Is the bankruptcies
Together and have them
Play together in this way
You know whatever applied to the personal bankruptcy would apply to the company
Trustee
I'm not a bankruptcy lawyer but
I used to work for a firm that did some of it
I have never seen a trustee object to join
Bankruptcy
And the reason obviously
Because they're not like
What the
What you join them for is so that it can go a lot smoother and easier and both trustees
So wasn't just a personal bankruptcy trustee but the one and it for his
Corporate
Bankruptcy John did and said yeah what that guy said basically
I've never seen two trustees file you know the emotions like that but
They're essentially saying No this is actually going to make it more chaotic because what applies to Alex personally
May not apply to accompany person
Under the law and vice-versa and your
Just going to Aldi
This confusion which
You know I'm willing to bet Alex also was hoping
What he could work
His Advantage because
Eventually is at the end of the day
Destructive agent of Chaos
Why not too bad in a bank
In bankruptcy for
As well
And the trustees
These are you know very strongly indicated
Absolutely
Play not this is not how they should be done
And the question I think a lot of people have as far as you know you you put a point to that this
Will end
At a certain point
I think
The big question
For most people is
The way that Alex is doing this now he's clearly stringing it out even more he's as you said
You know he's doing this
The trustees are saying no
At what point
Does biscuit stop.
For him
Because it's clear to everyone involved right that this is not
Nothing is in good faith
Rhino absolute
And I think
Drink.
This
I think another thing that dreamy today
Ace wise
Bear
I cannot stand
Grifter lawyers
I can't stand grifters
I also can't stand right-wing weirdos and you had this
You know
And then also I
Cover cases that have to do with pop culture so you had this intersection of all these
The intercept
Weirdo
Bye
Yeah this is a very specific Venn diagram that you are dead center in exactly
Exactly
Play and
Yeah I think that we have this
We have a situation where
I think people finally said enough is enough
You know we saw this with Rudy Giuliani being recommended that he
Disbarred
I think Bar Association
Since I finally had it of attorneys acting like they can disregard the rules
They can even
Willfully break the rules
And guess what
Here's how much it's going to cost
And it's going to be less but has you actually
Dissipated
Engaged
And I think that their Wall Street receives a fine that's one tenth of what they made
Heat off of the crime and you're like
Well that's that's just a cut
You know you're just taking a tent off the top that's fine
And I think this was a big concern with the with
Judge Gary Gamble
Judge Myers
Call her
Affectionate
I need some policy won't communities that are very very fond of both judges blood has
You know fun Texas
Mom energy the other one has fun New England Aunt energy it's
You got four judge Bella's butt
What a weird world we live in a strange world
So
Yeah judge Campbell was talking about you.
These kind of principles and how
She said that the cap should not apply she was going to go ahead and
A judgement
For the entire thing because
She takes her oath seriously she took an oath to the Constitution
Fusion she took an oath
But to also do what
Spare
And she said
This case is unique
This was a horrible thing.
What happened here
And this is the only recourse for bees fam
And I just
I'm so glad that somebody is
Is finally saying
You know
At the end of the day just
This is also about
Fairness
And what is right
And you don't want to incentivize
Go to say oh well if I just don't participate in Discovery
I can just
Drag this thing out alone and this is the most
The biggest number I'm going to have to
Write on the check
Yeah absolutely don't want to encourage that and again I think people are just tired of these
Please griffor lawyers
You know back when I was in Lost
School
I would complain about lawyer Joe
Jack's Rio everybody thinks
For such bad guys and now that I am an attorney
There aren't enough
Jorge
Evil lawyer joke that is my decision and other
Mark and I are you know not to compare myself to the great Mark Bankston but
You know I think that we engage with the law and a very similar way
And
Yeah it's just okay well
Here's the heart of a matter and here's what it is and we should do what's fair and what's right
And
You should not reward p
People who
You know consistent Libre
Break the rules
It's just basic stuff when you when you when you take a look at it at maybe I just
It's been brought up a Venn diagram but when you take a look at what has David ultimately strangely enough brought us all
Together
And the all of the lawyers in yourself and everybody
Is
Is the thing that
Drives us
Switches that
This s*** is unfair
This is wrong
And at the end of the day all of us I feel like are just
Unable to
To not watch that
In the same way that
Everybody looks at us and goes it at
Get your insane
For recording 705i episodes
I'm sure people look at you and say you're insane for watching all of these hearings
Or and I know it drove Mark and saying to watch all of that Infowars
That's what it is it's it's this is unfair
This is bulshit oh yeah do I truly have had that thought of you know
Am I
Am I the crazy one and then I'll see Norman be like you know at least I'm not doing that
Bright and I did listen to an episode of norms podcast for V
It was all know I've ever had to do for work I got to say
And I used to work at a combination Quiznos Baskin-Robbins in a gas station in Mississippi so
You know take that for what you will
Those are the most terrifying words anybody's ever spoken to me
Mississippi to Maine and it would be slightly more terrified
It was very
Surprisingly
But if you made it for Southern Gothic
But I guess I think that does Sprint
These things are what he know does drawers be
Because you know what
Tomorrow Queen
People like me it's
What ultimately drove me into law school
Is that at the end of the day I was always a kid
You know what he would say to your parents that's not fair
And I'd say 12
And I would respond
Why isn't
And nobody knew what the state about you know like you don't exactly
Kind of disturbing to hear from a child if I'm being honest but
I probably lost all my serotonin by the time I was ten so
But it's fine so yeah
I I got it way more trouble with that question
I think it was a t
Futuristic
To bake
And they said you know life is not fair
I said something along the lines of
Well then why aren't you doing anything about it
And that got me in real trouble because it can makes you confront that like why am I not doing anything about it and
Exactly going to be his hearings or without I'm not acting like that
Leonardo
Substantively changing things
But I have been able
To help promote
Happy family stories I have been able
I didn't think anybody would
What are you know what I was going to live-tweet like maybe one day
If somebody out there found it you
Useful I was going to come
Continue it but it turns out a bunch of people have
You know found value in it
Some people have even found we've all appreciated that I followed along with
With your tweets
As well you know
It's it's
It is I don't want to say impossible
But it is extremely difficult for me to watch a legal thing
What happened
Without like screaming at
At the judge wearing a robe I just thought you know it's all the sudden in my head I'll be like
Why are you wearing a robe this is the Matrix this is all a simulation you don't like I do it'll lose
I'll lose my mind so hopefully what you do
I think we should have shorts and courtroom
I think that need to be venex
The next cause I take up
I don't I don't know why that got me but whatever whenever she was like
And I saw somebody wearing shorts today and we do not wear shorts in my courtroom
I couldn't understand life
For like an hour
With this is just a room
What are we doing here is a lie
Services a courtroom
Going to be the problem when it comes to justice is that would happen
This is your being dragged out
Well exactly that's that's enough
Speaking of speaking of that you also understand that that is doing a lot of work in that
I mean speaking of
Lawyers being trouble you followed along with right now
Disciplinary hearing to write
Yes to an extent
Although it's been
It's been very muddy today
Everybody has been money that's all
Newman Normand you know what happens where and it's just
Yeah I I'm not sure exactly
What
Got one I have not been following as
Closely
But
I did find so far for the last Texas
Trial as well get a rental has his own attorney which is never a good situation when you haven't
Nesting doll of attorney
You know attorney with an attorney is always felt
Wrong to me like yeah I don't know why
Yeah it's I mean I would never represent myself a say a lawyer who represents
Some cells has a full for client
But
But also Infowars
Has has
A new attorney that they debuted at that
Hearing his name is actually Chris Martin
It's not the lead singer from Coldplay
But again there's like seven people in the world so honestly like who
Who's to say this how do you how do you take that job now
How do I just take that job now you you are a person who is taking law jobs
Is right at no point in time have you watched
The most disgusting display of legal hatred
That's ever been gone on a bit like gas
That's my next gig right what is happening
Yes it was Christopher Martin he is representing Infowars but they said when all when he sent
He's at a bit last Texas hearing
Reynolds said he is still the attorney on the Posner in Fontaine case
So
I'm not sure exactly what's all going on there but I suspect that there will be
Be some kind of dish
Disciplinary action toward probably Normandin all at this
Particularly with the Saints
Behavior
All that just what what you know I've heard I've heard sections and I understand sanctions
Meme
Money right
So sometimes they do so
One of the first things I did work
With Andrew is actually got sanctions again
Another attorney which I was
Brand new out of law school so that way
What is a band practice
I'll probably longer than I've been alive
But
So you got your first taste of blood on day one yes what was the
The Vampire Diaries quiz your blade
The lawyers are vampires in your a vampire that hunts vampires this makes perfect sense.
I understand everything.
Yeah and I don't necessarily enjoy like I don't want to go I'm not saying that every attorney is like
And every attorneys bad it or bad I even like pursuing but there are particular attorneys who are truly just being
Absolutely Wild
You need to call hyperbolic
Speeches by stock-in-trade so nobody's
W2 concern
Well I'm always and you know I I've been labeled a Firebrand in the in the past which you know some people say that's a bad
And I always take it as a compliment means I'm passionate and good label are about my clients
But
Yeah so he is again yeah judge Maya even pointed this out and said
You are 26
Teeth lawyer
To enter an appearance in this case
I thought she was exaggerating no
He is the 16th lawyer
And he did
He at that hearing did not know if he was going to be joining run all on that
On the pasta Infante
Cases
And so I was like
So what does that mean is that is there a possible 17th lawyer that my enter into this thing and judge my even said when he
He said yes I'm aware I'm like this
She said well you know what they say about being the third or fourth lawyer on a case
Right like like why would you do this
To yourself to get out of what they say about being the 16th lawyer on the case though is we've got a great baseball team
And we're really going to take it to the other associates
So you know there's two ways to go on this
Yeah it reminds me of you know a scene from Arrested Development where they talk about you know and open bear
Opening up a marriage
Buyasession riverworks
But it might work
For us
And so I'm imagining so with your lawyer saying
I did work for bed
Maybe I can do it
Bright
Right when you're watching this this lawyer talk to the judge
Can you see sense of
Dread or Zayed like
I couldn't go into that situation without feeling like there's a Sword of Damocles literally hanging over
Right I'm the 16th lawyer I'm like
Henry the 8th
9th wife
It's not going to go well
You know exactly I was
You know I a binky button
Attorneys
Basin and
Bellaire West
Balling
In Ferrari all them were even
Shiocton
You know them bringing in
16th lawyer now
You know who is honestly I'm kind of shocked Alex hasn't asked me in this
I would do a better job but I know everything about these cases because I've been to every hearing
You know cuz I'll at you know it's funny whenever he'll have a you know lawyer that's like oh well you know I need to get caught
What up on everything and it's like wow I'm caught up and I'm not even doing this for a living
Which I didn't like showhome case better than you do and I have proof I have no
Again yui sword of how
You know maybe you might
Has a bit deranged
But I mean I found it useful and also midnight owl so I do my day job at night and
You know I and I just thought this was important
And I knew that people were going to
Screw it up when they talked about this and I think that this
This is a case that is
Really setting valuable precedent
I think that there are ways
Is that we can tackle
Disinformation
And believable world and I actually think this is a really good way to do
Because V
Ennis you know
These people who aren't public
Figures are now being you know dragged up
Dragged through the mud by B's badass
And anyhow it is about time somebody stood up and
Do something and say this is enough
It is a horrible process and I would understand why somebody would
Choose not to purr
Pursue that because I mean you seen how
Long this is going and how he's doing the bankruptcy
Shenanigans
Everything but
You don't know but eventually somebody's got to stand up to a bully
Which is what Infowars is
Send what a lot of these
Disinformation Outlets are
Bear bear bully
They're trying to
Cause people to be
Be harassed or trying to
Money off of
Hatred and a
Anger and Division
It's you know
Somebody Auto somebody ought to do something about that as I as I say and what we've said it we've said
Time and time again.
One of the things that we do
Despise the most about
A lot of the
The coverage of
That the trials are
Regarding
Sandy Hook families
That that simple sentence of like
The families are looking for 500 million dollars or something that the families are requesting $500 or something
Sing like that
And it is
Just such a simple signal that is just wrong which is there they're not requesting money at all
They're stopping this guy
You need them stopped and I need them stopped and they're doing that and money is how it happen
That's like it that's like saying you know the money is the sword
In this situation
Not something that they're requesting from
Yeah and it and that is that is it in
Interesting way a
To frame it
In that
You-do-it internet
It's not about the money
And
There's been people that have said
Things like oh well you know they sued
This person and that person and Albert Sue and Alex
I've seen comments at people's made about
Oh this is too far over this is
Greedy and the thing about it is
Yeah you're going to ask
Because you're probably not going to get what you asked
Or also
You're always in negotiation starting with I'll give you money that's not how that works
Exactly
And Anubis
With this Casey how you you are absolutely going to start off high
I and
The fact is like it's obvious
It shouldn't be these families are requesting money it should lead with how to
Speakable his behavior has been and that he needs to
To be held to a
Account
That's what you said I counted
Money is a way to we get to
Accountability
But you know there was this
Discussion of
Oh well
Ignore me then kind of hinted at this
And his argument
Well
No amount of money
To compensate for
The pain
And
It's like yes man but you know what that's what we have
We Can't Stop racing time and make Alex go undo the damage he did and I don't
I think he would if he was presented with that off
I don't think he wouldn't years ago we put you in the stocks and throw things at you but we don't do that anymore so you
You always money
Exactly that's what that's
Injustice that we have
And yes it is kind of weird and nebulous
When you start asking people okay I sounded dollar value to
You know pain and suffering because again those are abstract Concepts in your asking
Someone to put a concrete number
And yeah it does get it does get very weird and fuzzy and you know
Very philosophical and even esoteric they are but
That's what we have
And so does idea that these families are just out there trying to get money
It is absolutely ridiculous when really the story
Leading should be
This is what this man did today
This is what suffering that he
And he knew he was cause
And he did all of this so he could sell
It's
Yeah and so he could perpetuate his weird world
Yeah
I didn't enter you're absolutely right as far as the
The directions
Things are going
When you when you talk about how
These
People
Somebody needs to
To stand up to this
Is bullying you know
For the past
20 years there's been nothing
But positive reinforce
From
Fox News and right-wing media in general in regards
Just bully people bullying that's what people want they want that aggressive
Kind of
Attack on
And
This may be
One of the few times that any of us
Possible serious
Princess brautigan
I think it might be the first time Alex
Experiencing serious
Quinces and I think that we're seeing
You do a repeated what happened
It's right that that y'all have covered you know whenever his dad would get him out of
Apple right
I think that this is a large case of that I saw that one of the Truss
That apparent
We paid his bank
See lawyer
Believers personal
I have reason to believe that his dad
Not so
Yeah so
I did I mean ironically one of the most damning things that was said at the trial though came from his dad which II
Appreciate on
On a Shakespearean level
This man has gotten him out of trouble over and over and over again
And yet with one sentence
Put a nail in the coffin is what he said
I I got up I think I got up and cheered
When he said and I definition tape
We try to
You know it see what Alex was saying on that day we try to emulate spikes
I was already said that
That is a moment Inouye
The trial moment with with Mark
Well will live on forever as as one of the Great
La Mona
But that moment whenever Alex
Texas dad
I mean it was
It was borderline
You know you can't handle the truth levels
To Otis
I mean honestly you a time I don't know how if I was doing a case like that and that was to my advantage
I think I would have somehow done a backflip in
Decor and I cannot do a backflip I would have somehow figured it out I would have Mary Lou Retton all over that place
I would not be able to control myself
That's it that's really that's really interesting cuz that brings me to the next question I have written down
Have you ever done a backflip in court no I feel like it would be frowned upon you know
I do I have not Hail Marys though that is that it's always worth it ain't you know I would have my favorite ways to win
That is you know when that when the judge will say
The equivalent of
You're being wild right now Stringer
But you got a boy
Sober
But yeah I'm
I'm so thankful that I got
2B you know even
The small part that I got to
Play here
I've really enjoyed being able to
Elevator
Family stories and talk about them and
You know their testimony cuz that's something also I thought that way
It was really important
Going to do is
Is 2
Talk about the testimony be
Family talk about what they
What the harm was done
I think in that context again
Story isn't
That they're asking for
Her mom Eva story is
Good God
Whitney Blake is it this is most evil and when the most evil cases I've ever seen
It is
Especially when you compare
Hobby family
You have
Made
Positive
Contribute good in the
When they have every reason to say f*** off to everybody
Everywhere
And
India pay still manage
B+
And try to bring light
And try to
Be a better
Horse in the world
For good
And then when you compare that with you know the greed and awfulness and hatred of Alex
You know it is honestly astonished
No it's it's almost comically
Pause
Of Good and Evil
It's it's so Stark
That it makes you question
Yourself big
Real life is
Never this
And it is and I think that you find out a lot in litigation
Sunday night as I say the truth is somewhere in the middle right I mean sometimes you'll have
It is very often be a case where both sides are making good points I mean that's why you're litigating otherwise somebody with a
Previously settled
But it's a completely you know right if it were if it were easy we wouldn't f****** be here that
That's number one yeah
And so I
Yeah it I feel like
You so rarely get those kinds of
Oceans and I do feel like
This case is going
Set a precedent you know I think Norm is
Right in that aspect and that Liars are going to be taken to account
People who break the rules and
Used to participate there going to be
Be held to account
And people are going to
Point to this case
And
I get it I know that the facts of his case or really you know
Daycare so
But I'm hoping that this isn't
But I'm hoping that
Can build into
Where we are take
These people who
Perpetuate this amount
Carlmont of the world
You know you should not be able to lie
About people in the most horrendous of ways
Is and make money for
I feel like that's
Very
Simple
And yet everyone thinks of him
What's so crazy about it is that you have to say it
That's that shitt
But you should not be able to do that that shouldn't exist is a sin
In English right
I mean 48 it is but when you say it like that then I feel like people understand more what
This is really about
This is about someone taking you know the most
Personal aspect
Someone's life
Especially
Grieving
You know the death of a love
And the death of a child
Absolutely
And
Profiting for
And it's
I think that concept of itself is just
So gross
And I think you do I feel like
Maybe
I don't know if you and Dan felt and
Situation but sometimes being worried about the jury being red pills
Or
Yeah yeah yeah
There was there were plenty of times where you know when when the jury has Quest
Every time the jury
Comes back with question
There's the I think the the natural ends
To try and overanalyze
Why they would ask this
Ticular question
See if that gives a
Insight into what they may be thinking
You know Adam
And so there were a few
It made me think there were at least one or two people who
Hi I was not stoked about being
If that makes sense
Yeah that happened to me too and that's when I had to remember they might be
Beat right cuz you know they're also not allowed to talk to
To each other so they may be
Be trying to illustrate a point for other jurors
Or to clarify for her own sales and I think the guy that was asking is if Dario was a lizard
Person was just having fun
Sure you do you say that
But I think that you don't because we are so close and we see
Do CDs radicalized
People in out
What is audience
Steven
You know outside of Alex's audio
The concern of course is
Oh my gosh everybody around me is like completely radicalized and then
Anybody else is just not paying attention
And that's a huge problem
And we need to fix it and I feel like
This really gave
Restored a lot of My Hope and a lot of ways
Where
People said no
This is disgusting and wrong
I don't have to know everything about Alex
Jones Center
And that's almost more importantly they don't know everything about Alex
Like to me
Part of the the jury's
A verdict in the way that
Restore my you know similarly I had restored faith in Indy
Humanity
Is is that
Without
The constant
Phresher
The of Alex's Media or Fox News or who
Whomever
Coloring
The way you think about
In a in a neutral setting
Every human being
Can come to the
Conclusion that Alex is an ass
That's what was so beautiful about it you know he is legally an a******
It's
Yeah if
Autocomplete Covington Tennessee gas so I was going to say and it just at that that really helped
With and I think that the similar thing happened with the midterm
I think that
It's you do an understated argument for somebody to go
Hey look at this f****** weirdo
I feel like that was actually defective
Argument against people like Blake Masters and these weirdos and you know the fact that we're always like
Oh man everybody's just f****** pilled of a gills and it's like
Yeah my phone number country
But it is and that's definitely something to watch and something to be worried about but
Most of the country is like
These people suck
What the heck even talkin about half the time
Took
Listen
Herschel Walker
Still almost 18 took
The single least qualified
Most hypocritical
Political candidate in the history of the I think the world
To lose a republican race in Georgia
Yeah that that did that
I mean that still is complete I said that's still concerning but at least you know all is not lost
You know everybody
All is not lost because at least these people you know are are really thinking about the issues I did love how judge Bell
Was so thankful to the jury though
She kept calling him a very conscientious jewelry
And noting how much they were on time and everything and people were asking me you know.
Are Judges usually like them to reason like I don't mind cuz you be shot
I was supposed to be here today
Sure I mean you think of I think most people would think of courtrooms because they do
Do their best to avoid them
As places of almost soup
Supreme solemnity
So it makes sense to them to think of all the Jerry's always on time they're always on time in the movie
You know but didn't realize that
Jury duty so up when I show up
Vibrate
So
Yeah but I think that judge Bell is really hit the nail on the head because they were like I saw that there were jurors that were
Engaged
They were
You know I could see where people were taking notes and of course you know
It's very funny that was happening the Connecticut case to as well as a Texas
Case where one jar jar is trying to take notes on
Soma calyxes saying and
In a table
The Infowars broadcast
And they just give up
Yeah it's impossible to follow and that that really
You know
And I felt like a lot a lot of people were
Worried that they were
Would come pay wouldn't
Can grass be important
Sabetha penguin grass
Oh yeah he did some bad stuff but I mean
We shouldn't be
You know solely held
Responsible or he shouldn't be that was
Go for it I was really worried about that but I think in both cases
Now we've seen where
The jury has
That's really really thought about the
And
Given their not you know
And I think also
They
Don't like
The argument that Reynaldo and dorm
I put forward
Cuz also it treats them like they're
Stupid
I've also never seen cases where your jury
That
That the defendant
Called you dumb
Again
But why do you think we're all blue-collar hear what the what the f*** is that about excuse me sir
Jury is in a regular Daria saying that she believes that it's a simulation to Annex
Sad
Yeah
Home adwent when she when she said that to the most basic jury question like which I think was a question that was mess
Turn on the degree of you know
Are you a lizard person in there like a do you think that
You know this trial is staged then when she was like yeah to an extent I was just like
Oh man
That was yeah.
Teresa gave some of the greats
She's going to go on unsung
I think in the history books for how
Absolutely insane she was in that trial
There were so many moments where she agreed to something
That you were you looked at her dead in the eyes
Just thought if I were bleeding out she would laugh
Like she has gotten
Nothing
Or would refuse to answer the most basic questions
12 year old who's getting detention like I'm not answering it
Or you know it's
Not answering was the was the main goal of everybody at in Fort Worth
Is it felt like it did feel like that I mean I'm and I think that's also by Design
Find write you you know what the Brittany pause situation I think it was very much by Design hey
Only let her know these things
Even if she asked about x y and z
Let's not tell her
Right
Right right there very much was that I've also never seen a
Random criminal defense attorney service a corporate representative
I've seen things in these cases I I don't think I
I don't think two instead will
Probably see you again
I'm proud to say that we are the the reason that Britney pauses bro
Because of well I guess that this
I guess my wife tweeting and coming on now has officially maybe part of a knowledge fight Cottage
Mystery
Yeah see there you go you're a bottom feeder just like us welcome to the club
You know its first
Oh
Oh man that was
Again again I ended up something that also I don't I'm like if the plaintiffs attorneys are aware of me and you know and I'm
Pretty sure Norm name searches himself on Twitter
I believe that 100% about me
Necessarily want that happening but if he doesn't who cares
But
I don't care about his but I know he knows about me oh yeah great job Norm
I believe that was yeah cuz that you were talking about
The great job he did to which I quit that you I remember it
The great job Norm
Absolutely fantastic
Can I can I ask you where we're almost at an hour and I don't want to keep you too long so first off
Can I ask you where can people find you obviously you're part of the excellent opening arguments podcast
Podcast
And
I've also just launched a sub stacks
Tubi
The writing on that
I'm in the middle of a move
So it's been
It's been kind of dip
But yes I've done that to sort of like a come
Company
My parents
Where I
Pop lock on opening arguments
It's right talk about you
You know pop culture at law and I also
Information and
Debunk disinformation
About Casey
I'm hopefully I'll be having some more of my own adventure
Follow me on
Twitter
Can just find me
Stringer at
Excellent Bell it because of my Southern
My very thick southern accent
Which I'm sure you've met
Don't don't don't look up Ace Attorney that one's on me that was a huge mistake
I feel like kind of rings better but
Sounds good
You can feel it
Sawyer
So yes before before we go I do want to ask you
5 people one of the questions that people to ask us all the
The time after
6 years of
This nonsense
How do you feel like a defect
Did you as
A person in the way
You think about that
And I was wondering the the same for you because
When you immerse yourself in this kind of space the way that we have done it
It does change
So I was wondering what kind of feelings that are what kind of feeling of change do you have
That's it
Yeah but
That's a good question
And so I
You do not to be thank you to be so it is even asked very good questions but this is
A very very thoughtful
I
I would actually say not to be corny about it
But I would say it actually has I feel like made me a better lawyer and a better Communicator with
How
I talked about the law with
Because that's something I've I've actually even discovered I have a real passion
Is telling people about what's going on in these
Types of cases
Providing some sort of an owl
I mean I don't know nothing
It's early what that mean
But also its
And the fact that
I was
You know very
Responded about
The state of
Legal
And
You know thinking
It it seems like all these
There's
Just so many grifters and illegal
Super fashion and it feels like the only way to get ahead is to
To be one of these despicable
People
And here I am
Refusing but you know there's no
I felt like there was there was like no advantage
Professional unless
I'm honestly I started
Ghetto trying to
Sebastian.
And I
I still am
Hopefully always
Will be
But
I
Yeah I feel like I have gotten
Hope again
And that there are good at
That there are attorneys
Care about
And there are Judges
To care about what
Behringer
Justice and
And doing the right
Right thing
And holding pee
And there are jury
The people who made up
Madhuri's you know
Boohoo
Say no this is wrong
And also about
Punisher
That we are now punishing
Who break the rules
Are grifters
I feel like that has
Change and
Made me a lot more
About this
That I'm actually seeing
Consequences
How far of a bat
Where's it felt like
Before
They seem to
To be the ones
Advantage while every
Everybody else was yeah
I feel like my faith in the legal depression
The legal depression
I was about to say that is one of the most inspiring speeches I've ever heard until you ended it with legal depression.
What is a Bill Pullman made us love in Independence Day we're not remembering that speech right there aliens
Kill us all
Iraq
Crushing it you were right it higher the store
Good feeling
There's that there's a reason the words are similar
But I feel like my faith in the
Profession has been
Restored in the fact that people are interested in hearing
About what the families are saying
And
What in visit just about
Oh Alex comes in and it explodes on the stand and then we all make memes and laugh and then forget about how
Evil he is
That's right
Which I mean we don't have fun and I mean that's fine at the end of a day but
He does his weird Highwayman DJ
Stop and throw hatchets
Well he's drinking in the office
Christmas Eve right but at the end of the day it is
The bankruptcy goes away
I want you
Will say but I hope I can get one of those
That's all I ask but that might be a big
That's that I don't know I think he had to sell that on account of it was
Two little man it wasn't manly enough for
His rationale
Oh yeah it's it's
Governor real man
But
Yeah yeah that is that is one of the things that we respect the most about
You and I
The people that we've
Surrounded myself
Is the
The need to put
The families first
To put the harm first
And we can all have our fun
After that but not
To forget that
The reason we're here
AZ is because of this
Do you know
Yes exactly it's a remember okay well you know yeah he
Is he says funny
Stop on the stand we can all make
Make fun of him
Of course but
You know but that yeah but that we don't lead off with
Right that we instead say
Oh this is Bihar but
He is dying to
Society 2
Ace family
He's too you know
The people who know these four
You know it it's
Again I'll trauma just
Kind of
Does itself and get
Down in thing
That's something I also
The degree of harm.
Really this has
It's true it's true in imaginable
So when you think about that way
You do 8
It doesn't make the money seem as overwhelming and large
I mean
You almost do get
Situation where you're like
Man is it
You know
Is this even enough
But
Time will tell with that but
See where it goes I mean you you you think about the is this enough and what one of the powerful things that
Did they kept bringing up with
How many people were
You know
How many people saw this in
How many people were influenced
Buy The Sims
Information and you know you think all 1.5 billion is
Is a lot but if you just had all of those people
Who were taken in
Give a dollar
We be at 3 billion people of the dollars or whatever do you know what it's like
Relatively speaking that harm he's caused
So huge
That's because we're so unused to money being that big
It's hard to breath
It is but yeah it's also the same difficulty with rapping
But your head around the amount of damage
So I think
Italy orders you know there's
There's
But we'll see what happens
Appeal form
This case on its side
Supplies
Juicy Noir
I don't expect him to
And they smoke
I say that now doing anything for the rest of his life
I don't really
Expected to win a raffle
For the rest of us it was bizarre cuz I GHIN it's
I did I mean it was kind of like a twisted puzzle I felt like an FBI agent doing string on the board trying to be like
Is he or is this
There's got to be a reason just making myself mad as I'm watching all these hearings
You know it
We'll see where that goes there and I don't know if Norms going to be handling the appeal
Or what but
I mean
Suspect he will
But
All that's left for Baraboo maintained that the the luckiest man alive
Is right now
Just because normix
It's like
For all the things that Norm is done
Whenever I found out
The next morning after mark
Had dramatically revealed that
Right
The next morning before they
They the jury of gaunt
The deliberation
I remember right now just going
To talk to the judge
I'm just being like
We would like
To have that not have happened
Can we get an extension on the 10 days or something is agencies just said I want to do over
And it's like that's that's
Unreal
But then you know now Norm is like
How about you just make us pay five bucks
Yeah like I got the mobile at right now and it's like to be an a******
And how are you negotiating with us
I really do think that the only way
You could win on or you know
There's no way you can get out with
And write as much as
What are the moments from Connecticut trial that cracked
Me up was
I can't remember exactly what
What it was
The moment but
Judge Bellas in Hayward having a discussion
Ejections
Inside German
Ghetto judge Bella said well I'm assuming there will be in a
Appeal to which Norm said what if we win
Twisted Bell is repeating herself as said I'm assuming there's going to be an appeal you know this is outside the
Presence of a jury and everything so it just cracked me off I hope she was a slave
Buddy
Yasso
That is fantastic and I've certainly had my fine there but you know when
Alex's lawyer say things like he'll he'll need a second job if he doesn't make millions of dollars you know who am I
So
Yeah that that's been fun too
I've enjoyed those moments in another moment that
Had me absolutely cracking
The last Texas hearing
Was
When all was there and
Judge
Maya
Wanted him to get his poster board
You do but he had his own props
I think you'll remember we couldn't we wanted that so bad we wanted that
So bad
And I still I'm dreaming of getting that
Well judge Maya said basically can you please take these out of here
We have them like in the back essentially
And you know these yours and Mark
Said that he would
I think he said he would give her an all 100 bucks for
And I
Died laughing
I just I'm so glad I was not hit in the courtroom in person that day because I would have
Oh my God I would have had to have one of Alex
Coughing fit
The cover-up mobile
Fantastic
I think that is a great story to end on
Morgan thank you so much for coming on
This was fantastic and it's been we wanted to have you on for a while
We appreciate the work that you're doing you know watching all of these
And we're just so grateful so thank you very much and if you want tell people one more time where they can find easiest way
Find me on the hillside Twitter
Ace associate Morgan Stringer and the ad is
Is Atmos string
Most
Brian
And you can also find me
On the opening
Podcast occasion
Pop culture in law and I'll
Hopefully have some yooper
Awesome thank you so much and I hope we will talk to
Again soon