Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Celine and talk a little bit about
Alex Joe indeed we are.
My bright spot today Jordan
Well I guess
I have
You know I for the last
Year or so I have wanted a PlayStation 5
First of all.
You couldn't spend the money because no one that had any of them if they were impossible to find
Before the Christmas this year
For the holiday I was able to
And I decided to get myself
A little bit of a Christmas present
And tell you I got the PS5
And I've been messing around with a couple
Boy games
Having a decent time enjoying some Arkham Knights
I I saw a Tara because I didn't you you told me that you got it
I had no idea what it actually was
The PlayStation 5
No I saw I saw a thing on TV about it
About Arkham Knight because I don't have TV or anyting sure it was it was over with my family for Christmas they had commercials and
It's Batman game
Spoiler alert for the first minute
It's a I mean
Look I don't know I guess
I've heard that I don't know this to be dreams I don't pay
A whole lot of attention but I understand there's some backlash about there not being Batman in it
Probably based and sexism a club level pass Batgirl is one of the playable characters share
Enjoyed it so far
It plays exactly
Essentially exactly like any of those old
Batman Arkham game
It's all you really want I mean honestly deep down it's just a bunch of ones
Zero's there are no men or women inside the video game atom
And then I started playing it as like mad I missed the Riddler trophies
That was funny was wondering to get Riddler trophy as the game as I played like maybe an hour into it like
Riddler trophy
So glad they're on your Riddler trophies
They're all over the f****** city of like I'm never going to get all eight
800 Visa whatever the flat there buddy
Anyway it's fun
What's a bright spot
Ill for a week or so ago
Concerned about her only communicating
Marvel
Including
Four different morbius cover
Morbius was a great way to
Appreciate your concern and the nice messages that
Percent of get well soon and such
For whatever it's worth you were not overly
Worrisome
And I appreciate your offer to it to help out
Whatever but like
You know we got gopuff now that's all we got some NyQuil
That's amazing
Yeah that is one of the few things that it does make me feel like we're living in the future
There have been
Service like that it was so weird to have in my mind like
I need Aspirin
Or or whatever I need Tylenol or
Can't get down the
Street to the CVS right
Or whatever
Not a problem
Really really spoiled
It's it's it makes me feel somewhat older I suppose or something but just like
The absolute amazement are you telling me that aspirin can be delivered
Right
Seems like that's not
That complicated of a problem
We took a while song
Yeah I don't know what
Exactly we got
Some sort of a cold or something
I'm not sure I tested for covid and I was negative so that did work some
Seemed like that was the case but
Yeah I'm feeling much better
You know
Well I'm glad to hear it
Yeah it's tough to take time off
Because it's fun I enjoy doing the show the best
Talking about this dumbass hole
Also
Compulsion to work
Ug who really do and I may have been working on some sites
You may have been working out those I think
Before we started talking
Sent out but I was not doing that while I was sick
Abundance of caution
Bother other side
Side stuff did you breathe and any bubble wrap and send it to China to teach
Teach them a lesson about amen
Good morning in China
Alright
So Jordan
On our horse
Then we're going to ride in on in Alexandria
So I decided
A little something and that was
Is that I don't want to do it
Play episode talking about another 2000 3 episode 9th and 10th
Hey holiday content is a little bit all over the place for Alec
True event here was what I
I saw this I was like
Go fuc
Yourself he had a video about panda video
And the title of it was how one man changed the world and you can too
I like how it's going to be about Jesus
Yeah
Of course it's Christmas time
Is it going to be about reset
It's about Alex of course it's about Alex
Yeah what band Change the World by UK to I was like this is not
The time for the season where maybe you should
You know if your is this a big
Big religious Outfitters you say baby
People
A theologian
Spiritual leader
Many would say
And devout Christian I think Alex
Nose
Christmas day more than any other day
It should be about out
Yeah I will say I didn't actually watch that video so maybe it is all about Jesus but the thumbnail of it is
And recover pictures of Alex from probably
Jesus that what that was like alright
My buddy
Have fun
Unless you're throwing a hatchet get the f***
Got to hear
About the year that has
Yeah for us it's been really
Interesting
Certainly there been
Developments Lotto
Things about Alex's court cases
Have touched us a little more closely than would be expected true
But I don't want to dwell on that I want to think about all of the
The dangling threads we have
This is just what I came up off the top of my
Okay
That's what else have we got
Monkeypox
Still going
The bride has been dropped
Entirely Alex
Not reported on beef
I almost zero case it's now in the United States
Nancy Pelosi's husband's attack being fake
Didn't
I don't know what's happening with that Alex you to drop that storyline chair
A nuclear war was supposed to have broken out by now only going to last a couple days
Shorts we have both nuclear war starting
And Selinsky was on Putin's payroll and all that
Does not
We have no update on that all the food plants
We're under attack
The food was all under attack
All of these things were supposed to make us scared this year
I think it I think it did work out but
Just wasting everybody's time
With nonsense
Strangled them scared about stop
It does feel like there should be a year and wrap up like like a whatever like a ATV Club or like top 50
See things of this year and if you really go through in like list
The amount of things that Alex
Wanted or should have happy
You're like that would be a busy year
Will be a busy f****** year
I mean it would be a disaster movie it would be a horror film
If
Westlake
You know like let's let's look at it as like a reverse Liar Liar
Where is Jim Carrey not being able to lie it's everything Alex says is spoken in
Twilight Zone Agatha Christie novel
The classic Knives Out mystery
Apparently also people are mad about
Are they bad about that I've done with backlashes I don't give a s*** I have not seen
This film
Straight but I've heard
Anyway instead of dwelling on
These dangling threads in like how Alex
Probably not going to spend the end-of-the-year cleaning up his mess I got this one wrong
Every year you should have if you
You should have a rose
Every year at the end of the year at the big ol holiday party
You sit up at the dais and everybody just kind of makes fun of all the s*** you made up
Sherp
I will come as a diesel tank
Cuz I'm picturing this as a roast like a Friars Club Roast right but each person on the dais
Is one of the things Alex lied about and they almost there
Alright
Feather the concept of the thing afro 608 somebody dressed as a nuclear bomb would walk up Abuela
I bet you thought I was going to drop
Here's the new bomb dropping on you I didn't I got something along those lines
You could be like a food plant on fire
Anyway we're going to be in past
Just cuz I wanted to
Way back into the Waters of doing the show and I didn't
Really feel like
Watching him
Navel gazing
Hello
What does the new Wok
So first
Vex shurco policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much like excess book vexing
Next
I'm the only known Republican in my company of 120 employees which include the info Warriors
Your podcast is what gets me through the day thank you so much
Journal policy wonk
Thank you very much
I'm cranky and winky is My Chosen Mount thank you so much you're now about to walk
Thank you very much is a Donkey Kong
Strong about a week is the
Something like that
Next damn listening to old episodes and it's my favorite thing when you say bezel bub
What Beelzebub Journal policy want
Funny
Beelzebub
Beelzebubs maybe it may be going way back to to like
When we were in your old roommate that whole thing more off and I would say Old Scratch
That's more fun
And Foundation to donate dn48 Studios
Juvenile policy walk
Thank you very much like it would love to but the Bill's already got it quite alright
Add to the mixer Jordan to so I'd like to say thank you
And if everyone is an alphabet no one is an alpha thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Catching up with your backlog in 10
You're busted my brain also it's probably my birthday by now thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
I have
Risen above
My enemies
And then we're going to
Comeback
And I mean
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty work for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f*** the horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
I apologize to
Yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's not even better the past
I like that I like that
It probably my birthday by the I think
It was probably by anniversary I was at
Just put it in there cuz they will celebrate it and we'll celebrate with you for sure
Celebration of you and the life
And what have you told him
I need a absolutely that's the way to do it
It's your birthday
Go shorty
I understand that is that you're 50
That was karaoke for the day
It sounded like you were saying Beelzebub
Bezel
So
The nights
And
When I play this clip you may come around to the idea that my witchcraft already knows no bounds
Information
Today
We're going
Discover and I'm going to cover
Orange
The New York Times
Martial law
So Alex is gearing up to make people afraid and then
Teens how bad her going to be coming to to the US
Think about
Covid
The thing about covid relief gets into my head now is
When you look back at all these
All the previous
Possible pandemic
You know about global pandemics could become a global pandemic
And it seems like they did a good job do we have to like reevaluate
But I feel like we should go back
And re-evaluate the quality of
Previous pandemic responses and be like holyshit
These guys were unbelievably great
What happened with covid it's clearly these guys were the f******
Warriors
I think yes definitely there should be a certain amount of that
I think you know it can be difficult because they are different
Agents shorter different viruses
It's hard to compare 121 and also some
Some of it unfortunately also does come down to lock
Some things that are slightly outside of your
Control or require like complex
Cooperation that sometimes you can't rely on other people to
True but but yeah I do think they're probably lessons of the past
Destined
You know other
Coronavirus outbreak stats
What happened then and didn't happen now or vice versa
Well I don't want to stick difference and that is that
Wasn't a millionaire
If it 2002-2003 SARS outbreak
That's our new conspiracy theory if there is
A potential disaster happening somebody needs to steal all of Alex's yachty
And make sure he's nowhere near it and then whenever the disaster is averted Alex could pop back up on there or something like that you know
Yes yes we will need to keep him poor as a preventive measure against future outbreaks
From his money
And also this is December 2003 this is a bit after
Sorry said already
Yeah it was contained in July
1003 that was when there was like alright
Where we got this we got a good handle on this thing is like sporadic cases in 2004 but like it
It's not December 2003
The speculation of
This being
It's going to cause quarantine seriously in the United
It stayed at
It's a Longshot
Oh boy
You must think I'm his mind and that is that he's about to go to Houston
Okay
What to do in Houston
There is place
They show movie
Okay Alamo Drafthouse
He's mad cuz they've got
Views
Don't they
No that's pretty cool. The Austin one is apparently cool because he won't stop talk about help
Mel Gibson was just there showing The Passion of the Christ
Right and
Apparently he's going to the Houston won
The guy who runs the Houston one comes on the show trying to sell tickets
Which is like
What kind of a I'm sorry what movie
Very busy
I realize I haven't smelled this out at right is doing an event
Right in this at the Houston
Draft
Where are you showing one of his films during the day and then they're showing they live
Okay so it's sort of a big event
Right but
None of the theaters at the Alamo Drafthouse ours is that big
And if they're needing to move tickets by having the manager come on Alex's show as I can
Do a little PS I don't know what's going on here this is
This is like
The bad version of do it morning radio to try and Celtic
Gets to a comedy show Absolutely
I just I just flew in last night and I still got to get up
5:30 a.m. to do this
Is damn Zoo crew show
Because the manager just called and said we've only sold eight
Tickets for Net10 ticket Soul just to do a show man bright implies one of two things one
Is like a really bad club or no draw
Yeah and
The draft house is pretty good pretty good clientele
Pretty good
Good movies
W many hours is backdrop
Announced they were doing tonight of they live I bet they would have done pretty well for them
Yeah maybe Alex is a negative factor in this
So anyway
He talks a little bit here about his last time
Doing one of these
Rescreening
Was about to start
Country
Probably
40 minutes
To get your tickets online
40 more than we should have
Open for free
Wait what
Folding chairs
I don't know they'll be there this time
Great place
It's a great place to meet like-minded people like Mel Gibson's Holocaust
Mel Gibson's dad was there so what meet Holocaust deniers
You know where to go what a git
What is celebrity appearance
The dead of Mel Gibson
Yeah dude we got Richard Spencer's Dad here today selling f******
Cars outside of the BMW so you know Nazis it next time I see bad they're doing all right for themselves
I should say
The interest of fairness
I don't know what Richard Spencer's dad's beliefs are I do know what hot you did something really sorry
About that
Also I don't know if I am in luck
I Do by Alex's story about
You letting people in free and out of this stuff
Sound like the Alex I know
But
This sound
Really
Low-stakes
Yeah
For the Alex that we know in the present day
Like somebody who's giving like
A family member directions of how to get in free to the show
Actor of half an hour early you can't
Show open doors
Alright babe oh yeah this is
This is an almost weird 222
Obviously people come from somewhere they don't just start where they are but
For this type of
Singto then
Steamroll into what it became you know your I would understand it just type
Peppa Pig
Later on he became a slave
More successful version of himself
Hope you know
Go back this would make sense
But we live in now where it's like
He's turned into
F****** Super shredder
After drinking too much booze and now it's it's all collapsing around
Episode not too long ago he flew to Kansas City to do a local radio
At this point in the past he is just like
I want to I want to say one thing
I think some people have a little bit less excitement about
The past episode does opposed
The present because
Present has a lot of like
Hot Topic
Some things that are in the news and no kidding Alex's take on it can sometimes
You know help understand where a lot of right-wing talking points are I understand that and I don't want to
Ignore that
Completely
But going back to the past has some other side advantages
And this day live
Show is kind of touching
She's close to one of them in that is
I want to find more movie reviews
I want to find more episodes where Alex
Explain exactly what he thinks
Art is saying
Timmy
Are you
Recently remembered that we did that episode talking about his view of the second Matrix movie
And Blake
Oh yeah to me is I need more of that
I need more of like
Alex
Saying I believe that this is the message of Avatar or whatever
Yeah him trying to interpret art outside of
Whenever he
Leaving politics in the n in really does try to get into art criticism
Art for its own sake
Yeah is one of the windows into a truly bizarre my
That is that is what I want to find
Is the gold of digging for these Hills
So anyway we get back to store
Sound a little familiar
U.s. quarantine
Programs
For sure
According to
Thermometer
99 + 4
Police firefighters
Medical workers
Has been altered
The fear Monger was that weapon
Remind
The Commerce
Martial law
In Colorado Springs
The farmers
When's the Commerce
Dynamic to the game that right-wing propaganda s******* like Alex have to engage in the
Call out a little bit here
In order to run their game of
Constantly making the audience afraid about novel and exciting threat
They're required to rewrite their own past ideas
Alex the compellingly freakout his listeners about covid being a lab-made bioweapon in 2020
It's pretty important for him to not give off the impression that he's just the kind of guy that says that all the time
You would lose a lot of his ability to convince them that he's proven that the
The sky is falling if they were made aware
But he's really is making s*** up
2020 the 2003 SARS outbreak is real in service of helping Alex make the argument that the
The current one is
Is not
Hey things have gotten out of control in 2003 the way they did it in our present antiva
Game as he has recently
But it wouldn't have been nearly as impactful giving his
Bar smaller influencer
And the Dynamics around social media not being there at the time
The model State emergency Powers Act was a piece of draft legislation that was crafted by a Georgetown law professor with
Support from the CDC
It was not ever adopted or pass on a federal level though some state governments of past elements of it
For instance in March 2003 Arizona passed a bill requiring the department of health services to redact
Personally and identifying info
From health record
Before they release publicly
The couple of these State bills do provide a clarification of what law enforcement entities
Can do to assist with Department of Health orders involving cortines
But it's a far cry from anything like martial law with Alex's say
Plus this is the state government to states rights or something
Also Alex fails to mention that his mortal enemy the ACLU is an entity leading
The opposition to the model State emergency Powers Act
Do the concerned
How about vague language
Which they could lead to civil
Infringement
House just ignores that
Because it would make it harder for him to paint them is
The evil demon globulin
This to his audience of acknowledge what they actually do
How does further mixing up his history
Saddam used chemical weapons on civilians in 1984 but the shipments of West Nile were made in 1985
They weren't specifically to Sadam Ali worth
Made by Rumsfeld but it did happen
There wasn't a recce scientist who previously been a researcher in Fort Collins Colorado who received shipments of West Nile
Presumably Ford lab
Research purposes
There's a huge conversation that deserves
We had and has been had but
Maybe could be had more about the unintended consequences of dual-use chemical agents
There were sold to a Rockin for research purposes
Before
Desert Storm
But that actual conversation is almost nothing to do with West Nile
And Alex
Is
All over the place
But today
The extent that you know our soldiers did
End up
Dino finding these
These old
I'm stopping and being effect
Did buy them
Is
On
Acceptable
Agree
But
It makes me want it like listening to that makes me wonder how old those conservative Bingo cards really are you know like that
Like are we going to
To find fossilized records of a dinosaur been like
Are there busing in
Protester dinosaurs you know like is it's the same s***
From the gym
Well you know you always see
People
I am a little bit worried about this coming out of my mouth now because I have not looked
To Intuit you know you do see those like political cartoons
That are
Ostensibly from
70 years ago you like thematically fairly similar to
To now when there is
But there's things that it like
What kind of mirror totally
Some of the Bingo cards probably
Rudy
Yeah because you know it
Because
Is it and it it has to be
Because the bingo card has nothing to do with what's being
Instead the bingo card is bad thinking
It is how you are thinking
Poorly
In response to an infant
So it's it's like a it's like any old
Logical fallacy
The fallacy isn't changing its the thinking that's causing
This is largely similar things
Like
Being
Surrounded by people who you perceive to not be like
AcuRite
New technology that you find Freddy
Those are kind of
Pretty
Common
Or Public Health crisis is another hot hot water changes for
Bad thinking
It's not going to be that sucker
Change
From time.
I mean just this
Emergency
1 out of 100
You're not scared
Super
40 million people
About that
You're the one
That is not fear-mongering
Jerk talking point of comparing a public health concern to the flu
In order to minimize
There were relatively few deaths from the 2002 outbreak of SARS
But a lot of it probably comes down to there being a robust response to it and ask
Getting lucky
Alex's just a little bit off on that flew Story 2
In 1998 researchers found
Fragments of the 1918 flu in 6 under the bodies from the Norwegian
That flew is one that really scares scientist
Because it wasn't really clear why it was so deadly and how it moves
So fast
Research on that end of things is
Top because there aren't exactly a ton of preserved samples of the
The flu the people
Printers work with
That's the goal was to find somebody
Who might have contained the virus
Got really deep
Frozen
Which led people to
To the Arctic
They tried the time machine but everybody was trying to kill Hitler with it and then it collapsed in on itself after creating paradoxes terrible ideas
24 bodies
Let's go to the cold
So from a New York Times article
Quote in a diary kept by the coal mining company here doctor Duncan found the names of seven men
18 to 29 years old
Farmers and fishermen who had just arrived here to earn extra money
Hey winter jobs in
The mine
But they have contracted
Flew on the boat trip from the mainland and died in the first week
Of October 1980
He's a fascinating story but ultimately they did not find samples that could be used for research since the body
Please turn to have not actually been buried in permafrost
As they had expect
Right and I'll just following this story he probably should have known about this by 2003 but in reality
The details of the story
The only part of the story that has any value is the insinuations he can make out of Sensational in it and inaccurate
Versions of headline
That's why it's still lives on in this form just
Yeah yeah that's
That's a bit different from the store the story they found
Living samples of the flu that killed 40 to 50 million people in their turning into a weapon
The story of they went looking and didn't find anything
Less scary
Less like at the beginning of a Godzilla movie when Godzilla comes out of the water and then blowing stuff up your like
Oh that's scary
But if it was just
Water
You mean like this is not a movie at all but there's like a gecko
Exactly like that it's not a movie
Vista Vista
Yeah
I think if I understand correctly from what I was looking at
Itzy
The issue was they thought that the people were buried deeper than they were
And so it would have preserved
M d price and it was not you
Even close I'm so the ground would have thought in Frozen
And thawed and Frozen therefore there's no
Usable samples that's a true like National Treasure ass moment you know that's Nicolas Cage
It's being like I figured it out we've come up with this long circular would circuitous route to get these samples
Because we can't find him any other way we've dug
F****** Norwegian Earth
There's no
I was reading
Maybe was a little unfair to the people who buried them
Speculations
They didn't want to dig all the way down cuz it was cold out to Lazy bad for my fault
And padrino you still markdown it was happy or whatever put the other the other one was a little bit less
I'm sort of suspicious
So that was like
They might have been scared of being exposed to a
I wouldn't want to touch Play Cloudy likes a little bit more sensitive
Quit jumping gravediggers won't help us save people from
Future
So Alex talked about this a little bit so it ends up mocking something that says in hindsight
Quite a good prediction
The one in Austin
It's a Marshalls
He'll require masks
For martial law
Brace yourselves for a
Or dr. iten was
Ghetto pretty
The commonly accepted in node within the medical and
Epidemiologic
The problem with those
Predictions
Is that they are true
Regardless of
When or if they come
Like when they come true is not
The important factor
It's not like all
He predicted something amazing it snows like no
This is an inevitability about
Lightsaber icing with humans
There will be another pandemic
How it f****** works
You don't you can't mock people in real life
Not a prediction math
That's how it works man
It will rain
Eventually
What exactly
You can have an umbrella
Or
Do you run the risk of getting
Wescom
And getting rain.
These are the inevitabilities
And we option that's the way it goes
You are still going to get wet
Sure
So I find it to be a little bit Rich that Alex and kind of beings
Smug about this when the guy was just
Totally right
Of course he was
Bombs
I'd Russia
We're not on Russia
Steambow in 2003
Russia
Bomber detonated explosives
Square
Victims
Peace at Russia
A broken window
The
Alarm could be heard
There are real terrorists but
Putin uses it as a police state Crackdown
So this one might be real
But yeah Alex says never never heard
Rush hour food
Doing this kind of thing
In the present
I mean
Steve
He called him and he said he does it
All the time like it's a regular like
Police state
Somebody's leg
So you pretend that there's a car bombers he has a habit of terrorizing
Our real terrorists
Somewhere
But not in Russia
Southall pool
Haha
Anyway that's curious
It's weird
So Alex a number calls
On this episode
This this
This color is I mean this this is bad news I don't know how else to
There's it there's something that we know and that is at Alex's films have a 92 95-98
Percent Effectiveness rate
Super effect
Yeah they're dangerous there more transmissible than most diseases yeah yeah
But unfortunately
The caller calls in
And says that like people aren't enjoying them that much
Alex's
Good luck
Jupiter police
Bro
Waking up roughly
Because lately I've been I've been hearing from a
All of them
Tri-County mental average
What are you talkin about mental Everett
Fingers that doesn't why would you edit it why would you edit it down
I got to be modest you got to stay humble
I don't understand
Okay so you're at
I think it's probably because there had been like
Some despondent
Ishq calls
Sure like there had been a couple people within the last week or so on his show who had said like
You know people aren't responding
2 XYZ
Is it maybe just in the sake of like
Let's at least match the energy that the colors are bringing
It's not over sell this thing it's going to look glaring
We're down 280
This is kind of like a negotiation strategy know you start so delusional right
Somehow the reasonable is even more delusional
The crazy hot
Absurd
I mean if you count plate
Then maybe a
People are nice
20%
Best
I mean
Look how many family members does Mel Gibson have
That does give the number
So Alex is down on these tapes man 80%
That's a big head you say 80% to 90%
What you mean 270
Everyone's a little bit sad
That prompts I think a little bit of a conversation about how important ingrate Alice's tapes are
Thank you for
Domus Jones
This Christmas
All the way
East Waco
This Christmas
Oh devil
Barbie song
Cancel
I really don't feel
We got that much wrong
I really feel like it
New York
Acenar own video our own interview
Porta potties
People to get a minute
Security
Everybody list
188 everybody
Country
Somebody
Do it
It will be quite
How much longer
But my wife
Fina Camp maybe be ready for some fun
It's going to happen
The police
I know you get tired of me talking about the
If everybody gets
Cacapon get to somebody for Chris
We would be
Anyone
Any one of them
You know what I'm talkin about to start the Mind thinking
Imitates on only way I got the fight
The only way I got to fight
Is it right now
If you want to give me trouble
Shutdown
I'm going to start putting out trying to put out 120
This is so sad wow
That bums me out
Creepiest Chris
Message from Louisiana Dentures I've ever to buy at what the fuk was that
Yeah man
Just give it to you Mickey
My VCR is giving me trouble
That was the saddest thing I think I've ever heard in my entire life my VCR is giving me troubles but the
The tapes are the only way we can
Can fight meme
God
Your leak genuinely afraid that your wife is going to be taken to a
FEMA camp and raped by a foreign Soldier
That's what you think
And the solution
Is spread Alex's Palmyra in marketing for Alex
Happened in that man's brain
Alex
Outfit
Alex scaring people about a hundred different things that I can't keep track of anything and then
Selling them the solution
Bissell
The impotence
Of Alex's
Just sort of model
Good example of that where it's like the only thing we can do is
Promote Alex's
Contact
This is the
The end-all-be-all of the fight against the globalist
Is just being Alex's Street to you
Yeah yeah
I mean the thing is
And I listen
This is a weird little
Side thing
What's what's
Strange to me about that
Is that Alex
Talks almost non-stop about like
Suicide bombers and Ed all of these things you know like
People who are in an actual fight
Driven to a point of desperation so serious that the only way they feel like they have to fight back the only thing they have to fight back
Back with his I live
And he's telling these people they're in that type of fight
And the way they have to fight with everything that God is by
Making video
Sprite and giving them to people and fixing your VCR
Yeah
How does that not
Breakthrough your cognitive dissonance
I'm not sure
Really really bums me out I'm not some
People who takes like holidays too seriously
I think you and I are both
Kind of like
Christmas
Real raised Christian of course
Have kind of a weariness of Chris Christmas
There is something about this guy being like this Christmas please make a copy of Alex's tape
It's like the worst Miracle on 34th Street speech
Please just believe he's from a bad Christmas movie
Sounds so genuine it sounds so Earnest it sounds like this man
What's to leave the world
Boys knowing that he doesn't have much time left
Xbox
But but
He's not saying I don't have much time left
Guido
No no I know that the world is going to end
When an old man says we don't have much time left
The could be duel
So anyway that call was a bummer
And this call is a little bit more fun
Colorado
Hi Alex
They don't like that
Going
About the videos
Day's been that way with
Call so far
I got a problem with
Olivamine
If two weeks or anything like that
Out of the three pack
The new one I'm not sure
The new one
Delivery up
Of the other tuna
I know you
You need to call this number
Right now
Banda will ship it out to you
Is that the office
Yes
For anybody
Gun Shop
Add any trouble
Well also the
I also
I got some of those Perry DVD
I'm trouble playing on DVD player
Number man
Whatever time
Parkour
Phone number for ordering
Call 8 a.m.
253 313 operator service
I will give you my office number and they will call you back
Today Show
Messages
Phone number Saginaw
Ninety-nine percent of people
I don't have a problem
2/2 weeks
The other one
Give me more details
Toll free number
Drop that service
Operator
You don't have your f****** text I'm in the middle of an explanation I know you're going to undercut this
Blaming people to call Center for right now the address
For the call center and they said that they had my address right they confirmed it I actually work at the call center
Fred's
Predicted on
What is God-fearing Folk
So it is it is fun to hear a customer service call
Reminds me of tech support with Bill Cooper love it
I love it it is something else Alex is being annoyed
Just got to sit there and take it
Just be like and call he's got to be like that let me try and help you
Your problem sir
I don't know why you just hang up feel like this is not
This is not an on-air problem my man I gave you my number to call
Please call that
Melbourne
Please don't continue
You telling me more things about how poorly my business is run
I know it
I think that maybe there is even a vulnerability that Alex has at this point in his career of like
Appearing that he has other people who do things
Like shipping
Departments in
Stuff like that
I did the
Got to be the one man
Business ideas should be
Looks like him putting he stamps on the envelope that I have
Yeah that that's kind of the image
Think maybe
Hanging up on the guy what kind of bus
About a little bit well I mean that's a good thing we don't do our calling
Because then people call it'll be like
I haven't gotten my button yet we're like yeah you haven't
It'll be there
Might eventually hang up on people to call
It will be there so are we won last year and it's another caller cousin h
Interesting story to tell about a National Monument
A couple little quick
Where we got the statue
Liberty from
Namely The Illuminati's
Posley
Ahead
Kaddish
Lucifer
Crown
Main Street Pub
Mainstream book saying stream books
Have made it
Very clear
To anyone who wants that information and the French
Sculpture is even
Alright so this should be
Widely known
That
It's not the United States
Symbol of freedom and Hope
Is actually in Illuminati
Daredevil
It's either a crossdresser or it is the devil
Yeah and it's got a illuminati crown and torch
Prometheus I guess maybe
Yeah none of this is
Based on 8th
There was speculation that
It was based
On the sculptors mother
And then
Two people heads
Suggested that the sculptors brother also looks fairly similar
Resemblance
FreedomPop around
And
You know this isn't like something that I was just pulling out of thin air right there are people who Bandy these ID
Videos about the like a model for a
Could have been his brother or
Something along those lines but
It's saying it's in mainstream book
And value know that sculpture Center
Try to be more interesting than he actually is
Based off of
Then you're going to because I'll
Secret
Michelangelo's David
Not ask
What wasn't actually a
Michelangelo didn't even know the
Nevermind
Andrina's
Did have a head
That's a common misconception
Conception
She didn't have an arm
She did have a head
And then the other arm fell off
Wait somebody stole the head of the statue
To have no head
Where to get the no head for
From
Sculpture that has no head
Plenty of sculptures that have no head
And you can make
Not have a head screw
So the 9th
You know
Picture
They're complaining about to Soros being a bioweapon so that's that's a good bit of fun there's an issue
Stuff about these two
Calls about Lakes customer service and said
Christmas movie speech
About these days
The sads
Bizarre preoccupation and then also Alex's a little bit of
Sponsor so that's
That's the crew
Christmas spirit
That's fun
And Alex has a big
Story
For the
Describe is a Nazi
Fox grabbing
Terrified
Story suck
It's tragedy and I'm going to guess that Alex is going to miss the forest
Patrice talking about it
He always does
On November 5th
2003 the police in Goose
Creek South Carolina conducted a raid on students at Stratford High School after the principal decided that one student
Was possibly selling weed
The student body of the schools
25% African-American
But over quote more than two-thirds of those caught up in the sweep where Africa
Ultimately no drugs or weapons were found and no charges were ever filed
Great a cynical view of things
Might lead one to assume that the only reason that this became a story at all is because there was surveillance video of the rated
Self and this is
Kind of bleach it to imagine
That this is
Good
Conceivably
Be happening in other schools and what that my
Must be like
What are the reasons that the story proceeded the way that it did is because 20 of the students who were the subject of this
Raber represented by the ACLU who had the resources to take this all the way to a settlement
The school district handled searches and
Established a fund
For the students who are victimized
Best cover medical expenses
And therapy
This lawyer that Alex has autism member of the legal team that is also representing some
Students and that's great as well
So much of this comes down to a conversation about
And I think it's pretty clear that Alex
Isn't going
One of the reasons that this case is particularly suspicious was the timing of the rate
Which took place at
6:45 a.m.
The reason Mississippi suspicious is because that was prior to the arrival time of most of the School's bus
The only buses that it arrived were the ones that picked up student to live relatively close
Which was a group that was predominantly black
In Essen
The school
Intentionally or not create the situation where the primarily White
8 students would arrive at school
2 seed of mostly blacks dude
Things being searched and made to kneel while please help them
It's a dehumanizing scene and the race aspect of it is
Pretty much impossible to ignore
But we'll see how Alex
I mean I just
I am not
Going to have to be a lot of effort
Can I have to be a lot of effort to
To pretend that this is not about race
Yeah
Well I mean I think
I think you could probably make
A couple of
Interesting ways
This around this one
Is that it's not all
About Rick's
There's a large portion and maybe if you want to focus on some of those other things to the exclusion
Turn of the larger conversation
But if that's
The way Alex Mike's
Cc is economic C
Because it's all about economics because of the
Regional
It's the areas
And then you could just be like well it
It's police state
You know like
Wow
There is there is a truth to it that this is
An appropriate policing of NTB
You know having
Dogs
Doing a research
Of a school over something
You have no problem
Cars are no real reason outside of a
Yeah kind of level of evidence
It's it's intrusive
Very least
Yeah all of the laws that we have
To keep that from happening
Yeah but it seems like the laws are being used
To make that have
Which is an issue
Babies fair enough that there is like
The police stady aspect
But
Against focus on that
Without looking
The broader picture of it
I think is a
It's not dealing with story as a b
Seltzer
Alex
Talks a little bit about a news story about this rate
And this
Is dumb
On one of the time
And that you cannot have a hole
Call GroupMe
Sweet
Personnel
Adduction
You do not have the dog.
Train
Dogs
So for one thing
Czechoslovakia dissolved in 1993
So if this dog was trained there that's a pretty old.
I have no idea why a small-town department in South Carolina with Outsource their drug dog training to Eastern Europe
But that seems
Kind of cost-prohibitive if you want the best you have to pay for it okay
Please start training center in North Carolina as well as Slovakia
Play the Czech Republic
Once they split apart and their dog training
Went to s***
So I was really confused about this
Aspirator article that Alex's reading from and it turns out that it says the dog is a Czechoslovakian
Alex
Taking the dogs breed
I'm pretending that it begins with the dog was trained in Europe I guess because it makes the dog sound more scary
I will say this I am slightly more terrified of an Eastern European German Shepherd
Stereotypically terrifying place to train soap again.
Also at no point in the article does it say that the dog whose name is Major
They don't attack
Dog
This is
Best Alex lying about a partner in the article that.
Describe the difference between passive
Active alert
Detection.
Some dogs respond to finding drugs by sitting which is passive train
Ansible Berkeley
Which is the more grass
Style
I was either lying about this or just making up a detail to create an angle for the audience
To hang on to that doesn't involve the key
Clear racism that underlies
The story
Everything about the raid in the search sucks
And I'm not minimizing any of that stuff
I'm just saying that I was not a good source of information on any
If you have the article he's reporting on in front of you and you watch along as Alex reads
It often becomes really clear how is process work
He's basically just skimming along and finding words to use as Anchor Point
And in this case Czechoslovakia is a
Pretty glaring an embarrassing one
This behavior is constant and consistent throughout his career so generally if people listen
Alex
Brother best for them to double-check his work so you can tell how much of it is just he's making up to sound smarter and more interesting
Weller putting
Literally zero effort into doing any show prep
Cuz why would you
Yeah
That's he knows that the s*** that he saying isn't
Truth why put time into preparing
It almost Works to your disadvantage because if you have a
Well-prepared lie
It's too good
Tubi
To be true xability
Stick with it so you can't change it as much later on your like
I put a lot of work into this bowl
I'm not going to just go ahead and say that Putin is a good guy now
Chebakia goddamnit
Hello how am I
Oh my God I can't believe that that's
How do you
So I got something a little bit backwards
And that is on
The 9th
That first Show interview with Larry Pratt
Gunownersofamerica is water filter
Their sponsor comes in
And here's a little taste of that
It really is
And
Alex Weaver
We got a couple of Christmas
That we wanted to share with
A thought crime
Yeah man can say Christmas got a war on his
Boy
I have some
Very
Left
What is that unseated destroy God type liberal
A number of them said Merry Christmas
Merry Christmas to you
2003 they care less than 19 years later
Even less the other
That's a lot of fun
One of the things that I think is interesting to Note 2 is that I'm noticing a
Trend
In this.
Alex's career where a lot of the Abbott
Add stuff is
Brokered programming
But
Pretty clear what it is
It's strange
Because it doesn't feel like they're trying to hide that they are an infomercial
They're still blending content and the pitch
That is for sure in April 8th
Really difficult
To tell what's leading what
You wouldn't
Never
Mistake this for not
A sponsored
Bit of
Whereas in the present-day and closer to the present day
That line blurs
Quite a bit
Yeah this is very clearly this is
The segment where I'm going to make money by letting this guy try and make money
That's the SEC
We all know it I can't say that Alex even makes clear while there I think it's actually just after the
Guy leaves
He pays for all of the bandwidth
Stuff on shortwave
So like
He pays for all of that
And in exchange she comes on and
They sell his water filter and I'm sure baby Alex makes money on top of that
Play to get to taste of each
Filter
Ethically speaking
You know you're not trying to
Firestone on anybody
Cannabis it really does come down to like
Are you focusing on an exaggerating water-based issues in order to sell water filters
And ignoring
Other real water issues like
You know parts of the country that don't have access to Clearwater because those aren't people who could afford your water filter
Wayfair
Angles in math
But in terms of like just trying to be like
We're not doing today
That seems to be a bit
Yeah yeah yeah the ethical issues
With this are more similar to like when
Breakfast cereal showed you what a balance
What's breakfast look like
And it was like
Bacon eggs ham
6 pieces of fruit
Two glasses of milk and orange juice all to make it
It seemed like the amount of sugar you were wondering marshmallow
Yeah yeah there's there's some information missing
On the 10th
Skulls
Detox dolls in pass man
Tell you what
He
Takes calls
Why do the same people
That does some true
Man
Metal Man in the same way that he's not going to sell out a theater without giving away tickets he's not going to open the phones
Not the same f****** people calling in Louisiana
Oh good I can't handle another Christmas message you no no no
It's another character that we know though
Is it old man house phone it's Dan Illinois
She's on
All the time
He gets out he must have the hotline number cuz he is constantly on
And I don't I don't play every time he's around because I don't want it to be excessive like I'm Dan I live in Illinois
Play this guy's Dan Illinois
It's not the co-host of info
No
This this Bears match
I think you might be
Maybe somebody
Are you doing Alex
I'm going to confuse about all this
Protesting against
Mel Gibson
Anything else like that
Where is a thing
Christian's brother exist
Believe In Christ
Scott
Which people by their
Hope he wasn't
Gotti was a blasphemer like
It says in the Bible
Trulia
Is it more of a Jewish
I am going
2 Chainz
My name in Illinois I don't want to be associated with from Illinois
Problem that people have with your religion isn't so much the religion part so much as the part where
It makes you go
They don't believe Jesus is God
And they that means that they believe that he's a blasphemer
So obviously we need to get one that's the religion part that's
The problem comes into conflict sure
Usher
The idea that
There is a I guess a failing of other people because
They have not
Become part of your religion
That that that is where
Comes it causes problems
Like here's the thing nobody's mad if you say merry
Christmas to them
Generally people are mad if you say
You have to celebrate Christmas and if you don't see Merry Christmas back to me you're the
Devil
Right right
I'm perfectly happy to say Merry Christmas or happy holidays to anybody
Whatever wine
I don't want someone yelling at me
There's no war on River my end
Nevermind
My Warriors
Play be alone.
Stop
Annoy
Prick
Alex gets another call and then another thing that happens
Is a b in 2003
Is
Colors call-in
Maybe Alex's like
Coast to Coast training
Is the colors of Colin with
Silly idea
And kiwi
Let's roll with that type of humor people
I wanted to go into something else I think
Interesting
And I want to know if
You heard anything
Think about this
Someone told us
Know someone in washing
DC
That
Behind
Control Talib
Before the year 2000
1060 route
To relocate with their families
Because
East Coast
Caribbean
So this caller is asking
Based on Intel that she has got
Higher-ups
Have a plan
Time to evacuate B
And Alex's responses are B up Island
You have no idea how about you think that they're trying to escape but you don't even
Know how much they're trying to
Escape I know they're trying to escape
So much more than you did that I'm the most knowing that they are trying to escape yeah
You think you got intelligence
You Maria Bamford character with whatever voice that is
This is a yes this is a signing off like if you're this person whose call again you're going to leave this phone call with
Boy my Intel is good wow Alex has
Those people who told me that insane thing are very trustworthy people and I can't wait to hear what they have
To say next
Things like maybe people who are
Literally in an episode
What does today
Very
What what I'm getting at is
The definition
Koto 23,000
Telegrafi
The meaning of United States is
Point that I want to make
Here is
Softer
On the court system
What is it that you protect you protect your driver's license look at your driver's license
Her name is spelled all capital letters
Human looking for Doom
Your corporation Drive Comfort Inn
I definitely need to turn around
Is our courts
Alternative
Coronavirus
Right right
Yep they found common ground and weird sovereign
Some s***
Just call in with some
Silly nonsense and Alex is going to be like you bet this is this all works for me
This comports with
My
Bizarre right-wing weirdo Dennis
But
Unfortunately
Sometimes
Other callers who have ideas
That run counter
To Alex's
Third world
Haha and this can't stand
And Alex has to push back on
For instance
Another call
It's from a guy
He's actually read operation North
Oh no and has a little bit of a concern
About how what could be a concern for somebody who's actually read it well it doesn't necessarily say like
People are going to be
Kill. There's that problem
Military forces
I got page 9
In route to Florida real or
It just talked about
You're not
Shooting archery
Just talking about the
What about the unarmed vessel
Dementia
Yasso
Who just bullying
But Alex is doing
Has rehearsed talking points about Northwoods which he uses to lend undeserved support to his conspiracies about things like
9/11 and the event recent Beltway Sniper attacks
Going to stand up to a person just reading the doctor
This is dicey territory
Two things that you see demonstrated in that clip
The first thing is the Absurd victory
But he claims over this collar
Exclaims of the document says that the globalist
Paramilitary forces will shoot people in DC in Miami and then explains
How to set up
This isn't really a cure
The document talks about developing a communist Cuban Terror plot quote
Cuban refugees seeking Haven in the United
This would involve killing anyone or any paramilitary group
Although it does say it may involve
Up to wound
They also say that quote via agents
And the release of prepare documents substantiating Cuban involvement would be helpful
In projecting the idea of an irresponsible
This is fairly close to discussing how to blame a patsy but
It's unclear if
The Cuban agents they're referring to dates will be blamed for anything
Where's the goal would just be to arrest some agents in order to create public
Perception that they should be to blame
Or
There's even parts of this plan
That suggests using Cuban Friendly's in order to pretend to be
Cuban communist in order to make it look like they were attacking something
These Cuban agents might even be dummies later.
Yeah it's splitting hairs a little bit here so I'm going to go ahead and give Alex half-credit
The document does suggest creating false perception but who's to blame
False
Fake attacks whatever
The colors that reads the part about sinking real or simulated chip
Refugees and I suspect
Closest he's going to get to a win
So you pretend that this fully supports
What can you just claim
But it does
I don't need The Disappearance of a win in order to protect the air of frustration
And that he's always right with
People questioning
This goes a long way toward
The second aspect
Does this clip putting that in motion which is the force the color to accept the notion
Everything is vague
And because of that all of Alex's unsupported and extreme
Conclusions are actually what the
It's Adam
Man with the collar read the words on the page that aren't there
Because Alex insist that they are
And it's something that the audience watches and on
Some level they probably understand
Yeah Alex understands reality better than you do so you need to subvert your reality to him
It is very bizarre and scary masks
It's the most f*****-up
Example of
Just
I mean
It's it's a big bully with authority
While you're holding a book
Yelling at you to say that the book says what they tell you
Doesn't matter what the book says
You say what they say
Yeah and it's
Work
And that it work
Over the phone
F***** up
Manuel that's me
Extreme ^ balance exactly
Like I can get it more if it's Alex's in imposing frame on your like on a desk
You know like trying to read
Quietly and he's got his
Big ass up in front of your butt
Over-the-phone Manchester know I'm reading the sentence
I was I was reading through Northwoods
I'm trying to find Blake
The instances of things that
Could be construed as
Like
Actual viola
Paris
Suggestion
And
The closest thing really is
That's sinking a boat load of cute Cuban refugees on Route 2
Florida
Disease does real or simulated
Right kind of the closest thing you're going to get in there
And
I mean
I think
Even in the context of the document
And the other stuff they're saying
Even a real thinking
Of the boat wouldn't involve be like
It's a real boat we're really thinking it and then
There will be life raft
Red stuff for everybody or whatever the people who are on board will be
Well I mean
But that's the point of the point of
The document
Is coming up with
A plan that isn't
Let's just go blow people up
You know the whole idea is very easy for them just to do so if that were the goal you would not need
If we wanted violence
Violence is our Jam man weave
You know
Make no mistake
The proposals listed in that document would lead to a whole lot of
Call goal of it being to provide a justification to attack you before they had time to enter
Mutual defense pact with
Soviet Union
Even the suggestion that they have about just
Harassing cubic
Could have severe consequences
Leaving aside any of the false flag ideas you might take away from the
It was a bad doctor
Good thing it was
Was flatly rejected
Because it would have resulted in a ton of death
However none of that death will be due to the false flag
Eggs that were suggested in the tech
That's just something Alex
Dentist
Right
I know there's another thing that people don't bring up often enough about that operation Northwood
Incredibly stupid plan
Not very well it's a bad plan
It's it's not going to achieve the goals
But they think it's going to
Probably not
And it's also not a plan
Sort of 8
Elevator
Throwing spaghetti at the wall coordinated
Obviously it's
The NSA Whoever has the document that was released
The full thing is 15 pages
But
Only a few pages of the actual
The other other
Sheets like the cover page and stuff like that
It's not a long
None of it is
Like
Very well-articulated about how these plans would work
Like one of the plans they have is just like
Start rumors and then the bread season
Lots of them
It does feel like it's more of a
Picture of a whiteboard of like one of those
Giant school classroom white boards with everybody's ideas written on it really small then somebody just took a
A picture
Ml
What's the plan
The the the actual
Appendix
Which is where
The actual
Be the sort of description
Plans
RN starts on page
Yeah the reason that it's confusing is because there is there's a numbering of the pages
From the original
At the bottom of the page right and what page it is in terms of be like 15 page
Does that were released
In terms of the pages that were released
It starts on page 10
And then it goes through
Fifth
So it it's just
Those five pages
And
One of them
Start rumors parentheses
Money
Use clandestine radio
Yeah
Start rumors spread
Just one though one of them is start riots and hear the Base main gate
Friendly Cuban
Not very specific
Put up on the wall
Go to
Okay
What else you got
Large fires
Scooters
I like that scooters who got scooters put it up on the board
So
I heard children's hands
With nothing else around it what it what it what was else going on
Also apparently
Outer space
For the spirit
People
Gavin accident
I mean it
Shadow Park
How are you not picking out something
Who cares
Glenn Corbett
Is
Listen we just
Figured out space
Like
Giada
Figured it out some 1962
And actually I looked at the date
This is like
Two weeks after John Glenn left
Warriors versus
Orbitz
So now that we got that figured out obviously we also have the capability
To knock it out of orbit magically actually hurting him
Doubt
Do you know what the
Big problem with this is
Oh boy
When you say big
That's a that's a relative value.
What is the
Premise
Of these false flag like what to be desired and gold
I believe it's to stop
The Cuban
From getting involved
The thing
It's to provide Justice
Suffocation to attack
Cuba
So whatever you do
Needs to be blamed on
Cuba
Cuba shot John Glenn out of
Lidl
Little Bill, all right now I'd I know that you and I would both think in order to
Say shoot John Glenn out of space
You would me
Rocket and Debbie capability to fire things in
Likes of which worm
Big short supply at that time
So much so that they were all monitored
All the time
I mean like I guess you could make an argument that they have
You know Alliance
Swiffer Soviet Union
And maybe they have rocket
It's inside your butt
At that point
Not really baby daddy Cuba is like a
Hey will get to you later
We got
Russia shooting people out of space
Yeah
John Glenn being false flag in space
He's not going to be a Prius for war with Cuba
Of all things
Concept
Actually convinced the world
That John Glenn was shot out of space By by the Soviet Union
The world war
Right
You can't just shoot a man out of space
That's that's just everybody's got to solve that problem first
That's my rule
Okay where is
View like sort of rules about no militarization of space coming to play
I think they came into play
Books like the 50s
I'm not sure but if it was
Before that then you could make an argument that it's the Wild West
Yeah that's a point
I didn't know it was wrong at the time
Yeah
I just think that this is stupid
I got to say
This is not
Volkswagen Bug bunnies place mats
Not on the list
Alongside start rumors start rumors
Steve Madden
Parentheses is one of them John Glenn got shot out of space by Cuba and barrettes
The fees are parentheses
Here's another one of the suggestions now
Consider the
Jump
Between this
Baseball swag
Log mortar shells from outside of Base interface somewhat damaged installation
I have low-tech and high-tech operations at the same time
People protect themselves against one of the other you can't be protected against both damn but use the word LOB
Top shot put
So throw couple grenades
Nearby somebody's house
I think maybe Alex doesn't have a great handle on this.
Might not know might not
Alex this is a fella from Denmark
Very exciting to get an international caller
Not so exciting find out that to you so maybe 90
We have the arms of the Illuminati
Time you attack Leelanau
Corruption
The Simon wiesenthal Center
Probably Alexandra
Island
Management
Maybe that late
Kind of
Connection Savannah
Inflation
Maybe
Well there's a lot of organization
It's a horrible thing
Way to push back on that
It's so Horace
It's so horrible to be called racist
Yeah that's all responses
Good but both promised to call her and from Alex
You know you
Is it some
Maybe startling
To go back in
You know just see the
Kind of
Consistency of these types of colors
Complete
Inability or unwillingness
I'm stopping any meaningful what do you think
Overtime that something would have changed
In some weight like he would have gotten more
Prepared for them or like
Would be more capable of pushing back or more capable of
The closing the closing the conversation down without having to go to help but it seems like it's been pretty much the same like
Law Group
Wish you hadn't said that Monday you know what you going to do that sounds nice actually I agree with you
Could be forgiven I think if you're in Alex's audience
If you came away with the impression that like
He agrees with all of the most toxic awful
Viewpoint
But
He doesn't want to say things to protect his own like
Bottom line
Or whatever
Like I don't
Think that's necessary
Sara Lee the case
It would not be very difficult to talk yourself into it if you're listening to this and
You know you have those
Portable toxic
I mean just based on all the non all the non word clue
The non-verbal clues
The tone of voice the way that he's pausing all of those little things could definitely make you add up to be in like
Well he didn't say his
1st and honest
Response
He said what he was supposed to to make the money
Yeah the refusal to
Even really recognize this guy is saying that like
The Jews run all of these groups that you are saying our evil at are like out to get
Patriots and Destroy Christian
You're not even
You just leaving that vert
I'm telling you the things that you're telling me
And you're just going like
Maybe
So this guy I would keep them on for a while and he asked him about that
Denmarkian who hates Jews come on
He asked him about like opposition to
To the EU
And I
That's wrong
About the EU
And then this guy
It goes forward even more
Most of them
Even the juice
I do know the Rothschild
I control the meat to Hendon
My two
Alright Sir William
Call from Denmark
The word
See how the Rothschilds run the media and then why you like to eat apparently
Those numbers are way off in terms of approval as I think he's very popular
The inverse in both country
Yeah I think you could probably find a couple
I know that grease was a bit lower
Pompeii
Call me favorability about
More than more than once
Yeah I think I think now though
Watching Everybody in the EU is watching Great Britain
Eat itself alive and I think they're all like
KB you douchebags
Full disclosure the numbers that I was talking about or from 2,000
So like
Stay relevant
Bully 2 2003
But I don't think that they've swung this far
The median is 26% unfavorable 72% favorable
Greece is the outlier here with 49% unfavorable 50
I mean if you recall what happened whenever the 2008 financial collapse and they force
Disgrace to eat it
Essentially
Instead of writing off all of the debt
Right
Outside of the EU even
Strong favorability
Among the countries pulled by the Pew Research Center
27% unfavorability among the 19 country medium
But they they looked at
9% favorable
Hey
So I don't know Alex is off of this guy's name from Denmark
I just don't feel like maybe maybe anti-semites from Denmark and Alex
Don't have their fingers on the pulse of the main
Good chemistry you can tell how this call was falling apart there at the end and outside like
You have to take care now
This is the Alex fulfilling the promise of talking to the lawyer of the student
From
Stratford
High School
Yeah in South Carolina
Not a very long interview and
This caller he has ended
Being there for some calls
It's pretty unfortunate
Because
The
The lawyer himself is blackmail
And he brings up
The dynamic Vincent play with
The video recording of the actual raid
Being similar in to the Rodney King
Beating
In terms of people being able to
To see the actual thing
Elicit an emotional
Respond to people
Experience it far more vividly than things they can only abstractly
Think about
Vanderbilt the number of callers call in and say how dare you compare this to rugby kick he was a horrible
Criminal
It's very
Weird
He seems like a just a lawyer who's trying to do a case
And what have you
I hadn't
Actually does
Kind of bring up the racial
Dynamic interesting
Yeah but it's on it's on societal unsatisfying
Unfulfilling
Dogs that are trained
Attack to train to be a
Two police in there
Police activity
They're used to dealing with criminal
Corsa
Do the criminals in
And to use that on
On
Age 30
Is the imagination
Imagination
Any one of our children going
Well what
What you said is very interesting and yeah and what we
Founded
If you can think back
60z used
The police dog in those in
Was that not only
Only blackston
Although this section of the hall
Entrance for the
The bus that was from
More Rural and
Okay
Remind and reminds me of apartheid in South Africa
Yeah it's a coincidence
I mean
You know if something reminds you of apartheid South Africa
It's because you just regular all the part-time
Where you are right now
It's in it's not apartheid South Africa is apartheid
South Carolina
It's always been there that's where it lives
It-it's
Very easy to convince Alex and his acquaintance
Unreal
Brick is huge
Bringing up
The two-thirds of the students
Who were caught up in the sweep
Were African Americans
And that
Is
An issue and for the
It's because the quince
Incidents because there were white students
Your 2/3
Two-thirds were African-American 1/3
Not every
Working America
Not if you
Think that the school is 2/3 African-American
Then maybe that is coincidental
But when you recognize it under 25%
Those numbers become
Much worse
Yeah they look real bad only if there's intent behind them I mean it makes
Tubi
The 2/3 number
Far more disproportionately
And it makes the
The 20 30 33%
The 130 other 1/3
Much less
Statistically relevant
That's what this is the extent to which Alex
It's just baffling for me
Like Alex does
He brings it up
She brings up apartheid South Africa
Spencer's very strange to my meme
What
Okay
Here's the problem I have
Here's a problem I have and it's a big one and it's one that I don't think we're going to get around probably not
If something reminds you of apartheid South Africa
I don't care what that thing is
It's a problem that needs to be fixed from the
Bottom up
If it reminds you of apartheid South Africa
It needs to be destroyed
So
I don't understand how you could even bring that up about the movie and then and then be moved on
Just be like hey that reminds me of South Africa
No big deal alright well I'm going to keep going
That is not okay
They like it and apartheid South Africa
Whatever it is
Fair enough enough
Yeah well I mean your policy there I think is it sensible
Move over it
Yeah yeah yeah
At least ask
A number to follow-up questions.
Don't accept
Any excuse that it's a coincidence
That's not the Alex Jones wife
Infowars is not made for follow-up
Coincidentally
It's like sucks Africa
Particularly when the thing that's reminiscent
Is targeted harassment and a
Abuse of black
Yep
Yeah
Anyway
In the past
There is some fun and there is some not fun
Ain't that the way
Always love
A nice
Customer service call on are always fun
The best
Dogs are pretty sweet
There's something there's something about Louisiana Dentures message
That is going
To stick with me I'm going to be thinking about very sad
Get another bite 27 Old voice that's possible
Astro
The nature of this stuff
Looks like the new pretty
Frequent
Instances of anti-Semitic collars that Alex has
No ability to push back on
And the fact that one of them is dead in Illinois who calls in every other every third show
Get through concert
Bentley is a regular that's
Troubling
Virus Thing 2
Like it's just the
The Echoes of the present
And that in ways that are
Kind of
I mean it is
It is
One thing that I love about the past episodes
Is that they are emblematic of something that's so crucial
Which is just a very simple
If you don't deal with the problem it's going to get worse
True you know
So many we see so many things where it's like
We didn't deal with a problem
When did
Information problem was there
Every reason to think it would take care of itself kind of or like
I suppose you know if you
Take time to know about things
You would hear these
Things to be like
Who's going to leave no idiot would buy me this noise and that's
That's unfortunately turns out to have been a naive
Position
Yep yeah that is
What is the second element to event that is
If you look back
Opossum you see all the
Dislike
Constant similarity
You know basically what you're saying
As if you flip it
It really does
Put into perspective the way that Alex
Deals with
Like immediately
And these stories that are breaking news now in the present-day that
Breaking news 20 years ago they doing the same s*** it
You know it kind of cuts both ways
Ideally it should be able
To illustrate somebody who's caught up in that
Wright cycle that like
No this is
This is the same
That's all
The carousel carousel
Yeah I mean
It's it's
It's hard to it's hard to not think like
Well this is a problem from then
But you know like when we were talking about with the Bingo cards this is a problem this is the same problem from the same
Bad thinking that's been going on for forever
And it just never been dealt with
Because either we never
Found a successful way to deal with it
Or we don't have the political or capital
Necessary to deal with the problem or the prior
Yeah I would have to be because
And it's so obvious
The biggest problem we're having right now is most people don't believe in the real world
Isn't that
That
Is the
The place the the point
From which
The so many crap
It is
It's just we don't believe in the real world
Point where a lot of bulshit start spreading out how to make you believe in real
The ultimate question
And it's pretty
Apparently to make people believe in on reality
Czechoslovakian dog
Oh my God
Eastern European murder dogs from
20 years ago
Another episode of a likely be as bomber ish
Website.com
We are on Twitter that knowledge underscore fight
But until then I'm Neo I'm Leo I'm dzx
Clark
I really feel like I should have thought of a
A bit during the time away
I had a whole week
Yeah but you were little failure in
Non sinking about
True
Here we go
The floor is lava
Holding
Alex
Kristen color