Important
I have great respect but knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Exit around worship at the altar of Selena little bit about
Alex
Jones Auto
Something caught in my throat
Oh damn
Quick question
Well my bright spot today Jordan is that I finally got around to finishing
Better Call Saul finally made it through the last season
Spoiler
Pretty thoughts I guess so good not enough level
Baton
That is fair always
Love that Lavell Crawford
So that's always near and dear to my heart tour in comic 4
Before just landed up in a weird situation long before he was on Breaking Bad
He was on
80s comic shows
Regularly Elysium on there
Thought it was hilarious find me and my buddies had his CD taking a fat break
Clan MacLeod
I'm a large dude
We got it man
But you just soak the delivery so great week and my buddies got scolded
Because he came to Deja Vu The Comedy Club in Columbia we got
Scolded cuz we were laughing too hard
Man and his voice is so distinct in any really uses it well
Yeah
Some other thoughts that I had
That's it
I don't know
I thought it was I don't know if this is their intention
But I ran out of
Patience with the character of Saul
I think it is there.
Yeah after six seasons how can you not be tired of a fast-talking con man
Well there's Thursday like pesos
Obviously that runs through especially like some of the earlier seasons
Turned in
To Saul Goodman
That is is pretty interesting like a person does terrible things but
What you feel for them actually
I just thought it was an interesting exercise
As in like
Where is the point where that has
We've had enough of that
Is it is intentional Bravo correct
Yeah
It's fascinating
The how how
What would I say
It's fairly difficult
Create a character that is
Morally bankrupt
And then still set your TV series with that
In as the hero in their own mind
You know
So he's traveling throughout this world and you see all these justification
Did you make
And you can feel the pesos of it right
But in real life you'll be like f****** s*** out of here for you man go
I also think it's not morally bankrupt enough
Do you know
I think there's a little bit of trying to take out of both bags if that's even a metaphor
But anyway it was enjoyable enough but I did resent that
It seemed to me that there were like 10 episodes of season the last season there were 13 but I didn't
It was fairly late at night
And I was like all right I'm on I'm on episode 835
Another app
Then you got to finish it
You can't not anyway with your bright my bright spot is
So
This is not a spoiler
Like Walt and Jesse Breaking Bad come back
For cameos
Got to say
Refreshing is hell
Zia's he Jessie
You know it right you forget
Like the amount of
Charm
It's like characters a lot of fun character that somehow you're like
Yeah man I'm route
For you while I'm not sure if that got old
Forgotten cuz it's been awhile since I watch Breaking
It does make me want to watch Breaking Bad again but I still have not
You know what's weird
Where is my response to Walt was this a******
Who knows
Viator up to doing that I apologize
Final Fantasy 9
Rice
Started doing the taco
Started doing a Final Fantasy 1 through 50
Marathon
He's just going
I think he said that I think there's like an hour break but essentially he's just started them take a little nap he's been going on for 3
Days or something now I didn't dislike
50 to 3 hours straight if you trying to speed run
Okay is there even a record
Lydia strikebreakers adjust settings own
Assume that it what it really is
Is an active Ulta
Right somebody
Is going
To do that
So what he's doing is doing that in order to save the rest of the human race from half
Is he doing it for charity
No I don't think so
I have no idea this opportunity perhaps
Everybody's watching I'm not you
To it here's here's what I think
Thinking about
So I know I've only played the Final Fantasy 7 remake
At your best
No it's a modern game
Has like the Aesthetics of
Of a
Good a fairly current game and I've seen the original Final Fantasy
B7
Back wheels Graphics look like it was only gone
The seventh one
Right
Who's the first one like azure
It was
I mean I want to say it was more like
Did Doug you had like
Just pixels then you would walk up and then left and it'll be like you got into a fight
Near like
Fight and they're like
You won the fight
The first one was Bubble Bobble
It's shocking to me I mean that would even be fun
I mean I don't want to watch this guy play for like
Days at a time but it would be very interesting to see the evolution of
I like the style and the Aesthetics of it and like
That that would be
Let's be worth it to skim through and then I saw some of the
Video game and I sat there watching for like 15-20 minutes
I would be like
Okay with putting on in the background
And he's playing it
You slowly losing his mind Izu
At one point I think I turned it on
And he had not spoken for like a half hour I don't know what's going on I do think there's something so great about
Endurance-based
Comedy
There's something
So
Kindred
I feel to him doing
Something and absurd just because you know it needs
Like the George Lucas talk show with their life they special they did 30-something hours of all
All the live-action Star Wars movies
It's what you got to do
You end up going nuts do that sometime every episode of Infowars Marathon
We will live that long we got to do okay
Somebody's going
Jordan today
We have an episode
To do it won't be days long
Situation
2003 episode
Okay here's why all right
I got down to business and I was I was I couldn't go back to
To the present we're going to check in on him
Clip of Alex from the 28th
So that was when
Gotcha
And I just was like I'm out
He sounds like s*** yeah why does it sound so shity a reminder Steven the audio he sounds like someone hit him with
The tranq darts like right before they started the show
It sounds
Sucks there's no spark of life in it
A-to-z
Bomber he doesn't go to calls
I got to get out of here man we got to talk about the present
I'm listening to this is making me sad
It's the end of the
The year I don't want to deal with that
He's just doing like
One of his big narratives
Was the covid-19 conspiracy theory that he's pretending is current but it's
The talking point that he had from January
Like he's just reusing it as if it's some new bombshell
Like I can't I can't do the
Anniversary of him make
Thing that b******* claim Sono your mind resets every year
Greatest reset
So I decided I'm going to stick around in December 2003
And this
Is a roller
Okay
At the beginning
You're going to think
You're going to be really serious about it
And then
You still going to be a little mad but there's some fun
The first Jordan let's say hello.
Got a couple of very light happy birthday matter
The first happy birthday Phil on March 16th from your favorite sister thank you so much you are now policy walk
Thank you very much I'm not possibly be that delayed
In advance
She did that on purpose
Add scented in it like
August
Just waiting like I bet they're go
Going to do it next
I don't know what the deal is anyway happy birthday
Happy birthday happy birthday Bell AutoZone
Bell
Hazard bow
Thank you so much your nail polish
Happy birthday
Kevin Love
2012 numbers are actually adrenochrome thank you so much right now policy wonk
I'm confused but also those are just words that really know how to put that together
Unlove in 2012
Was on the Cavaliers
Ari might still have been on the temperature
I'm wondering if this is a kony2012 take but I just think that whenever anybody much
Tony really
Stole 2012 from the Mayan apocalypse
Your mother walks policies and he'll thank you so much you're not opposed
Big robots
Sixth just read Brave New World in Surprise Alex is still a dumbass thank you so much and I'll probably want
Very much that was
Is the biggest Revelation from that book
Text did you read Brave New World Revisited
Next Dream Queen and pizza boy thank you so much
And finally Violet Beauregarde and they actually asked me to make sure that I point
Chimeras are people too
Thank you so much you're now
About
I'm a policy wonk
Alright so
We're in the past
December 11th 2000
I think it was first clip you're going to
To get why I said
This might be in a
Infuriating seeming episode
Call Kurt.
Poncho
Joining
Phyllis Schlafly is on but this
Twists
In a way that you wouldn't
Spectacularly
I'm probably over selling this in terms of it being some kind of like really fun thing but I found it remarkably
Ugly Entertainer
I also love the idea of Alex saying hello to the ships at sea
That was a that was a turn
I wasn't sure if he was on some sort of special broadcast for the troops
This is a Uso radio
Yeah
So there's some new stories that Alex gets 2nd and here is the first one
And we're about to die
The website
Paramilitaries
Northern
Except
Did hold on
Play did he just say everybody doing for the last 24 years while
Market
We'll see this is why Alex was concerned about the euro
To this has to do with it
Trio of bombs that were detonated in Dublin
On May 17th 1974 ultimately killing 26
And injuring hundreds more
This was followed up by another bomb that went off in Mont
2003 former Irish Supreme Court Judge Henry Barron Was preparing to release her
For detailing and investigation
Into British intelligence
Involvement
In the troubles
And one of the things that was a big takeaway was that British
Intelligence of likely cluded
With a loyalist terrorists in the carrying out of
These bombings
Everyone is shocked
This is awful but
Even the underlying report that Alex is using as a source stopped short of saying that it can be proved
Alex Azar
Uncertain and I'm careful about.
Detail
Another detail but Alex is getting wrong is that he saying that these bombings that British intelligence is suspected of involvement in
Happened in Northern Ireland
The two cities that they occurred in are both in Ireland
There's a pretty critical detail when you consider the Dynamics of Alex's ideas about false flags and all that
But you just get it wrong and then it's established and he moves on that's what was confusing me
Allegiances bombing Northern Ireland
To blame it on the Irish
But that's not what's happening
We just bombed
The IRA giving clandestine support to loyalist
Terrorist
In Ireland
That was
That's the story
In a way that would lead you to
The conclusion you came to
Cuz I mean historically
I'm going to I'm going to just go out on a limb here and I'm going to say
The British have not been on the Irish
Woodside
So Alex has this story
And a bit poorly
Natural gets details wrong
Nea like actual point
Of what this this aberrant the judge
Yeah I was putting out Dorothy
These stories are actually about
What
He does get back to another story
This was on our last episode
Seemed very strange
If you recall there was a judge
That said
Hey
If you said Jesus
Put you in jail
I do recall the prison
That was
I was very confused by this natural and Alex brings it back up
And we get some new details
Word
Facebook
Good for you
Little thing you should know about Samuel cat
I was going to say there's no way this guy is a cool dude
In 2009 he resigned his position is Judge instead of facing an impeachment hearing over charges that he sexually assaulted
Did multiple former employees
He ended up being sentenced to 33 months in prison for obstruction of justice involving those accusations
And in the course of it came out to that like he would tell
Repeat like people he was harassing that like I am the law sucks
I was trying to dig up his stuff about him saying that no one could say Jesus if his graduation but there weren't any stories of
About it from 2000
Three what you think there would be
If that was a true story
Fox News would have turned that into a
Years-long investigation
Multi here's the thing
What was poking around
Then I found an article on a Christian blog
And it started to come into Focus
Apparently this story about cat comes from a book by David Limbaugh
Titled persecution
How Liberals are Waging War against
Christian
According to this book
Kent made the proclamation in May 1995
Alex is reporting this as a present a story cuz he's probably just seen blogs that are repeating this thing that was published
In Limbaugh's book
Which came out
In August 2003
Probably biking
He thinks that this is
The thing that just happened that's because of lazy
Opportunistic reporting that goes on in
Sensational ass
Victimization blog
This claim is reported all over apocalyptic Christian Media and its told differently in different venues
For instance it's often reported as a threat about a graduation in the outlets that want to appear more news like
John Hagee doomsday preacher wrote about Canton his book
Can America survive
10 Prosthetics signs
We are the
The terminal generation
And it hits
Two little different
For one thing
It isn't about graduation ceremony anymore at this time it's about anybody praying in school
It also seems a bit more severe
Quote
Anyone who thinks I'm kidding about this better think again
Anyone who violates these orders is going to wish that he or she had died as a child when this court gets through with it
Alright
Okay eventually we're going to have
How to deal with lying as a problem
Right they're going to wish they died as a child this is insane
What the f***
Is happening
I don't know what you can't just say this
So I looked around a little bit more and I was able to
Find some news for 1995
Explain with
Okay
In Galveston Texas a lawyer representing four students brought a suit against the school
System because they had
Formal prayers
Before graduation ceremonies
And before every home football game
Head because of folks also they routinely would hand out Bibles
What's on school ground
Sprout a Class Act
Action suit against
The school district
I can find no concrete evidence that can't ever said anything about people who said Jesus wishing they hadn't been born but VSCO
Did eventually make it all the way
In Santa Fe Independent School District
Versus do
Where the Court ruled that these prayers
Even if they were written and delivered by students
Constituted policy of the school
And therefore broke the establishment
Claws
Interesting bit of trivia the lawyer who represented the school district in their argument that the arm feel had it
Was Jay Sekulow
Who would go on to be one of Trump's top attorneys and they perjured himself during the impeachment hearings
Life
So weird characters my backup
Does make sense in a certain level in a hopeful way
You can't be that many people with
No shame
Right
The fact that they are recycling
It doesn't fly that like there's enough people who wouldn't
Show me so many nights on the on the chessboard you know you can't have more or less
Well I guess
I was going to I was going to robot that but this kind of works for your argument to and that is that like
There may be a
Honda of
People who have no shame
But there's only
A few who have any Talent over here.
Sacrifice Randolph
Anyway I don't know if these quotes that are being thrown around are accurate and
More likely what happened is that at
The judge said if they were going to have a prayer
Sectarian
Which is Being Framed as he was anti Jesus and if you say.
I will say however the same Kansas
Giant piece of s*** and if there's anyone that I think has the character
Possibly say something like that quote
I'm not going to say it's impossible that this
This quote is real but if it
Is
It's being used
Very out of context
And it happened in 1995 years later on Alex ascioti's pretending
It's a little bit more
Yeah I mean a guy who's
Documented is saying things along the lines of I am the law
May have allowed a couple of Judge Dredd punishments in his time it might have been
The government
I mean I was thinking about it
It would be
The jet like us
Covering something that happened in 24
As if it was
Like happening right
Floppy
That's terrible
Yeah let's
Parable
Anyway
Does mother bad news
You all want
You love everybody
You can read Harry Potter which is witchcraft
The craft activity
But if you're
If you're in kindergarten
And you pray
Over a snack
You go to jail
Are you getting rest
I don't
Understand how you could
Could not see the glaring difference between
The two even as an offhand comment of being like Oh but you can
Talk about witches in Harry Potter all day there's that you want like
That's so not similar to pray
And also
I don't think you can get arrested as a kindergartener you can
Antritis
An adult but only if we pray
3 states Mississippi
Is everyone could be tried as an adult in Mississippi Louisiana because sometimes how do you pronounce
Okay
Misses
Have you been hanging out with a guy makes copies Alex's table
Mississippi
So I'm Alex has some
Deceit about this whole story about the you going to jail
For saying Jesus
Worshiper
The Muslims wear their head
Dresses
Accepted
First Amendment
Everything I can tell it would have been
Totally fine for a student to thank Jesus in
Acceptance speech
These You Came. The prayers that were being held before football games and before the graduation ceremony
Do you like a actual formal Benedict
Typically in cases like this Alex needs to lie about details in order to make the situation seem more egregious than a text
2 years since the real world version of events is actually fairly sensible
If you're not a zealot
But you kind of get
What the point is
Yeah you can't do
Alex needs to like
Lie
Because it's
Acquired
In service of amplifying feelings of victimhood the only thing that makes any of these stories
Useful things
Well I mean
Fuel if he were
Not to lie
Then he would have
Have to as a free speech absolute
Be against prayer
Being in that school
I think you find a way around it
Well his way around it is lying
Butcher but you could lie differently
I feel like that doesn't
The fundamental thing that I say
You can preserve your free speech absolutism by lying about
A different thing
Right right
No I agree with you so you could like twice
That that's the Alex Jones Way
Alex
He's a good mind
To do something about this
He's going to do something about this
Letter writing
Diabetic
You're going to need a timer
And he's an impact all of our
I think if there was a judge you was like
You can't say Jesus
At your graduation or will put you in jail for 6 months
I would totally say Jesus as much as possible
F*** you
Yeah Lanvin ACLU would defend you from Bono
I do love this
I got a good mind to go back in time and belt
The most banal use for a time machine one could imagine
You don't like I think that there is something to be said for like
Like if you are a student there and this situation that I was lying about is actually the way he describes
You should go Jesus or something like that
This is an inappropriate effusive
Student I think would be well within their right
To do that
For Alex to go there just
An insane person
Right
Hind
Side of the realm of like
Principal and more like
Exactly
That really is how it feels
Kitchen for me Chef seems a little bit
Student protests would be
We talked about
Louisiana man tape man
Episode
No longer
Super effective to like 80% on Alex's tabulation but he keeps his mind
Hey running tabulated and I have some great news
Backup
Things are on the upward swing
Giving
Some people that
Still have refused to watch him
No
It's real
Don't want to come out of that
Sleepy world
Percentage
What you say
Let's one
We we get
Literally
99.9
Percent
They did they love
Bankruptcy
He's thinking this guy for what he's doing but I think
More what do you think
Infor is like
Thank you for giving me a
Chard
Hundred percent absolutely
I am no longer down in the dumps with Louisiana tape man we are cooking
79.9
Both of us know that 99.9 isn't absolutely insane number but it makes me feel a hell of a lot
You better I appreciate what you're doing sir but I cannot imagine that you're giving out enough tapes to have a decimal
Decibel point this is nonsense at least
Yeah
Not a chance
So on his last show rrls episode weeks.
Salix having a conversation with his water filter sponsor
And on this episode Alex has another bit of broker programming with his water filter sponsor
It's a different person I'm sorry the same company and they make the same joke
Quickly
Chiron
Special
Whitewater
Radio host
Just get 6 months
Imprisoned
Absolutely nuts
Let's see you say that
6 times and that's equivalent to being a judge
Convicted of sexual assault
Multiple employees Route 3 months more than that
That's what I mean this is just a little stale
So Phyllis Lyon
And she has she has some point
That she wants
For those who may not be as familiar with talked about Phyllis Laughlin quite a while it's been a long time but she has come up she's
Been on Infowars in the past
That we've discussed
She is an old school
Far-right anti-feminist
Anti-communist
Yeah I figure
John Birch Society Jason
You better involved with them and then started
The Eagle Forum
Which is largely a lot a lot of work to do with
Anti women's causes
CareSpot in history for it very very strongly Auntie reproductive health
Access
Very strongly against women and workplaces
Against women making
Decisions for themselves
Differently than that but
At the end of the day there's a lot of that
It's okay if she comes on and these are the
Issues
That are most
Important
Well I think
One of the biggest
Is the out-of-control federal court
The judicial activist
Are trying to
Play claw
How to do things
No elected legislature would do
I'm so we find
Jimenez attack
State after state
The dead rabbit
The Pledge of Allegiance
Deborah
The ten
And to redefine
Marriage
So the out-of-control court
Yes
So out of control control Pledge of Allegiance
Getting rid of
10th Amendment
What you mean by that is like ten commandments not being posted in government building
Natsu
People are moving towards marriage equality in
Makes her mad
They're out of control
So don't seem like very serious grievances that will tell me the country
If we don't have children saying the Pledge of Allegiance every morning
How will they learn 20 years later how
I'm saying it was for them to say the Pledge of Allegiance every morning
Right maybe I'm
Weird but I don't really have that much of a problem with a pledge of allegiance
I know it's a little bit f***** up and kind of weird
You know just conceptually but
I don't really think it affected me that much
Saying the Pledge everyday I never felt that I had actually pledged my allegiance to anything
Not really it was the formality or whatever and knowing more than any
A perfect world maybe it wouldn't be something that happens
But the priorities I realize I'm not sure that it indoctrinates kids or anything like I don't
I don't know it's
It's weird
Just from
Like what
It is a stamp
I could be convinced
We have
A staggering list
Problem
That effect
Every single thing that we do worldwide
Play through now if we're talking about dividing up
Energy necessary to solve
These problems I'm not going to put a lot of energy towards the Pledge of Allegiance sure that's kind of situation
Begone
There seem to be as fundamental issues
Schools in
Students
That would be
Much more important
I find I mean but fundamentally I find it insane to pledge ones allegiance to any country or govern
Body or anything along those lines
See that's why I could be sweat
I wouldn't pledge my allegiance in f******
You
You have to earn my allegiance on the
The daily every single day. Where's that cat
Alex and Slam Flea in here I don't know if you heard this story
About this judge
Bratz your talk with the attitude
Control4 just judges hold marinade
Yeah
We cannot let the
The judges presume
To make law
Such as telling us
The Pledge of Allegiance
Probably can't have Mary
Why does a man and a woman
There's a quote from the judge
Quote
Marshall
Score
Houston Texas
Accountright
Is it outrageous or something
Constitute
Acknowledge
God
And this is why I am urging
That the US
Exercise its right
Established in
3 of the US,
2 West Rogers
Accord
Over the acknowledge
Mother of God
Telling that Alex can ramble off a story about Judge Kent is iffy
The current headline
Response to it without any awareness
She's just accepting Alex's framing
This was a big
In case in terms of religious
Expression at school
Like I said it ended up going all the way to the Supreme Court who made their ruling on it in June 2000
This is an eight-year-old story but at the point Alex's covering it
The ruling from the court is only three years back
Is it squarely in the Wheelhouse of both Alex and Felix Aviles
Right there on awareness of this is pretty f****** embarrassing
When Alex rattles office headline Phyllis should recognize what he's talking about in say that was eight years ago in that
Happened but she doesn't
He could be that
She doesn't know the case in which case
She clearly doesn't take the issue she's covering as seriously as she
She pretends to be the chinos full well that it's an old story but they pushing it as if its current is help
In terms of pushing her own narratives and the agenda
It's not that compelling to argue the courts need to be overhauled
Because of a news story from almost
The decade ago that such an on news
Everyone on this show thinks it happened last week
That's not going to really get the audience
Excited
You need that immediately
To make a threat to the audience feel press
Like I Need a Hero
Step Up
Victimization they're being told there
Right right
To be clear on this
This was already decide
In the Supreme Court
Yeah that's this point in time
3 years ago
Buy a d2000 supreme court if I
Recall correctly
The fight before Supreme Court that stole the election for Bush
Brett's not age
That's not it
Left-leaning judicial Act
Here's where you're wrong
I forgot that Aleta was still on the left wing-back
Alita was not on the
Court wait no
You was
Yeah
We wait
A 2000
Thomas was on the court hears what
Confused
Because the Supreme Court does come up
And Connor is a vote
Yeah
Aledo replaced her
And that's why I got confused because in this episode there is a mention of Every Day O'Connor
She's dead by 2000
Right I think she retired
Call Albert like what
What's up
Where do you place her on the ideological Spectrum
Very less
For now
But conservative
Apparently
She's a arch feminine
Those are real
Appointed by Republican
President
We're just simply
Somehow
Cheated or mislead
By the
By the people they appointed
For example
Ferrari
Appointed Sandra O'Connor
And he made the
Mistaken during his campaign
They're saying he was going to
Point of woman
And then she was the only woman
Shown
My guess is
He said to her Sandra of course you're pro-life aren't
She said of course
Surprised
And then she
Want to write
Took the appoint
My dad has
Things ever said
Too bad how they are
Reagan
Yeah that sounds right
Correction
Same bolita was not on the court until 2000
6 yeah she retired in 2005 or newer retirement 2005
Are timelines a little bit off
What was the one that I was
Robert
No no it was
Ibaby is the Tony guy
I'm great at Supreme Court names
The guy who looks like a toad
I think he's dead now
The guy who looks like a toad you say
Sure I do that doesn't narrow it down as much as we'd like Connor is still alive
No s***
92 years Young
Could have could have swore she
How about that barely know
John Paul Stevens
Is everything else now I think Kennedy
Yes
Candidate David souter
Okay
Through
Every every Justice
Politically active at the age of 12
So I don't have all of the Supreme Court Justices from 2,000. Feel right to me that'll
Toledo would have been there that early
We all we all have time
Confusion
Yes accurate was appointed by Bush
A fair amount of the justices on the
Supreme Court are kind of like
In a lot of it does feel a bit like
You know just fill in the blank of things to grab onto
But yeah
So Sandra Day O'Connor
Noted
Are fairly conservative
Member of the Court
Was a
Big-time feminists to trick trick
It's just because you didn't overturn Roe v Wade
But they're responding to
So now I told you there's a little bit of a toy
And here's here's where it starts to come into play
I like
Might not understand
The way his audio
Because they don't like Phyllis Schlafly
What
Interesting she Pals around with
The neocon
Well that's fair support
Bushcutz bear she's support
What's the GOP in general
And
Alex is trying his audience
Understand
Set the neocon
Are all
Bucking communist
They are all trotskyite evil who are in disguise
Because the only people who are pure are the Ron Paul types
The real severely
Right-wing people who think that
Anybody like George Bush at his secret communist
Before those people were the governor
And now that that was back whenever the tables have turned
Do you know the the Neo cons were running everyday
Yeah and so Alex doesn't realize this and I don't think he expects
That to be the response that they get when they take calls spray
So Phyllis is in there and they take calls and they're pretty hostile
Hey Alex
Thanks for the opportunity
Shuffle you don't followed you for years
I'd like to know what Grassroots movement you're going to get it
Involved with
No
Representative Ron Paul in Texas
In the middle of summer headache
Stop funds for UNESCO
A wonderful Amendment to the Giants
State
Commerce
I didn't hear a peep
Anything from Kelly shaft late to get on that know you may have done it
But you know
George Bush we knew George Bush when he was attacked
Workforce
Board nominees Workforce Development
Boards are running our counties
Running our town
Appointed
We are inundated
Confusion mr. Boyd chedelic that quits Indiana
UNESCO need 60 million dollars
All bad
Phyllis
Well you're right
And I was too tied up with other issues that I didn't get on the
Ernesto fight but I can
Completely agree with you
And everybody who
Who knows me knows that I oppose you
Enough
Getting out of your Nesco
Best things
Ronald Reagan
Well
I don't think there was a good reason.
Look I hate Phyllis Schlafly but she's being too polite
That's that's
There's got to be a feeling of like
Do you know who the
Exactly what I was thinking
What have
You done
I didn't work on the UNESCO fun do you even know what UNESCO f****** cares about
UNESCO
I am your favorite heads favorite skinhead
Before you were born
I was trying to limit people's rights when you were wearing short pants
For women could wear pants I was trying to keep them from wearing pants
That's how deep I go
Yeah this isn't like disrespectful honestly terrible yet
What you kind of like to see but it's quite a surprise to me that like
I thought they take calls and it would you know
Refined or boring
That's fascinating back then they hadn't
They didn't have the people in power so they were just trying to tear down every
Restructure
On the air go ahead
Hey are you guys doing
I kind of don't like
Take away that
You apologize
Republican Administration
I noticed that you
You said that
Reagan was
Full when I came
Saturday O'Connor
Phillips
Said that long beforehand that she's a pro board and now
Bush
I will tell you
Did I public
Opposed Pandora Connors
But at the time
Bush
Are you aware that
Miguel Estrada by the way
Is a pro board
Wedding friend-of-the-court briefs on half-and-half
Woman against pro-life
I have heard
Alright
Now you can't tell me Bush wasn't aware of that
I mean
Bo Derek
Excuse for that
Well I guess
Defending
I don't know
These people do not like her
Just feel like they're coming at her with a lot of grievances that she has
No control over whatsoever answers are fair I don't know ask him
Look for him yeah
Show me there is a fairness to that answer but like
This is exactly what would happen
Based on the way out
His prime
Anybody who's supporting bush
Is
Up to something or they're not ideologically pure enough whereas Phyllis Schlafly is been a major
Part of building d
Extreme right-wing
The Alex and his audience
To enjoy
At this point
Now at the same time
She's also Savvy enough to understand that like
All right there is a need
For me to work within some
Instructure is pursue these policy goals at the point when
There is a possibility of getting a
The past
A pipe dream nonsense
Things about
Ron Paul ever even making it out of the primary
It's not going to fly
Beetle respect that they have no respect
For the fact
What you like
Done here
It's hard for them to buy the way I talk
Love not heard of Provo pro-life
Proboard I'm down for it that's what I've got
But but it does
It does feel like
Concept
Of exploiting the system
Is not one that they are willing
To accept you know like
Definitely is not like
Listen
I agree with what Bush did about
She's like listen I disagree with them too
Can only ask
Exploit what I can explain
To accomplish
The goals that you and I both
I don't have the power
To do whatever I want and just say
It's a function I think of and idealism that was marrying Infowars back then that I don't think exist anymore
Taking over a little bit.
At this point there is like this idea but we have to have this expectation of
Everybody Must
You must demand them do everything
Yeah that you want
It's
It's kind of interesting to see
It run up again
Someone like Phyllis Schlafly
Right boot
By all accounts be
Royalty
In the space
That's it I mean yeah she that's like she built dizzy
In terms of far-right being a piece of s***
You know
A big part of it
Big Park
So I just thought this was funny
There's nothing really groundbreaking here but
When they went to commercial Alex forgot to turn off his mic
Wheeless
The gravity filter
Design
+ 888
Toll-free AAA
I just had a fun night about that
I'll pick behind the curtain it doesn't need to be like s*** talking whenever somebody. You know whose Sole shoes in fun is that is
Sometimes just
What are the times
Do you have a definite recognition that Alex
Screening them
Call 2002
Just a little fun
Back in the day this was such a weird operation that he could have them Mike's
Ellen during commercial what fun
Anyway Phyllis leaves
Man I feel bad for a little bit not really cuz you suck
I feel bad
Cuz as soon as she leaves Alex Tarkan talkingshit on her
He's doing a little dirty
Rosewater corruption
You're a communist if you're not for it
Where is
Well I don't know why
Have a great travel
Mike
Do a little disrespectful impression and
If that's something that she's playing Coy like I don't know
Securities is like any time we've ever guessed it on a live show that can
Continues after we've left
Like the fear is the moment we get off there
Just going to start talking
Consider these assholes
But I know that the
Good better good hose
Just would never do that
That right you know
So to have him do it both reinforces a good host would never do that and also it could happen to you
You
I thought I found it just tastes
But then also the other thing too that you noticing that clip is this
Like just
Consistent things that Alex does
Where you have something that key Zappos
Was too or bad
And the only way he can talk about it is also by pointing out something else that's bad
You are mad at her butt
Ann Coulter
So much worse
Right
There's that deflector anything that is just
Use can't deal with anything on it
Its own term
It's almost the apotheosis of that like choose the lesser of two evils concept
He's like that's literally his guiding principle of like oh I found this thing was bad
But mathematically this things worse
So I guess I'm cool with this
And yet at the same time you can't do that as it relates to
The GOP
Wild
Yeah
But the holders continue
I would like to talk
Because I would have liked to ask her if she wants
White 911 the road
Centuries OverWatch
I don't know
And also not a creature from Jekyll Island
She was chews friends of G Edward Griffin
What are you talkin about she ever read
Creature from Jekyll Island pets to probably has a special thanks in the book
It's crazy
Crazy
That's a wild
It's a code
Do you think she ever read creature from Jekyll Island
Like ask
G Edward Griffin what he thinks about Phyllis Schlafly
Addario yeah yeah
Man
They just eat their own they just do
You know the cycle for these right-wing
Shitheadsteve
Is that that rap lyrics
I'm who your favorite MC tells
The kids about
Schlafly is to these assholes
But it is
It is like a generational tide almost you know like
That's that early generation pushes things as far as they can and then there's a slow push back
And during that time. Because they didn't
When
You know cuz they didn't
Defeat the enemy
They are
Treated as failure
Here's another your treated as somebody who's capitulated
Pushing things so f****** far
You don't even notice how far they pushed it
You make you feel like they didn't do it
No they
Eat their own during that.
Then a new piece of s*** comes along
You know you have all this stuff it's an endless cycle
But simultaneously there is a little bit of
Probably
Sexism in there to pick up getting the same treatment
And he is definitely somebody who would be that past generation
Didn't get s*** done true
Ron Paul isn't kidding
Yeah I'm going to go out on a limb and say that you might
Maybe correct the right-wing has chosen a woman as a scapegoat
This is unprecedented the right-wing necessarily but Alex's audience in callers have
Clear a pretty clear
Alex has his collar and he's like yeah
My tapes Bohemian Grove
Person that I want to ask
Mr. post the same
That I called
And ask them
Ann Coulter
Set about
Offend
Supportive
You know
Quarter is as
Having done
Good things
When not heating
Bohemian Grove
The pace in the worship
Call Deedee mobile
No one is denying it
How was your day going
Worshipping Muslim stuff
Alright
Weird
80k one
Prayer
Needs to be in schools
But only my
Alright know that Muslims
Stop know if you catch somebody worshiping that Muslim self
Six months in jail
Suggesting a path that Alex should have gone down
Which is bringing up
How can she support George Bush if he went to Bohemian Grove
That would have been good I would have been good been good
Because then
I could convince
Her to not support bush
Because Alex is still holding onto like
The value that she holds as a far-right figure
And you don't understand
Be The Winning Edge in the history of all this done in a way that the audience
Not everybody
Appreciate
Hey so he could get Phyllis onto his team
Of this
Extreme
Only
Ron Paul only the farthest of farthest right is is good right
Then there could be some value in that for him
And meanwhile
Stalking was trying to tear her down
Daughter she's one of them even like the rest of them come on you have to say
But the things you say work
The other thing that I want to
Point out that I think is really funny
Is that
Alex is obsessed with David
Gherkin
Is this like
SS gergen goes the world you know like it's
Everytime it brings up Bohemian Grove
It's like
David gergen is talked about it
Yeah
I mean it was in the Washington Times
Admittedly
No one's denying
Maybe they were twenty years prior to this or something
Maybe they didn't want people to come to their phone and nudity and there aren't a lot of water
Easy walk in
Yeah
Sure
David gergen is not a onion
Notable
Figure now the public figure easily
Bruno butt
I don't know
Are you at the Oracle at Delphi the only reason that he brings him up I realize this is that in
Film
Alex Fox
To David gergen on the street
And brings up Bohemian Grove
And I was like towels
Is gergen I'm the guy who videotaped stuff in
It's knock it out and he's like well I
Disrespect you doing
I don't think that's cool you broke the secrecy
Good news like this figure of like
Monumental importance
Pop through the cell of Susan Basel
Bubble Bo knows he exists
Yeah yeah Alex is not look
A video of Alex with him so it makes sense to heighten this person's important
Proxy
Make sure he is the greatest then I am also the greatest pro wrestling stuff your competitor
Supposed to
If you beat them that means you beat
The best or the second
The bomb
No it sucks
One last clip pran to Alex's ruminating on his
I did I did
Mangrove
Should have brought that up the way he talks to himself on air like at 6
Motion picture
Making pho
Alright
Okay
Boggles my mind Harry Shearer is a member of the he's not he went one time
You got it like a guest invitation
Bikes for a day or so. You talked about this
A bit
Because I have all the things he does some like politics
Like his radio shows politic
Text Jason
Called like a little show
Or something like that
Alright
But yes we can
He has he has some like proximity
Cheetah politics
Have you ever seen Teddy Bears Picnic
I have not seen Teddy Bears Picnic
Can't believe that
It's 82 Major
Motion Picture do you would think that because it was written almost entirely just to attack Alex Jones
I would have some familiarity with it but unfortunately I don't
It's
Like I said on a day
The guest
Visit or whatever.
To The Grove
And so you decided to make a parody of
Love
Alexis video
Just of the growth in limited release
It grossed about $2000000 and it is a 0%
Score on Rotten
Tomatoes
That's not great the consensus of the reviews that I read that it was but it is basically like a
Not well made
Christopher Guest
Movie he has a lot of similar cast members
A guest
Some of that
Serta Sensibility
Is is still
Built-in floaties
Fred Willard
Is Americorps
Bob Einstein Super Dave Osborne Hellyeah
The cast list
And the only thing I saw missing from there
Was my man Bob Balaban
Malabar
I'm not sure that Alex is actually made fun of in the film since I didn't watch it but
Plot does involve a disgruntled waiter trying to sneak footage out
So maybe there's an Alex parody in there. It's
They didn't make the film to Mach
Alex no
The if there's any
Connection to it
I think would be interesting
If Alex was like
Enough of a touchstone
Harry Shearer to put
That
Wrinkle In
The parody of Bohemian Grove that might
Be something
That would come up in your like
Sort of workshopping ideas I like
What else can we do with this idea this thing by Jon Ronson we did that whole thing
So then that led you to Alex Jones doing the thing
Darkseeker
The secret rulers of the world exactly
That's entirely possible
Yeah
So yeah I don't know I
I don't want to watch
Just movie
But I might
The things are you for the show
Picnic
What if
What if it is just a
I don't think
Think so no wonder it's got a 0%
Ya-ya-ya your waist
To your goddamn time
Especially if you don't have her and you don't have the Balaban guy
I got to have the Balaban
Alright I'm pulling up the
The cast list here
Would you believe that it is not
Easy to find
On the list of credits
A Harry Shearer
IQ plays character named Joey Levitt
I also directed and written
It's alright check this out Michael McKean
What of course
Better Call Saul
John Michael Higgins my man told Michael he has in there
Alan Thicke play some self
Build blanket self that's not in order
Okay Fred Willard
Annabelle gurwitch
Call famously one-time Fred Willard came into the theater that I worked at Columbia
Orchids at Forum 8 Theaters
And we saw him come in and like
F****** Fred Willard
The hell is going on here
And no one believed me
It so I decided
But I would wait until he was coming out of the theater
And I would at the concession stand Yelp
And then duck
I did that interview that is a great meeting a celebrity Buffett
Morgue
Fairchild watch
George Wendt
Great Chicago
Yeah
Kurtwood Smith
The dad from that 70 show
Also make you cough more importantly
Obviously
Okay
Dick you are maybe the most famous linebacker on the planet
We're going to have you play waiter number three
The guy who played Jay Peterman
Larry Miller
Larry Miller that's a lot of talented people
What about to a bad person
Maybe
The secret element
Give me a recipe
Christopher Guest
Or
Bob Balaban I could be one of the three what are the three
Maybe making fun of Alex maybe not
Anyway we come to the end of this and it maybe not that like
Importance of an episode of maybe not a whole lot happened but
I think it's important that we do come
Some
Clarity
About whether or not people are going to get arrested for saying
Ali answer
If not not
Since
Probably not even
But
Also
Man
Seeing Phyllis Schlafly treated
Rough like this
It's not ungratifying in Subway's about it it's a little it's a little bit
A place where they should be heralded
People be like
No no no you're not
Conservative enough for us
It's kind of fun
It reminds me so much of like
Listening to that
Took me back to the debates
It's in 2016 when Trump just ran roughshod over all these people
Like
With with
Tons of political experience being dicks for 10 20 years
F****** Jeb Bush's a member of the political douchebag fam
All of that s***
And he just
You suck like it was that easy and everybody was like yeah they do so
You know like
Trump was the
Mafiosos
Of the Abby's people in two
That's what
They had started
That little colonel of s*** talking Phyllis Schlafly
Is what lettuce do Trump
What they're like
They're basically taking a gamble that the emperor X
He has no clothes
And in this case they're wrong
Rutgers Phyllis Schlafly
Does have
Conservative Bona fides much deeper than whatever nonsense they're on about
But in the case of trump
I'm in the book nothing Cruise
Ted Cruz is that should have ended his
Little worm
Yeah still didn't
Me think about it cuz I can't even heard Jeb Bush's name absolutely much less with an!
I mean I said
Please clap
In the past but he'll live on
Is that
Man
Rough
Like your grandfather
Came up with the New World Order
And then your brother
Was president
For eight years and started
The longest war in American history
Did 9/11
Play you are remembered as the guy who asked people to clap
Please clap
Brutal all because Trump took that risk
Of you saying your new clothes
It turns out
Also the other thing too but the this last leaf twist
On this
Is
The way is a quid
You pointed out the way I likes
Was like
She's all you know the kind of turns on her a little bit after
The she leave
Is so
Spineless
The worst
Heralding her is like a a l
The conservative movement as introducing calls come in
And he's got to get on the wavelength
Colors
And that's to me I think of a mark of somebody
Who's
A word that's shameful s***
Furious
I mean yeah it any show that we went on it if they've started talking
You should about it afterwards
When we had a fine conversation on
I be liking out there they're f****** done in my glasses funny
Because it's funny that I'm certain that the Cog disguise
Continue to make fun of us after we left
I'll forgive just about everything
But they were also making fun of us while we were on
If I were slightly I'd be like
I'm not taking another booking for
This guy
But I think she does
Cuz you probably didn't listen past 20
She's got off the phone at
These colors products
Some spirited good points cuz she was very diplomatic with them what a bunch of fellow
We'll be back maybe we'll be in the present to receive your next
Cuz
Maybe maybe I'll be in the mood to listen to Alex p.m. both
For whatever
But we'll see
But until then
We website
Do its knowledge
Sprite.com
World on Twitter
But until then
Emilio Emilio
I'm dzx Clark
In order of Phyllis Schlafly I would like to announce
That I will be starting
Bring my own organization
And it's called the
The quokka forum
The sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color