Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge vype.com
A little bit about
Alex Jones
My first year
Jordan today it is
I finally I've been resistant to join see bbworld
The Comedy Bang Bang
The idea of it
I resent
All of the Earwolf business model
And everything sort of funneling people into this
This is
The service of man you know they had the Howell
Just seems like you get your s*** together what is going on with all this
Hi this is
Hey what's up to this cup do another subscription to you by it's not surprising that these creative people
People are bad busy
NetSpend
The problem is they're trying to be businessmen of the first
What are you guys doing I don't know I'm sure there's information that I am not privy to and there's some sort of an explanation
I don't know what it is but anyway I'm deeply resentful
Of course
But I finally signed up and the reason
Was because I didn't realize there was a show
That's at 10 bolts does
About his character Randy snutz okay
He has a show called hey Randy
Bandits
The best
Okay
It's so good
I don't know what it is Percival Tim bolts is just amazing
When I first moved to Chicago
Every Sunday night me and my buddy Dan Sherwood go to the family tree hope
Houseboat accident
Ohio
At 10 bolts and a couple of dudes there improv show
Yeah and he's just
Is Brillion
So funny and this character there's just something about it this Dirtbag guy
It just takes it
It's very relatable and
His instincts are just so
Goddamn sharp the rest of the people who run the show too or just
Of course it's just very few things are like really laugh
Out loud kind of things they get like
Got guttural don't I know it man it's
Just the best literally my entire career trying to make you laugh and it's not easy
What we've done 780 of I've got
480 wisdom this number in Capitola
You shouldn't feel bad
That's a load number but it's
Compared to other flags
Anyway hey Randy grape grape
Amber and I
I really hope that they're going to make more of them
Because
There's only nine and they're all
Betasso no need to make more episodes get to work man
Mother stuff that's a might be worthwhile on their bananas for bonanza
Everything took that behind the pay while I was I was weeping weeping uncontrolled
Absolute well there's more of it there
My bright spot is I have absolutely torn through can lose the grace
To King's books
Fantastic Can't Wrap cannot recommend them enough
What he does
Is he takes
The 100 Schools. Of Chinese philosophy between
You do 400 100 bcee somewhere around there
And kind of anthropomorphize is it
Into a fantasy version of China around that time. And it said of Confucianism running roughshod over everybody else
You know because they have all the weapon
In this in this situation
Taoism actually kind of has greater sway
Along with us I mean it's fantastic
Okay
Sorry I got really excited
I thought you were going to finish your thought I was letting her know and then I got confused
You're doing great. Better
There is a historian
In the twentieth century for my money the greatest historian of the 20
He wrote
Buy the history of Chinese philosophy
And when I say V I mean like literally
He is the most important
He did it
He synthesized
The history of Eastern philosophy in the history of Western philosophy Hood now you got home
Anyways I've never read anybody who's I've never
Met anybody or talk to anybody was also read dr. Fang Yuan and reading this this
Quadrilogy
The first time I've ever met somebody who under
Understand that
It's amazing I get I can I can see why the you have this this excitement
Whatever you care so hard about the Warriors maybe somebody out there listening
Maybe you'll make a new friend so I'm excited but you're weird Niche interest
I would never Ariana stay I would never argue philosophy with anybody if I didn't have that book
Open and ready
Because it's
Every did the Hundred schools.
Is all of its Oliver
I I mean anyways what I'm saying is anytime somebody says
Philosophy and a white person said that I discounted a media
For me that's too many schools
Well that's why they got it all School sir
There they are the 23 schools.
Patrice could do school
Stop so Jordan today
Episode
It's the new year
Okay hey
Recording is on January 1st 2023 alright
Wendy's
But I decided what would we do we got a send-off 2022
You know it's even though we are in 2023
We're still emotionally closing up the book
That was 2022
No thankfully Alex Jones on Saturday December 31st
Final broadcast of the year
Okay so I said hey
Final broadcast of the Year seems like a perfectly closed
Exactly
So today we're going to be discussing Alex is Saturday emergency
Last Broadcast of 2022
And we will see was he at me as we go through this now you to determine whether or not this Rises to the level of needing anime
Emergency broadcast maybe it does maybe it doesn't
How much money he makes at the end of it will
Determine
Whether or not it was successful right if he doesn't make a ton of money it's not for lack of trying
Do you swing it
The magic salami spoiled his birthday surprise baby, thank you so much you are now if I was you want
Thank you very much kills most insignificant Fox thank you so much
Ewok Richard from portslade asks
Am I alone in noticing that the Red Alert theme song samples wrong impression by Natalie Imbruglia thank you so much
This is come up many times
Barbie string portion
Of that Natalie Imbruglia song
It is also the theme song from Alex's endgame documentary
And the reason is because it is a sample
String
Cut videos in like editing software
And that is where they are they all ended up getting it from
It's like one of those pre-built in string let's bring it back down to
You and I both know why
Little bit lazy
Little bitty Eazy-E song
Matter
Tonex
A happy birthday from Jules
I'm a little late on that one or early
And Beef House thank you so much and I hope all is well
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
If it's just Beef House
You end with B
Evergreen
So I thank you so much to quoting past and present technocrat
Technocrat drops
Carissa and Marcus to the summit of Mount Kilimanjaro
Thank you so much you are not our technocrat
I have
Risen above
Miami star
A list for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f****** horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
I apologize to the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's not really but also that was fortuitous
The name of that drop because Carissa is also the name of
Scandal is on again off again girlfriend
I'm just I'm just blown away here's what I needed to start 2023 Dan the idea of some
Someone
Standing at the summit of Mount Kilimanjaro screaming
Jar Jar Binks
What we've made an impact right right through the canyon
Echo Hill words loser little titty baby
I'd like to apologize in advance for this out of context. This is mostly
In case he wants to put this in a cell
Daniel Goddard
Snow
But you can easily see where that picture to a sub certified
Start off of the episodes Alex's
Emergency Saturday
His day off
He's coming in
So it's such a Gordon
Stuff going on
Are we are on the final broadcast of final emergency transmission
Of this insanely dangerous
Believe me
But also important year for awakening
Thank you for joining us
On this
New Year's Eve
Emergency
Transmission
The political and cultural begin spiritual economically
Planets are aligning
Everybody from
Pope
That died
Barbara Walters has died
I want to do a
Review the giant stories in Earth changing events
What happened versus the distractionary
Things that are unfolding as well
And I want to look at
Globulus rollout of their climate lockdowns
Now being initiated how important
Wherever you are in the world to fight back against those and not submit to it
Not sure that the former Pope and Barbara Walters dying requires an emergency episode but yeah we all rational
Lies our actions in our own ways use the first pope to step down for several hundred years nobody knew if he was ever going to die
Why you're not you don't know he's supposed to be a loophole exactly considering the Walters was 93 in Pope Benedict Was 9
85 this seems like too very predictable and unsurprising public figure.
But it's interesting to hear Alex in it
Justin talking about the big import
News anchor
Planing about all the distractions
Generally speaking I completely agreed there way too many distractions in the world and particularly in the media but where we
Blue pants is that I can say with absolute certainty that at least 75 per-cent of Alex's content is a meaningless
Distractions
But he's just reporting based on a tweet or a meme or something
Almost nothing he covers means anything and more often than not he's just making
Shut up
I would challenge anyone who loves Alex's show and thinks
To contact means anything
To go back and listen to his episodes from earlier in this year
And Marvel at how many things were emergencies that mysteriously resolve themselves
Edward never mentioned again
How does business model relies on constant distraction because
If he doesn't keep the audience hyperstimulated there is a serious risk
But they'll start questioning some of the basic details of the stories he covers
Then realize that he's full of
Bulshit
And there aren't any climate lockdowns but that is probably important branding to look out for in the future
From the folks who were looking for a new place to put that Auntie covid lockdown energy
Keep the covid you got to keep the lock
Right
And I imagine here's the way my
Brave sort of like sees what's going to happen it's going to be 130 and Arizona are they happy
Go outside exactly if you don't go outside that you're letting the government tell
Tell you that your skin can burn I predicted that'll be like you may be part of the rationalization of where the rubber meets the road
Yeah that is the problem with climate change is that
Like Barbara Walters in the Poke. And you can be like that there's going to be 140° temperatures in Arizona soon
Certain inevitability
It's a way we get
Sit on the distractions here we'll talk about the big story
Sportster what are the big
Chronicle this year
Is a dizzying
Prospect
What are the biggest issues of the year
Dude got you 1.5 billion dollars
Mass censorship
Program
Surveilling and suppressing
People on this planet
Bring an incredible draconian
Authoritarian
Taryn
That could be the top story of the year is the top story there that seems to take primer
What's the first thing you mentioned
I don't know I don't know if this is accurate
Is anybody doing
Do you want your baby
Do you know anybody honestly
Is anybody doing that
Beautiful blessing to you and I don't know
Is that could be the top story he's not saying it is he sort of spitballing
This reminded me of the lead-up to who is the most important person in the world there was a little bit
Doesn't go that far but he does
Is this Vuitton Story video
What is the time
I thought we were going to go that direction but it's it's just a little bit of a little bit of snot
Isaiah
There's a giant Awakening
That is cascading and exploding into bigger and bigger
Finale
What
Is that the biggest story
The biggest story
Then the last
12 months the back has been broken the biomedical
Tyranny
And that it's come out that they knowingly creating covid-19 and
Call Donna poison shot
From the injections
February 24th invading Ukraine
Years of the West
Proxy war
Enticing Putin
Text that dangerous Plunge
Wildin on the precipice
A thermonuclear war
I'm a ladder
Operations
Escalation
Chart
I'm not particularly into your endless
Trying to quantify with the biggest story of the year was
I find that stuff
Kind of be a distraction but if Alex wants to play that game
And by the way
The thing that I think you could say he lands on his if there's an Awakening going on as the top story
Also none of the stuff you saying is true and perhaps more importantly these are instances of stories that Alex reporter
Very differently at different points of the year
Covetous basically in Evergreen narrative for him wear everyday some new blog post or sub stack article
Conspiracies corrected vindicates in Forever
It's a fascinating improv game where he finds new ways to be proven right everyday
Forcing his audience to pretend he hadn't already been proven right yesterday new and different ways
To be proven right about different things I'm okay found the 40th Smoking Gun amazing
Nobody f****** guns to modify a story about that Invasion repeatedly over the course of the
Here because it kept being wrong
Before The Invasion Alex was certain that it wasn't going to happen and it most Putin was going to Annex the Don boss with his ex
Play Russia anyway so he had the right
Like to do that totally cool. In solid Intel that selenski was a
Putin double agent and that Russia had paid off all the Ukrainian generals who would just submit
The war would be over in a day or two that was close as the war dragged on and Alex's horse to come up
With rationalizations for why you wasn't
Wrong and why Putin was right to invade he bounced around to a bunch of different storylines but the most popular definitely seems to
The notion that Putin got suckered into invading by the West
In order to distract listeners from questioning how wrong Alex has been about this at every step
He constantly talks about a nuclear war is just right around the corner so you can heighten things to ridiculous level of be able
The fall back on something like
You want to split hairs when nukes are right around the corner
It's just a silly game
I'm excited for a year-in-review type experience here though you know it'll be fun to hear Alex lie about everything he's done inside the
This year I mean
It's it's
Kind of insane it's it's a little bit like
If
Pitchfork
Ran all of their album reviews
Right
They just made up the album's like they did they didn't actually exist and then in their year-end list of the top 30 Oz
Albums of the year
They just made up 30 completely different albums
Of like anagrams of the previous ones about what is half
Or even like in addition to that you'd have like
An album with a reviewed harsh
Actually
We love to 200 but I didn't write that never heard of that
Severe severe things
Start here to reflect upon at the end of the Earth
The border is gone
That's one of them
Wait already that's the year were they admittedly just got rid of the Border
Completely
Finally after 45 years
Slipped Away
One way of putting a job really insane here
But
We're not really about
Focusing
Most of our attention on the past
Study the past
Cover have a lines of History intersect together bring it to where you're currently
But more importantly
Infowars is known
We're looking into the future
Oh my God
What is going to come
In the days and weeks and months and years ahead and how
We are not just
Pawns on the chessboard that don't have any will
We can decide to be major
Players
In the destiny of humanity
God's grace
Land for us it will simply
Except
We're about to find out what the secret of 2017 is my man we're going to get to it finally is it Megyn Kelly
It is
Infowars is not about looking backwards
It's about predicting the future
We have just broken a story published three years ago in the New York Times so there is that
Yeah there's this is this is silly
It's a fun way to look at yourself and I understand why Alex's likes her to self perception would be
Beavis
That's way more fun
We have basically this as beat the Preamble beginning of the show talking about what is
The top story of the year make this maybe it's that border is gone
Retired
But really what ends up taking up
The most of the beginning of the show
Is
Long talk about how you got to give Alex
We need to now look at the nuts and bolts
Other programs
They've gone from
Beta
Operational
After I mentioned some of what's coming up
After that
And then we're going to continue on here today but please remember
This is a very special thing
It was built by God Providence
Inspiration
And by millions and millions of people
Spreading the word
And telling the truth
And supporting this broadcast
And it is revealed
Hated
By the enemies
Other people
Affirm
By the corrupt governments by the out-of-control
Power-hungry
Zaino
And one little pot
Chicago
The most important
Nexus point
Focal point
Of light
In the Gathering
What
Our light
We also
Stand out even stronger
What why they want that life
Snuffed out
Immediately
And that's why you have to let it burn into your brain
Should have
Wait
Chills going up
Spine
Realizing
How important you are
In just the last 48 hours
Infowars has had the largest Brute Force
Attack
In our history
It was 200 plus million yesterday morning
The Brute Force attacks went up to
Billion
Request
There's only eight billion people on the planet
Millions of computers
Hijack
We know what about that it's 2023 now
Everyone knows what about
2 then
Blood Infowars
With two that was as of this morning DDOS attack please
Billion
Finish
Request
Ascent course they weren't targeting infowars.com
They were targeting Infowars
Store
Dot-com
Those
Bastard
Infowars
Store.com
Is awesome
I haven't gotten into the website they're not trying to get on
Maximum security on it
They're just
Flooding it
GoDaddy
No matter how big
Servers
McLeod
Overwhelmed
By 2 billion
Request
We're talking
Millions of requests
Every few minutes
Don't you get it
They can't handle the idea that you would
Give Alex money
You know they can't handle the idea
The people would support Alex and his bright light
Shining in the darkness until they do these massive attacks on the store
Central website take out the store
Against that go to the store and buy all the s***
I didn't
Probably but you won
I don't I have no idea why I know why anyone
Would think that the Infowars store is safe with their information
This year we've had
A million different
Massive Corporation
Compacted like
Millions of passwords and release all over the place
Why would Infowars have better security than any of those I think you judge some of that stuff
By like
Surrounding context
You know like
You see enforcer like this is a tight ship
This is the kind of place do you know crosses Artis dots their eyes they're on there on top of shift
I think about when I think Infowars
I think detail
And fairness I don't think I would trust them with a dummy address
Find some way to get my real address just by looking at it if I opened a completely clean
The new email address
But yeah so they have this DDOS attack
Resolved now so you can go and give Alex money will buy his s*** now
I don't know that he does this a lot I mean like
Maybe there was a DDOS attack of some sort I'm not sure about the two billion number that seems excessive
But yeah it mean he has this a bit I mean that you just as bad
Bad the security
Cloudflare protection or whatever
Show me some sales
Going on
Of course
But one of them is something that I thought was sold out like six months
Think about how important
That is definitely
The enemies of freedom
Desperate
The block you from knowing the infowarsstore.com and get a great product
Restore.com
You and your family everybody to get them
While you're there get a signed or unsigned copy of my
Obelisk
By the way we have a fundraiser going
Leaving by the regular book for 20-something box
Broadcast
You really want to support us we're selling
Signed copies for $99
Just like
Fundraisers in Drive
We don't get taxpayer money ready globalist money
We have you supporting us
I am so they'll sell a coffee cup
50 bucks for t-shirt 400 box or ball cap
Gmod
Cost that you know the
Coffee mug didn't cost that in
Pizza token
No sign that you were supportive at a key juncture
I look I am
The most
Critical person of Alex in the world and of his business practices
Even I have zero problem with him selling autograph books at a markup
I have no idea why you feel the need to be defensive about this
Maybe it's because there's a ridiculous level of Bryson Kris
But he's entitled to put a price on his time
If he wants to say that it's 70 bucks for him to sign a book
That's his right to do so
I mean I look at I have a I have a paperback of Douglas Adams
The Long Dark tea-time of the soul and I have a hardcover signed edition of The Long Dark
T-top with assault I'll tell you what I think one of them is worth more money
Sure and if
They were being sold you would expect one of them to Costco
Incidentally back when that book came out I would sign thousands of copies and wouldn't stop talking about how difficult it was
Somehow they were all sold out
A limited availability thing like his dumb silver coins but I guess either they weren't sold out or there is
The finite number of these signed books after all
Just trying to exploit the audiences fear of missing out on the opportunity to own a piece of History by creating
Artificial scarcity among this s***
The sign the books and salamida a******
The thing about the stakes for him
Is that all of these sales pictures
Have the like
Depth
Of Gravitas
Emergency broadcast crispin's Day speech but it's
Leg in their beds
What they wish they had a signed copy
Beautiful
This is not this is not good
No it's not and Alex has this habit of undercutting some of these sales picture
Like you got to get this signed copy of the book
But why would you do that want to hear this
Where to have signed books
For two more weeks
And there will no longer be any more signed books
The great reset
And the world
Except for one limited edition
Sometime in the future
Consign it
Inside each book I don't know when I'm going to get around to that
I want two people requested that
So there will be a limited number
Sometime in the future
A few thousand copies
Show me shine
Weather
And then that's it no more signed copies of the great reset the world so if you want a signed copy
Your last chance
If you're thinking about buying a signed copy would like you to obviously rather have the copy with some art in it
Is that a hundred other folders
Cr3 puts in there
Yeah I feel like that's that's an anti sales pitch
Cool why not buy it now and also buy it later but actually the one that's more valuable to buy later
Paint-by-numbers kit of Hitler's dogs
You know all of his dog panting so I'm going to put one of those and I'm going to sign it Alex Jones
At least one of my books way that dozen
Valuable
So Alex
So you know
Eventually he's going to put some art
These books eventually that's going to happen
Yeah these projects that he doesn't get.
AngelList puppy discusses another project that he's going to get done which I'm going to say he's never going to get done
Final offering comes out
Six months from our God knows when I'm
Oblivion
They're beyond 9 months pregnant
That
Will be getting done very very soon
I'm not complaining this is a total war
I'm always putting out other fires in attacks
Twerking information on
And so I apologize lister's then
The projects we had planned already launched
678 months ago
Reset
Coins from 77
Bitcoin.com
You're going to get in all sports
Free the Olsen parks in Derry
Email
Specials nobody else gets it
For free because you are
Coin purse
Jokes
Sports broadcaster fourth coin
It really wasn't a founding member coin
Teddy Roosevelt
A couple thousand of those coins left
Bringing founding members
Status everybody leaves their email there as well
All that. Once
TBH
And information of material
I'll just go ahead and tell you I've been planning this for over a year and I am going to start
Some commercial free
Podcast
Better
I'm sorry what
Documentaries
Special events
How much are the stuff at all built it's already I just did not
Producing media yet
The information by Waterleaf.
Everybody remember
I just going to be sent
A free lifetime pass code
This isn't going to work
Why make us
Subscription site
The problem isn't
Like man Alex doesn't put out enough contact anybody
Fill his shows boring s*** doesn't have enough content
Why is he putting out more non-conference mostly red blink it's always the good stuff will behind this pay wall decor
Yeah I mean there's no ad breaks because the whole thing is that
It's all in that the whole show is at its all one big ass
Write in a commercial free podcast that's behind a paywall is like
If you put commercials in the thing goes by to pay while you're an a******
Play some kind of subscription service
Hitmaker mistake you still going to commercials for his s*** in the stuff that's behind a paywall
This is this is silly
I mean look we have the
Constant talk of
You know there's going to be this
This show of all colors show that's going to be coming out
This is just
I don't know infrastructures they're great
Maybe
Sure doesn't sound like it
And this is a step backward
Honestly like
He used to have the prison planet TV that was the subscription service that like
Had a lot of video content in it
And and what-have-you this is a move back to his old model
That clearly wasn't
Like enough
We didn't work
In a way that
This
Excessive sales
It does it's just going to be chasing after diminishing returns even if
He follows through with it which I don't think
You will know I mean if you follow through with that the only other smart thing to do is wind everything else down
You know that's what you would have to do in this situation because he's not going to
You come back but that's antithetical to the way that he presents himself as he wants to get all the information out
Can't wind down
To get the information out and you want to like
Have a Awakening among the masses then your shouldn't be behind a paywall
Because then you're selecting for who has access to that information
And that's just
I don't know what's up enough money in a lack of
Intelligent enough to
Yeah I feel I feel like this is bad for him from a laxative
Subtle messaging perspective and it's also bad from a financial perspective cuz no one
Is interested in that
It's the people who bought the founding member coins
Things are going to get free subscriptions to this anyway those are people who would have bought the subscription
Decides
And not just that but I mean everybody
Can see with the way that this is going how desperate sounding it is like
Hey if you were 1776 founding member like here's the thing about founding member stuff
If you were a founding member and then they're like and also
Now we're going to give founding member status all these other people up right you're like
Okay so it doesn't really mean anything does it I don't feel that special about the thing that I did that was special
The thing supposed to make me feel special you have not removed the one thing that it does
Members only jacket
Via the it flaps are stupid
Yeah yeah it does kind of is it's a little disrespectful to the people thank you
Who founded
Yeah I mean
It sucks
Because it is clearly like the
Last-ditch effort they have it creativity towards finding new revenue streams
You know I mean this year has seen a bit of that a man like that a recent Wars was an interesting swing
They kept they keep swinging for more money they just don't
They never knew why they were successful in the first place
So they don't know why any of their ideas aren't working now here's the ultimate irony
Is B like prisonplanet TV when I was doing that
Was successful
If you could have kept like a bit of homeostasis total if he hadn't been a greedy a*******
30 hadn't tried to like
Constantly chase money and grow this s*** to a point where
His overhead is ridiculous
He hadn't done that if you didn't
For like being a celebrity and be really rich
He would have been
Shockingly successful able to do all of the information base
Stuff that he ever wanted to do
Kept it there
I mean
I'm going to say this and I'm not going to go out I feel like
It's not a new story
Huber Swift Talent
I think we've got that one on lockdown
Well you know
Considering the sheer
Volume of stories about just this same thing we wouldn't be living through another example of
Express
Yeah
It's so old
Alex is taking a bath on
On the website and everything he's losing money
But I do humbly ask all the viewers and listeners to really
Fundraiser right now because
230 250,000 dollar underage each month
Last 6 months
Not good
Everything all my money's gone I have
Like
$50,000 in my private bank account now
I don't have any extra bank accounts
I don't have
Prostrate
There's a trust in your name
My children
I put my $200,000 to account there
For kids
But got that money
I'm telling you there's there's nothing there
Understand you be happy about was wealthy and
How much are stamps
And I'd be fine with you I get it
But I'm showing you
When I tell you that I'm on E
All My Children
Which I don't like to do but
And before God
Aya put 90
8%
Of my resources other than my home
Into this life
And
That's it
I'm totally committed an
What's so frustrating is were right there
Some thousand dollars with
Pittsburgh is not hard
Each month and people just say hey
I really need Vitamin D3
How how my God
I mean look $200,000 a month or whatever in the in the underage
Is bad that's not good
Because I would assume that's factoring in all of the sales
I never
But he's bringing in his net
Under Siri that's what he say
Yeah that is bad I mean I do appreciate whenever he he throws in that one little detail
As though you were already arguing you know you like I'm putting 98% of myself
Accept my house if you want to sell this house
I told one of my 7000
I'm going to argue with on on that lie it's going to be me being like a ha you haven't sold your house he's absolutely
About all of this but I do like the idea that
Are you putting it on God and all his kids he put 90 per-cent of his resources
Now
Let's let's find a way that this lie works by emotional resource
Resources is a very specific word in my nickname
Private bank account very specific words you're using I don't believe her second is $50,000 a bank
Ridiculous
Dario
Also come on if you're at no point in time as ever but has anybody ever sworn on God and there
Children without the intent to lie about it
Yeah
You say the truth if it's true it's typically performative when your life
That's generally when people whip stuff like that out
So
Money
Give this guy money
Democrats is not the beach that they're going to side with Ronnie or not it's you
You hold Infowars
In the palm of your hand
You decide
Whether we're going to stay on here or whether or not
So I know
While you were supporting I thank you and I appreciate
I ordered some along time ago and liked it or whatever
You're too busy and well you're right about the New World Order
And so
Maybe you think informs the service purpose
Then the den den den den
I guess we will
Not be on the in the future
Because
Maybe I am maybe I've been breathing right so much now that
It's time to hang up yeah that's the problem
That's the problem
All the time
A million billion
You're finally getting this is going on and the blinders are coming off and I know
We're becoming more influential in the halls of
Political cultural thought
If I were a listener who tuned in for this I think I would have turned it off by now
I would conceivably be looking for a year-end type of show where there's some information being covered but it's just an excessive
Protracted Financial whining session this is just unacceptable
Contact
It's all good and well to beg your audience for money but at a certain point when that's all you're doing for the 1st
Half hour of your to our year-end show
That's too much
It's okay to have Advil help fund the message but when the message is basically just the ads
What value do you offer in audio
If I were listener I'll probably be recognizing that this is actually a very fitting
Gearwrench / Alex to be doing
There's nothing unique or knew about the idea of him spending way too much time complaining about his heroic Financial battle
And I will be asking myself if I ever saw that changing
His bigger conceivably a time in the future when Alex isn't going to be doing this
When he's shifted into a place where the money is fine and he can focus on actual information
Obviously if you're honest with yourself you have to recognize that until he Flames out
This is how things are going to be
He's going to be an angry passive aggressive panhandler pretending to be fighting imaginary supervillain
When you look back on his career
You have to ask yourself why he even needs money
He did his most influential work long before he had to supplement line and every major event that he's been involved in
Past that point
Is been a disaster
In the before time he had things like Bohemian Grove 911 Waco and being the true voice of the Tea Party
I was the real tea party with Ron Paul
Ron Paul Revolution
Well he's been Rich he's got Trump
Pizzagate
Defaming the head of Chobani the Sandy Hook lies and trials is divorce Jade helm
It's all been embarrassing
You really shouldn't have money I mean it is
It is unfortunate but the thing that makes the most sense to me is like
This is a Behind the Music VH1 from the 80s
You know like this is going to go back to his roots but I mean like he's
He's Def Leppard
Behind
We're going to get to the end
Sounds like what was it all for man during their meteoric rise it was all fun and games
And then it got dark
I think if you take a step back and look at like the sort of trajectory of his career UE is like a ban
And that had like
Better chops
Before they made the big time I made the big time
I don't know what their early stuff was like
Did they do the Sex on Fire song Fire their first album was like
6 years before that is pretty good as the metaphorical
Drake out like a slightly more like add a little bit of black Rebel motorcycle
Motorcycle club to The Strokes
And that would be their first album
Okay
That makes sense to you
Damn I Remember The Strokes may we go
At the Elmwood
Unescapable when I was in college did seem to be that way
Nonsense
Super long
Add s*** into a little bit of
Discussion of Alex
Family
And we get a little story about his dad was the smartest boy in Texas
And the story is a little different than other times you stole the pass
Print out flyers
Go to the mall put them on the
Windshield the cars
This is how we're going to win
Because I know this is the most fireflies out there we're having
The biggest effect
The things I talk about I know where real and I know where the globalist plan
I tried to recruit my father
To join the Eugenics call
Top of his class
High School
My grandmother thought he was being
Eisenhower Wizkid program
18-wheeler with a giant Ruby laser to his
House
Texas
Do you have the top test scores
That's what Eisenhower was doing
That was JFK
Built the laser they said that's it really
Really
Bunch of pieces
Pretty sure you didn't just a real cheap travel Kilmer
Houston
And looked at the laser
Operation
And
And he thought he was in a program for NASA was not the program for NASA
And by the time he got into college he got out of
So this isn't how Alex is told the story about his dad's recruitment in the past
Every time I've heard him tell the story before it's been that his dad was the smartest boy in Texas so dr. Irwin spirit
Tried to recruit him into the extermination price
Speer was a professor of biology and botany at ut-austin so it doesn't quite match up with this laser story
The waste of such amazing laser talent I mean it really does sound eerily similar to real genie
Write it but it is fun I mean this is how I guess if I were a liar I would try to like
Shift
Stuff about like my being in the gifted program
The farm system in Tripoli
I'll buy a vagary of chance I had a reading level a little bit maybe I was behavioral East
Slightly weird but in a non-disruptive way to get
Stop being recruited maybe this guy be better if we just let him learn too much
About the Knights of the Round Table instead of what worth
Cool could be a problem if we board him yeah it's but I would I would I would recontextualizing
That looks like the beginning of the globalist plot to try and bring me Envy that's one thing in those David Jones.
A position I would love to just
Grill him on his personal history like
Alex says you did this what did you wear you the smartest boy in Texas
Are you the smartest
So Alex his dad
Made a Lasik and then because the stupid the principal was was
Mean they shut they changed the trajectory of the laser to hit his house where a lot of popcorn was waiting
Bloated in Eisenhower showed up
Jobs
So what happened with his dad and uncle
This is on his mom's side I believe it at the Hammond Uncle Buckley's dad
Cuban press
Then my uncle
Wasn't Iran-Contra
Call me about it
Hydride
You know why you got up
U.s. government trafficking children out of Central America
In charge of a bunch of stuff
No further
Online when I tell these stories
They go well
Big'o
Jones is one of them
Because service family
MRNA
Husk
Ecohealth Alliance is there vice-president
Was there a medical operation
Expose everything
It is probably going to prison
You judge
But none of that even matters
You are now
Staring down the barrel of this thing
And you're going to have to decide
Whether you're going to speak out and fight back
And there's no
Better place
Speak out at fight back
Infowars
Dot-com basil
And don't let these people win
Wow pretty good
Also your uncle if you was in charge of stuff he was he was trafficking children
I think about his
Personal mythology of his family the more it's like wait
Every story you tell about your family is at
Morally dubious your family fought for the Confederacy
Force for evil in this world at your uncle is involved in Iran Contra and was trafficking humans
That used for nefarious purposes and apparently was a so-so day
Which has its own negative unintended consequences
If his moral compass is shaped by what he thinks are war criminals
Punjabi by imagine this would be like well the only way I can justify my family being filled with murderers
Child traffickers and I'd awful people is if
There's an even worse
Globalist Empire out there is no good in the universe
0 think about the people he associated with are the longtime people who have been like in his work
But folks like Steve pieczenik
Or Larry Nichols
These are horrible people
Monsters
Absolute Heroes within the infowar and Alex's hottie and switches
It's totally tell Alex Alexa is family terribly
What
You got a donut
By Alex's s***
You know you know
You know
It's going to wind up at the Infowars store
Every allroad
Sometimes the journey is just fun sometimes you got to sit back and enjoy the the way you get to I think that time was definitely one of
The less predictable forgiven for thinking that that trip to the store
Was going to wind up in a different place
Yeah
To look
There's a high cost
To the infowar
There been a lot of soldier
Tobin Lofts
Infowars is just a focal point Barbara Walters
Made major sacrifice
You don't know about
To bring you this information
I'm going to leave it at that
I'm talking about people have died
To bring you this information
Many bothans
Guide
People close to me have died
To bring you this information
I paid extremely heavy price
Bring this information but
Donuts because God watching
And I know we can beat these people
Children
Are counting on us
To do this
God's watching this is a test
And if you don't do
You don't stand against this
But who's that who died
If you don't turn off your targeting computer
And Trust the force
Those f****** missiles are going anywhere near that.
Who died
Like to get this a turtle
Sorry
This is all nonsense
We've had a bit of
Meandering
In the beginning of this
This episode because of this is what Alex is doing
2nd year
But
Get down a bit
I had like we get what we were really looking
For which is the 2023 predictions
Yes finally
Year you were here to tell us the future tomorrow's news today this is why you
You show up
I tried to write notes last night this morning
What I predict
Going to happen next
Deprived
So hardcore
And
It is
So nightmarish
I don't even feel Worthy
Not one of these again
Broadcast
Myself in a dark room for about 6 hours
Okay
Flashlight on
I really need to
Look at all the information and then try to put
Put the pieces together
Look into the future
But I've already got a really good idea the stuff they're going to pull
Able to get into
Marcy weights
In the zone where
Equations are
Exactly what they're going to do
And then different projects they've got and then how we can stop them
With critical information
I guess you're not getting those prediction
Italics in a dark room
I've got to go trip balls in a room by myself so I can see the future I got to go pretend I'm developing phone
Photographs I'll never take right right
Yeah I want your reaction that because it is of god.
Worthy to kilometers
Sometime it's also code for there's every reason why I should have something totally should I do
There's an expectation that I would have prepared
And I would give it to you
But I do have
So let me tell you about how hard I tried to get it
And
I'm being
Modest
I'm being responsible by by saying I can't cover this right now I am but a mortal vessel
For this
This information that is so important because it's supernatural
If I could be Supernatural I would have been able to achieve it however it's a goal that is only a chiva bus
Right so I'm going to go lock myself in a room but I got to do
Soup healing
At least we can cover them
So I mean it's a little bit of a second place
Consolation
Surprise now well
Why do you do this
Let me move on from and now into the news
But when I tell you that we are
In your hands
That's truth
I'm asking you
I think about the fact is there really
A question of whether or not you're going to support the broadcast
Really
You want to give up to these people cuz that's what it is
I guess we're not getting to the news we're going to talk more about that
Little p****
If I were on the fence
This sales pitch is making me want to stay away from that fence
See ya
Yeah
He's going to try and get you in a timeshare
Are you into that really you're not going to give to me what what
You're going to have God to answer to Ackley great
So anyway we're not going to get to the news instead we're going to get
F****** so weird this show gets weird
Your brain is a giant
Electrochemical transceiver
Alright
You can talk you can dial your brain to any channel you want right now
My free will
I can dial to the Satan Channel
I can go into that bathroom in there
And what DLC is available
Seidlitz something else jump right into me in the driver seat
Absolutely
People's arms out of their sockets
Could you get me all sorts of evil inclination
And understanding but only had to hurt people
And people like fauci
There is a system of anti-god anti-human
Inside that body that's running that body
That's a biological Android with one Mission and that is to humiliate you
Cut you off from God before they kill you
Reminder
People you disagree with
Are demons
It is not just
A disagreement
People
Pardon the dial
Molest children
With a spike protein goes into the cells
Generations and is passed on the children
Causes of mutation
They are turning people into mutants
Now
Don't say God didn't put
Something interesting
What
What weapon formed against
Prosper
What
It is electrochemical
Shall we need
Turn the dial to the Holy Spirit
Broadcast
And obviously if you been to dial the other way
I don't want to turn the dollars.
Too good
Turn the dial
Porter-gaud
What but if you don't want to be cut off
The creator of the universe forever
And be with these things
That Free Will and decided to be nice things
Then you better take that dial you better turn it to God and you better
Sledgehammer
And break that.
Are you can't even turn the
And I finally got to that point the last few years
Wow what progress are you making this progress
You know what I was when I was little
When I was like 9 or 10
The pastor at our church
He had me he had me hooked
I thought he was I thought he was very smart
Cuz he was really well-read and he could
Quote all the stuff right you know do the whole thing
And then I went to the youth group for the first time
And the youth guy
Was trying to do the exact same thing
Because he sucked at it
He accidentally revealed all the bulshit
Right that feels so much like a youth group speech of like
Listen you're not ready for the pulpit buddy
You got to stay in the gym
With a bunch of kids around you playing the guitar
I know all your friends are telling you that hyperventilating a bunch is really cool but then
The devil will come again
So there's three point
In that
That clip that aren't that play together that are really weird
One is Alex saying at the end
That use
It's no longer able to tap into that devil dial
Which is contradictory to the beginning part where he said he could stare at himself in a mirror turn that off
Heather that's contradicted by him saying that in order to turn the devil dial you need to kill people or abused children
Exactly cuz look at yourself in the mirror
Necessary or Alex's revealing that he has killed a bunch of people and that is why it anytime you want it
You know he's already turned the devil
Sure that might be whatever you want a walker
Again
The more he talks about how he's morally righteous the less it sounds like he understands what morality
Gidle that you doesn't know I don't think so either I think that Alex said that like God has a thing that helps with the mutant
Or whatever I think he said that in order to be like
Hey you don't answer is gokil
Anybody who's been vaccinated you got a pillow
It's a little bit of precarious his language
Answer or whatever is the
Back door that you can get to hurt
There's a self-destruct button God put in there on his own you can just
Hate them forever and give me money or you can talk to them and convince them to turn off their mutation
Through the Holy Spirit
What a great metaphor
So we got some more talk about dial
This metaphor is pretty pretty big and Alex's head today
Ears
Or I cannot even turn on the Satan
I'm not even tried but in your dial is rope
I gave my bet experience
Likes you
I don't even think I've got this
That's a good thing
It's like
Rear view mirror
Camp Seymour
I'm going someplace
I'm on a path
I'm on a trajectory
I want to get in line
With the Holy Spirit
Future
Only teleported to the next dimension
Oh yeah
Do you want that here have that
I'm right there right now
God right now
Unbelievable
God
Come to me
Dial
Turn all the way to God
The more I stand up against evil the more I go to
The more I could turn the.
And then it becomes
Good thing
Tamor I'm attack
Vegan stronger
Sure my body looks
But it's just a vessel
And is a symbol of the slaves
But I got a lot of your interview stuff with
Copy.
Godby.
What's today
Espionner
Imprisoned
Okay
Back to back
I want to get to the rest of it today cuz it was so important Sky News out of Australia
Weather Ronan Dean 7 minutes long it's the best of nation what we're dealing with
And then
First I want to hear
AJ explains genocide plan in 5 minutes for about a year ago
About
And then I want to play
The clip from sky
This is life
Then later I'll play clip 10 maybe you shouldn't have nut like no commercial broadcast
If you're going to have like production meetings
Durango supposed to
Had a very brief conversation about this whole dryer to starting a dumb show
Have a meeting before the shows
Start so be something
Is there a Marvel hero that like it's
Stronger when you hit them
Probably just got to be
I don't know the characters well enough but it's got to be some super
I think you're feeling that seems like a villain power black panthers Powers is that if you hit his suit it absorbs
The energy
And then he can later Channel it back cuz it seems more like a sweet thing
It is a suit
Let's not like the power that rightly the power powerful
Travel through time who if you shoot them with lasers he absorbs the lasers and then he has a gun cable maybe something like no
Alice's dad true
He would be bad he's not good at lasers
I mean he's good at lasers
I just that's all I can think about when he's talking about how like all these people
They're Dede s*** on me and it makes me stronger and God's dial
Dial
Ticket about Liz likes
At the end of this speech I'm waiting for them somebody to be like okay Alex
I don't think you can share these AA meetings edible
That's it we like to give it to everybody but Alex Alex Jay is it okay
I don't think you
You can come back
But maybe for the next few weeks don't you
Bill W doesn't want to be friends anymore
Your acquaintances
Boy
So Alex
I don't know why Ted Bundy's on the mind
Why would
Hebe Danville
There's lots of stories and it comes out in the court all the tales of
Ted Bundy the famous serial killer that would
Drive around is yellow Volkswagen cuz it look non-threatening
18 year old woman coming out of the mall after work and he said hey nice suit
Get a coffee and have dinner what's your name
I think you're really nice
McDonald's
And then
Tweenies anthropomorphize this story
And say put these hands
He finally got caught this one woman did run
Is that
All the rest of them
Did what he said
And the farmhouse in a basement and put electrical tape on them
And tortured them and raped them for days
They were used up
And as soon as they weren't begging and pleading and crying and
Power out of there
As soon as their eyes went dead he go ahead and strangle
Bloody chunks out of them
You know what
I didn't in the yellow Volkswagen
And I eat
Put your handcuffs on
And
Metaphorically
I'm going to bite
Take your nose off
You're not
Want to win
We're not in here
With you
You're in here
No metaphorically New World Order
I'm going to pull your teeth out
What
And I'm going to Stomp
Like that
Black hurting kids
I mean
What did Sirius people
Comebacks
Murdered them of the truth murder
Their credibility
You're so close
Choclo
Getting our hands
Around their political maps
At Mass murdering serial killer fauci
100 times more evil than Ted Bundy
Look at his apps
He loves
Killing children
Well I mean there's a
Yeah this is grotesque
There's something that I really think about you really kids
Insurance called Infowars you know Lake and there's this idea of like there's a war of information
Spell violent ways of talking about like
Information is
You hear stuff like this and you take him to like the way
Geed
Dyke
Does his show and conveys things until stories
You really get the sense that he's more into the war aspect of it then the information
Like the information was just kind of an excuse for him to
They have these disgusting fantasies about murdering his enemies
Like that
You think I'm going to put my hands around your political throat
No informational relationship with it
Miring in disgusting fantasy
I think that's what he really gets out of it and I think
Mostly emotionally with the audience
Connect to a stew
Yeah yeah I mean it is it is kind of emblematic of that type of relationship that talks
Toxic masculinity has to the
Insofar as it
Cannot
Express itself the way it used to with you know just
Difference and impurity
So toxic masculinity now has to
The tie itself
To some sort of
Imagine justification
Until the war is all that was ever interesting
It's just that after the war had to be combined with info
F*** it we'll do the infowar too if we have
But this isn't like the way that the information War cell
And like our 2003 episodes next they're leaving
It's not true finding the long periods of time
Having a Jo fantasy about murdering fauci
This is pretty common on his show now
Maybe that's another effective those
It does seem that those two should go hand-in-hand much like I don't trust them with their private information my private if you
Based on surrounding context I would not take the supplements based on
Hughes
Here's what I think Behavior
I think this guy screaming about how everyone who disagrees with me a demon
It's probably someone who should give me something that I put into my body without asking
Needle sx2
Legos on yellow-bellied wants to kill five
A miserable
Demonic
Madrid Hotel
Look at that man
If you have any discernment
If you have any spirit
Got in uu snow that is Diablo
That's what I'm looking at
That's an accomplished psychopath doing it for 45 years of gotten away with it and thinks he's God
He looks very tired
Open the Eyes up with the
Satanic
Ted Bundy
No no no he just
Gives you that
Look up I am a psychotic
Can I have killed Millions
And I'm going to kill Millions more
You're not going to stop me from your children of mine
Eminem murdered I'm slowly
I'm a snake
You see her while we tell her
Maui shipping
New World Order lockdown prison City reports we back
So this is a good clip to use as a little reminder that Alex is basically an idiot who can't even do his job anymore
He's been the first half-hour of this show begging for money and complaining about how if you don't give him money you'll have God to answer to
Then he spent the next half-hour yelling about completely insane nonsense about tuning your brain to God or Satan
Frequencies
Heaven trambley grotesque fantasies about torturing
You killing his imaginary enemies
After that he throws it to reports produced by other people
This highlights perfectly with Alex's good for
He's a really effective conman in terms of sucking money out of people he's already convinced
Stentor is revenue stream
And he's better than most at improvising violence fantasies
He doesn't have the shame that most people have which would stop them from descending into these disgusting diatribes about what they want
Metaphorically do to their enemies
Most people would find that embarrassing but Alex has cultivated a Persona where he gets away with pretending that
It's a mark of his passion
Neither of these things rely on any work
No preparation is required to peel off a revised murder fantasies and Alex basically isn't working script for
Looking at this point we could do that more or less in his sleep
Anything to take to work is antithetical to his present a way of doing business
That's because Alex really doesn't give a s*** about this stuff passport you can get out of
He cares about the performance of trying and the performance of carrying so deeply but at the end of the day
It's Crystal Clear that he would rather spend his time off are doing
Anything else
Other than working on making a good show
Yeah this sucks
Yeah
I mean I think the
Problem is maybe he used to care about the performance
You know he used to care about performing to the best of his abilities maybe but now it seems like
The performance itself
This garbage do it is
You know like he doesn't even let you know that it's over the top
It's unbelievable parents
I feel like it used to be a better actor
Currently
Plausible way to look at him and disagree and be like I think he probably means that
You know I think
But like I don't think he believes that people are.
Rubber to the road
I don't think that he actually believe people are possessed by
Yeah I figured this is
A
Tightening of his wanting to other and demonized his political enemies
And people that he
He disagrees with I mean ironically it is
More acceptable
To literally demonize your opponent send it is to
Metaphorically
Play demonize your opponent
Yeah
I mean look it's it's
Is trash
Yeah except for like a little funny moments like
I'm going to do those predictions and then that baby.
I would just say that you should
Try you should maybe try
I know that he is averse to that
Bye
You know when you're saying that like the performance is worse now I think what it comes down to is that
Previously
Earlier points in his career
He didn't
Have anything
Right you didn't have like an Empire he didn't he didn't have this stuff you're funnier when you ride the bus
That old Sinbad Quotev like you're funnier when you ride the bus somebody up that way
Not as funny private jet you're not really
All that convincing as a populist propaganda
It's a little bit Fendi up this kind of b*******
Sunnyway Alex plays a bunch of
Special reports and he comes back with
Another 30 minutes or so in this special year in emergency broadcast
It'll be streamed out until 4 p.m. tomorrow when we do this Sunday
For 6 p.m.
Then I was back again 6 to 8
I can't stress this enough Alex has done nothing on this show
Who's 30 minutes begging
30 minutes of meeting was ranting about spiritual radios
I meant 20 minutes of Special Report
They're truly feels like there's no reason for Alex
How to do the show at all except to try to bring in money
A him to lash out a little bit to an audio
Truly wild because even I kind of thought there would be more meat on these bones I saw like emergency Last Broadcast of the year
Like at least
Try to do something
I mean
To meet me what is most emblematic of what's going on here is just that that like
If you who's going to decide whether infowar stays on air or not bro you know when he says that
That's such a
Fatalist viewpoint
He does that a lot though
What it is and it is true in a sense
You know it is going to be whether or not the audience response only you can stop forest fires and only you can give me my
Money
You need to project to the idea that you are doing something to earn that money
You know I'm he's not doing that would be good
Yeah justify the year exist
Why is this investment worth
Making that's so good that's kind of more what where what I'm feeling lately is like
He used to at least try to make the pictures
Worth it you know like he's justifying
The the reason that you would give him money and now it's just give me money yeah you know even though
I was kind of thinking about that and I think
That is
One level of liquor
Looking at it and I think
That's wrong
Sort of
It is correct if you look at it until it's wrong sort of if you look at it from a perspective of like
Trying to deliver information and like even if information
Drawing
More stories like that
Yeah he's doing essentially nothing
Thing to earn
But if you look at it as like it
It's no longer really Infowars 8
Feelings Wars
Sure that way then
He is doing something
To elicit the donation of the investment
Creating bizarre emotional stimulus
For the audience
22 react
You know I just watch
Cuz I think you I think you have a really really good point
I just watched his dark materials
With my wife
The largest issue with that is that
It is emotionally manipulative
It's not actually good or bad or anything like that
It knows the ways to make you feel
Something without having earned
Exactly
Yeah that's kind of something in audience finds gratifying
About that emotional manipulation whether or not it's conscious
Want anything you're not going to get
From other media Outlets
Somebody
Screaming at you but how you buying a vitamin
Sprout time is fighting the devil subways
Kind of authority you can't you can't say it's not
We wouldn't be here if there wasn't something about it yeah and I think that might be part of what is on
Satisfying
About a lot of his present they stuff is it's just like what do you do with that
Yeah he's just
Making
The audience feel things I guess
Yeah what is there to talk about if what you're really doing just going
Hey you feel like this
How you feel like that
It's a it's a little bit less
Meaningful
Freeway Alex talks about to have any gauges
Some of this that there's others
Victory going on
And I would save this is a bad way to gauge thing
Things right
It's out of control
Trouble
Remember
Ago
Joe Rogan put a clip of myself on his show out
Whenever the media was saying Bill Gates net worth
People in studies
Maxine gets sick
Alex Jones is a liar
Set himself show
Joe Rogan show that clip
I got more than 10 million views on his Instagram
In 99
Watch percent
300 comments I spent hours
Several times looking at it
I mean
We know you were eugenesis we know you want to kill us
About the New World Order
Last time I looked at it
Had
Something like a million,
Andy was just all
Exposing their water
Snapshots
It's now like that
So there's your AI
There's your censorship board
There's your CIA
There you all try to silence us
Didn't work scum
We kicked your ass in this room
Yeah you may know a lot of people play White made hundreds of billions of dollars to do it again but you just found out
We're not as easy to ride over cuz you thought we were
Because of
Comments on a
What am I hearing that correctly
I mean who cares
About these comments first of all
Second of all
I don't believe him
Let's pretend he's telling the truth
Hours reading these, the serious problem
Do other stuff this is not a useful
That's not a respectable way to use your time
If you're Alex Jones
Is it just
Reading comments on social media
Something here I think it's time we replaced democracy
With
Governance by YouTube comment
Sure like however many like plus minus whatever it is you need is it on game of assisting
But I do like these ways that he gauges things like that the past your head
Randomly coming up with numbers about how effective is a b
Eighty-five 90% Buffet
And now we have
Skimming through comments on a social media post
For me is a condom 99.9 percent effective
We're going to get to these future prediction
So let's think about that
And I'm not
Popping out here
Spencer
Cartoon in Monday
Napa tune in tomorrow
I'm going to have to call my wife
My office
Computer with a pad paper
And I really need to predict what's going to happen next year if we all stand up
Weather for probabilities possibilities are
Honey I'm not coming home all right I got to lock myself in my office to see the future
Okay in my other jobs
You know when I was doing another job
Sure me going like I listen
You know what you're right I got a buckle down
I'm going to handle that
I don't want to make you wait till tomorrow so I'm going to work all night for it I'll get it to you tomorrow
Because I'm not on air
Well
I mean look
Debatable
A year predictions
Episode Shore
But to be on the 31st of December or January 1st
It's appropriate for either extra now what you were doing an emergency December 31st episode in you
Emergency bringing up predictions for the future it would be in there but no
He's going to he's going to tell his wife
He ain't coming home
But actually a code
Another plant
You know I'm going to do something even better
Sure what's that
I'm going to take off
I'm going to check
I don't know if your 5 days or what
And I am going to go to the country
I'm going to go to the mouth
Nothing makes you think clearly
I can pop them out and then
Jar Jar Binks
Hyzaar
Want to go to the wilderness
And
Like on Sean
I'm going to come back and lay out with
Next year
Oh my God
Really get in that zone
All the pieces come
Sometimes when you're taking a jogger
Really immerse my
Myself by myself
By myself
In the woods
And then I'm going to come back
And I'm going to tell you what I believe they're about to pull Maxton I was stopping
Yeah man I got to go to the woods
OK Google
To see the future now I'm trying to work on I'm trying to work on the conversion here because I know about inflation
Button
So got Thomas at underneath that tree for like
Decades right he said under there for a long long time well could be one day could be 5 days but he was coming up with the
Life philosophy that could last for attorney
So
Just picking out a Year's predictions WhatsApp
At like
Depends on
Algood the air is
Good points on
How alone he is
Distracted by a squirrel
I do love this escalation though I am not worthy to deliver
River this information
I'mma tell my wife I'm not coming home
I'm going to lock myself in a dark room 6 hours
Who knows how long I'm going to be there
And I'll come back when I'm good and ready and I've seen the future okay
There similarities
God
So we are recording this
On Sunday
And
It's actually when Alex's show is on
Until I have it pulled up here on mute
And it's unfortunately in a commercial so I don't know
So I will give an update as soon as we get out of it commercial break 22c
Very excited that we are now currently watching
Or I am cuz you're on the other side of the screen but there's a CBD commercial
Alex's slabbed life
Yeah I mean it's cool now
Alex's a Acela
It was an interesting thing I was thinking about about how
You're all he has these things that are so important
They Don't Really follow along with who his sponsors are
A particular type
You know
I really that
That's not his style I never heard him talk about CBD
Now it's
Super important
It's very cording to his commercials
I don't hear him talk about gold that much anymore
Which is interesting
Here's what I
What I'm confused about supplemental I never heard about how important like X2 or iodine was
It is strange how those things became very important once he sold
That is weird in the commercial of Alex in his tank
Yelling at people trying to cross the border good trait this is this is weird to have on a Butte
Visual
Popping out the top of a tag yellow going to pull Hornet immigrants
Who
Dark
It makes me
Despair of a future
Because when I was you know when we were growing up
You have those dare commercials where it's like if you smoke weed one time you're probably going to kill your little sister
You know like you're going to die brains going to be a Friday again version of cannabinoids can be sold
On the f****** corner street
Everybody whose old used to be like
If you smoke weed you got to go to jail for the rest of your life they're popping gummies left and right
Edit no point in time as any to have anybody going like well
Here's what we're not going to do
This all over again
Let's just stop this let's get rid of this
Criminalizing drug s***
We got to figure this been there before so many times
It's very unfortunate
I'm sorry I got distracted cuz Alex's attic
No he's not in the creek what's the point exactly
Alright we're coming back from break back from break what do you think do you think it's going to be out
I don't know if it's going to be a wee in the third hour and weed the fourth time does the whole show on Sundays himself cuz it's only
Play two hours so there's no I guest host
Here's the thing I could see him being there because he talks a lot of s*** but I can also see him being gone because all it work
Requires him to leave
Yeah and not working is something he loved prefers the latter to the former
Is it going to be Owen is it going to be Harrison
Maybe going to be out
It's Alex
This is says it's life but it could be a rebroadcast of some sort but yeah it looks like Alex
Didn't go to the woods
In the future
In the past
I mean
Predicted 9/11
And that was from a dream okay
In July of 2001
And it doesn't have shelves until September 11th saying
Blow up the World Trade Center
Breeze's a pretext for domestic
Control
Bring under control system
Then in the future
They're going to use that
Apparatus
Against the American people
Patriots
And
People said how did you do that
I got the zone
And
It's almost like
Close Encounters of the Third Kind
Allegory
Transmission
Building the mountain
The mountain
Transmission outside
Composition
Come here meet with us
And that's really the allegory here
Is that
I need to
Get in that zone because
That would be understanding
Thoughts of what they were going to do
And
I didn't have dreams of the burning building
And it was
T
Signpost
Of where we're going
It was a lot of
Interdimensional
Power going into the future because
Continuum information
Possible Futures are there are actions to Stone
Don't do that
Zacian back
Nope
A signature in the future
In the past
Interdimensional sonar
Why
There's like a waterfall
I don't know I like some sort of new age you nonsense and every now and again they're going to talk about the time-space
Continuum and all this stuff and like these possible futures
Whatever
I'm going to leave that alone
In terms of judging that. I will Judge Alex on this front that is
He doesn't know how to read a word on the page there is that I'm not going to trust him to interpret
Signs
From possible futures of the space-time continuum
You do I do I do appreciate
Celebrating talents that are not you know like
Some people can't read but they're very good at visual art I recognize that that's possible however if you are talkin semiotic
Learn how to read
Even like interpret Concepts or any any of that kind of stuff
Rapport at that skill-set so I would imagine he would get a message from the aliens and he's completely with
If the game of telephone trying to explain
Do us who got it was well I mean I basically
If what I heard is correct about his explanation of the allegory of Close Encounters of the Third Kind I do not trust
Anything he says about anything
No
I would imagine. Tell him to shut the f****** and that he's telling us
Movie different message
Shaped like me
So Alex
You know a lot of his reporting is based on deep sources that people have died to bring to him
Technically not true but true definitely not true most of it is actually memes and dumb stuff that he saw on social media that he does
Don't know anything about there's that like this
Keanu Reeves
But he even reached out a few times through his producer
Assistant
Films they ordered more
Because it's
But I got to tell you this is a really creepy
Keanu Reeves
Emma movie
I want to play this because
Short
I'm wondering what he said ask her
But he says It's amazing And really cool
Little girl at a director's house he was at
Said I don't care if things are reality I don't
Arabs are real
That's the whole thing about the Matrix
Manipulate a spiritually to make false
That's how they believe that short shark
Defraud Freewill
Literal power light
You know people say stupid
Cuz I don't actually know and he's really smart talk to most people do people say he's stupid
This is a very dangerous cliff
Because they're a child
Philosopher
You want to be in The Matrix you decide you want to be in the front
But children can't differentiate that's why they
Have sex
That's the only reason
Statistically it's good to protect them until they're able to make those decisions
I think that people they don't think they can of Reeves a stupid but a lot of his characters were stupid
He was younger
Play the Good stupid person like Bill and Ted
I feel like most people can wreck
Nize that
When you're in a movie
Right you are
Pretending to be a different kind of Typecast in a lot of that with lutein
Impression can linger in people's mind
Particularly in the last like 10 years 15 years
20 years I think
People have taken
Quite a different view of Keanu Aziz
Become an adult
But I don't know I don't think that Alex
Maybe they talked in passing
Like during waking light outside during A Scanner Darkly
The playing this up a little batteries correct
To about the plot of The Matrix
People into making false choices
We needed better eggs
Listen when the batteries on your controller wireless Xbox
Controller way-back-when sure when the batteries go out you get desperate
I get it
Now I would enslave an entire race of people
But they realized they weren't nice to them either so you got
There is one way that ilex is kind of correct
Inasmuch as
V-very select
People
Out of The Matrix
The architect
And the machines are trying to get them to play out
A false choice in order to reboot that cycle
Still want their battery
Right that is close to it Alex is talking about accepting it's only a very select people
The rest of the people I don't give a s*** what
Choices they make within the Matrix
Importantly
It is an allegory
Not a truce
Now
Yes about Alex's found
Brianna Reeves
Terrifying
Oh no
I mean if it's dangerous than
Terrify gripes probably here
Maybe I'll try to get ahold of Keanu Reeves
Good luck
Please do please track it
Chaotic
The club
Cuz I don't want
You said
I don't know the context of it but this is
Creepy as hell
I don't I don't know I was having dinner with friends house
Director
And he had some
Kids nurses
Like a thirteen-year-old a fifteen-year-old seventeen-year-old
Is a parable
Matrix
Until the directors like moment you just tell them it's about
So I start to say well there's this guy recent
I kind of virtual world and he finds out that there's a real world and
He's really questioning what's real and not real and he really wants to know what's real
And
The young girl was like
Why
What do you mean she was like
Who cares if it's real
What you doing
You don't
Care of its real
Just like
No
Awesome
That's awesome
I mean it's awesome I mean it's awesome
Did you cut
Play that again
Play the club
Again here in just a moment
Where junkyard
I don't think Keanu Reeves
Send it.
That's awesome that she doesn't like reality
I think he said
Something about a film or something he's doing is awesome
That's another deception affect my gut tells me
Knowing Keanu Reeves
That
I don't like
Something Alex could do
He can take two minutes to figure out where the clip he's playing came from
He's just playing a little snippet of a clip that was spreading on social media but if you really cared at all and wanted to present his
Audience with any real information
He could have taken me literally 2 minutes
It took me to find the full interview that this is from
This is from an interview that Keanu and Carrie-Anne Moss dude with the verge
Virginia Vance of the release of the 4th Matrix movie year old interview that Alex only has any awareness of
Because one of his underlings found it on social media
And now he's blindly playing it and wrestling with what the context for this could possibly be
What does he care
Context
Easily accessible
It's right there for him to find he doesn't need to call Keanu and find out what he said
Just watch the f****** 18 minute interview
How to repair it did you
Did you call Kiana to get this information I didn't I just found the interview with with what power
Google
It is a jump cut
But
It's also more or less in context
Yeah I feel like it's the first time
In a long time that
But the real world is almost a
Head of our science fiction
I mean the whole idea
Trying to pursue
When can we make it
Photo-real when can we fool
I mean all the deepfake fitting you know
Technologies that are happening
Wow
No no baby
Almost
You know it's like War
It's the why
Right we can't we have
To keep
Species has to keep creating a species is like oh I can do that let's keep going to do that
No one can predict
The future
I don't I don't know I was having dinner with friends
Director
And he had
Kids
Like a thirteen-year-old a fifteen-year-old seventeen-year-old
The two haven't seen the film the major
Tricks
Until the directors like but why don't you just tell them what it's about
So I start to say well there's this guy recent
I kind of virtual world and he finds out that there's a real world and
He's really questioning what's real and not real and he really wants to know what's real
And
The young girl was like
Why
What do you mean
She was like who cares if it's real
What you doing
You don't
Care of its real
Just like
No
And I Wild
Awesome
You think it's awesome
I mean it
Awesome
This idea of that
You know so in a way what you and I are kind of
Speaking about his car like a legacy
Feeling
We're almost like
Oh you're older versions
Let It Go
I know I'm the mom at the kitchen table like talking about
The possibility of like
A virtual world
For my kids and I'm crying
You know
That's how it feels
For me
But now I just
I know
Kind of like sitting around the table and
You'll be able to sit around a table and talking
Which is one of the issues that were being
Yeah confronted by very
He's a really interesting interview in the jumping-off point for a lot of this is the creation of the Matrix Game
Which utilize the Unreal Engine to take assets from the actual movie
As well as digital Recreations of the actors in the film to create very realistic Avatar
This prompts the conversation about the implications of being able
How to create virtual versions of actor
Will they even need the people to make movies in the future
It touches on like Carrie Fisher being in Star Wars posthumously among other points
County was saying that this perspective that the young girl was bringing up was awesome but it wasn't like in the really great definition
Turn of awesome it was pretty clear demented in the inspiring all
It was even does this hand gesture where is it
Anyway this is an indication of Alex's work process
He doesn't literally no preparation for the show because he doesn't give a s*** about the quality of the product he's make
He knows that the audience is captured and they don't require much of him so he's just
Freestyling this b******* out while pretending to be friends with Keanu
I'm a good day at work
Yeah whatever I found this dumb clip and now I'm going to
Make it suspicious but there's a cut in it but then not do any
At all
No
Curiosity based investigation 2
What was going on here
Yeah if I was going to guess I'd be like
Oh so somebody found that clip and Alex was like
I know Keanu I'm going to talk about that
Or I was plausibly implausibly able to claim I know his because we were in Scanner Darkly
Theoretically together
Anyway Alex didn't go find the clip at all
But he's decided he's going to make some conclusions about it
This is what the deceivers do you saw this place that take
It's always got to get ahold of Keanu and find out the truth
But but the issue there is that's what the left does they deceive
How is this
Something Keanu
He really said it
Let's let's make him say what we want
What's get rid of his free will
Show his identity
And then misrepresent
What he really sad and let's do it
Video
In front
Of your face
This is really sad
One of the reasons it's really sad is that
If Alex knew anything about where this clip came from
He can make this so much more of a meaningful conversation
Because ironically the issue peoples images being made to say things is exactly what a lot of this
This interview is about
H&K Auto in karianne wrestling with a technological advancements in the house that impact the Dynamics of crew
Creation
Their conversation is way more insightful and interesting
Some of their comments
End of this presentation and that would elevate it past the point of just being an idiot blindly responding to a clip someone else
Found on Twitter and he just decided all I want to talk about this today though the left edited this boom boom boom boom boom
Call the left
Well I forgot that we have done that one man. This is how they deceive
The left is trying
To take Keanu from us alright figure of note
For the past
However many years and now he's on the left saying that stuff is awesome
So that their left doesn't want it because he is an FBI
Anyway cuz he was a great college quarterback so they do like it
This is all very stupid and if Alex today
Grain of work tiny little bit of Google
How do you see a clip that has a jump cut in it and you're like just Google
Where is this from what is this actually
Before you decide to get in front of your billions and billions of listeners
It's just pathetic time would I write a joke or even a premise I Google the premise just to make
Picture that somebody hasn't already written a better joke
I don't know I don't know I don't know
Okay let's
Let's let's hit some of the news here is that news clip 9 because
Go to Twitter
And you
Vicious mockery
Stop
And it's
Titled
Watch a Cell B
Until another cell
And it's under an electron microscope
And shows another cell go over
Some enzymes
Membrane
What
Resale and then
The other cell an amoeba
The guts
Mitochondria
Check
Michelle it's just killed
Spell up
Bellevue go to Twitter
A red line under the comments this morning
More
Oh poor cell it's so sad it's so mean it's true
All the shows how we need the vaccine to save us oh my God these horrible YouTube comments
And I show all this compassion
For the shell
But not the compassion
The unborn baby
Yeah my God a man
Quite effective
I mean
That's
That's a Twist at the end that I almost want to relive
That's that's that's so f******
Serious
M Night Shyamalan level twist
Surprised you didn't know
Norco most evil found Alex
Stop
Paying attention to freaking murder replies
REI when I was growing up I always resented it when I would go to the library
And I pick out a book
Can somebody that wanted the Librarians or something would be like
This is above your lip reading level I don't think you want to do that
Cuz I was like no I can I can absolutely read at this level and I want to learn more
And now I'm like oh I
Totally understand like the moment he starts talking about cells I want to be like no no no
We got to go all the way back
You're not ready for this yet I cut out a long portion or he tries to talk about mitochondria just because I was on my
My God as I could I couldn't even handle it this is above your reading level
You're trying hard
You bring up an inch
Everything idea about this like beyond your reading level thing because I think I think there's like a dynamic
When you're younger and you're like trying to read above your reading level
Good because what you're doing is challenging yourself and like
Do you know a blade on a on a
And I think that you can grow through that as long as you step up to the challenge of this other
Material maybe you don't fully understand it all the time but you pick up some pieces accept it with except your face
Failures with humility as
Corrections to be deposited the reverse which is
He faces a lot of his ideas on YouTube comments and Twitter replies
I am like
That is reading below anyone's
Reading level
Basing
Ideas on that just
Nuggets often
Like there is nothing there is no challenge to that there's nothing
If you want to make whatever argument you want you can find Twitter replies that'll make that for you.
It's just a shortcut to being able to make whatever point you want and pretending it's based on something
Look somebody think of the unborn babies
They care so much about this cell
Stupid
All these people are saying it on Twitter is there for
It has meaning
Yeah there is there is something to be said about it extreme of passive information
Completely ruining your ability to actively search for a
Yeah so I started reading a lot more whenever I quit Twitter
God imagine if my work process was
Finding Twitter comments
But we're against
The number of things the number of slight changes to either of our personalities at this whole thing Falls
Stop the news
There is a clip of
Keanu Reeves that Alex didn't see that he is
Decided to drop
Conclusions about the new forgot that
Also accelerate another scalp
I love
I love because
Complete inability to wreck
Recognize the like
It's not the cell that human beings are reacting with empathy to be
Situation
Imagine if themselves in that situation I'm going to come in there and get to other situation
I guess that's not a very widespread response of empathy for this I think a lot of people don't persona
Necessarily a cell not like the cell itself is under attack
With your Alex
You do what you can
So there's other news and we get back to those deaths
Those
Big
Expected deaths of 90 plus year old famous people
But who else
The queen
This year
On the last day of the year
Singers funeral mass
On January 5th 2023
And the number 23
Synchronicity we're going to try to get Leo zagami on the show the next few days
Today we need an answer I get it a holiday
Even grieving
Ethan is a very
I got that for you
Little point
If the number 23 was really all that important then they probably wouldn't
Killed him for another day or two
Cuz he died in 2022 so the twins
3 number isn't the end it's the funeral that's important there's no one in either direction
And the other celebrity that is about Barbara Walters
Barbara Walters
Daikon
Play
Rude
Respectful
I understand like
Very funny though and not liking the median what have you but that's
That's rude
Alright man cool
Hoo-boy
That's that's very funny
So there was the news that's the news
Bugatti
That seems more reasonable for him to say about the
Queen that it does about Barbara Walters like Barbara Walters worked her ass off and the queen was just boring the queen you know
Call me the queen did some things and we forgot that day that you was a patriot
Tory Lanez radio
31 last clip
Please commit in the new year
Spread the word more than ever
Share the club
Shirley article
Weather report
Prada
How are you
And your body and your families against
Infowarsstore.com
Make the commitment
Make the decision
Today
However you can help fight
And I salute you and thank you all
That's it for the final broadcast
Insane
Wild year
2023 is guaranteed even be more insane and will be here dutifully
Cleaning on
Dear life we hope you keep us down there
God bless
And I'll see you in the year
What a meaningless wow
Iowa
You know trying to find things to hold onto
Foothold
And look I don't expect much
This guy is disappointed me for coming on six years now or whatever you don't like it
I get it he sucks
No big deal where where a little bit late to be surprised by it now
Still surprised at how bad
And this was
I mean like
Some
Do what number do do song anything
Why we can't do a year-end
Roundup or anything because we go too far
We be like well if we're going to do with your Roundup
We have to do it I would rewrite Auld Lang Syne
It would be nearly the resources hours
This is just
Just
I don't know it's a wet blanket on a year
You know he could have he could have tried
Instead
It's just
Excessive begging for money
Rambling about meaningless nonsense about a
F****** Satan dial
And then
Actual Newsies covering
Are clips that he saw on Twitter a man celebrity deaths he doesn't care about and one
Maybe that he could have covered but Leo zagami didn't answer his phone
What you going to say
Can't do it
And then also
Blake let's not forget
The promise of the predictions
Just being
Sweetly unpaid off
Think I'm going to go to the woods
And now we learn here on Sunday didn't even go to the
So how are we going to find out what's going to happen in the future
If Alex does believe he can see the future he is depriving us of
A vision of the future by not going to the Woods by not locking himself in his office
By not doing that he is
Harming the world
Yes
To actually follow the things that Alex believes
To their logical
Conclusion
One can only assume that Alex Jones himself is doing massive amounts of harm to the world
B
Lacey
I can sign off on that
That's what he believed
You know what it's ironic because I think it if you tried harder he would do more damage
Because he does such
Little work
His carelessness
Describes a lot of problems too I think you probably cause as much damage whether he did a lot of work or not
What kind of damage
In in my estimation of him
I think regardless of what he does
He should probably have two or three people watching him and controlling his baby
You know like he can't he can't not
Be the worst
Identify
He's just the worst
Steps like I said improvised murder Phantom
Do you know
I don't disagree
So I was going to happen was that
Next episode
Define doubt
If you get to these predict
Can batter
To know these predictions I'm going to be running like a hawk
I'm going to be I'm going I'm going to be going a fine-tooth comb through everything he puts out
Until he gives me the predictions of what's going to happen this year I'm not picking any New Year's
Is predictions or anything like that I don't do that not what I'm interested in though dad
What is your prediction
For one of Alex's predict
What do you think one of his predictions Maybe
Lockdown
Another bio-weapon probably
Something like that one big swing. Here's my guess on his big swing Hillary becomes president
My guess on his big swing
Is he's going to say
That they're going to take out
For real
I don't know how to but I have that concrete of a prediction
But we'll see I don't know
Here's what I'm willing to do
Nevermind
I'm going to walk this back I was going to say I'm willing to go to the woods with Alex in order to get these predictions
But no I am not I'd like to go to the woods but Alex would ruin
So anyway we'll be back hopefully with some predictions of the future
Until then we website
Yep
Until then I'm Neo
I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
I'm going to go lock myself in my office with the lights off and a penlight for 7 hours
To see the future
What the sex robots
Alex