I have great respect for knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guy
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
I'm trying to talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
Jordan Tim Jordan
For you buddy what's up
Wings on at the library
It's being built
I'll be in burnt down
Are Library of Alexandria as soon as the one-year talk
Talking about no no
A modern-day Library
Will be burned out eventually
Number of issues of the American opinion and what-have-you John Birch Society that collection is coming
Together
To think about like
Start with a little bit of specialization
Because
Who's going to be randomly trying to
Define things
That makes the haunted little bit more more challenging but I don't have a real Target
Until I decided they were I'm going to begin by trying to
Compile as much a
As a can of revillo polliver works
And I found some
The very terrible things so far
Deliverance
Real terrible
Very
The reason I chose
To go in this
Misdirection
Is partially because it believed that a lot of his ideas about the wax
And the Western man and Chris
Things are very relevant to the right-wing
As it exists now and I think a lot of people
Don't have that thread
Coppola Maybe
Flooring that a little bit could be helpful
But then the other thing was that when you
You think about the John Birch
Society which is
Cornerstone
The materials that are that are going to
In this thing I'm putting
Together
The first meeting
That they had
The founding members
Is that were there a lot of these people were business
We were industrialist
They were members of the National Association of Manufacturers
You know it.
Most fat
Candyman
Haha
To work
You know I am sure they had ideas they weren't primarily idea
Where is
Review lopi Oliver with somebody who is there
And he's an ideas guy
Can somebody who has a lot of
Fury
About stuff and when
You know
What do you look at
That
Constellation of people
That's the person that I find most interesting
The person who's going to have more writings
That have like
Implications for maybe
The way that the organization
Well yeah of course I mean the businessmen are obviously Outsourcing their thoughts to other people to they
They don't have time to think
And I'm sure they have some
Get some thoughts
My
I thought it's an idea needs a to make a sound better
I'm so excited about that
I've got his against
The grain
Here in front of me
The first the writings of Professor revillo Pendleton Oliver
And there's a number
Chapters in here that
I think I think
Speak for themselves spell trouble
There's a nice
Editorial here a white Christian racist defends his faith
I mean
Brushing Lee straightforward
I would accept that
Especially if it was a white
Erase
This defense is racism by just being like
I really want to
Fbm
There's one chapter in the larger section Race and History distortion
There's a subchapter Anne Frank's diary
Great
Yeah so this is the direction that some things
They're taking here with the the library no some
A little bit
Slow in posting pictures
Little update about that
You know how we've seen so many
Failed stand-up comedians become right-wing
You talkin we have idiots
What's great about
Ravello is that
He was a ridge
Generally
The great reveal
And because of
Has failed magic career well
Here we are
I wonder if it is
Pronounce reveal Arevalo
Close
But we never hear his name spoken aloud
He's he's like
Given name
I think that is it like but it is also an aunt like
Palindrome
Reveal Opie Oliver is a palindrome
That's f******
That noise a little bit
If that's the case I got to blame is Paris
I mean I think
He deserves a response that you could change your name I don't know
This is his name and why
That's annoying
My bright spot is I finally got turned on or I finally listened
Listen to the big
Big Thief album
From last year strong new warm mountain or whatever it's called
Big Thief featuring Chief Keef
Not that one
I don't know I don't know how to answer
Rigby for a long time
Because to me for a long time they sounded like
If Court
Courtney Barnett
Headed gang gang dance
I know that means nothing to some people but yours was great
Big Thief
But I don't know where to slot the
I don't know I don't know how many other people and I don't know what they are
Is this rapid was Pope
Can you name people in my guy
I don't know them either I'll tell you this
Skepta loaded everything
Okay that's the problem
You know there's a little bit of everything in there and it's not always focused
It's enough to be good at the thing that they're doing this album is good
Okay
A great is there any
What's that
Genre that I
I loathe
God dammit
I don't know
Soft rock
Most of it is too chill for me
That's right that this discovery I find it
To relax
This is making me worry about the future
Yeah I don't I don't appreciate that
They're either still relax
Text until order
They're putting that
Like image on
Right right right
Deceiving you it's actually terrifying right
The implications of inertia
Bossa Nova
I don't know is there a is there a Bossa Nova type of influence
Antonio Carlos Jobim kind of
There is no
Bossa Nova
Maybe you call Big V fast little bosanova there
Okay
Anyway I'm glad you're enjoying that outfit
Episode
End-of-the-year broadcast Arkansas
December 31st moon on all of my checks
And we had the teas
From Alex he was going to
Reveal his predictions
For the coming year and I decided
I can't do that
So what I'm going to do is I'm going to lock myself in my office for 67 hours
Tell my wife I'm not coming home right I'm going to take care of this and it's got to be dark in that office
And then he's like fuc
You know what I'll do you one better go into the woods
Right for a couple days escalating to I'm going to the woods for a couple of days
God has got to tell him stuff and I can only happen in
And he needs to cry and walk
So we tuned in as we were recording a last episode on Alex's Sunday show
He was in studio interesting but he did not go to the woods
Did they turn all the lights off so we could talk
In the dark
But he barely talked
He wasn't talking about that much
Okay it was an interview with Francis Boyle
Francis Boyle
The guy who is a bioweapon
Pain specialists of some sort
Apparently some thoughts
But Ukraine
A pointless interview we did not get predictions about the year
And then the second hour
I was just rerun
Alex
So well
Here's the thing
I tuned in on Monday and what do I find
Yeah
No I'm still on Earth
Sure but I've been forwards is still on Earth 2023
No. This is arbitrary
Demarcation of time I refuse to acknowledge that is an
The new
D-Generation X
No the New Age Outlaws Harrison Smith and Owen Shroyer
Fuse
You've got Harrison Smith
Final movie
The snooze
Put you to sleep
You just start talking for a long time
No but it's me matically fitting
But then Alex I guess would be
Triple H
Or maybe
Shawn Michaels
I mean I think he's more Hulk Hogan now
Well that's that's like the New World Order
Attitude Era is not as complete as yours
Cousin Buckley is Ravishing Rick Rude
Savannah Hernandez cuz she's the only female that I think is still around
Billy Weaver's gone
Kaitlin Bennett I don't think
You still around I don't even know if
She still around
Actually works
Like she work for The Blaze
But she still has a channel on Bad. Video
Nick Fuentes could be Ravishing Rick Rude cuz he had a mustache
Mustache
Anyway Alex's Underwood's it appears
On Monday or something
He's just not there
So that left me in a little bit of a bind
Because I was
Obviously wanting
To get to these predict
I'm very excited about that I want to know what's coming
Responsibility
And I'm not
Boy he really is a psychic too
So anyway I felt like
I wanted to tell the world that we don't have the predictions
That is not a full episode
I am so I thought like well we can spring collect 2003 we can make some progress
And it Dawn
That actually
We are right
At the point where Saddam
Gets found
You got found on December 13th okay 2003 and our next episode as we're progressing
Through will be December
So here we are okay we get to figure out what
When Alex
Heard the news
That does damu saying
I was about
Clearly if I remember my
It was
Czechoslovakia who did it
Correct know they drained the dogs
That's found Saddam
Jimjam
Thank you very much Happy it's cool whenever Dad gets to it birthday
Eric from Kate are puppies Meadow Bandit and horseradish Peapod dog thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Happy birthday
Next thanks to Alex Jones for my new gender Gremlin race
Thank you so much
Thank you very much
Luke I am your father thank you so much you know if I was you want
I'm apologizing
I-beam
I don't know why nobody's tried that would be
Before I feel like that was that's been there for
We're on episode 762 or what
Did European studies really prepare us for this a thank you so much
Could you very much and squash curious as join the party thank you so much
Very much
And we got a technocrat in the mix
Apology to because they wanted me to play an out-of-context A Drop of myself
But I don't know where that is in the emails
And they sent me this message
A couple months
I have no idea
But if they resend that email baby I'll play it in the future
Or something
But in lieu of that they asked
Score
Danielle had a great idea for a shout-out but Dan and Jordan didn't listen and now you're all stuck with this stupid shout-out
Thank you so much
You are not a threat
Don't get mad until you're brilliant someone
Sodomites
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much
Begets
If I understand correctly
Were they was that
Referring to if you decided not to play the clip
Then they would be like well this one would be good yeah here's the name if you don't want to do this
I mean shuttle big at you
That's fantastic
I appreciate her but it also could be talked into this is too much of a hassle absolutely
Sorry about that
We got this episode to do and I want to say a little tease
And that is that if you stick around
Until the end of the episode we will have a new song by DJ Daniel that we forgot to play earlier
We're great you know what it's
It's one thing
To just like yeah we kind of forget things
When it's like
A couple in a row it doesn't feel great so there is
You and I both have
Strenuously avoided
But there are reasons people have other people work on
Yeah that's true
Staffs there people designated to remember
Bright
Yeah
Never going to happen with us but
Looking over at the other person Hoover this show
Could maybe get a planner or something
How do I
There'll be a new song
The Highwaymen
Episode
And I we start on the 12th
Actually we don't have any clips
It is a boring show nothing happens
I
I couldn't find anything to grab onto
Alex is killing time
It is not even interesting
But
There's a commercial
That I heard on that episode that I thought was worth bringing
Everyone's attention
These drugs prescribed for free
Doctors are prescribing drugstore
Does muscle relaxer
Anti-anxiety
The list goes on and on
3 / 50
Superhero lock birth control
Medication
Viagra prescription
Rdoctord
If you don't call 1-800 615-7094 wait now
Over the phone for 3 if you need to call one 806-157-0949
Alex was advertising for a
Drug shopping
Kind of like it's one thing
I don't know actually I'm not going to drink couches and everything ends up like muscle relaxants painkillers
The kids are some dangerous things to be taking outside the supervision of like
Doctors Care
Soma is one of the things
I mean when you're when you're on a commercial
The one thing
I'm listening for is if you are
Reinforcing
Once more
Just so you know
We have speed and dick pills
I think we know what people are asking
40K
Okay we're doing this for a while
Drugs now
Gintama kids are going to solve all your problems
What's today I mean this is a mess but it's also there is
There's an element of it that
Plays just deeply
Unethical
This can't be legal
Right
I don't know is it wasn't legal 2003
Look I don't know enough about the law and I assume that it is
I assume it's somewhere it's legal
Be there some sort of a loophole or something then
I'm not saying that there is to be arrested
Teacher pill terrible
Like eyevertising for the Emmy I think that it's even dicey to advertise like gambling
Yeah I think that's a little bit Shady
I think I think even
Maybe I'm bore anti advertising been a lot of folks but I understand people taking a
Eggs for
Some things that could
Eventually be dangerous
But like this
Is a do you want free access to medications that could
Potentially
We we destroy your life
And I'm Alex Jones somebody who hates
Pharmaceuticals control meds
Psychiatric drugs
Take speed and dick pills
Preferably together and with alcohol
Psychiatric meds to
Is a problem
Hindsight's 20
But if I was
I'm sorry
It is
Soak
Clear like oh yeah the opioid crisis is 100% coming
100% carbon
Yeah yeah you know
Alex Jones
There should be appointed which like I understand that this ad is probably run
I'm through Midas resources or Janice
You know like this is Ted Anderson
Since fall
But if I were Alex
I will put some
Sort of
Standards in place where I'm like no
You don't do this
We were going to get
You're going to run the risk of getting our audience addicted to pills here at will.
Destroy their lives well they maybe don't need them or
I mean
That would only make sense if they were operating under similar rules as like a is like a drug dealer of some sort you know like
They would do something like say the first taste is free
And then later on whenever you came back to them because you're addicted to it
You wouldn't
Get it for free but clearly that's
Wait a second dance
Well they're not going to be shipping a freezer law
Yeah that sucks
The 12th is a Friday
The Weeknd
Comes and goes
Saddam got captured over the weekend
And so on the 50
Monday always do a deuce dump on the weekend yet
I'm trying to find a way to connect this to like you always get fired on a Friday
Empire dad Auto Pride
On Monday
And
Here is where he's at
I mean at least doesn't beat around the bush you just
To the news
Houston Texas
Morning-after that's why you doing
In the
Before
The governor
What up what up monumentous weekend
I mean first of all you had Saddam getting captured and then Alex was at the Alamo Drafthouse
Movie screening
I have to say that I think Alex is a little bit
Annoyed
Did Saddam got captured
Because
Kind of makes it so you can't just talk about
The the show and how much of a success it was assuming that Alex would be annoyed if he had gone down on the plane with the Big Bopper
Fred wasn't given
Had billing
You know like that kind of
Alex will be very frustrated if he lost
Any
Clapdaddie one
Wait what you're saying that he would be upset if he was on the plane with the Big Bopper
Buddy Holly
Oh wow what
Backwards by bad I'm backwards if you only reason I bring it up is big
Because it runs counter to the argument
Suffer out there playing in Chicago
What's the problem it's all there
It's really true though it hurts
So we don't really know what Alex's Vibe is
You know there is
Kind of thing these supposed
The capture
But there's not really a sense that he's like this is fake
Or anything
And that continued
It was him
Why do
Don't know
It's kind of refreshing to your Alex or say that he has no idea what the reality of a given situation is
You never hear him show that kind of weakness these days
But in the past Alex's brand was being a
Smart truth-teller
Not that he's a prophet ordained by God and given a divine revelation
And a guy who can also
See the future
Can sustain a little bit of uncertainty in 2000
3 which is
Just kind of
Like a normal person
Me not knowing things is actually one of the most
You're one of the strongest
Things that a truth-teller does
Not know that
Right2know
One who speaks does not know
Exactly
No
. blood
That being said all that being said
Alex is not being above board
All the surface he's saying that he doesn't know what to think but he's very clearly
Trying to imply to the audience that they should
Think that the capture of Saddam was Fay
All the external context that he had so the coverage serves only to justify coming to the conclusion that it was
How to draw their captures have been faked
Before which is supposed to make the listener feel like
Deciding saddam's captors
Is a more rational a
You may notice that Alex is not doing this kind of insinuation
In the other direction
Providing defenses for the listener
Who may be inclined to think that the capture was legit
That's because there is a conclusion Alex
What is driving at
If he's trying to hide behind
Pretending that
He's clueless and I don't know what
I think
I mean
It's obviously
More likely for him to lean towards
It was fake
I mean that's
Is
Bailiwick
You know on the road today
I'm a little confused as to why he's not in this one
You know in this
Particular
Situation I feel like with the knowledge of
Saddam's doubles all over the place you know everybody knew that was going around roof
Really good shot at least
Is it for a few days
Albion like
I don't think it was him
They have to prove it I think they're fake
I had a couple thoughts about that we'll we'll get into that a little bit as
Things go along
But also interesting Lee there is not really any inclination
Towards the double
And stop even though he does bring up that there were doubles he
Sweetie
Insisted that this is actually Saddam
Interested yeah because he
He was saying that some other time
In the Knox
Too distant past
Some other picture of Saddam was a double
He has a lot of ideas about whether or not
Saddam's next
Toothpick
Question for him I but I do believe he measures next week
Critical
It's a saying that man has a real thick neck
Yeah so Alex continues
To pretend that there's like
I don't know what's going on here
The war
Was not Saddam
We know that was
What Alex is doing here is teaching his audience how to argue a point while knowing
Nothing about the actual point your argue
Leaving aside the dubious nature of some of the points Alex
Just listed off
Even if all of that was
Totally true and accurate none of it would Prove It saddam's capture was
Real
That's the argument he's making could conclude that the globalist
Star capable of fake
Eating something but that doesn't mean that they did
The goal of the style of argumentation is to overwhelm the person you're arguing with
It's a barrage of points
But don't prove anything but it's
Literally impossible for someone to respond to an oz
In any satisfactory way
You see this kind of behavior returning social media comment
So it's kind of
Kind of makes sense that I would have gravitated to strongly to that
Here's how I would respond
Okay
I would ignore most
I would say
I thought of all things
If I recall correctly
Osama had a bit of a Honker
I wouldn't I wouldn't
Choose the size of his nose to measure that he had a large nose
Right nothing wrong with that or give him a vets
It's not a nose like a banana
Can you speak playing around and shooting I was just sitting in a hole with a
30 wives or whatever
Wind going down that road be your first instinct was better
Which is just stay on the point that you're supposed to be talking
Think about which is the Saddam
Do you know about it
You're not he's not saying anything right
But that's why I feel like we need to get to
To the bottom of this whole song
Cuz you're not really saying anything about that but I want to know what he thinks about when he
PCS osama's nose you know like
What is the size that is large
Super small
In that pic
Do you know what I'm saying
I see maybe how you would want to have a good time. Arguing with Alex here but I don't think
Get the fruitful Road
Fair
The second goal of this kind of thing just kind of argue
Imitation is to make an argument without having
Own the fact
But you made that argument
How much is arguing that Saddam captured was fake
But he has every ability to pretend that he's not
If you were to say that he's making that argument he be able to weasel his way out of that by there's
Say that
Meanwhile Alex has been saying that Saddam fled to Belarus with his kids in a bunch of
Gold ever since he was ousted
Power so
If you're a person familiar with the content and narratives that are active on Infowars
You would know that what Alex is saying is not I don't know
He saying like basically that he wants to call it fake but he does have the right talking point
Anchor that claim yet
So he's going to play dumb
He'll take a bunch of calls and hopefully one of them will make a
The point that he could use to strengthen his conspiracy but me
Make no mistake
Alex isn't looking
For information that will help him arrive at the
The conclusion that the capture was real
If that was the case then
Would call into question
So many of his other narratives at the Iraq War and the pieces would start
The fall
It still needs to be fake in order for all these other things
To be maintained
Yeah I think that's one of the things that
Applicable in so many different ads
Except life is
That type of
Thing when somebody says that type of thing to you you know the
I'm saying this but I'm afraid to take
Responsibility
34 it
There is no point in like trying
Convince them of
They have no interest in being
Convince their they're trying to get
Through this
With what they have
Impact
Do you know well and there's a
If there is a conclusion or an ending point
That they're angling toward
And that they're going to
Keep moving toward
Regard
You're not going to
Talk them
From the delay so much of this other stuff is pretending to not really know and and all this
Is the performance
That kind of
Totally makes it
Seymour like Alex
Is doing a
Investigative process before he arrives right
Conclusion that
One way or another something was fake
I don't know who did this but it has that Fingerprints of every Republican I've ever seen
I'm just saying that they might be bringing up
Alex has a
Conspiracy here shocking
It's kind of
Decent way for him to go in order to maintain like I said a lot of those other trappings
He has that would intersect with
Saddam being captured
You know the I'm thinking of it more like Jenga
Like its
Pulling
Peace out
Does not make everything terrible
Frederick as if you were to say like oh that you do everything that they're saying about this captures totally accurate
Then the whole
Adult our Falls
What
Customer Hotel
Was cleared
Yes Alex has decided that the new way to go with it is he was a he was a prisoner
He was held captive
Right
You do not know when a person
I just feel like that's not I mean
Sometimes you know when a person's on drugs
True but you do not know when a person is on
Mega blanket
You can suspect
The Navy has cause to be a little bit
Suspicious
Seeing somebody on TV
After they've been in a hole for several days
I don't know if you can tell if they're on drugs or one way or the other
I think that might be a bit of a biased
Circumstance
Study on this
Being a hole for a couple days my kids
High as hell
Now do you see this is a good way for all of the
The things that Alex has said already to sort of biri contextualize
So
When
The when Saddam was asked
Different powered there was the he flew out to
Belarus
This Kim
Go along with that
It's like that was
We were wrong about that
The intel was there but they got double-crossed
So they kidnapped
Saddam in the hole and they were holding him
In order to be turned over
In order to
Give the global
The Big Boost
Put them on ice
Even even for Saddam they would not have
Put him in what amounted to a cough
Right
As far as a prison goes out at least put them in a room
Well
Yeah but
You hide in a coffin cuz you're trying not to be found
Or you don't want to be found until it's time for The Prestige reveal
The reveal that we have been keeping a sit-down with a coffin
Okay
So
He was
Coming back from Houston
I was listening to these talk radio station
Discuss the Saddam
Discovery
And he decided I got to get in the mix
Hotel room
Good morning
I'm trying as much greater thre
Iceland
Burbank Capt
What
Why are you calling
My regular
What
President
We've heard Alex yell at some people about lying but their calls to like seem like that I guess he's
Condemning himself here
No I don't believe that this happened
Necessarily
Doubtful but it's fun it's fun story
If it did happen
Which
Again I don't
I think
A more likely explanation for all of the things that Alex's describing
Is
That
The people who are producing a radio show
Had enough
Colors
Who maybe had the perspective that Alex in his own persona
They got the sense
This isn't going to be a good call
This person's going to be a pain in the ass to talk to I don't want to talk to the
This person
Where is his sort of Yokel character
Vetta is like I think that everybody should be
Maybe this is somebody who we don't have this voice calling in an entertaining
Come on people you got to stay listening right there might be a
Higher demand for that then whatever Alex
Just bring to the table and they're trying to do a show
Short so maybe that's
What
Penny Pincher
School.
Let me put you on this
So Alex calls in and they're like
Your Alex
Of course we can't punch
Do I dare
And then Alex goes in
Doing his cabin character and then they go hold on I'm going to have to put you on hold
Alicia
The Character Are You shiting me
We got to put this got we got to put them on
If he does the character
That would be fun
But again
It's not happening at solutely. But that is the way that I would believe it happened at it happen
Yes
So Alex spell gets a little bit more into his Saddam kidnapping Theory
Brog
All consistent with being in a coffin
Failure
Before the election
I don't think that's a bush
Administration
Let's get it
Because I do know that their first interview
And
Define this
As audio or video
But I have read
The transcript of Steve's first interview
Here's that they hadn't
Spoken before
And that is in 2000
Wow so they
They are in each other's lives
Maybe not like super
Closer
Email every now and again
Steve saying absolutely insane things possible
The kidney failure the Marfan syndrome thing is
He's a Steve Hallmark
Answer this
There's a part of me that thinks like I do that's
That's what Alex
Just trying to
Skewer with me
Trump
Ministration
Figure
It just
Checkered to me that
People used to
Text
Conspiracy theories to each other on
T9 can you imagine Flippin your razor phone open
Typing out like a long series of like here's what the Bush family
The Furious I got charged by the text back into the blue
Oh my God that's brutal he's not my plan here man come on
That's no good Lowe's of the days
You kids don't know what it was like trying to pill people on a flip phone
You all have it still good
Reviews like
Like
Newsletter
Far more effective
So
Alex
He's like really trying to leave
The perception
That you're I don't know what's going on here could be anything
But he's very clearly trying to argue that it was
Airport
Everybody
Palmetto
Conclusive evidence
Wait
From being in a coffin
You're concerned
Alex is making a ton of arguments for why this is a
The fake capture and he's attacking people like Dan Rather in the mainstream media reporting
It could not be more clear what Alex's position is
We still doing the song and dance about not knowing what he thinks
And I think
Part of that is that this position helps persuade listener
If you comes up guns-blazing yelling about how this is fake
He might be able to
Convince some or even most
To the audience
But if he does
Is it this way where he's slow plays his argument and pretends to be neutral
Alex is able to walk the listeners
To the conclusion
While making it feel like they were the ones
Who came up with
This is a pretty solid manipulation tactics but it's also
Requires a little settled
All this kind of thing off
Live nowadays
Now that is the real vibe that I get
From the way that he's deploying is ready
Yeah you know I also have the sense that
Free I am a prophet that knows everything and I'm always right about everything 100% of the time
Maybe he
Wants to
A1c
To go there
Right away
But he also has to talk himself into it a little bit
He has to give himself a
Pep talk
On why he should
Give a full throat
You know it's very shortly after that I doubt he's had too much time to think about it let alone come up with a solid plan
It's Sunday morning and this is Monday
We had plenty of time
I'm sorry
Sunday morning in this is Monday so he planned
No I'm saying if
You were somebody who
No use your time wisely
I'm saying all things being equal for a human enough time to come up with an argument
Right it's not like you found out right before you got on air then
Then I whatever into it is kind of
I think there's some Merit to that
Be
Images of like going to
The callers that I feel like it's B I need
Find where my hand hold a is here
I need to figure out what narrative I'm going to be able to hinge this on
I think there's that
Couldn't do it
Today is because
Today his character is
Is All-Seeing profit
You know he doesn't need to talk
Himself into anything
He's seated from
Yeah there's a week
Weakness to uncertain
Present whereas in the past
It does not
It doesn't hurt his position
And his branding
22 have that
Sort of uncertainty
When you start a cult you can doubt but
When you get to assert
Point you got to be all-knowing
That's just how it goes
Get some calls and they're mostly dumb and not really all that interesting
Necessarily get any any
Sort of
Thing to hang his hat on
There is a tall bikes
The tone stays
Fairly consistent throughout which is
This is fake
But also
I'm hatching a little
But some of the calls her kind of interesting
Alex
Because when they threw him in there
You can see if
Pacific Direct
Indication of manipulation and insertion of the actress
When they say that he had more
The God of War
Cedar Inn
Before the Pediatric
How they place them in the god coming out
Is it like that
One year anniversary of 9/11
New York Lottery
Right so if I
Alex is responding to the caller this way
Then he's reinforcing the argument that the Mars bar is being in the
A part of a calling card that the globalist through using
The only the elect
Good day
See the messaging of it
Furthermore
Those things
Have happy
So if you're comparing them to things that are concrete
Then that would suggest
That so is
Conversation is always like
Barely revealing of Alex's
Actual like
He wants the message the audience
Takes away from his show today
Right
I just
Just can't get enough of
Can't get enough of those solid
Foundational arguments of
A Hi-C they said this thing
911 and this person said this thing 911 clearly
Do not understand
And even that
Not really true
It came up with that argument
Alex
Call
And this person
I have something to ask about it
So I wanted to
I want to ask you did you ever hear of me
Sarah before
It isn't
First Patriots
Martial law
Oh yeah
I just heard
Some about I look at
Get their website but I didn't
What to draw Anna
Glad you know about
That's Aurora and Jess Aurora those are the two things
Like really popular and qanon
Yeah I know those are like Proto q-ship National Economic Security and Recovery Act
And then
Jesser has the global
But yeah I took this idea that all debts are going to be forgiven and I'd like
Great
For Alex to be like
That's bulshit there's something that is so beyond the pale
He's not entertaining any that's just
It is it is just so f****** weird to see him just be like
Nope
Bulshit
I mean even even tried a little bit with
You'd be like oh that's but even then he heads
He will try to go often
And then we even when he couldn't though
He still didn't just go on and say like
It's all bulshit he was like oh there right about some things he had to had to do a little bit of a middle ground
You can
If you think about it for a little while
I think you can come up with a pretty decent
Sense of why this has to be
Amatis undermines his own
Conspiracy
Like if this does exist
Then there is no reason to worry about the things Alex wants you to worry
And that is completely anathema to his
They space
I mean it is
It is still a similar kind of way of doing
Things like keep your keep your
Followers or whatever
Stasis
But in this situation it's in a stasis of like
We're on the cusp of everything being fine don't do anything
Another you do can really affect the coming of this
Rhinoceros
The only thing you can do to stop Nestle
Is giving me money
NFA different type of engine after fight it exactly
The fight
These are terrorists edging in in opposition to each other
More clip here and I think
That Alex is
Hey, this is
Basically just what we
We've seen it's obvious that he's he thinks it's fake
But the way he's talking
Think about it as these
These layers of
Dynamic
And I think
But maybe this will develop more over the coming days back in two
I will see about
But for now Alex has to be wrong
About this
Amazing
Or high-level bath
We need to go back and see what it was that we said
At the very beginning
Cuz I wasn't sure but I think I jokingly said
I bet he's just going to keep on saying it
Yeah I think I probably disagree with you but I gather going to be way to ship
Things around
Disconnect
December 2003 this is still his position that the bath party is being installed in all the powerful
Iraq
Amazing
It's it's
Very disconnected
Astonishing
Yeah
What what what
13 year old me would have been like
And it goes to show like how little
The audience
Or whatever like that should be glaring month-long thing he's wrong about over and over
Over and over and over and over again
Consistently
New reality does not penetrate
I mean
It's on the other hand it's not like they are
Necessarily mean nobody in the states at that time was
Very
Well-versed in like
Here's how you tell apart the bad party and you know
Yeah but that is the bad part of what are you going to say
Please invasion
Better cover
For putting the bath party in all these position
Sorry I was right 99% of the time
Beginning man
So we come to the end of this and we still don't have the predictions for the coming year 2023
But we are I'm on the beach
We will we will we will bring you those predict
So you can live your life
Accordingly
Right otherwise we won't know in which months
Chicago will be nuked
This year
Yeah we all know summer
A Fall of Rain could be a hangover
Content sugar things are possible in this
Scituate
So we'll we'll keep you posted on that
Are we come back
Shortly.
Indeed we do it's not right
Yes we are also
We are attorneys that knowledge underscore fight yes
We will be back but until then
I'm really
Emilio Emilio
I'm dzx Clark
I'm thrilled to play this great new
DJ Dan arti song free
To enjoy
The Highwayman
Actually I have a couple.
North Korea
Delivering
Trueway Harbor in May
What is the time supposed to do
Glenn Beck
Detroit
Shift psychic awareness
Ecology
I'm not ready to start the show
No
Dot-com
And now here comes
The sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work