Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge
Stripe.com
Play Welcome Back to fight knowledge I'm Jordan
This is a podcast where we worship at the altar of Selena and do anything but talk about Alex Jones
That's correct
Jordan
Bright spot today ideas you know I'm going back through all the albums that I may have missed from 2022
Year-end lists
Bration from my
Annual list of bangers no I did not I did not
But BlackSalt and Danger Mouse put out an album
Very very good and not Lisa which is absolutely spectacular
It's produced in such a way that it has that old kind of
Grittier feel you know that like will those early mixtape days you know back in the late 80s
Some of those early Roots songs like like
2.0
Back where it all started
Illadelph half-life
Around
Alright
Leonard up did you have likes
Some albums that you were like
Just leave
Are you going to be for likely month of January albums do it too
I wanted to listen
You know that kind of thing and then I've listened to a lot that I
No I'm grumpy
Alright what's the pop music that reflects
Grumpiness
See
This is interesting I'm the king of the Grumps
And I kind of like right now. Have solutely yes
Maybe something a little bit of Darkness
With that
The group Sally Shapiro has a new album out
Duo and DJ guy and
Kind of melancholy
Take me to albums
Together and then they quit
They were tired and then
I didn't realize this but it was recently put out a new album called a sad city is it a little bit
Does it have that kind of fun to know enough about Ladytron I can't really
Isn't that something that you recommended to me
A number of times in the past
I don't know I don't I don't know how to eventually
In the next couple of years we will be right back where we are now would be safe
What does that sound a little bit like Ladytron about a different probably
Today's get around to it I'm not good at taking recommendations
But yeah I've enjoyed that sad City
Album
I will definitely be listening to that
11 attala discount
Anthony
Annoys me
What up now I can't do it anymore so frustrated today
We do have brought to
I'm going to say this to you
Recently
Things have been very races
Wow
That is true
You know like pretty much a Non-Stop drumbeat of somebody being racist on The Daily
Sure right sir and I'm tired
Of that
It's been going on a lot so I thought let's try and have fun
Without racing
Okay
Okay that seems anathema to over the course of time doing the butt
I think it's an admirable goal right and I think I'm coming
Close
At least
On this particular episode
It is a show called Dreamland by this guy named Whitley strieber
Oh I know him
Going on right now
And I'm sure I'm sure he's right this somewhere
I'm sure he's racist I'm sure he's anti-semitic somewhere but not on this particular episode
One of the names of the I remember even from like back in my days of like
Reading the blogs and message boards
Conspiracies
Controversial figure in that if subways
He's never heard of him before
And then I looked at it with the interesting about him is that he's a fairly
Successful science fiction and horror author
Right in. John R at school
Right and he is also a guy who writes about Bigfoot you know and how like we're going to find
Dim sum that you don't like that kind of thing so it's a little bit like if he is Isaac Asimov
Was like I write great science fiction
And instead of the rise and fall of the Roman Empire it's like the rise and fall of the far blue viens
That kind of thinking maybe it's maybe it's heavily veiled
Fiction
Do you know like maybe it's
Maybe you
We're the fools were thinking that we should take what he saying about Bigfoot seriously might just be more science-fiction here's the thing
That's kind of what I'm talking about with his guests
Today interesting
I don't think he's doing that okay
Okay it's got the might be brilliant like immersive fiction author
Should be an Improv Everywhere. Something and his name is Joshua
Kuchen
Joshua
I think before we jump into that I think that Patton Oswalt
Had a mention of Whitley strieber in like one of his first album
While that was where my brain
Yeah
Which one is that
Might even been in the
No not the Robert Evans
B
That was that was coming into comedy
Shingles around that area before
Three years three or four years before that invited
The famous bowl
He is interviewing Joshua kuchen about his new book
Ecology of Souls
Who I am
We're going to get into that
But before we do how about we say hello to
Resume walk
That sounds like a great idea of team stats
You are now a policy wonk
Chunky honky-tonk you are now a policy walk
I'm opposed to any morricone who is tired of hearing Alex used
Ecstasy of Gold
From Good the Bad and the Ugly coming out of Ed brakes
You are now
Ennio morricone
It's that whatever
Okay alright
We're not going to do that we're not going to do this with your handwriting.
God Lennon
You are now a policy was to Linnea Linnea. Jesus Christ learn how to write
Are you sure that's not true
And the fan of Jordan you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy
Oh okay I'll text okay
Eminem fan Jordan hero rhymes
We also have a technocrat
I'm so sorry I've listened to your entire back catalogue twice
You are now attacking
Crap
Start don't get mad until you're brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Jesus Christ
Very much to all of you
By then so
Today we're talking about this interview on Dreamland
The Ecology of souls Ecology of souls Joshua ecologically
I thought you said
Economy of souls at first I thought I got we're going to get some black soul Bank
No it's it's
More of I mean
First off
I've read the book
It is
Roughly 300,000 words
I do know you do I can I just have to plan to do this yesterday morning
Sure it is
Almost like a like an adventure adventure from like the 40
1800 coming back to the club and in Britain being like
People
South are you know what's that
Got a vivisection it was sold
And in this region fairies are known for their particular wings
Fun at the scripture okay sent an anthropology
F*** rules and if it were real
This person is so convinced that what he's saying is just more like
Documenting the kingdom phylum
Jim versus genie versus you know all of that stuff
As it relates to the sort of cataloging and description of Souls
We all knows what the compound noun is of a soul
Right I mean you know there's like a murder of crows there's a there's a blessed Union of Souls
No I don't believe this way
She likes me for me my God
No it's not the name of that song There's a band
Leonardo
One hit wonder by like
Bush no
Bush
Yeah what are those 90 Sum 41 or something like that
Different cattle
They were pop punk
Bush was more like
Just on the end table grun
But like a Jars of Clay version of purple rain rain on my face
Grace the flood what's the Stacy's mom one that was founded
That was later just go later
Pleasant Union of Souls had the Hey Leonardo to like me for me so I also I believe
Love is the answer I believe
Love find a way
Terrible
Yeah you're well you're not selling me on
Hey Leonardo pretty good
He goes into the compound noun
But there are a few threads throughout this interview
That are happening at the same time and yet entirely unrelated
Before we get into too much
How about an out-of-context
How about it
Felt like a woman to me
Okay
I assume he's talking Souls
It's
He's a person who that was pulled from the commercial
Which is him under hypnosis
Explaining how he was having a sexual encounter
With an alien
It's alright it's just
For me it's just so funny
When he goes
I thought it was a woman
Yeah there's a little bit dramatic my favorite
Absolutely
Stop by today were talking about Joshua kuchen
Ecology of Souls and I think stryver introduces him Beth
Go ahead and play that
Britton amazing you book
Cold
Recology
Absol
He's the author of
Critically acclaimed books
Trojan feast
The food and drink offerings of aliens
Fairies and Sasquatch
Which we have
Talked about
The brimstone.
An in-depth examination of Supernatural
Sense
Otherworldly
Orders and monstrous me asthma's okay
Of the night
History of supernatural child abduction
And where the fruit
Prince and highest range
Kissing a Bigfoot
Phenomenon
All of the
Very cool
All of them loved by you I mean we didn't
Talk about all of them
Once we
We talked about
Will up by
You loved
I'm cool
People
Loved
Yeah people loved
They didn't talk about all this
I don't know what it is about that one title that is just
By the miasma the okay
He was pretty excited
I also was pretty excited
Out of all of those books the only one I want to read this one about weird Smith
Otherworldly spell show up
I don't know that book I could not fight I think olives might be otherworldly is a smell
Cuz I love the smell of them that you open a jar of olives
Sure
That's otherworldly 2832 which Mandela effect for you
Somebody gave you the smell of olives in Another Universe maybe maybe not necessarily Mandela effect
Witchcraft
Otherworldly
Ripped
You know any other smells
The world that's it that's a great question maybe like
Fresh cut grass
That's that's that's
What's the different sets of different
Sure
Fed is petrichor
Which is the smell of dirt after rain or something along those lines but
It's very very important to Doctor Who friends close to fresh cut grass you know
Both are lawn
Adjacent
Pretty much
Absolutely turns out we just want lawn
I think I mean it's impressive anybody who's written
More than one book of nonsense
Yeah it's always going to tip my hat to that
This man
Is an impressive writer
In-N-Out in some ways
He is an impressive writer
To the point where if he were writing in at
The you if we existed in the universe
Where what he's writing makes sense
He would be like the pop historian
Yeah like Barbara tuchman of imaginary
B******* you know what I also want to hear about the food offerings of the fairies and wizards and
2:10
Fairly interesting it's got to be like what the food
Springs Arby's stuff like
Ambrosia
He's he's a classic
So everything that he does and the reason that went music Classics you don't mean like
In terms of the Academia
Like Greek and Roman history
Fairies and the foods they want to series as just like what we
Kenzie and fairies or whatever it is you want to go on there
He's talking more like
Everything from human history that might resemble a fairy falls under the classification
Fearraiser
Therefore you can go from region to region
Almost anthropologically sakes in this area fairies are fed
Berries on the table
Mary Berry fairy berries is one of my favorite British cooking show
He's kind of got that and that's why people love them
In this world is because
Everything he writes
It's is exhaustively
Ridiculously reference
His bibliography for the Ecology of Souls
Runs 160 Samad page
Too much
And it's all pretend
What are references
Is anywhere from like a scientific paper from the 1800s
To a poem
To f****** cave paintings just being like became famous
He's proved it I bet it's also like three of those pages or zebit
Exhaustive
Crazy I'm exhausted
Strivers starts out the way anybody any good interviewer would
Let's get some background information
This is the start of one of our threads
Which is Strivers interview Style
Okay
Joshua
You spend it all
Where do you ask
From know your
Your
Curriculum vitae on your website
Is Joshua coaching.com by the way
Doesn't really tell us much about
Jealous about what you
Done
But
Tell us more about
Who you are your musician among others
Well I suppose that the
The simplest thing right away is
To see that I'm sitting here in Georgia wearing Wisconsin
Sweatshirt and I'm from North Carolina
Understand exactly
Eazy-E funny about it
So you live in places like
Whitley did say like where you from non-sequitur answer but
It doesn't really tell us much about this person other than he's moved I guess what he's trying to say is like I'm a little from Eva
Everywhere in the South I suppose
But I got that's that's not really answer
Latest Wisconsin.
I'm having a day North Dakota recent North Carolina
Is Georgia Wisconsin North Carolina that's what it was you know what though
Debatably the South
Wisconsin North Carolina South Carolina for sure North Carolina
Debatable Wisconsin definitely not
He's not getting too much information
To give you an idea of what Joshua looks like
He's he's he's a
Pretty large dude
He's six-foot-three he's half
Superman
Pretty bold
With a neckbeard
Psych no
Mustache is all around the neck
That's not far off from a look that I might have been pulling it some points in high school
It shaved my head periodically and I had an Amish beard
You know I had the the tried to connect with my Mennonite roots
You're doing it intentionally but
If you're dunno
Something older person
Well. It's not a problem but it doesn't it's not
Not for a 15 year old
Sol will continue on it it'll tell us a little bit more
Yes sir so I was I was raised in North Carolina
20 minutes north of Charlotte
And I will
To undergraduate
Go to the university of
For music performer
So I came down to the University of Georgia
Where I got a master's in music literature and a master's in
Journalism
And you know big cities have a certain gravity and they sort of pull you in overtime so I'm
Getting closer and closer to Atlanta
I might have to get the
A cheap escape velocity at some
Point the right now I'm in the Marietta area
Okay well I didn't tell us much either
Sure
I relate to this visit
Whitley's Charming me a little bit
He's got a certain style as long as I got to look into either these guys
Beyond this episode kind of gaslighting
Graphical stuff
Yeah she's either response to the question
It's just like
I don't know
Maybe I'm not charm here's here's what I'm
As far as this goes
I think
What Whitley is looking
Looking for is more of a supernatural aunt
I think I think
It's more
Based on what we've heard so far shuttle running about that
It feels more like the where you from is like
It should be
Where are you from emotionally where are you from like what's the another your lineage
Through this b******* as opposed to like
Geographical locations
You stop that
And how you're afraid you might end up in Atlanta
Worse Fates than ending up in Atlanta is better than Atlanta
I've got certain charm I'm not saying it doesn't
I'm just saying I don't know I've never been but I've just talkin out of my ass
What caught my ear is he is a musician who has a master's in music literature
So I wanted to see what was going on
My man please
Booktuber
Okay that was not what I expected you were not expecting that cuz this is
These types of shows I was assuming like
He has a master's in Theremin
Tuba solo
Wow
What you doing the Duke of Earl
Do Governor that was one in particular because
One is video on YouTube is just a close-up of him and his tuba like right on his face
And then the tuba
And then attached
The tuba is a cup holder with a full beer in hell yeah
I do
The whole performance
Is there everybody in the band gets their own solo and that's why I
Play that audio just a little bit beforehand because you want to come to his solo
He went into the audio on the video cut it out and added it so he could be and I respect that
This might also answer the question of the namaste
Mouthpiece Chafin can be difficult on a tuba
You know you're not wrong I had not considered that I played a French horn and I remember
They're being
Difficulties
I had not considered that that's a good point.
Yeah anyways this through the marching band nerd if I ever heard one. Seems like it's tough to play the tuba and not be
Again I feel like I'm fairly confident we're not in racist territory here I don't know why
But I feel like
You can't be a racist tuba player
You can't be in a band playing the tuba and being racist at the same mileage Italy have no counter
Examples but I strongly disagree with you
I think it wouldn't be too hard to find a racing tuba player the clan has tuba players
That's fair
You're right
I don't think they're tuba players in the soul that they can't like
It's tough to play the tuba with a hood
Mouthpiece
Oacac so anyways scriber is going to is going to continue his investigation
Navigation here and he's going to keep telling us a little bit more about his background a Joshua and where he comes
What the heck
Heck
Are you doing writing things about
A new mythology of death and the Paranormal for example
I didn't hear anything in any of this
Tells me why you do what
What you do normally that you're brilliant
I mean these books are
Phenomenal
Wet Willie's telling on himself never been to Wisconsin
Everyone there is it to the new ideology of death
Yep yep
That is what your college visits a new mythology of death
Interesting
Yep that's
Pretty heady now another reason why stryver might think he is very very brilliant
Because Schreiber is referenced a lot
Okay yeah
Quite a good way to go to good review
Especially the part where I've been in a bunch
I think you hear why I love
Strivers interview-style just so just
The heck
Are you doing how's the feeling of being rude and less their friends and that makes you assume that their friends when they
They may not be so high in the weird
Community
Feel like you can pull whatever s*** you want to just says whatever he's thinking
Also you got to be pretty old
Oh he's burial yeah cuz I thought he would be dead yeah yeah he's very very old
The 90s quite frankly
Like an art bell type
I can't remember when that was maybe there
But that that's well I mean also that's why his his questions take a little bit longer to to get going
Is it takes a while for the bolts are rolling down the hill
What's going on in this book is it the little bit like
John Hodgman book you remember
Do that.
Unlike that feed the hobo signs
Right
It's a little bit like that but if John Hodgman was telling you
Confidently
This is a
Real
Buckeye am describing to
Keep going on
Go ahead play the neck
That's very kind of you I guess
Shy but he knows
Just kept on wanting to interject that I guess I read to me
Show me books by this
Streamer guy
That sort of put me off on this path
Oh I'm a real
Torn in the side
Of the ordinary world
I don't belong here
Well I think you're right about
You don't belong here
Yeah the cracks unlocked
Correct
Where are we in
I'm here
What's glitches jump in
There's a lot of
Cool stuff
In this book about
Fairy
Folks
The ecologist
So we're going to talk about
This is huge idea a new mythology of death
Asuna paranormal
Over the course
Because that's the
TitleBucks over the course of the interview
But let's talk first
What about the series
Oh
The others
No I mean
I've had them around in my life
My wife
Lot of my list
Have to
Why do people have
I looked it up during the eclipse he's only 77
Really I thought he would be older than 90 days
You see him if you look at him
He looks great for 77
Sure
No I mean he looks great for
He looks very bad 475
I got that wrong he looks very bad for 7790
Weird
It's a strange thing where you have like these people slotted into various places in your brain
And like I was
Iodine ooh that name and I was almost certain
He was ancient yeah
Yeah it is it is like stuff
It's old when you're young as you get older seems twice as old as it was you no like
If it if your dad Reddit you know even he was only thirty years older than you you feel like it was a hundred years the same time
I mean Barbara Walters just passed
She was in her 90s
I think our what we're describing is that we don't know how old AJ individual celebrity may or may not be
I need to make flashcards
We need to practice on this we got a Verizon all this stuff
So the fairy folk are involved
Yep yep yep easystart about the fairies I mean I'll say he starts a chapter like
I guess with this sentence
There are also physical fairy doubles
Whoa
. isn't that something
That you
You can visit
First sentence that's a great person
8 using also in the first
Sentence of a chapter probably go
What is a
Physical is it like okay so I'm guessing that fairies are not physical beings are kind of ethereal
Ghost like
Creatures or something and then
There are also doubles
They can take physical form
Or do only some take physical form
I mean
Cut you off
Too many questions Papa
There are also fairy double
The also refers to
There are human doubles
There are
There's space doubles there are there's just doubles of everything
How else you can play
So there's two things that exist side-by-side
Is it weighs what he tries to to get through with his
Is is main fees
Let me do that just mean twins a little bitty
But like who do
It's a little bit like parallel universe kind of stuff
You know you got another one of you
In another universe that we can never access and may not be
Okay but you can't see
But if you're in that universe
That he lives in
Then you got
Where you from
I'm wearing a t-shirt from Wisconsin
So what coaching is doing is trying to create a grand field theory of pretend
Trying to
And what he does is he
He takes from everything
And I mean
Everything he can
He he pulls from
You know Greek mythology
Peoples from
AAA did the Christianity abrahamic religion kind of thing he pulls from Eastern philosophy
And he's trying to put all of this stuff together into one thing
Right that's not going to work
It stuffed
To do
I guess I just know
This has been tried before
Well doesn't work
Yeah go ahead and keep going
Mastiff
Frankly I mean
It's a
Really something
Thank you so much
It's sort of
It sort of evolved
Into a snapshot
Highlights
I think about these
Make them all sit together
Because I am in a lot of ways
Pan paranormalist
Like that I want to see
See how the Fairy stuff.
It's in with the cryptic
Good stuff and I will
You sit into the
Do your folks
Eddie Bullard
He drew a lot of similarity
The UFO contact
You got
Kenneth ring obviously whom you work with quite a bit
Experience
Contact
It just seems like every contact modality
We has the Fest
Of the same shared at
Regardless of where it is so
How many makes a good point
Bananas much as like if we're all going to do all this pretend
Stop
We're going to have all these ideas
Back to have to exist in the same unit
You know like so that what is it is there something
That supervenes upon ghost
And fairies and squat
And all this
Is there some kind of a like
Unknown Universe law or something
That explains this kind of stuff would have to be
Right he's easy with crazy about him picture think
What's crazy about knowing I read his book what's crazy about him is that he's kind of
Got a good
Thought process
In insofar as where he's trying to take the
His is philosophy is this
Something along the lines of
If any of these religions are true
Right
Then there's a chance that any of them are
Sure so
Either they're all true
Or all possibly true
Or none of them
Because if a religion is possible
If magic is pause
Possible then all bets are off
All magic
Is possible
It's itsy it seems like if there is one magician
There is potentially you talk
Exactly
At the same time
If there's one magician
It's possible there's only one magician
But he
He saying
Thought I don't
For see him coming to any
Good conclusions necessarily but
I I think it's it's an interesting
Well what's it what are the conclusion that it comes to is it going to after he goes through all of his talk
Where is URI would look through all of this and see like
Okay well you see this
This isn't real we prove that that's not
Listening
We proved that's not really proved all up so much of this s*** is real
So by your line of thought I'm just going to go ahead and say
But none of it
Right
And he goes
You can't prove it
The doll real
Yeah that's a problem problem
On the other hand though
It's so well-researched
It's so
Janja and let me try and give you an idea of
Some of the things that I'll do he does a couple of academic trick
Which are fun
Well uses big words I heard that already
That's one of the big ones of course but
He uses his references
Very deceptive
So I'll give you a tall man
Listen to this
Overwrought
Typically red-eyed from her continual crying
The Banshee appears as a woman with long hair in a green dress under a grey cloud
The others Cloud her and white
The color of bloodless corpse as
And ghosts
Or Greek spirits who appeared pallid
Because they were deprived of the Sun
She loves brushing her hair and is considered
Very dangerous even today to pick up a
Straight comb
You find laying on the ground in case it belongs
The fairy woman
The Banshee fairy woman who's crying all the time
Remember just leaving friend
He's got
3 quotes
M3 references
For those quotes
Ch1 has their own referee
Now what are the references comes after
What are the
Citation citations comes after
Cloud in Cloud her in white
The color of bloodless corpses in ghosts
Is a
Citation from that
But it makes it look
Visually like he's sighting
The typically red-eyed from her
Continual crying the Banshee appears line making it sound like he's backed up the most insane part of that
He's always crying
And that she's always crying all of these things are crazy
Referencing a different way of describing something as what
Oh wait what is with the citation is like 2 at the Souris Houston
The it's just the the cloud her in white part that's no good
I do I do think
Okay so just
From
The perspective
I don't know I feel like that that description of a banshee does
Does the Banshee dirty
A little bit
Well you saw there's for descriptions of a banshee in that one thing but they're all accurate
Exactly
Problem
If one of them's real they're all real
Sometimes red sometimes White
Dressed
Always crying Greek to brush hair
Pick up a comb are in one paragraph that has multiple citation
Two things that have nothing to do with proving that it's
Is the advice that like if you see a comb don't touch it
Guess it's good advice
Sure
The weird part is the to this day like
Hey man
To this day that's
It's still real like we haven't aged out of
No not like not like being like
This belief still persists to this day I thought the Banshee was like yelled and hurt you with noise
Well that's one type of Banshee
From this region
The Banshees are well known for their Bubba
I thought that was like the defining characteristic that's the one thing people know about
Maybe that's because of the Marvel character banshee
Well I could babe
I feel like man she is a fairly young like a banshee is kind of a expression
Users manual
What color clothes
Does Banshee have in the gygax manual
Tattered
Tell Josh color is a standardized
But the tatters are
So nice you crying
What did you do
See that's what I want
Well that depends on what's wrong
We all share the blame so we get into twin tracks here
This is where coaching and streever kind of
Start
Branching on separate pathways
Alright Cutchins going to start talking
King about his book
Schreiber has
Described as a story to
So I think you're going to see these start to play out over this next couple
The afterlife is it
Some sort of
Realm where time is
Is held in stasis
Skip to be amongst everyone is passed on
Their ideas in older cosmology
Especially from
Imperial China
That the afterlife
Was again
I'm mirror
Version of
This world where
You know according
To that you would have to get up and work and there might be
Technological process
What happens on the other side of this failed
This is their technological
Process
The technological progress that happens on this side
About as well
Egyptian farmers
We'll have to get up and plow their fields and worship all the same gods and basically life
Continue
So once you take
That little
Tidbit of information and
Frame it within
Some
Speculation
Ufology
It's been around for quite
Sometime
This is literally after
Life technology
It starts
To get really bizarre
That sucks
Yep
Three bums me out
If there is like an afterlife that is eternal and you still have to have a job
I mean I like podcasting I enjoy this but I still don't do this for absolutely I have no idea
Why everybody wants eternity
There's no end to it
Now what that did
Is that got stryver a little bit excited
Because he started talking about technology from the other side from the after
Okay like a like a rake
Right or a sickle for the farmer
A little bit different
Because
Stryver is fairly convinced that his
Cochlear
Was
Brought over from the other side it is technology
From the deadline
Does make sense
And he is going to start telling us a little bit about
Okay okay this
Sounds good
Well I think it must be
I was certainly
Convinced
That
That was
Exactly I mean that's what he said
But the man said
Fascinating about that man
And folks
Those of you who don't know the
Story
I have an email to Mike this is a this is a long clip so you can cut in at anytime this story on Glisan
Bisturi
Meander
That makes it all the more important for me to pay attention cuz I got a track
These are dumb talk and enjoy it
Also
Don't you have some experience of the world of cochlear type of implants and hearing aids
Are you sure I'm positive 100% sure they have not been brought over from the other side I mean you were involved
That industry this makes it sounds like a cover-up honestly I was in the hearing aid
Part I wasn't in the cochlear implant part so I only know that hearing aids
Thoroughly EarthBound
See you do you have any grounds tacos
There was a doctor
Who's King 2
Get it X-rayed and he was on his way to
Asking me to get it removed
Are there was a removal attempt years ago
Rafael Fortune
But in any case I wasn't going to get it removed but whoever was
Involved with
It did not miss
Necessarily
Real quick
When he says it is it like a tumor or something
Just a cochlear implant
Coco I didn't know what the it was in the other side
Baby more nutrients
Force
Let me put it that way
So couple of nights
For the
PET scan
Was
Set up
I had a
Visit
From
Two men one of whom I know
And I say I know him
I've seen him through four
In my life I've seen him
I've seen him
I had seen him
But I went I went out
The desert one night
Ben just
Time completely alone out in the
And then I've seen
This additional
And he proceeded to explain it all.
And
To explain the
17 Rod of a story and ever
Everything then said that is based
Chiclets
Had been
Its technology is
Joshua's just said
Other side
But he wasn't in
The man
Is
Identical
To a man I know well
In what
Who has no
Idea
I'm going to tell
In fact we're can I have
Have lunch later later
Today
And I'm going to
Story for the first
He's going to love it
Keanu
Is I love the story I'm sorry
Stupid
One of the strangest things
You said his ever
In my life and in his
I had a second do about it though
He's never heard the story
Years and years
I don't have those
I'm not the
There was in the rumors
Spilled people
Room in the cabin
Spelled with p
One of whom I knew
And
He was in italics
Through my
For a long time
And
File better way
Think anything more but I never told a soul
The name
Not my wife not any
I've never
Spoken it
Fast forward
Years
No I won't
Justin talking about
The normal human
Part of it
And
He proceeded to tell me
Of
Kiss encounter
Experience which
Total blackness
He doesn't remember anything about it except
It happened
And he was reading it
I met him when he was a boy to our a version
And
He came away from
Experience
He said with only one
Sing
He had been remembered if you've been told underlined
In a detective novel
And he was told that this
Person
Newsom
Did he have been
Told
Never
Does switch
With anybody
Heifer
The name
Ended
Active now
What's the
The guy
Witnessed that
Sexually
You're so ready to respond you are not ready for the kicker I will sleep for about the last minute
Go back to where people can't see this but I was waiting a pen in the air haha
You really hit me at the end tonight
Now I don't know what's going on
Because here's what I was thinking I was like I get it I get it when I get
This guy is like he's he saw this guy as a kid because
He the other guy the kid
Wright was having a visitation from Alien
And all he had was blackness
He doesn't know anything and that was because
The aliens were using him
To visit Whitley
I got it you got the story then the sexual encounter in the name
Detective book I kind of lost track of time
The Only Name Penny underlined in the book Hercule Poirot
Witness
My sexual encounter with the other
Oh my God
Unknown
This is part of the story that he's told
Plenty of times you must have butt for me
I enjoyed the mystery
I'm trying to put together
The whole the totality of
So he's been visited by this person
The three times
Cindy's life and this person looks identical to somebody that he knows and is real
Life who he's going to have lunch
And Lisa Kai
It when he was a kid had a visitation is all just darkness because he's body
He was being used to visit Whitley fast forward 30 years now this guy had underlined
Find a name a detective book
Because it was the name of somebody who would watch the Whitley f****** jokes
That is correct
That is the story talk about this
Let's let's hear touch of the responses
Okay
It seems like quite a challenge
Yes
The forest that says okay that's the one that makes the most sense
Say more words but that's what that's
It's like these little
Mystery box
As developed
Send sis a hoping you'll tell me a little bit about
The relationship
Between
The guy who I know it
Absol
No idea
Of any of the
The other meetings iPad
Giamarese doppelganger whatever
What are the
What is going on
Really really
It does not relate to his book whatsoever
But if his book is like this
Sort of
Pan idea of
Then it does
Everything relationship
That's the problem
Stuff inside of stuff. This is what I'm supposed to be here for it
Just like this guy who I know in the real world have blackmail on me from what
Read about him having the Leverage
Oh yeah and I mean it is going to go on strike
Focus again this is another log clips
Stop whatever you want but I'm glad
For it though cuz I I do need contacts
No
Often been tied
All manner of
Phenomenon
And
Seems like something like that might
Maybe what
What's going on with that
Scenario that you outline
What's the part of this
Schedule
Maybe even this place
Time Fraulein
Because I think that
What time place unsworth
Part of the
Visual was able to sort of wander off on a
What's up
Obtain
Information
I don't know when I first saw him he was a
The boy
He was about 13
I
Encountered him at a baseball game
And
He was sitting
With
A gentleman from the
Defense
Whom are you
Who hit her face
The Tall Blond
Ledge
And it in
Out in Boulder
Colorado
They're gone now they're not there anymore and that's also
Shutdown
Very active
And I was rather surprised to see him
And I assume is with three children then I assume these children
Or something
Special because he wouldn't
The Ben with the mother
And it was quite clear after
Couple of
Moments
The baseball game
Seemingly
Brandon
Ticketed
Sitting beside them
It was nothing random
I'm about it I'm sure
They could read my mind
They were good breeders
And I so I figured whatever
Is going on here
I don't want to
Interface
Kim director
All kinds
The problems that
I'm with the
The greatest
Compliance
Are you cannot imagine
Believe me
It's a it's a path
You don't want to go down if you're
Deeply enmeshed
Siam
I didn't say anything
Left after
Loyal
But boy
You talk out here about
Fairy birth
Hairy Birds
I don't want to call it a talent but a pension
For switching topics train tracks
That story didn't help me
I'll be honest I mean from what I can take away from that store
Here's what's going on
Alright
He went to a baseball game
And this guy was sitting next to him with his kids
And his kids that the guy's kids were talking to him and it sounded like they knew exactly what he was thinking good readers
Grade level because their dad
Is allied with the tall blonde people right and he's with the graves you don't want to be
They're still there
The
Fight you know they can still be friendly enough to watch a baseball game in silence
What
Is he
Cuz I
I assumed
That this guy who is in at lunch within himself wherever similar age
It's right and so he would be a kid at that point to right right
So why is he why does he know the dod agent
Who's talking to the kid
If he himself if wheatly himself as a
See now that's a problem that I'm having
Maybe he's an adult maybe he's a butt bit older than this lunch partner
I think he's either
In this situation he's an old man
Himself
Like this is like in the past couple years or so
This story
So he's still in his mid-seventies and this friend is like
50 there's
Write up as a kid
Well that's when he saw him in his dreams as a kid look like as a kid
I don't know what you look like as a kid
Yep
Idaho ZIP code
This is this next part is just money I
I just love this bar
Okay
Oh
Another thing
Wanted to ask
You so badly is
Crazy
The fairies
Converse
There adverse
Iron
My cab
Over
What are the largest
Themes of iron
Planet Earth
The Iron Mountain
Record storage facility
Is drilled into it about
20 miles north of the
Magnetic
Yeah it's it's interesting because
I think that
The only thing I say
Thank you
Ferry and Ferrum
You have the Latin word for iron
That's kind of what I'm thinking is at play here
What's what's funny to me is
That was not a class
Just telling him that he was not a bunch of hired who is opening up for the question of what's the deal
With fairies being advertised verse 2
Ironhide I mean I don't know if he is
I think he's I think he might be asking if fairies will still come to his place if he lived on top of all this iron
I would say not
The available information
Steer clear of Iron Mountain
It must be
It is just
Ferrum though
I mean like that's just what that's the whole thing that's going on in similar
Yep that's that's pretty much it
Yep
Something we know and love about Alex is his ability to go to add brakes
Let's see how Whitley
Compares to that
Well I feel like I was brought here to do a job in
It never occurred to anyone involved
Vacation song
You're awesome
I forgot the first race
Completely you'll be
Be delighted to know free dreamlanders
So I might blast you more with the little of banners
Sayang-2
Please subscribe
She will not do
But that's okay
Here let's do a break now here's this year's a break
Probably be the only break
In the shoulder
Okay
Here we go
Read reminders goodbye for a few minutes watch these
Will be back with Joshua kuchen
The Ecology of
His website is Josh
.
I think he's depressed
Stripers not doing well
Sad
Which you want
Do right
Certainly not now thinking about it
I'll put the thing up to tell you to subscribe but you're not
Palliative care
The weirdest thing is that I saw a child
Who was Whitley and he told me 6.
30 years later
That's the part that you just can't ever get best that's the end of that story
This is the break is just a commercial for his you know documentary about how he was under automatic writing
Eating hypnosis kind of thing sure he's telling this story
Of how he had sex with an alien or whatever it is
That seems really primary much bigger
What kind about it is it's just sleep or else it's so obviously just
Sleep paralysis even just going through like the symptoms of pressure on the chest
About it is just lie Perales inhofe and it's intercut with these lifetime style Recreation
So there's plenty of like
Like that just also itself sound effects work
And then
As we come back to break I want you to hear this because this is bananas to me
Have you ever read communion
Or have you never read communion
It's out
Any new edition
Mareep
Powerful
Subtly
New cover
It reflects the fact
Put the visitors are now
Looking back
Because they truly are
You can get it
From the unknowncountry.com store
As a Kindle
As a beautiful Sumptuous paperback
Bored
Unabridged
Audiobook
Read by me
No the first time in the whole life
Communion
It is been read
In
In audio format
And believe you me
I shoved
Start breeding
I put
My life my memories
Intuit
And I trust you can hear it in The Voice
I sure felt
While I was reading
So get communion
Listen to it
Read it
Communion
Is Centrelink
Importance
All of our lives
We're talking to Joshua cut York
No I think it wasn't I heard the audio change a tiny bit
There I don't think it was
It's possible but I think there's a chance that was pretty important
Did Josh communion with a came out in 90
So for the year I was born a happy birthday
For however many years that is 30 something years
There has been no demand for an audiobook
Not one time has it been read on audio no one has wanted
Audio book audio book
Gay man
What we're at is the we're going to reprint it how about you doing audiobook for 35 years or whatever
Gotta want it
I don't know you must have an audience fan base
But I think it's not a selling point that he read it
I think anybody else where you can get
Weird NPR Garrison Keillor but creepy voice
If you ever read it
Review
Skip over the next little chunk because they start talking about
Drugs
Okay DMT and they start talking about otherworldly experiences
And then after like
Five ten minutes of talking.
I've never done
I've never done any hallucinogenic at all
What
Get the f*** out of here it's not appropriate not appropriate
Imagine
Pretended drugs are
Are bad or whatever
That was a
Symbolism
Well
You've got
You got a lot of
Throughout a lot of
That are called psycho
You're not familiar with that term
You are
Mister cultural osmosis
We think of
Celebrities would be like the Grim Reaper or the angel of death or
Anniversary
Egypt or Hermes
Sportbelt
Valkyries
And some Norse mythology
But these are figures that leave you a
Frost depth
Threshold
I take you and they guide you
Depending upon the Serta
Religious system
You might actually
See them cross
Your live stream
As well
Donna Leedy
These figures
But also you see
Certain natural phenomena
Episode of the Moon serving the psychopomp role of carrying Souls
Animals
And
The animals that you see almost in body
Almost always
Companionship and or transport
The way things like
Obviously
Meeting you at
Being faithful
Horses which
Take you places that boring animals
Birds which
Can travel to play
Knox
Butterflies
Cycle
Soul away
On your wings
Mullets cuz my other creepy
What is one reason the butterfly or like a bee
Well a butterfly is a psycho pump in Mesoamerican called what about a be
I think he's a pretty chill but they've got wings so they might as well be mosquito anything that has wings
He literally said anything with wings sure
Okay
Pterodactyl here is here is his a psychopomp pterodactyl
That's my new alias
Stop doing the anthropology textbook
He gets into the the new mythology he's creating which is essentially the
We're all scared of death
And these are all things that we've made up
To help us get to die
All of it
UFOs
What do you think of UFO is if not a fairy
If somebody was a 1500 they wouldn't know what a UFO is they'd say it was a fairy if somebody was in the thigh
Thousands they wouldn't say it was a very they'd say it was a gym
If somebody was in the 500 they wouldn't say the Jinn they would say the but you know so he's just racing all this same s*** back
Back and back and back until you get to the very beginning and what it really is
All afraid of death
Oh and yeah the Sun and moths
And mob
The whole thing let me try this on
Psychopomp in Psycho circumstance
I don't know what that is love Pachelbel
Is that your
Graduate
Canon in D
But it's email graduation showcase
Sampled by Vitamin C Graduation song
Well actually if you look at the history of Kamala do you like regular
Remind us of death
Hey
But yeah so everything everything is about death
Or is it
I think it must be over maybe not there's more there's more
Motif a lot of the behaviors
What popular ufology would call UFO occupy
Seems to me rural other
Behavioral
What's more I mean
You are so is
Is a transportation metaphor
Like that's primarily what it is it
What everybody talks
Where they are where they come from how do they go here look at way they travel
It's all about
And transportation metaphors are almost
Always
Metaphors
The River Styx that's the whole thing all right now is there is it actually about
Technology
From the future
From the other side there's technological elements do it this spacecraft
Or the boat
Right
Strivers
Argument could be made
You know it we know Italy
I know when
The other side
Does
Have technology
Because I'm wearing
So there
4 by wood
UFOs
BuzzFeed
Technology
From another world
Now we got that gas
That is
A house built on Sand there is nothing supporting any of those premises
Just because we've established that my earpiece is from the Dead Land
Therefore there's technology from the dead land over here so why you not UFOs
Here's the thing
Here's the thing about this and this is why I feel like this is our most non-racist
The interview or whatever today silly kind of exactly because there are no metaphors
For like the other is the Jew in this situation
The other
Is
The up it's just
It's really it's the literal other why are you even talking about Jews or or land Beyond Death
No there's no mistaking it for something else you're going to listen to three more episodes of this anyway I take it all back
Never going to listen to three more episodes that's the point mist
You're going to be quite a demand for you to listen to any more of this
So anyways at the end of that he said I can you guess what the fact
That he eat at the end of it he goes well the fact is
Can you guess what it
I'll tell you if you think it's one fact
You are wrong I was going to say something along the lines of like
You don't need birth control with your fuckos something like that I don't know
Becca
I have a
Been in another world in a
Jeep with
Another guy
This kid which
This is all movies
And
Ridden the bicycle
In another world down there
Down the street here about a year ago
You're in a half
So
Are these worlds
Is there really sort of Anna
Ethereal world of the Dead
Are we kind of oscillating back
And forth between
22 very fish
Or a third possibility
In another world is interesting
But far less interesting than him kidnapping a child in a jeep taking them to the
Another world in a jeep with another guy's kid
Every step of that sentence gets worse
Court transcripts
Nickel the details but legally I can't
Important
Message to send
Don't get into other people's food
It's just sleep paralysis that's all this is
Autobike yeah exactly in another world
If he's asleep driving is Jeep with another person
No problem
So finally Cuts is going to get his chance to talk a little talking about his thing a little bit and
Well I mean again he's trying to synthesize all of this into one just you know
We're all afraid of death
I hesitate a lot of time
Times to go download
Rabbit hole because
I think that we can
Conceptualize
Dimensions
Pretty
Strange way like we think of it as a place
Hugo
Really if you look at
Essays like flat landed
It's about
If someone is a two-dimensional figure
Finger on the page they're not going to see
Your finger
So I think that
Sometimes we just
Glitch in and out of these
I think that sometimes
We go there
Mom where were you seeing and then submit
Sometime witch
Happens in
Yes the UFO experience but also Ferry Lenox
Experiences and also India
And also some cryptic
Muffins
Even some
Shamanic trap
Workout a body traveling things like that
Who sang that's all going into deadline
Yep
All of it that's his big revelation
And that's why the the secret for him is like that
Even cryptozoology kind of situations
Are actually this whole thing
He used to be I mean he used to be the guy with otherworldly smells man here's what I tell you what he'll smells like
Sulphur
What about
The ecology though
I don't feel like I've gotten any grasp on ecologically ideas
Well I mean
Essentially it is
Cure all these creatures
Do they use photosynthesis
Honestly he does get into some things like that where he'll be like when he was about the food
Totally said that this is what that he's like a clearly that means
That means that the fairies eat this so you know he's like that's totally what he does anybody make
Picking up any food I will quote
Literature metaphor
Is it 100% when he died
He's just throwing in
Can anything he's like all the Canterbury Tales
We see that horses that actually
Written into the place where we know that horses are psychic
So yeah I mean he wraps it up here and
And I mean I kind of
There are some things again like I hit stop
Process makes a certain amount of sense
If you if you follow it
He's just
Created a completely different world where it
It happen
Brightwell
The thought process is okay
But
Be looking at
Empirical evidence
Should lead you using that thought process
To conclude that this is all b*******
He just skip to the part with the evidence
Process I don't have a problem but it's the application
I think what it is
Is
For so long you know we've been living with people who don't live in reality
But in such a way as to exploit it for or to
Alter it in some way where is it feels like this guy was just like
Nope
Unreality
I'm going to do something else
Fairyland
That's what I'm doing
Cool
What happens when a culture
A global culture
Is Maps
More or less ever
Square inch of the
We find that there is
What happens to
I would argue
Transposed
To the Stars
All that baggage
We've always had
The psychopomps
Votive
The Transporter
The sun pulling the
Pulling the Chariot of the sun across the
The sky all that
It's transpose
Used to this
Very 20th
21st century
Moteefe
The UFO
Sure
This point is basically
We create things based upon our responses to culture and belief system
And they're essentially the same things going back and back and back we just update them as we update technology
Right
And the the idea that underlies the like
Okay so somewhere on Earth there is this
Underworld or whatever and around there is no underworld
So we put it into the Stars
And then eventually we're going to
Be able to go into the Stars where to find it
It's not there so they'll be another thing
It's because the underlying thought or whatever it is is what's more important than the idea of actually fine
Finding the underworld or whatever
So now if you were to take this and to just look at it from like okay
Now let's let's apply this to like human psychology
That seems like an appropriate neck
Spell wrecked
But I don't feel like that's what he's doing no
Okay
Cool I mean it is kind of fascinating insofar as he tries to he tries to reconcile that with this
It's idea of co-creation
Right and he acknowledges that all of this stuff is in our head
That's the that's the reality
But
There is also another world worth actually real
The fairies have a physical body double my friend right
And that is how things work exist in your head
Accepting that other world where the
We create them
Iamthebay exist
And that's how it work
Right so we
You know I don't know map it used to be there be monster
You know it's just what you're saying it's it's a hippogriff it's Turtles all the way down you know it
It's it's just always going to be another turtle
Yeah yeah
Isn't that
That's the the
The concept is that like a tulpa
No I don't think so
I believe that's the the name of like an idea of like something that you
You think of
And it becomes real
Delegate the manifestation of an imaginary thing that I've heard like
Used in some of these other like soda
Project Camelot interviews and stuff people with these sort of
Theosophist store
Paranormal ideas
Right I mean that's that's kind of what he's he's that's why people love him so much
It's because he's trying to make it so everything is real
Right away you believe it
But
The Voice where everybody's mixing things up is there forgetting that this is all about transitioning into the other world
Midnight about
Fighting or or belief systems or whatever it is
It's all created
Because you're afraid of you mean to tell me that it is okay if somebody who associated with The Tall Blond aliens
Getting out of the baseball game
We've all come to the right place to hold onto this
If you have others in the right around the corner for you buddy I guess it is
Respond to this
Tour de force of his argument
The summation of you apology
The whole thing I'm going to guess
You lived in Wisconsin
Then yeah
Folks for
I have major allergies
Jesus always
Everybody knows
These days
Anyway
I have remembered
The break
But that I
It's not a break
This is the end of the show
For the Freedom Riders
Oh oh
Bad remember the bridge
I have allergies I'm confused it's a break oh no it's the end of the show
That's the whole thing
That's not it that's that's kind of ending with a whimper
Yep well I mean I guess the show continued on it behind a paywall but that's just not happen
Yeah not happening to the real stuff man
I honestly almost there just cuz I wanted to see if you finished
The story of the other guy who's going to lunch
I'm going to guess not
I would love to use what I want you to do
I want you to keep listening
I want
I need you to find the story of the guy in the Jeep
Other person sketch
For legal reasons I think you need to put that stuff because otherwise we
Baby needs to be reported to the authorities
That is a good point I think we're sitting on a lot of need to be reported in this
Yes it is interesting I mean it's benign it seems like for the most part that's what I was going
Going for I wanted
Fun
Benign fun
No looking your eyes away from the Veil
Bulshit
Sure
It's just right there
It's all real but the lesson that we've learned
From doing the show for Dino 56 years is that that doesn't exist
That is still in here somewhere but not from the guy who plays the funk tuba
That's fair food that is always safe harbor
I mean come on
It takes a it takes a certain confidence to take up the TV
You know
It's not it's an instrument that most people gravitate towards
What's that one that the sousaphone is on the wraps around that's the that's the marching tuba
That's a lot that's a man who's wearing a lot of sousaphones in his day
And as a former marching band member
I salute you
I I did not I did not join the marching band like I said I play French horn for a little while
Then I quit
Cuz it sucked
Well then that's the end of the episode that I have for you as well thank you I would say this is Ben
A lot of fun
Appreciate you finding something benign to talk about
Next week
Will have an episode for you probably not in Dreamland
No certainly I think we may actually even like
Find out what the predictions for 2020 three kind of up in the air at this point
But until then we have
Droz.com we are on Twitter
Neither
Leo dzx Clark
Nora by Daryl rundas I'm not the juiciest Ice Cube
I am you know I'm just I'm just Jordan you are the psychopomp Incycle circumstance
And now here comes
Robot
Alexandra Thurston color