Jordan
Knowledge bike I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy or the bad guy
Knowledge
MoneyGram
Alex
College.com
Let's sit around and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
What's up
Is abs
Bright spots are a little bit trivial in nature summer just like an album we enjoy or
X trivia
Right and today I had a good ice cream flavors listen to Sirius 2f
Struggled with sleep
And such but it's been going a lot better over the past week
I've been
Managing to keep a better like sleep schedule and like I'm not
I don't want to get ahead of myself of course because these things happen sometimes getting
A good Rhythm and make it then it gets thrown off but
I mean sleep has been one of the things that had plagued me the most in terms of like
The path of my life
So I got to like laying in bed for hours not being able to fall asleep and and
And such an m
It's up it's been it's been great and this is this is partially
This is my bright spot and that's hardly a bit of a announcement
And that is what this episode never sleep again ever
Okay and the reason for that is I'm going to
Advance publishing schedule
I'm at for a really long time but when I tried to do it like
Years and years ago it didn't work right and so I'm going to set up this episode to post
At a decent hour
So I can in future schedule posts ahead of time
That might be why
I look forward to hopefully being able to keep this up
Because it's it feels so much better spot for me than it is for you that's been a cheap source of concern for me for
For God damn years now you know and it's I'm trapped in this helpless but I can't sleep for you Dad no but
Kamalame or something guitar over the head
Those were good days by the way
Brightspot
I know that we discuss this
I'm a little bit worried about Uncle howdy
Just an update on that okay okay oh worried about worried about Oklahoma
Anyway which is greater concern reporting that I am still worried
I want my bright spot is today it's that time of year today is the start of awesome games done
Quick the marathon that last for like that's always happening
We are so you know every 6 months like a solstice you kind of
Yesterday
Scary fun they're going to Mary's a lot of money for whatever causes
Play games
The founder is taking is done after this year right
And they started the whole thing where we can play the awesomest game quickest
It's also a competition
Now he started in his mom's basement 13 years ago
And 13 years later it's
40 million dollars plus
Intonation how cool is that that is really cool
I'm Amazed
Congrats
So Jordan today we've been up so to go over and listen to the situation that we find ourselves
We need to know the predictions for 2023
We need to know what is going on
Because
What what's going to happen on January 15th January 16th
Know what's coming
Paralyzed with fear of the future
I can't leave the house now Grand heading to the house to begin with R
You can change the facts of the same yes it's so I regret to inform you that Alex's doping out of Studio
He was gone all of the week
Saturday rolled around 11 maybe he'll come in and do a Saturday show
As of the time the recording this witch's on Sunday he has not
Sunday show is still
Broadcast from his his studio so we don't know if he's going to back on Sunday course
We're life in alert what time is
Where did Susan why we had to fill in and do an episode which is fantastic thank you for doing
People people really enjoyed it
And now
We're here again
And do what are we going to do
I don't know is it going to be better today no
We are not going to talk about Alec
Actually
Play another deposition to go over cuz this is a behind-the-scenes guy
Okay and we'll get down to business on this and explain what's going on but first
Let's say hello to some new ones so first Auntie races tubest
Tuba it's too how do you spell how do you say that
Yeah
2X
To be available to play psychopomp and Circumstance at your next graduation thank you so much right now if I was you want
Next I made my girlfriend listen to knowledge fight and now every argument is a false flag
Thank you so much
Thank you very much! Take as much as you want
Thank you very much
Next policy Joseph Watson thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
Alex the Space Ace thank you so much as you want
Very much
We got 23 technocrats
Merry Christmas to chance love
That's with an ass
Trance
Charles Schulz love
You are getting Noel
Oh you're not to take a crap
And Chris LeBlanc to purveyor of dark arts and listener of only the best buy gas tank
You're smart you're now technocrat
And I became a technocrat even though Dan like Scott and Jordan sang the English version of The Girl From Ipanema
Bossa Nova rules thank you so much you are now a technoc
Natalia Brody
Someone someone sodomites a bucket
I don't want
Jesus Christ so Jordan today we have a Depo
Position that is from the Connecticut case that that is where
We are at this this is a fella by the name of Tim fruge
Yeah I don't know if you know much about the other man
Dimensions of him in emails and suction he's got something to do with the marketing but the internet
Right he is like a stuffed with the online sales
And he's the business director basically large umbrella set of
Things that that is responsible for
Having grown from the position of just being like
In charge of some Warehouse stuff employee that Alex hired ever
He was a Michael j.fox it from The Mailroom to the top of the board he's he's been around pretty much
Forever as he tells in his backstory for this in this deposition
He was working at like a dry cleaner kind of business or his delivering
Things like trying to sign up new client with Service app and then from there transitioned into
Alex mailroom stuff as you put it
And then just things kept going as it grude more responsibilities adidon until he
He was the
Head of business you know I mean if it weren't for them being part of Infowars there's a certain
Charm to their ragtag hiring process that I I mean I don't know it's mostly
Contact space
That was the fastest I've ever had that
I need you in my warehouse project
I have long been interested into a shape because he's in that it's a name that rings out
Through like the entire time that I've
Done this podcast
He is someone that Alex references obliquely his name shows up places right as laikoro
Run it by Tim
I wouldn't put it that way I don't know who's the money man but he's
A lot of admin kind of
Various places pops up
And I realized
When I sat down to look at
Deposition that I ain't never seen Tim for Jaipur
Wow and he is a Charming
Looking forty-two-year-old
I don't want to know I'm not saying this in any kind of pejorative way but has a thick boy
Charles Hart
Call Coop.
He just he strikes you as
Like a cool guy that your dad knows or something
I'm looking at him right now and me and maybe it's not it's not a big beard though
30 years from now that's a Santa Claus but right now he's cool Santa you know I
I picture young Santa Claus with a giant beard but it's like
Not what
Regardless of and I should also say that I was routinely called young Santa Claus while I was in
He strikes you as
Like a pretty generally decent fella
Interesting and that is interesting because you're not used to that
No
LOL say I had a fairly positive impression of him
Through this and then by the end of this I think he's
Maybe one of the worst people who works at if I was going to say this is freaking me out no it's a it's a very
Path that it takes to get there but
Turn the right temperature
He sat for a deposition in January 2022 having previously said four like
A really brief one
And then he comes back
I'm doing this remotely
And we're going to start here at the first clip there's obviously the beginning quite a bit of
Look like
You know
Introduction what did you do to prepare for this
Questions you know like the answer yes or no just so we can calibrate the device getting them will get into the Rhythm questions
What have you
We get to jumping in here while they're discussing the. Of Infowars growth they were seeing
Quite a bit of growth
And in the context of that we learned Tim's salary okay
And you were right you were aware
No
I would not I was never involved in the sales at that point
That would happen
In the 2000s
11 2012
Somewhere in that time frame yes as we grew there was just need for people to step up
And
I was there and I was willing to learn and
And step up and help where I was needed
Around that time was to oversee
Online store
Correct as well as you know ordering office supplies and handling
You know
Your
Your AC guy is your plumbing guys your construction guys that was sort of my
What I was doing at that time
Salary menu
Best I can remember it was either 45 or 50,000
Annually
Was it when you
Or when you when you separated
It was $200,000 a
Goddamn
200,000 a year
So we have the on-air personalities that we've seen like Owen Troyer he makes
About Daria makes about 100,000 a year
And yeah it's a a 200,000
Hey you know you started fifty Grand you have more responsibilities that are added on I kind of like it
Normal
Assertive trajectory and Pat it's just it's got its got quite High
I don't know capitalism
Anymore
You know like
Hermione for my decade in in because I was kind of in sales you know so I never got raise
Is there anything it was either I did good or bad there's not Mission yeah yeah there's that whole thing
You like that is that is absolutely not how describes his
The conversation he went to work every day and at the end of the year he either got a promotion or did he did that corporate thing that people have
Talked about in my world that I've never experienced his responsibilities deepveer into sale
Advertise
Strange
A lot is that a little Tomatoes like a lot
But I don't know if
Still that is real that is also
And then if you look at it just on the scale of like what we know of other Infowars people what they're making
Beasley
You pay people want like
You think they deserve
Abby died I would think that that's
Kind of how
Payroll generally Works according to this
Obviously tempers his role is more important than Alex's
Second banana on-air personality
He's more important than knowing you can replace Owen but you got to keep the money flowing like it or not you know the only problem I guess
Yes I have is I'm not sure exactly what's meant by money man
You know like I feel like money man is a guy who injects money is something like ten million dollar man
You know more about the guy who's who's in control who's who's at the at the like
Loggerhead of the flow of money right right right there and all the money flow comes towards him
And then he kind of
Directed elsewhere I do think that's probably fairly idea
A lot to not that great
You can replace it with another contest
Borrow this fella
He's grown with the company to heat
I really
Man I'm conflicted about this guy anyway
He left
Infowars
In September 2020
And then I was gone for about a year Jordan came back
And he came back you came back well I mean 200k you can't really earn quite as much everywhere
He might've been doing fine we'll find out where you landed
His return makes some sense to me actually
Albie's you could look at it suspicious laying like are in the middle of this litigation and get this guy back in the fold or whatever
Keith as he describes it him and his wife are both from Texas and they'd moved to Utah for another job
And they visited Texas and they saw their family and they realized
Miss my family I want to come back
Alex offered him his job back
And you know he came back that doesn't feel suspicious to me at all
But it is
Weird
Loyalty that I wouldn't expect from any company I've ever worked at
You know
I live for a year they probably be like sorry you shouldn't have f****** left a****** you know that's true
You got to consider how things ended
In this next clip
Circumstances
I
Was stressed to the max
I have some health conditions
And the stress was getting to me and everything kind of came to
I had when me and Alex got into an argument and
I grabbed my bag told him to
Go off and walked out
That was the end of it
I'm being Alex Jones I'm he was just complaining about everything I was trying to help
He was complaining about something else
I don't remember too much of the details but it was
It was Alex
Being Alex as far as
I can't say the word cuz I don't want to swear but
He he was just being a jerk
So Alex is being an a****** from
And watching this that maybe Tim doesn't like Alex that much
I mean you know if that's that's the problem with your foreshadowing on him being the worst purse
Maybe potential is up there you know that kind of a very interesting
My first
Hackles are being raised
This seems like a person who is capable of agency and thought
And that makes him terrifying because that that's a big part of it
You go be the worst person you know like panties a bit of a straight shooter
You know what the f****** a****** that's why I quit
Did you quit being Alex
Because this is
Starts to give you a good impression of him because you're like yeah
That makes total sense
Do you put up with it for a long time you probably making way more money than you would have been
In some other career makes sense finally had enough of this a******
Sure I mean the problem though is
The Moore agency you have
The more responsibility you have for your action
You know that's that's the way it's always kind of the math is worked out in my head I think Alex is a piece of s*** but I also don't
Think Alex really can control his behavior at
You know like
That that sucks but use the slave of many decisions that he made years and years ago
Prayers that he has put upon himself but you still has completely disagree with you on that
Nuances that are pushing him in in various directions
Tim has more awareness and more
Sort of clarity of decision-making than a lot of the other people that we've seen deposed or
Sphere
And
He doesn't seem as desperate either at that as now somebody's other
Dorks right
So yeah he quit because Alex treated him poorly
It turns out
Acquit
In that stress
Had to do with
Your responsibilities for the way in which
The way
All the issues that at that place there are
Forest fires everyday
And
At that moment the reason I walked out it was the
Alex Jones was treating me
So that's interesting and like
You seems like if there's forest fires everyday then a high-pressure work environment
Something that's going to be like why you quit things work around here
Just Alex being a dick
Which but that's another thing about the choices there is that
If he is saying that that is happening and that's why he quit
And also saying there's forest fires every day
What that means is that he's watched
Alex be an a****** to countless people and watch them run out
And this is when Alex started being a real piece of s*** to him first
You know what I mean
Yeah that could be
I have some slight theories that are may be impossible to prove
But very Reason by this next clip
That's correct
Yes
Ready Alliance Group
What's that
And is actually a dry cleaner
The
Storable food company that
No
No slide out
The storable food that he saw
Yes
Work
Cracked
So there's a part of this that is
You know
Kind of understandable you're the guys working in these business relationship sure you would know these people and you could go ahead
You know you got a place totally that makes some sense
But then you also have to consider that this is September 2020
This is during the sort of
Middle beginning of the covid time this is when Alex is pushing the server
Storable food where they are needing to expand
They are setting up a new warehouses they are a company that is in severe growth
I would not be too surprised
If there was an understanding
Or something where it's like you go
Go work for them for a bit or something I can't prove that just a total Theory
But Alex maintained a
Very very close relationship with the storable food people
That continued
Through this time there was
I remember when it was there was like a time that he went to Utah himself
For the storable food visiting that
It seems like this is all the way too closely connected for it to just be like
I quit Infowars and that I got a job at the their mate one of their main sponsors
About that tho
Is that
To me that makes a lot of sense just from
It's like no no
Malicious behavior kind of situation just because
If you're making 200k a year and you want to leave that job
There aren't many jobs where you could step in
Do a similar kind of salary point
Without having an intense personal relationship with the people already there it's true so you know maybe if
He's not going to go
At McDonald's or some s*** you know he gets over there maybe doesn't make as much money
But he's got a position over there he's not starting over
There's a benign explanation for
And I understand that
I think that there's a very decent chance that that is what is it play
I also have some misgivings about
How Alex would take that
Totally
If he leaves on bad terms
With Infowars out early
I find it kind of hard to believe that Alex would be okay with him
Taking a roll veterans somewhere in the ballpark of $200,000 right he's one of his main sponsors
I find that difficult
It is possible I don't know it's just weird with with people
Such as this
Who have established a track record of malicious behavior
Do not require it or even ask
This is definitely a situation where
Is possible to read too much into this
It's just weird
I bet ordering dinner there's something Shady going on with these assholes you know you can't tell you don't even know why
Yep yep
Type of people drink half a drink
And then send it back and say that's not what I order
Alex made his kid a rope swing under a tree branch Shady
Right there
Discuss the revenue stream back in the day
It was another supplement to my Clare
So you had things like
Advertising gold sales the cut Kickbacks of all the the filters the whole thing
You had a lot of that but then there was another thing
Correct
What I believe yes at that time he was still selling advertising
.
Between
So there were times where no there were no
Advertising sponsors
Anyting
At certain time. I couldn't tell you which ones were out that that time frame
There was no sponsors for advertisers
Mr. Jones would have
In addition to advertising
And wanted to highlight their own products
This is the first time that there has been
Concrete
Recognition of pay-to-play we've been talking about that for years it's been suggested by
Remember folks it's
Something that's been discussed on message board and people have theorized about it
Anonymous comments but yeah this is
This is the first time that I can see if there is like
Actually definitive this is something that I Alex offered
You can pay
To get him to promote your stuff
And pretend that it is
Just a regular interview
We're going to get more into this later in the deposition so put a pin in that but that was a really big moment
Now in terms of my understanding the house operate
There's so many times where it's like there's no way that this is not pay to play
But to have them concretely say it
That's comfort
Yeah you'll be surprised to learn what the rates were not high enough or too high is the question
We'll get to it okay
The product that
They ended up selling liquor supplements or what have you
Alex likes to pretend they have like Infowars lab
And you like a developing all these product
Because it gives like more intimate a connection with
The product itself
It feels like it's it's something it's more directly to know yeah but unfortunately that's all
Mr. Jones
That he intended to sell online
Crap crap
Mr. Jones
I guess so I'm not sure I know I was not involved
That possibly yes
Aware of
Systems ever
Investing any money in
Research and development
I'm not aware of
Why would they
Your understanding
That
Suppliers
And then
Rams down
Alex Jones
That's my understanding
Yes obviously that's what they did they just put a different label
On everything that we sell it but also why not sometimes we just you are indeed though
Company take cheap s***
Speak to it and pretend that it's magical in some way and then put another
Fun label on it totally market up the markup is Alex holding a picture of it that's it that's the whole thing
Something like
Chaga mushroom
Salaciously
Adding Force to all of it that's all you need or super Blanc
Super Blanc
Things that Alex likes to pretend he's that he's not that connected to like
How how is show is moving products
You know it's just all these is on there
And obviously he's got to be concerned that some of the business side of things
But he is not like
Doing things in order to like
Kush
Na na na
As
Online
Store
More and more
Simply managing
Aspen
But mr. Jones was also involved
In
Operation on a daily basis
Prince
Volume
Every day after
Program
Yes
Because mr. Jones
Wood
Is products
Increase volume
Yes
Nutcracker
Wow Shady cynical
Alex gets out there starts screaming about God and all this stuff and then gets
Excuse me Pharisees let's change somebody in the church real quick come on now it is
Oblique portrait
Free day
Evan sucks
What if we had a TV show or something like that
That would be the part that sucks the most
Is like having to give a s*** about what the sales were on your thing like
All I've ever wanted to do is do the show part it seems like that is part that I
Enjoy so maybe
What are the things that you get looking at this too is that
Kind of a bummer to recognize that Infowars is like a business business
Yeah you know the various that Mystique that Alex
Has about himself or adjective
Tomorrow's Buddy Guy everyday
Big located by Ed's work today
That sucks dude I scare the people enough to buy myself
Songs
I'm so glad we hooked Elsa
David Jones Alex's dad and his deposition mentioned how whenever they see big spikes in traffic they tried
To replicate
As you would I am so this is brought up
Then receive 10 minutes
In on this
Disorder game
I'll represent to you that Mr Jones testify
Testified in substance that
AJ what time
When
There was
Try to determine what my
No I don't recall I never
Redder
Watch David Jones is staying but
That makes sense in business it
Something is working to keep doing that
Yeah man
Something
Mr. Jones endeavor
Objection
I don't know what he's
Thinking but
You know like I said I would provide him the information
What he does on his show is his thing I never
Talk to him about what he plays on the show
Her anything
But if he requested the information I would give it to him and he did what he
What he does
Personally
Maximizing the store
I mean
To what I could do on my side yes
Window wizard
In
In Revenue
Trying to
Objection no I never
If there was a spike in sales
During his show
I would tell him whatever you did worked because the cells increase I never
I never looked at a show
I mean I can't I can't listen to his truck too much for me
It's very distracting while I was working I never
I have no idea what he was doing on a show
But you would think him
Alex's show is too much for him that is some psychopath s*** right there really is that is some really terrifying
Crying like oh yeah no I get that he Slaughters young boys but
Don't it just cuz I said I don't watch it just cuz I work there doesn't mean that I care all I'm concerned with
Selling ads for the slaughter
Water than join the thought right
My heart that had on and then I go home after work is over
Obviously not necessarily as Extreme as Slaughter but I like
It is a real or enough thing
That to me is bleak
There is a
Real cynical approach to ethics that's the type of s*** that I got from the second clip of it's like this
This dude
Knows what he's doing in his choosing like f*** it
Auto Care
Consider
He's been around for a decade ever brought on
And he was there for a decade
Wow Alex
Just did all this s*** that's like I don't fucken want to watch this nonsense every day I choose to go to work
Alex is out there helping storm the capitol
Can I go to work
Alex is in the Capitol building that's interesting soul.
Spike in sales while Alex is in the f****** Capitol building
Court is saying the same to Hook families are exaggerating
F****** insane and a little bit later to
What's crazy about it to me is like
They they really do
Evaluate Alex's show like any AD campaign would be evaluated you know like so if we hired
Jon Hamm for this car commercial does Jon Hamm sell more cars than if we hired Sam Jacks
So you know like that kind of thinking only it's Alex's entire show
The show itself is the ad
For the ship
You know and I mean like as this goes on they could talk about being able to have like hour-by-hour breakdown
Sounds of like way more traffic going to the store
There's so much more awareness of like what they're doing from a business standpoint
Then you'd ever get from
Any interviewer deposition with Alex or corporate representative
Use Google Analytics
You know it's stupid honesty speak into that is like
I mean it's
This is a tentacle it's
I'd say that
II
I am
Remit I I won't say that like he's worse than people who do s***
Who do bad black lives matter flag on fire
You know
There's blame to go both ways
But this is someone who knows better oh yeah and he's not a True Believer yeah and that to me is
Carrier a little bit
Absolutely I mean
It's it seems extreme to be like oh this person watches
The kids Slaughter
But we're talking about somebody who lost a lawsuit for 1.5 billion f****** dollars
Truly awful behavior and he was like amen
I just got to work you know
I was like I was there selling ads the entire time Alex was defaming these family
Total now that you've lost 1.5 billion dollars I still work for him and I don't really care that much
Willing to say in a deposition I don't listen to his showed stupid
Not going to go well
Will get more into this later the deposition
Tim knows that the stuff Alex is saying is b*******
He knows he knows that like
I can't watch a show the ads that are being sold
Based on tricking people with b******* with stuff that he knows
That sucks
Hideaway
Tim would tell Alex about the traffic that came to the website and Alex decides
What to do about it
I would tell him if
They're letting you know it's it like
The more people that are in Town Square the more people that are going into the shops
So just by default the more people going to the news website
I mean you're going to pick up
Traffic coming over to the store because we had banner ads running
Now
Audience members infowars.com
Right
Yes
He wanted to talk about
Correct
As you
Email before you
Listen to you dated March 11th 2016
Yes
And
Chris Ellison was the e-commerce manager for a certain. Of time
Yes he reported to me
And
Email
Infowars.com
It was just
And Chris is doing boy there
Know Chris was gone Chris has gone for quite a while now
He is sending you an email
Oh that's not
Yes
Hellboy
We saw the largest traffic Spike ever
On March 11th 2016
Yes
Yesterday we capped out at
So we got a giant spiky
The biggest Spike that has ever been recorded according to this email
And we already also have an understanding that
You know Tim would report these things
To Alex you should be aware of this and seems to not really beat the I don't know
Your email about that stuff
So we can little bit more into the email here
Largest spider ever
Yes
Activity
Yes or no
So if there was a big news day if there was a big story
For whatever that CNN Fox drudge everybody was covering
It would
Send more traffic to imports.com which in turn would send more craft Imports store
Mr. Jones
Play result in additional traffic
Common site
Yes I mean
Scrap
Tim tries to play some little what if games
Sometimes it's just
It's bad traffic not getting increased sales and stuff
The maybe it's DDOS attack maybe who knows
Traffic
So here is where he tries to pull something that okay
Largest traffic Spike ever
Well if not yes then took cool thing I would
Tell him hey largest bike ever
I don't remember this but if I'm looking at this and I'm putting myself back in 2016
He's telling me that there was a large
Largest spider ever
That didn't contribute to sales
And if you scroll down and look at that map
Screenshot he sent
That would tell me that we were being attacked on the store
Because it happened all the time
Where
Whatever players whoever players would send Bots and
All kinds of stuff to try and Spike the traffic up
On the stored over on the server to bring the store down
That happens all the time so
If I am looking at this today and putting myself in my shoes from 2016
I would say that's the point that is means
Is trying to be made is
Hey something weird happened this could be an attack
Yeah that would think Matthew I would say we got a ton of traffic
Okay
I guess I guess that's what it was but I guess and it drove Bunch traffic
Crispy Gold Spike person not see that in the news
Email is
I mean here's the thing that I feel like
Tim does not
Alright
Is if you're going to try and avoid the question in the positive of like
I know what he covered
And therefore we adjusted things according
Right
That is essentially a true false
Right if you also say we know when it's
False
That means you know when it
It's true so if you say
Well we figured out when it wasn't a DDOS attack
Means you know when it was something else and conceivably you're like
Maybe you don't remember this cuz it was years in the past moment you were digging into this
Trying to understand the traffic explaining it away is a DDOS attack
It reveals
You know investigation exactly
Yes and that that is that isn't heavily implied there
But yeah it wasn't
Now that was just
In 2016
How much do you think Infowars was making per week
Ringing in
Oh my
God I don't want an so I mean I did hear the one number they tossed out was like almost half a billion.
Dollars one year
Right so you got to figure that puts yet
What 100,000 a week
Well here's where we were
You have
Army
Oh s*** wasn't no a million presidential things
Because
You believe that the existence of the presidential race
Contributed to an increase in your weekly Revenue
Well I mean everyone was it's the presidential cycle I would assume
That's what it is I couldn't tell you definitively but
That's what makes sense to me
Infowars
Store.com
Wewe average revenue
I don't recall a company show me but
I don't remember
Wait for it wait for it
There's a cameo coming
Free Speech system dearly days
Pump-action
Ballpark is Bean
Corporate representative
Absolutely
Oh my God
Humane one of you
Hide for the court reporter please note that
Addis
While I'm gone
Yeah yeah yeah yeah just logged on his only appearance at all in this deposition
Is as somebody who's accidentally streaming to
I love it I need to bring up that Norma lost his ability to correct
Does law for 6 months
Yeah yeah I mean it's tough it's tough to him to call his bottom feeders if you're stealing our B man that's
That's kind of harsh tweeted something about a gravy job that's pretty
Norbit it's funny because
The number of people he is fooling is precisely zero
0 people were like oh see he's got a cool enough sense of humor that he could expand and
You were trying buddy you're trying to deflect
Yeah but
I love this
Kind of
Fame with Norm where he's like
Just the guy who fumbles onto the scene
Showing up at the deposition like this was just it was it was delightful
Also you can see forshee laughing
Tim doesn't take dorm seriously hyperchicken lawyer from Futurama
Every there is the point where it in Futurama there's the point where the chicken lawyer
Is talking to to fry and then
The reveal is the lawyer himself was in prison the entire time I was like that's
Prison giving you legal advice
And also like a can you help me get out of here I didn't pose Bale presumably
Decide to double dip watch it Tuesday
Irene the funniest part do the funniest part what elevates it is
Is B the audio is
Somebody saying that the corporate representative should be prepared I believe it's the judge in the Texas
Corporate representative should be prepared is absolutely the best at end of course that's what should be
See you there man beautiful
It's and there's also a native comedy that he seems to not be able to
Mutant right away can't figure it out
Something was going on before that
After the million in sales a week right which Tim is trying to attribute to the
Dunno the election year
One of the things that's fascinating is all of these people at Infowars
There's every single one of them to a person
Engages in improvisational explanation
They're presented with a set of facts and they're like here's why
Balls out every single one of these people I don't understand what I wrote down is like
You can you should be able to hear at this point like
Oh this is a question
You know the answer to
And you are asking it to me I would like you to just tell me the answer and then I'll agree with what you say
Is Drew if I'm allowed to talk
I'm going to make up some b******* that's just who I am
Tim is a little bit more of a serious person at Ryan's but he still has that to that trait that to Habit
It's very weird enough time at the year for his office you're going to make up reasons for any
So we talked about this at the beginning of the notion of Alex doing pay-for-play
Play kind of stuff
Answer this comes back up
So advertise sorry can you
Repeat the question sorry
Two, who wanted to come on this
That is not
So black-and-white
So he would charge advertisers
To mention their products and stuff on the air
Ray can't remember him
Charging a guest to come on the air
Just beautiful
Just
When when there's live me show you this never it never
Never stops
It's just there
Yeah that was information that Tim is volunteering that is going to be contradicted by the next week
Need to say
Say I have never been aware of Alex
I asked you for money to have people appear on the Shelf
Mount saying that you charges to mention a product
So that is is one thing
It's another so black-and-white to call it in that it's fine to take ads
It's fine to do that
It's fine to have you know brokered content that's kind of revealed as such sure it is not ethical
To have people come on
Who are paying
To have an interview with you as if it's a normal interview that is promoting their product that
Is kind of messed up
And
Here's an email of Tim trying to sell exactly
An email from you to
July 29th 2014
That you are informing Mr eduire
Acosta
Desperate
Someone with Bonner and partners
Alright
Further
It is email
He said next week
Meaning
They talked about
Yes
Between 15 and $20,000 tip
He usually charges I mean that's
If I am putting myself back in 2014 Alex asked me to write to him
To basically let him know the value of him coming onto the show
Good good good good save SolidWorks time
This is just trying to make sure he
That was one of the ghetto I almost
It's normally charges 15 to $20,000 for this because he likes he's going to do this as a freebie
Yeah everything I do better. I think it's just trying to make this guy appreciate
Feel special
That is just as psycho is Daria being like well don't they feel nice about hearing that their kids might still be a
Instapsycho crazy got to push back
I think that Daria is way more
Much more hurtful when I said it out loud I realized that I had gone farther than I text
Disconnected from like what
Normal people would species going on
Introduces like a
Really
F*****-up kind of
Thing into Alex's world because
If you know that this is something that he does then you can't really be sure that any of the interviews that he does
How much of it is stuff that he actually believes in how much of it is stuff that he would promote
Just his own accord and how much of it is he getting paid 20 grand
To just have a little conversation with this person it's free money on the table and who's getting suckered you
The Listener it goes It goes from being like a Rush Limbaugh clone show to being more like
An infomercial
2 a.m. trying to sell your knives except for
The people selling you knives are like
Well one
If you don't get this knife everyone you know is going to die
And to this person selling knives as maybe the greatest knife salesman that ever existed there their best nights you know
Knife infomercials are fun
Cotton books
I really think that this is something
That is
H-E-B a big problem
For Alex's listeners even if they are people who are like staunch believer in this stuff
Because introducing
This kind of doubt into the things that you are seeing on his show
It should really make you question
Stop you even if only twice in the course of his career people actually paid him $20,000
It's still
Is
It tarnishes
I'm pretty much every interview we can never be sure that it is above board and pure your currency in
In a cult is
Infallible truck
But you know like
We will do anything that this person says because we completely trust them
And this should be
A tiny doubt should be the end for you you know you can't be an occult if you're not one hundred percent it
Yeah there should be an erosion of trust the gas when this
I probably won't swing there
Which was admirable
And it comes up with another swing
Ian
You are
And advertising proposal to which Free Speech systems will receive $46,550
Or
Different ad placements related
Alex Winter
Wow
Where we going here buddy call me the number that Alex gave me
But that's a typical sales pitch of hey I'm we're going to give you a value
This
To come on the show if you do this
That's the way I'm reading it I honestly don't remember this cuz it was so long ago I'm just trying to and don't ask me how my first
But yeah I mean obviously wrote it there and usually charges
15/20 it's giving an incentive for him to buy the ad package for 49,000
You're basically saying
Ask you to purchase ads
Website
That's what it reads yes
Turn up Selma Wild
Okay I get what you're saying I get what you say
It's not like the warranty package is what drives us man with give you a free warranty that's a sweeten the pie
What you know is really about giving you a valium
Ironically
Bill Bonner is somebody who like
Alex
Should have on
They shouldn't need to extort him
He's like a guy who wrote for the loo Rockwell is a Libertarian type conservative
Finance
For a book
If you can afford a budget of 60 K and advertising that book is
Probably going to do that book better be doing well by the 46 that you don't have to pay the 15
That's fine if you got 50 cases to sell on your book 46 it's a big difference I hope you make it back
I hope you do
It's
I don't believe this either though.
Closer than his first explanation I think to be unbelievable
That they open with a 15 to 20
And then somebody goes like
That's the most money we've ever accepted before we'll take it
I think
That he probably has a situation where he charges this
For people to come on
But also uses like an offer to try and
Cell if possible so I think I think that these are both
Probably true there's like a pay-to-play thing at that also it is used to induce people into these laws
Larger packages
Of even so it is still
Like the same issue remains
All of it but it's and that's almost even more
Damning again because that's
That's business
You know that's people who have a business plan
Who acts
In terms of
What we do to maximize profit which is exactly the opposite of the way Alex likes to present himself
Which is the proper
You betcha
So Alex has taken this money conceivably anytime he's promoted something
He's never told the audience adina's
Are you aware of Dallas ever telling his audience
He had on
No
Content
13 repeat
Not that I recall
Well
Why would you
This is something that come up over and over and over again like in these depositions in my head I'm always like
His next question is going to be like
You realize that's bad right
That doesn't happen
Okay you just said the things that you said you realize those are bad
Place to scold
Utility
That's shady as hell
No children would be disappointed
Did you write you understand this
I think that there are you know with one of the things that strange but Alex's show is that there are instances
Sentence of times where you can
Kind of tell that something is brokered programming gas but the line is gray a lot of the time
And that
Even for me somebody who's watching with a critical eye and looking
Looking into the
Stuff like
Sometimes it is
Difficult to tell
Introduction of this
Into the possibility the range of possibilities yeah
It makes me think whenever it's gray it's probably pay
That's not good I mean it's h22a weird level
It's it's like
He's almost scamming scammers with this scam
Scamming the scammer
Getting them
And then scamming his audience like you
You taking it from the top and the bottom Willie it certainly tends to make sense of why there are certain people
Who show up for a little while and then aren't figures they purchased a package
MLB package is good for 3 months totally was a big figure
While and then
I haven't I don't know where he is and then they found out that the advertising budget was too much for that
Mike cernovich was on quite a bit pretty regularly and then was gone for a while
I don't know if that's
Don't necessarily what's going on but I wouldn't be too surprised
I mean
True true
So speaking of things that are expensive
Buying Alex's product
Not expensive Alex buying it
Yes
So did the product line that Alex launched called amerex Essentials comes up and
This is like the deodorant and body wash and threaten to turn for men
He's trying to turn this into a like a you're going to buy this stuff anyway buy it for me as well kind of
It didn't work
They made a lot of money initially
And then people just we're not interested
In this next clip we learn a little bit about the mark-up
On Emirates Essentials
Revenue for 96
Yes
In
Was
104.
A cell yes
4A
Profit in that two week period of 359
Elementary menus
Pearson
400%
On that particular line
Injection
I mean
The number there it appears that
I'm not sure about 40% I can't do that math
But that
Tropic appears there it looks right
That's pretty damn good.
Very good Alex does like a 60% also still like marked up
At least like 150 percent
Man
That's good
If you can get it
Boy yeah I mean the markup on hearing aids for the longest time was
Anywhere between two-and-a-half to three and a half
You know and that made sense for a lot of businesses cuz they're all
Mortars you know like
It's all over head and shittin you got to do the whole thing
That's that's what the business
This had to do to survive
You know it was the it was the companies making the cartel level money
But I also would
Guess that in this instance
Some
Higher markup makes sense because the purchases are lesser other scare sir
Time purchase or like
Maybe once every few years or whatever
So I feel like a markup on that in order for these businesses to even be able to do survive that makes
Where is the Kia auto ship in Lake routine purchases
Black level of a markup for something that you're going to be buying
More and more and more like regularly
That's
Let me try and put it to you this way
That markup was there because the total
Profit on each one of those was like
10%
You know like of the total amount anybody spent
You get a little bit as your profit
Not
400 f****** percent
Yeah the actual sale that's
That price gouging
Yeah yeah
Thievery feels very out of sync with the way that Alex describes
Bible taking a loss on this
It's on 400% profit I'm only getting 300
Cool
So Tim was involved in ad sales
For a little while
Yeah and
You know for a bit he hated it though
They imagine that is not especially it Infowars probably not the most pleasurable
Because you end up like
Selling
Ads for
Unscrupulous businesses
Remember that
Email
We were discussing
Earlier
Where
Barbie
Email from Yahoo
If you go
To the
Is emailing
The website
Yes
Was
The Proposal that you offered him would be to
The pier so
So I looked into it a tiny bit and self lender itself doesn't seem like it's one of the most Shady biz
Genesis in the world like
They think that there are
Instances where this can be
Something like Sloan-Kettering something that is helpful for people to build credit but it also is not
Necessarily
Always the best thing to do not necessarily always safe for folks
It's not
It and said something that I feel like Alex
Audience
It doesn't seem like a
I think to offer any any Finance thing
If they give you a good offer
Alright
That means that you have to adhere to every say it like there's their offers are deviled like
Like you follows a riddle a perfectly and it works out you f****** one time
There you're there
Oh I'm sorry the fee is $7000000 and also you work for us now
Good deal then it's a great deal for them
They're not doing this out of a desire to get you out of debt or get you out of bad credit that's not what
Like the whole world has good credit at the end of their business
Cashing places don't want to cash checks for people they don't love cashing check
So I mean
This is something that I find to be a little bit
As an advertising gambling would be worse right
It's A Step Above today we have Timmy the bookie over here and he's going to advertise on bedding
A lot of money on a losing team
So he can break your kneecaps later in terms of things that Alex has promoted though like maybe it's not
The words that mean yes I have been ads on his chauffeur called
One of the Vibes that you get
Is the Tim does not
Care
He is not interested in the infowar
And maybe doesn't even actually like Alex at my
Describing on the show
What was Publix on nipple wards.com website
Conversations with mr.
No
No I didn't talk to Alex about
Newser his show
That wasn't
I didn't care about that
My bad that wasn't
My job
Nano
You had no idea what he's talking about on show
Bike ride
I mean some days if yes maybe but most days
I made it a point not to listen to a show
Because it was too distracting
The website did you read the website
I don't know about everyday but most
He seems like a guy who wandered in one day and just stuck around
No you're outside
Alex is on his show yelling about how he's in a war against the f****** devil
And stoking hatred against marginalized and vulnerable populations yet constantly
Today
F*** you with your I don't watch his just sometimes and sometimes it look at it
What a gesture weasel
Oh my God so this is kind of funny okay
Maddie asks why he doesn't watch Alex's show
So distracting
I really have to answer that question
Alex's voice can get me
And I don't officially agree with a lot of what he says
Yeah
I don't want to hear his show his voice is annoying and I don't agree with the stuff he says
Oh my God
That is f*****
Baddie dark.
The dark
That's some real worm s*** well the paycheck was good
That's no I know and that's why I have this feeling that like I think he's maybe
He knows better
Oh yeah the other people are True Believers and where they don't know any better
Money money drives people crazy
Yeah wanting money is nut
You know like
But it's I have no sympathy
I'm just marking on the phenomena that money can itself be is a form of wage slavery you know like
He can't not be in that
Money-making range
You know it's so Central to his identity
I don't know about that maybe it is maybe it's not I don't know much about him outside of the things that I've gleaned from
Hearing about him over the course of the time doing the show
And this deposition but like
I have to assume
That if you don't like the sound of this person's voice
You seem to not like him that much as a person
You don't like his show you think the things that he covers you disagree with
If you've been there for a decade it's money
There's no other way there you're making more money than you would elsewhere so you make
You make peace with the fact that you're
Basically your position is facilitating somebody to be a demagogue screaming
You don't agree with it
Unfortunate that this is the word that needs to be used here but he is a f****** Renfield
The irony Bono
So the question comes up about whether or not Tim had any feelings about Sandy Hook
Being fake
CJ's sending you
With the
Daily Show logs for Friday March 14
Current
And you'll see that
Wolfgang halbig
Join Dallas
Examine the host of peculiarities
Yes
Personally
Never had any dou
People
Never doubt my mind
In
You never suspected that
United States government
Was somehow involved in
Staging for spanking that event
That's
Never had a doubt
And also was fine
Taking money and working for a guy who is demonizing the parents of those murdered children that I was
Very aware and convinced and certain actually were murder
This is the type of f****** like
This is the interviews in a crime documentary about the mafia where they black out that you can't see it
His face and he's just like
Yeah we murdered people left and right you know you know you told you get told the murderer Caillou go murder him and then you go home to your wife
I know you like that
That's not okay ma'am you're told to run the online store for a guy was Albion real
Piece of s*** Master you do it
Well well I mean I didn't I didn't like murdering that guy it's not my idea you know but I was told to do it I didn't like her
Harassing those families for you know decades but
You know you can you do what you told you just look the other way
Look the other way man has
Not been able to do that
No that's why we're unsuccessful
Well I mean yeah we're not successful on that level correct
It's the word I meant
Dark to me
The notion of being intimately involved in this company to the point where you're the business director and you've
Been there you're the seventh person Alex's higher probably
Maybe one or two of those people are still around
At this point 2014 or whatever
And yours like
Hey
This sucks that shooting did happen Alex is saying all this crazy nonsense
Oh well
I don't care
But how can it not be a big problem for you
That's the thing you know I can understand everybody else because I understand believers
At least you know I get belief yes I understand that if you truly believe
Then it is not an ethical problem for you to be a part of this system because you do not believe it is unethical
But for this
This
Don't understand I don't understand just being like Oh yeah I know what I'm doing is wrong
But
$200,000 well here's the disconnect
He probably doesn't think they're what he's doing is wrong
I believe that he is a morally neutral piece within an immoral system or something like what
Alex's doing is wrong
What I'm doing
This is money man
And that
Fox Berkshire
We didn't care for what I was doing on there that's for sure
Contact with
Overtime mr. Jones
Featuring
Premonition
No I don't recall that I know that
I
Personally thought it was
Not
Right
For him to do it
But
No again I never listen to show
I don't really care
What he did on the
I didn't know I wasn't aware I didn't care but also I thought what he was doing was bad it was wrong of him to do that
Where
Really weird strange
Yep
Hitler's housekeeper band like what
Blissey
I don't know what he was doing out that a lot of dust
Hideous
That's all I know about
If you do the other things it kind of
Drum stands out is that like there were people who had a problem with this
And there is
Demonstrable evidence that they said something about
People I call Joseph Watson Rob Jacobson
There's both of them there confirmable
Instances of them having a problem with his coverage
And speaking up
Yep
Temperature today is somebody who is
Claiming videos
I didn't believe this stuff but
He didn't care
Nope he didn't care did not give a s***
Yeah
That is some that
I'm real f*****-up s*** right there man
Answer he's asked why he had a problem with what Alex was doing
And he struggles to answer that
I don't find this compelling
General weirdness
This program
Injection
I don't know
About all the details but I know he was talking about it
You understand why we're here
I mean
What did you consider
Well I mean I just said something you don't
Don't talk about
Stop.
That's what you got
It's just
No
It's not something
Because there's nothing wrong
National
I don't know what he
Bills or thinks but me personally you know it was
A tragedy
And it's not something
That you cover it the day when it's in the main news and then you go on
That's what I personally would have done
And you know I just
Talk about it
Warriors
Denied it.
Generally I don't recall specifically but most likely and yes
Okay
I find her to be a another improvised excuse type answers
You can't even
Articulate why the thing is a problem for you
Which leads me to believe that he doesn't care
Yeah it's not really that you don't actually really have a problem
You know you're supposed to
Unlikely
I would have done it that way
But you know
People do things
That's your response
You're in
There should be things
That you go
This cannot be
The irreconcilable between you and I and I am a I am a fundamental part of this operation
This workplace
This show
Existing
I am critical to it happening
And I don't give a s***
About the effect
Fact that it has
That's that's
Even even under like the most
Use of responsibilities
It is due to your actions personally that these people work hard
I'm such a blase attitude about it is just banana very bizarre
Reply Quiet Riot Eva problem
It's just not done not how you do things please please
That first you must send a
All right and then another letter of introduction through your second
It's not how it's done in polite Society being whatever you've been watching about extreme and I think that Maddie was trying to hit on something
Thing they are that would have been
Another question that Tim wouldn't answer put
This must
Have to do with how Alex was covering it is the problem
What is the how
That is the problem exactly
If you say that you're uncomfortable with it
What is
Exactly are you talking about your answer determines how we go forward your answer being
Alex was talking about this obviously isn't a problem because it's a news event
Exactly cover
Enzo
Tim's attempt to be like well it's talking about it
Longer
That unfortunately reveals that if he
Actually had a problem then he was aware that he'll accept talking about you
And that kind of undercuts a lot of his pretending to like I don't even know what Alex is talking about
Stop knowing when not something means you know when something
Exactly
So Tim disagrees Daleks maybe like
Over half the time
I agree with some of what he says
But I don't agree with some of what he says
But absolutely I agree with his right to say what
He
I don't agree with them about half the time
Maybe more
F****** Voltaire over here I don't agree with what you say
What are what is thinker
If I were somebody who was listening to Infowars and believing this stuff I would ask myself
How it is possible that Alex is 7th employee who is his business manager
Does not believe the s*** that he says on it I mean
If the stuff that he's saying mean something and he's on a whole
Crusade
I would guess the
The person who runs his business
Would be somebody somebody who's on board with the themes and the content of his show
We sell is fervent
That's what you're going for you ask ask these questions of yourself
How is the baby number 2 number 3 person at Infowars somebody who doesn't believe Alex's s*** is real or
Means anything I find fascinating
That these are public
Like now I need to I want to know more about the things that I participate in and whether or not there are people in that be
Business who have given depositions that I should know about
You know what I mean like I have time every time I buy a f******
Tired or something should I be Googling whether or not a tight executive
Was Joan telling obvious falsehoods about house tide actually kills people like what what don't I know
Call about deposition
You're never going to get out of this hole position hole
So the big article of course for Infowars traffic was the Adan Salazar
Article the FBI reports no one died the sound of course
Beretta
Maybe
Sure
Cam
Regarding the FBI's recording
I don't remember
I wouldn't
Read not for me
Not my style
Well I mean yeah but just look at all this stuff I mean
It's right there in writing it was obviously done so
Any other Auto
Baltimore traffic
I do not recall being aware of that no
That's interesting because
You're aware of all these fixing traffic seems like that's a big one you would be aware of
Very noticeable even just from a
Just scanning a grass yeah I do believe it is very possible that article and that's because he thinks
Did everything they talked about his bulshit why would you waste your time reading this article
It doesn't matter if she's interested for you to know what's going on waste
I don't find this entertaining so it's not for me the FBI says no one died at Sandy Hook okay whatever
I never had a doubt in my mind that the people died there is a normal for most people react
Action upon I wouldn't read something like that
I don't f****** work there
Yeah I'm not the person who's involved with
Monitoring traffic
To the site and the store and this is one of the biggest traffic articles
Easiest reason easiest reason this is absolute b******* is because
If you were that guy
Your job is to find out what it is
That cause that huge Spike
And that also includes what is in the article that might have
Contributed to that because also and emailed about the
The article on the big spike I drive
F****** camp
He is one of the writers yes
Work
Not really
Reproduction I'm not
We have a pickleball League
Yes
Author of the article
I was not aware of them
Yes
Email blast
Regarding
Okay
U-Haul
Screenshot
Alexa
In Google analytics, correct
It appears some yes
Correct
Yeah I would be upon request
No
F*** you now
Pure something
And what it shows
Is a spike in traffic
Around September 24th
From the rest of the line on this
Correct
And this is the type of
Earlier
Where it
I mean if I was something I noticed yes
What what
So far
I can't say yes to this cuz then if I did then I'm making Alex aware of the GI
In traffic that was due to this Sandy Hook hoax article no we already said that we try and reboot
So are you yes or no maybe I don't know if I was if I was aware of it I did email the dawn Salazar this
Starcraft that had a big spider
There's something so attractive about that positions because I feel like any anybody who's ever been in an argument with
With their partner or significant other whatever
And they remember something different from you you know they're not lying to you
But if you know you remember about it there's a party that's always wants to be like
You know what
Let's go to the tape
Let's see exactly what happened real quick I don't think you're going to like the way that it goes that is this to
TV show you this email
Sneaky Fox
They never have to be asked
Follow-up Quest
Know that it never comes up in like people like Alex in these because he works at Imports
Their lives
Do not involve follow-up questions
They don't involve any difficult
Positions at 8
Meticulously
Alex
Princeton
Then I will take calls and say he'll take any critical call these hangs up on people yells over him
To be in a position where you're forced
To like
Back cancer something but
Well how about
How about blank
Is very fast
No they can't defend their actions under any kind of a dairy
I should know in the until they're forced to retreat to improvisational excuse-making
Very transparent
Observer hand Bazaar
So Tim has said that they I would tell Alex about that
If I noticed
Here's a discussion that they have about how big this Spike was
Ask yourself if you think this guy would notice that
I had a silly yes
Between
300 500 down
1.75 million
Practically the same height on a graph
Yes
It seems like occurring at the same time
Correct
Yes
And
Spike's 2
From what is
Kind of a rolling average
1.3 to 1.5 million to just under three
A selfie
I mean it seems like a
Pages
Is from mid-september through October
Yes
Oh boy
I I don't remember regularly looking at visitors purses
Maybe the most important measurements of your continuing I couldn't tell you one way or the other to be closed on
Who knows
Can't
Imagine a world
Were you would ask him like hey is this
Dick traffic
The kind of thing you would notice ever him say no and Eddie believable
This is unnoticed
Right
We're doing our total B dad so noticeable was it like unique viewers goes from 300,000 to 1
1.75 million honestly honestly you know what
Chris can I call you Chris
I agree that this seems a little bit unreasonable but I will tell you
I kind of took a nap that day it's on me I was asleep you emailed this to a Dom Salazar
Somebody broke into my email because I was falling asleep and I didn't want Alex to know he
Can kind of be an a****** I don't know if you told you tell him that he's traffic is
Part of that I don't want to be a part of that he could have reacted really negatively towards me you would have said Adam
Boy at all this is so unbelievable like
Vanilla
He is unaware of this is so
Laughable we're we're in
David what do you f****** do territory
Answer the goddamn question
Now there is a sort of retreat
But he couldn't
And that is like
This is traffic to the website
I'm really more involved with the store no like I granted I monitor the traffic
And stuff and how it relates to the traffic to the store
But you know I'm more focused on the store
Unfortunately
That Spike also was a seed in sale
Spike like this
In traffic
Between September
That would result in corresponding spike in Revenue
Real quick this is a bit of a longer clip and also you probably are noticing now there's voices in the background
Wherever Tim is broadcasting from or recording from those people talking in the hallway
But yeah this is a bit of a longer clip just to preserve Conte
Georgia
Possibly
But we you when we go to the report earlier that showed a spike and
There was no cells I mean
Who's worthless traffic so
It just depends
That's the tone of voice you want let's see
Let's see
Ending to show you down
Spreadsheet in front of you
Okay
2010-2018
Barely but I do see it
As the Director of Business operations
Spreadsheet
Am I correct
It appears so
But I will tell you I would not be familiar with the spreadsheet because
I never looked at
Spreadsheets 3D card had a dashboard
That I could log into and see and I
They didn't have spreadsheets
Daily sales
It appears
Dot-com
Because evil.com website we got in operations
That's correct
In traffic cam
The same date
Third week in December of 2014
She can you not
That begin on September 24th
Buscar September 23rd
1229 dollars
September 25th
Show the $1,000
Define that noticed
Yes
September 26th
Bee sting
Slight
Correct
Spike in Revenue
I would say that is
Yes
It depends because what is Worthy's Evergreen it is a spike yes
Thank you
Yes you do
Yes
If there's a new launch of a new product or that could also be the case but yeah
Something's happening
Launch new products
Absolutely
What you're seeing happening
Website traffic
Corresponding with the publication and distribution that are
I could not tell you that 100% but there is definitely a spike in traffic and definitely a spy concealed
I cannot tell you that they are correlated at all or happened at you know there's no relationship between them to add
They are there I could not do that I would have been chilly just start narrating my feelings at it while he's asking the question be like
This I know this I know where this is going donut
Oh God I mean what do you want me to answer what is the weather
Yes okay yes
Maybe it's worthless worthless traffic
Why did you do that part I was going to do the thing and then you were going to leave it there
Yeah
So I think we can see here that there's
A real difficult argument that tempers is trying to make
About being unaware of this
It seems like he probably was fairly where this and is playing dumb
And good for him
Pulling teeth with these people
So there's a lot of this deposition that I have not included because it's a discussion of like
The software that was used to run for shopping in for store
Some discussion of why Alex wanted redundancy and having two stores make sense you know
If one goes down you've got the other
There's quite a bit of conversation about that that is interesting I guess but not real
Really that important
So but not really
31 last clip year and it's a little bit off the beaten path
And it has to do with
The fact that Tim was a bit of a point person in terms of getting people to produce
Things for
Discover
And tell me that
My God no
Okay yes do you mind
Resuming a little bit
That's much better
Prince I Would note that the second page actually appears
March 29th
Ear piercing
Clarify this affidavit to deposition
Let me look real quick
Yes this better crew
Your role in producing response
Cancel
Systems LLC
Text messages
Yes
That sounds right yes
And
You instructing employees who
It sounds right
No point in time did you think
Maybe that's not a good thing to follow up with some of these people
Reminder email at 8
In case you were wondering apologies for saying guys I meant to say people
People
Just send us
This glimpse
Was very different than a lot of the other depositions that we've had it opened the door into another song
Side of things the business guy in his face is never around anywhere
And I think
I think you suck
I mean
I think there is a
More touchdown this quite a bit. Like that more so than any other person didn't divorce
Seeing deposed
A complete abdication of any responsibility for what they're doing
Just someone who clearly doesn't like
Here's the thing
There's a possibility that he clearly doesn't like Alex it doesn't like the show and all this
Or
He understands that that's
What a normal person
Would do
Turn on the front
Of not liking Alex's show because obviously
No one in their right mind would think that this is a great show either is pretty
Man I mean I think
To me it's a bit like
If you know
If you're the Executioner
Doing the is that lethal injection or whatever and you're actively against the death penalty that you're out
Out of your f****** mind
You know like
You can't
You should get a new job
Do the thing you know you can't do it yeah I think you have a moral responsibility to leave a job that you
Ethically opposed absolutely
Yeah and forever for him to just decide
Callously and cynically just like
You know what
F*** it
Sure
00 injecting I don't give a s*** I think a lot of people
In in some corporate environment probably do have some misgivings about
The companies that they work for it
To the extent
You know you're working for a right-wing propagandist to agitate against people and communities and
You have to be aware of like that's I don't believe for a second that he doesn't
Doesn't have a general sense of the stuff that Alex that's bad because I mean quite honestly as you're saying like the
You're aware of know you're aware of yes because he doesn't agree with the stuff that's on Alex Jordan he's aware of it
You know like something to disagree with that you're aware of what it is that you are a part of
Exactly even if you
What are the details if you want a game points
For being against it or like
You're still aware of what it is you still
Cash the check
Yeah 100%
It's like oh yeah you know I was
Sure I was I was the campaign manager for Lindbergh but I'm not an anti-semite
Okay I don't think that I think that's a way bad idea
I was trying to make him president but I thought it was a bad idea to do it you know
I have some more depositions and stuff to that will get two down the road but
You know it's it's weird there's a there's a batch that I have that
They're more conflicting then
Some of those are the ones that we
Covered in the past like Alex's
Obviously there's a bunch of bulshit and he's being a dick and
You know what have you Daria
I mean granted Arias was crazy and conflicting and then scary
So like that I knew once we have the audio video of it I got a while
This Tim Forge one is a bit conflicting to me and some of these other ones are too so
You know granting a new chapter I guess of deposition
Congrats are good this is weird
I think what's fascinating
All too often
Is that
Look like
Anon-v shows
Tuesday on these shows
You know it
You can you can create this
Fictional version of somebody and then whenever you see them in those
Moments where they're not on camera where there have to be people
Humanizes.
And in this regard I think every deposition we've it's done the complete opposite is dehumanizing
I know what they think the more I'm like
You're an alien from somewhere else cuz this is bananas
Yeah and then what strange 2 is that
This is the first time that you have in it
He was some guy was there in the business section of stuff
It wasn't a a Persona or anything this is just you're getting a
Clear
First view of him
And that is something that's a little bit different Salazar granted never seen him on camera
Read his word seen seen him on Twitter
I never seen a creative output
From temperature
You know I wonder if that is exactly though what you would need to be to be the money person at Infowars you know you
Can't be a believer because the believer is not somebody you want handling money
That's why you have an accountant also I mean to do that
Would require the sort of moral of absence
That is it's not that he's exhibited
Xzibit exhibit
I don't know
Maybe God damn
But it still sucks I terrifying again I want to run away from these people and I'll allow it now cuz we're done
What does Jordan another episode hopefully with the prediction for 2023 so we can go about living Our Lives
2526 we're going to finally know what 2023 women's pattern here mayonnaise
Hey you owe us yeah
But will be back until then
It's not right.
Ross on Twitter
Text Clark I'm
Man I'm getting
Fucken tired of
This word elope Oliver
That guy sucks
From the introduction to his book The I don't even want to say the name
But
The introduction to his book he explains
That the first born
For six generations of his family has been given the palindrome
Legacy thing
And now here comes the sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work